Ginny Training in Dreamland

[September 1st 1991]

Ginny waved sadly with one hand, eyes fixed on her identical twin brothers’s retreating smiling faces and waving arms as the Hogwarts Express chugged out of platform 9 and ¾ in all its scarlet metallic glory.

Harry was somewhere on that train and it was to him, more than anyone else, that she waved for now. Fred and George were fun. She liked them a lot. Ron had been a prat ever since she’d stopped worshipping John. Percy mostly ignored her, and when he did say anything to her, seemed inordinately focused on how her behaviour would reflect on the family.

Harry though, Harry was her anchor. Harry gave her something to live for, something to look forward to. Before Harry, she’d attached herself to John in the hope that he’d sweep her off to a world of adventure and romance, a hope that she now knew would never have happened. She’d have died. A soulless corpse on the damp floor of the chamber of secrets, briefly mourned, quickly forgotten.

Ginny’s eyes hardened slightly.

Harry wouldn’t let that happen. Harry had been training her and she was doing the best she could to learn everything he could teach her. She could now do wandless magic. Wandless magic! Bill couldn’t do wandless magic. No one she knew who wasn’t being taught by Harry could do wandless magic. Okay, the only spells she could use were stunners, the shield charm, the stinging hex, and finite incantatem, but it still made her swell with pride whenever she thought of it.

Harry was her prince charming, knight in shining armour, and wise old wizard, all rolled into one, and right now, said time travelling hero was shooting away from her into the distance, further and further, until, finally, the last scarlet carriage passed a bend on the track and disappeared from view, leaving only the faint cloud of white smoke behind.

Ginny felt a squeeze on her non-waving hand, held in her mum’s unwaveringly firm grip.

“C’mon, Ginny, time to go. We’ll start on lunch as soon as we get back.”

She turned, looked up, and nodded forlornly. “Yes, Mum.”

They both made their way over to the station floo where a queue of wizard families waited for the floo.

Eventually, it came their turn. Her mum put three knuts into the floo powder dispenser, and Ginny caught her muttering, “Outrageous pricing,” before she was resolutely nudged towards the floo and sent on her way back home, quickly stepping out of the Burrow fireplace with what she hoped Harry would say was agility and sure-footedness.

When her mum joined her moments later, they immediately started preparing lunch, peeling potatoes and cutting up chicken breast for brining.

Ginny knew her mum could do most of this by herself with magic, but she also knew her mum was intent on keeping her as busy as possible. It really wasn’t fair. Just like the broomstick Harry gave her that her mum and dad then confiscated. Ginny knew it was somewhere in the Burrow, but she hadn’t dared go look for it. She pouted. Not yet anyway.

She sat down at the table, ate lunch, and listened to her mum talk about Bill and Charlie, articles in Witch Weekly, and “I do hope Fred and George behave themselves this year, for goodness sake.”

Ginny laid down her fork and knife on her now clean plate. “Mum, I don’t suppose I could visit Luna this afternoon, could I?”

Her mum frowned from across the table. “No, Ginny, please stop asking. You’re still grounded and that won’t change until you start telling the truth.”

Ginny bit down a comment that she’d never lied, just refused to tell.

“The outside walls needs scrubbing. That should keep you until dinner.”

Ginny pushed back her chair, hopped off, and made her way outside, grumbling all the way.

The soapy water flowed through her hands from the sponge while she scrubbed the wall as hard as she could—no matter how silly it was assigning her this job when she could barely reach halfway up the wall’s window frame.

It wasn’t always going to be like this. Harry was on the warpath. Harry was going to push Slytherin House to be the most powerful house in the country, and she was going to help him, and, maybe one day …

Words spoken long ago floated through her head.

‘For better or worse, our fates are intertwined, decreed by the powers that be themselves.’

Ginny felt her cheeks heat up. She shook her head. Maybe, one day, yes, but focus now. A few hours later, she finished up her task, dumped the dirty water down the drain, and strolled down to the orchard.

She picked up a stick and thrust it out in front of her.

“Depulso!”

She ducked to the side.

“Impedimenta!”

She dodged an imaginary stunner.

“Petrificus Totalus!”

She pretend stumbled backwards, and pretend fell unconscious, just like she knew she would if she’d actually tried to use such a clunky spell against Luna in a real duel. Seven syllables was far too long, and she’d still never beaten Luna once.

Not that she’d had any chance to train with Luna since John ‘I-let-my-girl-friend-get-possessed-by-the-dark-lord-and-die’ Potter had ratted her out and she’d been grounded.

She play duelled for a few more minutes before her mum seemed to realise she’d finished and called her in so they could go shopping for dinner.

They walked down to the local muggle shop like they usually did, her mum keeping a careful eye on her at all times. There was a magical food shop, but her mum preferred to shop muggle for food because it, ‘saved floo powder’.

They got back home and Ginny was dicing carrots, standing on a step so she could comfortably reach the kitchen counter, when her dad flooed in, leather bag bulging with loose parchments, face looking tired.

“Ah, dinner smells wonderful.” He kissed her mum on the cheek before turning to her. “How was your day, Ginny?”

“Fine, Dad.”

The three of them sat and ate, her mum and dad trading stories and anecdotes and occasionally asking her opinion.

“So, Ginny,”—her dad put down his glass of butter beer—“are you looking forward to starting school again?”

“Yes, Dad. It’ll be nice to get out again.”

Her mum stood and started bustling plates and cutlery into the sink. “But you’re to be on your best behaviour, understand, young lady?”

She fought not to roll her eyes. “Yes, Mum.”

“And no visiting after classes—straight back here, understand?”

She grit her teeth. “Yes, Mum.”

“Good. You need to get ready then.”

Ginny pushed back her chair and retreated up the stairs.

“And no more giving Lady Potter attitude!”

This time she did roll her eyes.

She quickly found her books and parchments and stuffed them all into her school shoulder bag. She then reached to the hiding place under her bed, retrieved a tattered copy of one of Bill’s old school books that she’d found lying around one day, and snuck in an hour of reading before her mum’s voice loudly announced through the door that it was time to go to bed.

Ginny extracted herself from her worn and threadbare summer dress, pulled on her slightly less worn night dress, and slipped into bed.

Soon, the whole house was quiet and the moonlight from outside bathed her room in a peaceful glow.

She reached to her neck and grasped the precious necklace that hung there, hidden and protected well enough to avoid the notice of even the most suspicious and nosy mother in the galaxy.

Ginny relaxed and snuggled as much as she could into her flat, thin pillow, and, mind flitting from scarlet trains, to castles, to a certain lightning bolt scared boy with green eyes and black hair, slowly fell asleep …

…

… And then she opened her eyes. She was standing on a beach. A mild breeze whipped her hair. Seagulls cried overhead. Her nightdress had turned into a black Hogwarts robe just like she’d seen all her brothers try on and buy at the second hand robe shop—except these looked new, and felt far smoother. Warm water washed over her naked feet and robes, sinking her feet into the sand, leaving a fine layer of coarse grains on her skin, and a creeping heaviness in her clothes.

“Hello, Ginny.”

She whirled around. “Harry!”

Harry caught her as she leapt at him and wrapped him in a hug.

She leaned back, grinning impishly. “Well? How did it go?”

Harry grinned. “Pretty well. We got the same ‘Harry Potter is to be left alone’ speech as last time, the girls held their own on the train, and John made a bit of a fool of himself by screaming that I stole you from him.”

Ginny’s eyes widened. “He really?”

“Yeah. He also attacked me with fourth year spells.”

She snorted. “Wow. That’s real smart. ‘I’m totally not a time traveller! Oh look while I do all this insane stuff!’ ”

Harry smiled. “To be fair, being a long term time traveller is so far outside the range of possibility that it’s extremely unlikely anyone, even Dumbledore, will come to that conclusion.”

“So, what are we going to do now?”

“We’re first going to get you used to training in dream space. Things can work a little differently here. It’s almost the same as training in the waking world, but not quite. It’s also similar to training in your mindscape, but with one major difference. Do you know what that is?”

Ginny shook her head.

“Here, you don’t make the rules, I do. This is important because in your mind scape, it’s very difficult to set up a resistance to yourself, which makes it difficult to train anything. If you want something in your mindscape, it just happens. You can’t practise duelling there on your own because the moment you ‘want’ your imaginary opponent defeated, he will be. It’s not impossible to work around that, but you’re not at that level yet.”

Ginny nodded.

“I’d also like you to fight a few more rounds with Luna while looking for things you need to work on. Self analysis is an important part of training.”

“Okay. I can try to sneak out tomorrow night.”

Harry nodded. “Tomorrow night sounds good. Right!” He stepped away. “Let’s get this started then.”

A half dozen wizards, all twice as tall as her, and all wearing death eater masks materialised around them.

Ginny’s eyes widened in shock.

“Move!”

The cloaked figures raised their wands.

She started to dive to the side.

“Crucio!” shouted from all sides.

A light shock passed through her body. She seized up and ploughed into the sand, unable to lift so much as a finger. She turned her still functioning head, spat out some silty water, and glowered at Harry.

Harry grinned down at her. “Fail!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny woke up the next morning fully expecting to feel like she’d been run over by the Knight bus, but amazingly, when she patted herself down, she didn’t feel a single twinge or soreness. Dream training was amazing.

She kicked off her quilt and made her way downstairs to breakfast, where her mum peppered her with questions, comments, and extracted yet another promise that she would behave herself with Lady Potter.

The next few hours passed in a boring routine of washing dishes, collecting eggs, and helping her mum re-label various jars and bottles, until kitchen clock number two, which actually told the time, announced in a Yorkshire accent that it was almost ten o’clock and that little Ginny needed to be getting to school.

She headed back upstairs, changed into her going out robes, grabbed her book bag, and dashed back down stairs, narrowly avoiding knocking a miniature Egyptian sarcophagus from a shelf that Bill had sent home a few months back.

Molly Weasley brushed an imaginary bit of lint from Ginny’s robes, took a pinch of floo powder from the mantle piece, bid her stand in the grate, threw it into the fire, and called out, ‘Potter Manor’!

Ginny stepped out into the massive ballroom of the Potter’s and quickly made her way to the second floor, only to be met just outside their classroom by Lady Potter, or rather, ‘Lady Lily.’

Lady Lily spotted her and gave her a cheerful smile. “Good Morning, Ginny. How are you? Did you enjoy your summer?”

Ginny regarded the woman who’d both ditched Harry with those horrible people and then didn’t so much as lift a finger to stop him being thrown in Azkaban with guarded eyes. “Bits of it could have been better, Lady Lily.”

“Ah, yes.” Lady Lily hesitated. “Well, you know your parents are just worried for you, don’t you?”

“Yes. I know.”

Lady Lily frowned, concern creasing her brow. “You can always come to me if you’re having any problems …”

“Thank you, Lady Lily.”

“… Even if you feel you can’t talk about them with your parents. You don’t have to face things alone.”

Ginny felt anger flash through her, but she clamped it down. She bit her tongue and said nothing.

Evidently some of Ginny’s emotions showed in her face, because Lady Lily took a step backwards and showed a brief look of sadness, before straightening up and adopting a far more formal air. “Well, Miss Weasley, class is starting soon. You’d better get in.” She indicated the open door beside her.

Ginny nodded and ducked inside. She sat by the windows towards the back of the room, which over looked the Potter Manor quidditch pitch. Around twenty other children, aged six to ten, sat around, reading, working on worksheets, or chatting among themselves, showing each other pictures from their summer holidays and comparing souvenirs, accompanied by the occasional loud squeal or shout.

Soon the class got underway and Ginny fell back into her old routine of compartmentalising everything she didn’t already know in her occlumency library while thinking of other things and occasionally letting her magic seep out of her fingers to help train her toxin resilience on top of her occlumency.

That was, until Lady Lily brought out a black stick with a ring attached to the end and waved it around.

Ginny perked up.

“Who can tell me what this is?” Lady Lily asked.

A figure on the opposite side of the back row raised its hand.

“Yes, Miss Black?”

“It’s a dark magic detection device. My father sometimes gives them to people in his job.”

Ginny’s hand trailed to her necklace, almost without thinking.

“Excellent, well done.” Lady Lily waved the device again. “The DMLE uses these to check muggle places for magical items that have been created with the purpose of causing harm. Now, why would this help with that?”

A boy in the front row raised his hand.

“Yes, Mister Hargreaves?”

“Dark magic is magic cast with the intent to cause harm.”

“Exactly. That is what we call the magical definition of dark magic, as opposed to the legal definition. It is the responsibility of everyone in the magical world—that includes all you children—to ensure no bad magical items end up in the hands of muggles.”

A girl in middle raised her hand.

“Yes, Miss Fawcett?”

“What about normal magical items? Isn’t it bad if the muggles find them?”

Lady Lily put down the dark magic detector and treated Miss Fawcett to the smile teachers give students who’ve just given them a perfect subject transition opportunity. “Yes, and it’s important to keep magical items out of the hands of muggles, but most of the time, it isn’t crime to let a muggle get a hold of one. Much like the entrances to the magical world, like Platform 9 and ¾ and the Leaky Cauldron, wizards who make magical items, like chocolate frogs and gob-stones, are required to build in anti-muggle magics into them that only run out when the magic in the product itself does.”

She turned and wrote on the board. “THE PLACE OF THE WIZARDING WORLD IN THE GREATER MUGGLE WORLD.”

They spent the next half hour discussing how the magical world kept itself secret and how they were expected to help ensure it remained so. The general message was that everything was a-okay and that the magical world was totally on top of everything.

Ginny eyes, though, kept straying back to the dark magic detection device on the table. She just couldn’t help it.

Eventually, Lady Lily asked them if they had any questions before mid morning break.

Ginny raised her hand.

Lady Lily looked mildly surprised. “Yes, Miss Weasley?”

“If something was originally charmed with intent to cause harm, but then someone else used the thing with intent to help or cause good, would the thing still read as dark magic?”

Lady Lily bit her lip. “A very good question.” She looked thoughtful. “I’m not sure, but I suspect it would depend on where the magic came from. If the magic came from a plant, it probably would. But if it was channelled through the wizards own magic, it probably wouldn’t. But, on the other hand …”—She tapped the desk with her chalk—“If the item was parasitic, and used the magic of someone other than the ‘user’, then I don’t know. It would probably change on a case by case basis, depending on …” She paused and seemed to realise she was rambling. “Well, anyway.” She put the chalk down and shuffled parchments. “It might. Thank you for the question. See you all after the break in twenty minutes.”

The class got up and made its way out of the classroom. Ginny made to follow them too, but not before catching the eye of a certain Black heiress, who quickly averted her eyes and pretended that she hadn’t been staring at her.

Ginny arrived back home later that afternoon to another pile of chores courtesy of a small group of cows who’d wandered onto Burrow land. Damn them. She’d just finished forking the resultant harvest into the now steaming compost heap when her mum called her into dinner with orders to wash her hands no more than three times.

Straight after dinner, her mum handed her a shaft of wood with a sweep-bent bunch of twigs at the bottom and the news that today was floor sweeping day.

Ginny fought back a scowl. Was she trying to mock her? What followed was definitely the most boring hour with a broom she’d ever had, and it wasn’t only last night’s all-night session with Harry that caused her to catch a nap straight after.

Later that night, Ginny lay in bed, staring at her bedroom ceiling, and listening for the tell-tale lack of sound that would indicate her parents had turned in. When she was sure they’d fallen asleep, she quietly slipped out of bed and got back dressed, pulling on the rag-tag assortment of muggle and wizarding clothes, which she charitably called her duelling outfit. Tonight, she swore, Luna was going down.

She opened her bedroom door without a creak. The landing was silent. Ginny knew all the stairs by heart and her descent was as quiet as her stride. She padded over to the back door, carefully raised the latch, and slipped outside.

The night was black. Clouds blocked the moon from lighting the path and Ginny spent a few moments letting her eyes get used to the darkness.

The path was a mixture of gravel, broken up by the occasional oddly shaped paving stone. Ginny hopped from stone to stone, always careful to keep her feet from making any sounds. She reached the end of the path.

“Lumos!”

Ginny’s heart leapt into her throat. She swung around and flinched away from the light that washed over her.

“Ginny! What are you doing?!” her mother’s voice shouted, shrill and angry.

Ginny’s stomach dropped.

Oooooooh bugger.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And then she gave me an earful for over an hour!” Ginny threw her hands up and paced up and down in front of where Harry sat on the bottom steps of a huge Aztec pyramid in the middle of a dreamscape jungle. Everywhere around them, the sounds of a thousand tropical birds squawked, trilled, warbled, and chirped.

Harry grimaced. “Yeah, that didn’t sound too good.”

“I just don’t get how they caught me! I swear I made no noise. They were asleep! I’m sure of it.”

Harry looked thoughtful. “They’ve probably put detection wards around the doors and windows.”

Ginny felt her stomach slowly sink. “Bill.”

Harry nodded. “Not unlikely.”

“Then what do we do now?”

Harry’s eyes gleamed. “First, we teach you to feel magic. You ready for that?”

She nodded firmly.

“Right, this will not be easy. Come and sit here.” He patted the spot between his legs.

Ginny hesitated for only a moment before nodding, walking over, and plopping herself down with her back to him.

Harry leaned over and took her arms in his.

Something washed through her. She gasped.

“Did you feel that?”

“Merlin, Harry, I’d have to be dead not to feel that.”

“That was me flaring my magic. Now, I’m going to do the same thing, but less so.”

The same feeling as before washed through her. She let out a long breath and leaned back into him. “I still felt it.”

Silence descended for a few moments.

“Did you feel that?” Harry asked.

Ginny’s brow furrowed. “No.”

“Right. How about this?”

“Still no.”

“Close your eyes.”

She closed her eyes.

“Go into your occlumency.”

She did so.

“Imagine a sea of water flowing around you, through you, feel it on your skin, in your veins.”

Silence

“Did you feel that?”

Ginny frowned “No.”

“How about that?”

“No.”

“Or that?”

“No.”

“Well, then, How about …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And once you’re done with that there’s a packet of peanuts to be shelled over there.” Molly Weasley left Ginny to her tasks and went off to inspect the chickens.

Ginny frowned over her pile of unpeeled potatoes.

A few feet from her, a large wooden spoon magically mixed bread dough in a large porcelain bowl.

Ginny shot the door a quick look, put down her peeler, and stepped over to the bowl. She closed her eyes, reached out her hands towards the bowl and tried to feel the magic.

She tried to imagine water flowing over senses, tried to imagine the flow of magic around her like a tide, like a river, like a trickle in a mountain stream.

She scowled.

… Nothing.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny sat in Harry’s lap for the sixth time in two weeks, this time at the top of the Aztec pyramid.

“Form a stunner on your finger tips.” Harry’s firm but gentle voice pierced through the murkiness of her own occlumency induced fuzziness.

She felt the ever familiar magic pour through her body and into her finger tips, but she didn’t let the spell escape.

“Draw it back into yourself.”

She let the stunner fade away, feeling the extra magic pool and flow around her body, a slight pressure under her skin.

“Do it again.”

She felt the stunner build up, felt it flow away. She felt Harry’s finger tips press lightly to her own.

“And again.”

She built up the stunner, drew the magic back into herself, and gasped when she felt something else, something foreign, flow down her fingers. She snapped her eyes open and saw Harry’s own fingertips all red-lit.

“I took your magic inside me?” she whispered.

“This is a dream, Ginny.”

“Ah.”

“Close your eyes again. This time I’m extending the finger distance.”

Ginny nodded and once again closed her eyes.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny sat in class while Lady Lily passed out the different maths and English worksheets for the different age groups.

In her hand, she held her self inking quill. A self inking quill, which was magical. When she was sure no one was looking, she closed her eyes, built up the magic on the tips of her fingers for a shield charm, but didn’t let it escape. She withdrew the magic and as the magic retreated back into her, tried to desperately suck in anything else she could from the quill she held.

She opened her eyes and scowled. Nothing.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny crept through the tunnels of the Aztec pyramid, eyes flitting from side to side, trying to spy out anything that looked suspicious in the row upon row of strange bluebell flame illuminated pictures carved into the rock. The bluebell torches cast soft light across the passageway, giving the feeling of being underwater. None of the sounds from outside filtered this far into the monument to Mesoamerican magic. Everything was quiet.

She closed her eyes, imagined magic flowing and streaming around her, sent out a tiny pulse of magic through her fingertips across the wall, and instantly drew back everything she could in its wake.

There. Something tingled down her fingers. The tinniest sense of a presence. Of something, almost beyond her ability to detect it … but not quite.

Ginny grinned, reached into her pack, drew out a wand, pointed it at the wall and shouted, “Paint ball!” A splotch of paint splatted onto the wall.

A faint pop sounded next to her.

“Harry! I did it! I found one!”

Harry grinned back. “Yes, yes, well done. You’ve activated trap number fourteen.”

Ginny stilled. “Trap?”

A huge rumbling approached.

“Have fun.” He popped away.

“HARRY!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny looked around. No one seemed to be paying any attention to her. She stood up, made her way up to Lady Lily’s desk, and picked up the dark magic detector that Harry’s mother had left there since the first lesson when they’d started on magic-muggle relations almost a month ago. She closed her eyes, pushed her magic into the device, and waved it over her head.

The device did nothing, which was good. She’d hate to think what would happen if anyone ever found out about her necklace. Knowing this thing didn’t react to it was good.

She slipped into her occlumency and reached out with her magic like Harry had taught her, trying to feel her own magic reflected back to her through the device.

It trickled back into her.

She felt it …

She. Felt. It.

Ginny’s eyes snapped open. She stared at the dark magic detector, eyes dancing in triumph. She’d done it! She’d felt the magic! Hah!

She did it a few more times, revealing in her mastery over something that only the most powerful wizards were supposed to be able to do.

She then spun around and walked back to her seat, unable to keep the huge smile off her face, not even caring that a certain black-haired witch was watching from the other side of the classroom, violet eyes narrowed in obvious suspicion.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny slipped out of bed, wrapped in darkness, already fully clothed, and padded across the room.

She opened her bedroom door, closed her eyes, and opened her senses to magic.

Heart beating faster than normal, she crouched down and started to run her hands up the door way.

There. A line of magic reaching from one side of the door to the other.

There. Another one, half way up the door.

And there. Yet another one, this time at the top of the door.

She felt around the doorway for other clues.

Nothing.

She stepped back.

It wasn’t even a perimeter ward. It was like a magical tripwire.

Harry had said it would take another few months until she was up for trying to actually crack even the most basic of magics, rather than just feel them. Dare she try to sneak through now? She frowned. Damn straight, she dared.

Ginny tied her hair in a ponytail and shoved it down the back of her shirt. She wasn’t robed, so that wouldn’t be a problem.

She took a step forward and reached through the space between the trip lines, ducking her head through them, and carefully bringing first one foot through, then the other.

She made her way downstairs, arms thrust out in front of her, carefully feeling for any other trip lines or wards. A drop of sweat ran down her face. Her heart beat wildly against her chest. With every step, she half expected her parent’s door to bang open, and for her mother’s voice to thunder down, promising domestic serfdom and no dessert until she was eighty.

The backdoor had a similar set up to her bedroom door. After she slipped through the trip lines, she carefully closed the back door behind her, and stood in the backwall’s darkness, body coiled, knees bent, waiting for any sign that she’d been caught again.

None came.

After a few minutes, Ginny stood up and let out a sigh. She grinned. She’d done it. A month’s hard work had payed off. All those moments caught in between chores—all that time spent before, after, and during class, probably looking like she was napping or slacking off—Harry said learning the basics of feeling magic with her level of occlumency took around two hundred hours, and she was sure she’d put that in, at least.

And now! Her face firmed. Luna was going down!

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Consciousness faded back and Ginny looked up into the smiling face of Luna, who extended a small hand to where she lay on the damp ground around the Lovegood plum bushes.

“Try again, Ginny?”

Ginny bounced up, face determined. “Yes! I swear, I almost had you that time! If I had broken through that last shield I would have won.”

Luna smiled a dreamy smile. “I’m sure you would have, Ginny.”

The two lined up again.

Ginny crouched, arms bent out in front of her, fingers spread like the claws of a cat.

Luna spun in a circle, tossed her handkerchief into the air, turned back to her, and brought her hands into the pose that Ginny had started to think of as Luna’s ‘Good girl’ fighting stance, hands held together straight down, shoulders back, legs together. Really, all she needed was a parasol and a bonnet.

The handkerchief floated to the ground.

The duel started.

There was a large flash of red light.

Ginny shielded … and blackness took her.

…

Consciousness faded back. Ginny looked up.

“Try again, Ginny?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The bread was in the oven and Ginny was sweeping the kitchen free of flour.

She stopped.

She looked around.

She opened herself to magic, felt the air around her, looked at the broom in her hands … and frowned. Now, where exactly would her parents keep it?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The landing beyond her bedroom door was as dark as the night outside her bedroom window. Ginny sneaked up the hallway to the stairs that led to the upper floors, all the while feeling for any wards or magical trip lines her parents might have put up.

She didn’t find any all the way up the stairs. Nor did she find any past her parent’s bedroom door. Her dad was snoring loudly, a trait that apparently passed in Weasley males, and which made her very glad she had a room to herself.

The stairs up to the attic was similarly unguarded, until she got to the very top. As she opened the trap door to the Burrow’s topmost floor, she heard the telltale sound of the ghoul that lived there. It snuffled and snorted in its sleep. Ginny felt her magic respond to her command. A bolt of red light shot towards it and the stillness of the sleeping instantly became the stillness of the stunned.

Ginny looked around and saw a likely trunk in the corner. It was reasonably new and the dust on the floor showed evidence of an occasionally used path leading to and away from it.

She took a step towards it and stilled.

Her magic senses tingled.

She felt the magic wash through her like a stream, just like the flow of water Harry had so many times primed her to feel, right in front of her.

Her hands raised and moved across the face of the magical obstacle.

She narrowed her eyes.

This wasn’t like a trip line.

This was like a ward.

Not something she was ready to tackle yet.

She sighed.

Guess she’d have to keep trying to beat Luna instead then.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The moon was full.

Somewhere in a thicket of plum bushes two girls sidestepped and cast, shielded and dove.

A stunner hit Luna’s shield. It held.

A stunner hit Ginny’s shield. It shattered.

Ginny cursed, and fell.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The moon was a sliver off full.

Luna threw a plum into the air.

Ginny aimed with her fingers spread. The tips of her hand glowed white. A stinging hex fired towards the falling plum. It hit. The plum exploded.

“Again.”

Luna threw another plum.

Ginny aimed again and again the plum exploded. She closed her eyes.

“Now.”

She snapped open her eyes. Two plums reached the top of their arc. She flung both hands up. One plum exploded. The other failed to connect with her hex and fell to the ground with a sad little splot noise.

They both stared at it. Ginny grimaced. “Not that good yet, I suppose.”

Luna smiled. “I guess not.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The moon was gibbous.

Ginny panted as she faced of against her serenely smiling opponent.

She swore she was getting better. Her stunners felt sharper. Her stingers felt crisper. She felt the magic flowing up and down her blood vessels, nerves, and muscles like a tide. Back and forth. Back and forth. Magic under her command. Magic under her mastery. She flung her hand forward and loosed a stunner.

Luna side stepped.

She snap adjusted her aim and loosed a stinger.

Luna shielded.

Ginny narrowed her eyes. She brought both hands up straight in front of her.

Luna tilted her head.

Stunner, stinger, stunner, stinger, stunner, stinger, stunner, stinger, her hands flashed red, white, red, white, faster and faster, bolts slamming into Luna’s shield like a boxer’s fist flurry.

Luna stood her ground.

All too soon, Ginny felt her magic drained from her body, now refilling directly from her core, weaker, less potent, and still Luna’s shield held.

Ginny said a bad word.

Luna raised her other hand. Her fingers glowed red.

Ginny didn’t even try to dodge.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“I just want to beat her!” Ginny shouted, waving her hands and knowing she looked like a petulant child. She didn’t care.

Harry smirked.

“I get so close, then she just throws up that damn shield and I can’t get through it!”

Harry continued to smirk.

“Please, Harry!” She skipped to where Harry sat on a broken, massive stone pillar and batted her eyes at him. “You’ll help me, won’t you?”

Harry’s smirk didn’t fade.

She scrunched up her face. “Harrrrryyyy, pleeeeaassseeeeee. Show me something. Some awesome trick. Teach me a new spell. Something—anything! I want to beat herrrrrrr!”

Harry jumped down from his pillar. “Okay, okay. Let me have a look first.”

She grinned.

Harry moved forward and placed his hands on her shoulders “Look into my eyes and think of your last few duels.”

She dropped into her occlumency, looked into Harry’s eyes and brought those last frustrating fights to the front of her memory. She felt Harry’s legilimency probe and surrendered to it. Images of her fights flashed past her consciousness like an omniocular on fast forward.

Harry dropped his hands and looked thoughtful. “Luna really is getting stronger, isn’t she?”

She growled. “Yes! And It’s so frustrating.”

“Luna took your full spell chain—basic though it is—head on, and outlasted it. That shows a large difference in power.”

Her shoulder’s dropped. “So, I’m just weak?”

Harry frowned. “No, not at all. It’s more that Luna is unusually strong. And if she’s like this now, the difference between her and most other wizards will just grow as she matures.”

“Are you trying to depress me?”

Harry laughed. “No, no. I’m just revelling in our friend’s potential.” He smiled. “How do you feel about having Luna at your back in a fight?”

She paused. “I must admit, I’d feel pretty good about that.”

“Exactly.” Harry hopped back onto the pillar and swung his legs back and forth against the stone. “So, you ready to hear how to beat her?”

Her eyes flashed. “Yes!”

“Right. We’re going to be improving two combat attributes. The first is speed. When you’re up against someone who outmatches you in terms of power, you can compensate by being faster, by being able to close the distance between you quickly when you’re at full power, and being able to run away and let your magics recover when you’re depleted. In other words, by controlling the space between the two of you.”

Ginny nodded.

“That means lots of sprinting, jumping, changing direction, etc.”

“Okay.”

“The second attribute, is efficiency.” Harry tapped the stone. “Tell, me. What is the most efficient way to protect yourself from a spell?”

“Not be where the spell lands. That was one of the first things you taught me about duelling.”

“Yes, well done. What’s the most inefficient?”

“Conjuring a physical obstacle?”

“Again, well done. And something in the middle?”

“A magic shield.”

“Yes. Another?”

Ginny drew a blank.

Harry grinned. “Spell swatting. Think of it like parrying with a sword. You use your wand, or in your case, your hand, to bounce a spell away from you. It’s more efficient than a shield, but not as efficient as dodging.”

She frowned. “That sounds awesome. Why haven’t I learned this already?”

“Because it’s very hard to do. It requires, what for a normal person, is an obscenely large amount of control over your magic.” Harry’s grin widened. “Control that I’m sure you now possess.” His smile evaporated and his voice firmed. “Ginny, bring a stunner to the tips of your fingers as though you’re just about to launch it, and hold it there.”

Ginny closed her eyes and let the magic flow through her, she felt the intent, let the intent form into a spell, let the spell pool in her hands and up her finger tips, she held the spell as close to the edges of her finger tips as she could without loosing it.

“Open your eyes.”

She opened her eyes and saw the tips of her fingers glowing bright red.

“I’m going to fire a stunner at you, and you’re going to hit it away with the tips of your fingers as though you were hitting a bludger away with a beaters bat, understand?”

Ginny slowly nodded, afraid to break the fragile hold she had on the spell.

“On three. One, two, three!”

The stunner flew towards her. She made to hit it away. The spell hit her fingertips, and the world went dark.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny put down the half-full basket of apples she’d been filling up from the apple trees in the orchard for her mum’s apple pie, and idly waved away a wasp that buzzed around her head. She looked towards the end of the orchard and bit her lip. It had to be about a hundred metres. Her jaw firmed. She lowered her head, planted her right leg firmly behind her, let her fingers lightly tap the ground, and exploded towards the far tree. Every muscle strained as she bolted as fast as she could, as fast as her body would possibly allow, and in moments, she passed the tree. She slowed while taking huge gulps of air, her lungs insisting she now cash the bank drafts her muscles had written.

A few minutes passed.

Ginny turned back and looked to where she’d left her apple basket, narrowed her eyes, lowered herself, and took off again.

Again and again, she tore up and down the stretch of orchard. Five times, ten times, fifteen.

“Ginny! Are you done yet?”

Crap. “Ahh …” She scrabbled to pick up the few apples that still lay around the path she’d carved out and glanced up into the trees for other easy pickings. “… Yes, Mum! Be right there!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny bolted towards Luna, both hands in front of her, both hands flashing red and white, both eyes fixed on her rival, both legs carrying her closer, level, and past.

Luna spun to face her, but Ginny was off again, throwing spells behind her, zigzagging and shielding until she was out of easy hit range.

Ginny ducked behind a tree, breathing heavily.

“Hi!” Luna’s face appeared around the tree.

“Gah!” Ginny swung around to get away and they began a frantic game of chase around the large tree trunk. She formed her next stunner and brought it to her finger tips. Suddenly, her foot caught in a tree root. She stumbled backwards, Luna appeared, and a flash of red shot towards her. She made to hit at it, but the stunner slipped straight through her fingers-tips. The last thing she saw before darkness took her was Luna looking at said red-lit fingers, seemingly equal parts surprised and curious.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Push the stunner to the very tips of your fingers.”

Ginny nodded, eyes closed, Harry’s arms on her own, his chest against her back.

“Now, pool your magic again, form a stinging hex, and push it into your hands.”

She nodded uncertainly, dipped deep down into her occlumency, split her consciousness between the intent to stun and the intent to sting, and tried to form two different spells at once. The stinger wobbled into existence, unsure of itself, and dribbled through her body, moving with a nudge of her stinger consciousness here and there. The stinger slowly pooled in her hand.

“Well done, Ginny. Now, as carefully as you can, push the stinger up into your fingers.”

She tried. Her lip trembled. Her finger tips glowed redder and redder. “H-Harry, I’m going to lose the stunner.”

“Shh shh.” Harry whispered into her ear. “No, you’re not—just a little more.”

Ginny’s whole body quivered. She could feel the stunner on the very tips of her fingers, no, it was beyond the tips. It was like the magic was both in and out of her body at the same time. It was raw intent given shape in the world. Holding it there was the hardest thing she’d ever tried to do. Every part of her brain screamed at her to cast the damn spell, to make real what she intended.

“Hold it there—Just like that.” Harry slid away from her, and she was left alone. He walked in front of her and pointed his wand at her.

“Ready?”

She gave a single slow nod. She didn’t trust herself to move any more than that.

“Stupefy.”

The bolt shot towards her.

She swung.

The bolt hit the tips of her fingers … and bounced away.

She let out a long breath. She’d done it.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Ginny! What are you doing?”

Ginny came to a stop, gave her mum a blank look, and glanced down at the vaguely wand length stick she’d been gripping. She looked back up. “Running around the orchard trees?”

“Why?”

She smiled, innocently. “It’s fun?”

Molly Weasley put her hands on her hips. “Well, enough of that then. Come back to the house. We have guests tonight and we need to get started.”

Ginny nodded and left her makeshift obstacle course, with its apples for jump points and pine cones for crawl points.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

She was so close. So close. Luna wasn’t steam rolling her anymore. Power could only take you so far, and Luna wasn’t nearly as fit as she now was. Ginny’s eyes flashed and danced. Magic flew between the two girls. She was holding her own!

Every time Ginny’s casting slowed, she backed off and evaded her gray eyed, dirty-blonde haired nemesis until she was back to strength.

Whenever Luna slowed, she’d pursue.

Back and forth. Back and forth.

Luna was tiring, but then, so was she.

The two stared at each other across the Lovegood woodland clearing, moon shining down through the opening in the canopy, casting silver light on everything it touched.

Luna’s normally dreamy eyes hardened.

Ginny scowled.

Luna straightened. Raised both her hands and let loose.

If Ginny thought before that Luna couldn’t match her powerful defence with a powerful attack, she instantly found herself to be sorely mistaken.

Spell after spell shot towards her. She spun away and legged it for the safety of the trees again, dodging as much as she could, shielding everything else, and ducked behind the nearest trunk.

Now.

Magic pooled in her hand. A stunner formed on her fingertips. She pushed it as far as she could. It vibrated, desperate to become real, to fulfil its purpose, but she held it, not letting it escape, unwilling to will her will.

Yes. YES!

She stepped out from behind the tree and instantly swatted away Luna’s first stunner. And the second. And the third.

Luna’s eyes widened.

Ginny grinned. “That’s right, Luna! How do you like this!?”

Luna frowned, looking thoughtful, and raised her other hand.

Ginny crouched, eyes gleaming.

Luna shot stunner after stunner towards her and she swatted away every single damn one of them.

Yes yes yes. This is how it was supposed to go!

Then, suddenly, something unseen slammed into her, she doubled over, lost her stunner swatter, red light filled her vision, and darkness took her.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry withdrew his legilimency probe. “It is there. If you watch Luna’s hands you can see the whiteness of the stinging hex that she lined up just after one of her stunners.”

Ginny pouted. “I didn’t think this was going to be this difficult.”

“If spell swatting was that easy, everyone would do it.”

Ginny’s shoulders dropped. “Okay. So what’s next?”

“Sit down.”

Ginny sat down.

Harry sat opposite her, cross-legged on the Aztec pyramid stone floor. He held out one of his hands. It started to glow red. “What is this?”

“It’s a stunning spell.”

“Is it? How do you know that?”

Ginny hesitated “It’s red.”

“Lots of spells are red.”

“You’re forming it in your bare hand. The only wandless spell you know that’s red is stupefy.”

Harry tilted his head. “Ginny?”

“Yes, Harry?”

“This is a dream.”

“Oh.” Ginny felt her cheeks warm up. “I forgot.”

“Quite.” Harry pointed his red glowing hand to his left, loosed the spell, and they both watched as it connected with the sand beyond the stone they sat on and left a streak of glass where it hit.

Ginny stared. “Was that … ?”

“An alchemy spell? Yes.”

Ginny turned back.

“Now,” Harry continued, “close your eyes.”

Ginny closed her eyes.

“Reach out with your hand.”

She did so.

“Open yourself to magic. Allow yourself to feel the spell like you learned to feel for the wards in the Burrow.”

Ginny nodded. She felt a small tingle of magic and breathed in sharply. “I feel it.”

“Good. What is it?”

Ginny frowned. “I don’t know.”

“Open your eyes.”

She did so. Harry’s hand glowed red.

“That was a stunner. Now, close your eyes again.”

She did so. Again she felt the slight tingle of magic, but this time, it felt slightly different. She opened her eyes. Harry’s hand glowed white.

“That was a stinging hex. Did you feel the difference?”

Ginny nodded.

“Good.”

“But,” Ginny frowned. “Am I supposed to learn what every spell feels like so I can swat it away? What if I run into a spell I’ve never seen before?”

Harry smiled. “Don’t worry. The point is not to assemble an encyclopedia of what spells feel like, but rather to discern the intent that spells contain. It’s the intent that makes a spell what it is. That’s the theory anyway. Like with everything magic, it could all be rubbish. At the end of the day, magic is magic.”

Ginny nodded slowly.

“You’ll see what I mean in a moment. Close your eyes.”

Ginny closed her eyes again.

She waited a moment. Then she gasped. Peace, love, and belonging swept over her. It surrounded and wrapped her and she felt like she could face down the greatest evil and laugh.

“What is the purpose of this spell?” Harry asked.

Ginny didn’t even need to think. “Protection—Protection from evil.”

“Open your eyes.”

Ginny opened her eyes and saw Harry’s hand was glowing white, but it wasn’t like the white of a stinging hex. This white was misty, pearl-like, silvery.

“This is patronus intent. It’s a defence against dark creatures such as lethifolds and dementors.”

“It’s amazing,” Ginny whispered.

“Yes, but notice that you instinctively knew what the spell was for. The intent behind this spell is so pure, so refined, that figuring it out was easy. Close your eyes again.”

Ginny closed her eyes.

She waited. Then, a feeling crept into her body and froze her heart. Fear gripped her. Her whole body started to shiver. Something was right in front of her. Something that wanted her destroyed, to be nothing, to rip her soul from her body with no chance of reversal. “H-Harry?”

“What is the purpose of this spell?”

“D-Death.”

“Open your eyes.”

She did so, and gasped. Harry’s hands were bathed in green—emerald green. Little ethereal skulls of green mist orbited his finger tips, chasing each other and snapping their jaws.

Harry’s face was grim. “The killing curse.”

Ginny shuddered.

Harry waved the spell away. “Those were extreme examples. You now know what we’re looking for. We’re going to work on two things—Detecting intent and increasing your sensory range. Ready?”

Ginny’s jaw firmed. She’d come this far, hadn’t she? She nodded.

“Then close your eyes.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny regarded the distance across the Burrow pond. She bit her lip. Her eyes narrowed. She turned, walked back a way, turned back, planted her foot firmly behind her, lowered her self to the ground, exploded towards the pond, hit the edge, jumped, extended both legs below her, hit the edge on the other side, swung her arms wildly, tried to get her balance, failed, and fell backwards, hitting the water with an almighty splash that shattered the otherwise quiet October morning.

She climbed back onto the shore, soaked, dripping, and shivering.

“Ginny! What were you thinking?!”

Ginny groaned.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“What is this?”

“A stunner.”

“What is this?”

“A stinger.”

“Good.” Harry sounded pleased. “Take a few mores steps backwards.”

Ginny backed up a few steps, still with her eyes closed.

“Now, what is this?”

Ginny strained, tried to feel the light caress of the magic on her skin, buried herself as deep as she could in her occlumency and blocked out any and all distractions. “It’s … a … stinger?” She opened her eyes. Harry was grinning, finger tips alight with a bright white spell.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny took a step backwards, leaned forward, and ran, full tilt, towards the long pile of leaves she’d piled up in the orchard. She leapt at the line of twigs on the floor and landed in the leaf pile, scattering a good number of them, and making a huge indent in the pile. She got up, inspected her distance, made an unsatisfied grunt sound, went back to the line of twigs, and moved it back another few inches.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Stunner!” Harry shot a bolt of red at her.

Ginny pooled a stunner, brought it to her finger tips and swatted the spell away, almost without having to think.

“Stinger!” Harry shot a bolt of almost invisible magic at her.

She pooled a stinger and brought it to her finger tips, instantly switching it with her stunner and letting it flow back through her hand.

“Stunner!”

She swatted it away.

“Stinger!”

She swatted it away.

“Good!” Harry smiled widely. “Now, again, but without me calling out the spell names before hand.”

Ginny took a deep, long breath. “Bring it on.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny leaped over the pond, hit the other side, rolled, jumped up, laughed, pumped the air with her fist, and ran off to get ready for morning classes.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny felt like her muscles were on fire. They’d been at it for ages.

On the opposite side of the clearing, Luna was panting, doubled over, clearly nearing the end of her tether. Her normally dreamy countenance was shattered. Her eyes were going in and out of focus. Her hair hung down in front of her face, yanked out of her ponytail by the constant whipping this way and that.

Ginny swatted away another stunner-stinger-stunner combo and followed it up by loosing her own stunner and stinger, which fell into Luna’s thrice damned seemingly unbreakable shield.

Ginny wasn’t thinking. There wasn’t room for thinking. There was only room for doing. Swat, dodge, cast, retreat, advance. Over and over and over.

She advanced. She cast another stunner. It hit Luna’s shield.

Luna’s shield shattered.

Luna made no sign of intending to move, hands planted firmly on her thighs, still panting heavily.

Ginny’s heart leaped. Victory crept into her eyes. Her hand glowed red again.

Luna looked up, still panting, met her gaze, and grinned.

Ginny loosed her stunner. It flew straight and true …

… And Luna swatted it away.

…

…

…

Ginny groaned, sank to her knees, and let out a desperate cry of frustration. “That isn’t fair!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Luna always was extremely intuitive with her spell casting. She picked up occlumency faster than I’ve ever seen anyone else, and I still haven’t managed to replicate that trick she did with firing a wandless spell with her tongue—not that I’ve been trying all that hard, but still.” Harry sat opposite where she sat with her head in her hands.

Ginny raised her head and met Harry’s unruffled gaze. “It’s just so frustrating! It seems no matter what I do, Luna’s always one step ahead of me.”

Harry smiled softly. “You’ve come an incredibly long way in an amazingly short period of time, Ginny.”

“Not far enough.”

Harry’s smile turned playful. “Well then, how would you like to try something that not even Voldemort managed?”

Not even Voldemort? Ginny frowned. “Um, Harry … if I can’t even beat Luna what chance do I have of managing something that even he couldn’t?”

Harry shook his head, still smiling. “You underestimate just how far ahead of most people you now are. But let me rephrase that a bit. How would you like to try something that Voldemort considered learning, but never actually decided to, because he could never quite find the time and there were always other things to do?”

“Is it dangerous?”

“In theory, it’s no more dangerous than what we’re already doing.”

“And it will help me beat Luna?”

Harry grinned. “Ginny, if I didn’t know what was coming, I’m pretty sure it could beat me.”

Ginny stared. “When do we start?”

“Tomorrow night.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The next morning, Ginny walked into class to see a group of her classmates all surrounding something on a desk. Shouts and gasps and cheers filled the room.

She sidled over, peered through a gap in the bodies, and gasped.

HOGWARTS TROLL DEFEATED BY FIRST YEARS!

Picture after picture of several witches, barely older than her, battling a huge mountain troll, three times their size, presented themselves to the excitement and fear of the congregated students.

Her eyes fell on the names in the article and her eyes bugged out even further. That was Daphne Greengrass! She was the other witch betrothed to Harry! And one of the other combatants was one Hermione Granger, ‘Vassal’ of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin. That was news to her. Harry had never mentioned Slytherin House having vassals.

Ginny watched the Greengrass Heiress lunge for the beast with a transfigured sword, only to be smacked away. Another picture showed another armed lunge, this one together with Hermione Granger, the vassal, plunging both the swords into the troll’s thighs and exploding them when the transfiguration ran out.

It was so different to what she was doing with Luna. Duelling with Luna had started to feel like a tightly choreographed dance. They could only use three spells—well, four if you counted finite incantatem—and that created a very predictable form of combat. It was all about speed, power, and energy conservation.

What she was now looking at was pure chaos, with elements of teamwork thrown in here and there.

Someone appeared on her left.

“What the hell is this?” the someone shouted.

She winced and turned to see Alexandra Black staring at the unfolded paper in shock.

Moments later, the violet eyed girl had snatched the paper up, eliciting howls of protest from her peers. She cast her gaze over the paper for all of a few moments before throwing it back to where it lay before and stalking out of the classroom. As the Black heiress left, Ginny swore she heard ‘Luna’ and ‘Slytherin’ and ‘Harry’ among her many mutterings.

Ginny frowned. She almost wanted to chase after the girl and ask if she knew about Harry, but one thing stopped her. Alexandra Black didn’t wear a silver lightning bolt ring.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And then I woke up the next morning with no memories of where the stone was.” Harry finished.

Ginny leaned back and rubbed her temples. “Harry. Wow. Just wow. The philosopher’s stone. I mean, wow. And you ran into the basilisk.” She shivered.

“Well, that’s most of the story. There are other things, but they’re still on a need to know basis, and until you’re at Hogwarts, you don’t need to know.”

Ginny nodded. “Harry, what are you going to do about the basilisk?”

“Nothing. It’s a thousand year old magically perfect killing machine. I have no intention to engage it until it’s absolutely necessary. So until we have a good way to deal with it, we evade and contain instead.”

“Rooster crows?”

Harry shook his head. “Oh, that it were that easy.”

“And you being a parselmouth?”

“First come, first serve. Literally.”

Ginny sighed. “Well, you said we were going to try something not even V-Voldemort managed, or at least tried. What is it?”

Harry picked up a black pebble and started idly tossing it up and down. “The way I see it. Your major problem is that Luna has just enough extra power to keep you from ploughing through her shield with brute force, but she’s also been matching you in terms of efficiency. Luna being able to figure out to spell swat independently, after seeing you do it only a few times, was amazing.”

Ginny’s shoulders slumped. “Thanks,” she said dejectedly.

Harry continued as though he hadn’t heard. “The one area you clearly outshine her in is physical fitness and raw speed. So, we should focus on your strengths. We need you to be so fast that Luna doesn’t have time to shield.”

Ginny laughed bitterly. “Luna can cast a shield as quickly as it takes her to raise her hand. You want me to be faster than that?”

“Yes.”

“How?”

Harry tossed the black pebble up one last time, snatched it from the air, did something that Ginny didn’t catch, and, suddenly, held instead a white pebble.

Ginny frowned. “What did you just do?”

Harry smiled. Did the thing again, and was once again holding the original black pebble.

Ginny’s frown deepened. “I don’t get it.”

Harry pointed behind her and to the left.

She turned and saw there, on the ground, the white pebble.

The white pebble disappeared, replaced with the black pebble with a tiny clink sound.

Ginny turned back and saw the white pebble back in Harry’s hand. “You’re switching them.”

“Yes. It’s called a switching spell. Normally, you learn it in your sixth year at Hogwarts.”

“And how does that make me faster? Unless …” Understanding spread through her.

Harry obviously saw it because he said. “Yes, that’s right. Unless you switch yourself.”

“Yes!” Ginny jumped up. “If I could do that, I could appear anywhere around her! I could switch myself to wherever Luna’s shield isn’t, and stun her before she had a chance to cast!”

Harry held up his non-stone holding hand. “Easy there, Ginny. You ready to hear the difficulties?”

A sinking feeling crept through Ginny. Obviously it wouldn’t be that easy. She sat back down again. “Go on.”

“No one has ever succeeded in switching themselves—not that we know of. Voldemort had a theory that casting the spell with a wand does something to the spell when redirected back at the body. His idea was that you can only switch yourself with something else if you do it wandlessly, and obviously, the vast majority of wizards never learn the advanced occlumency required for wandless magic, and then even fewer refine their control like you’ve been doing, and so are automatically precluded from even trying.”

“But …” Ginny began.

“And of those who do know the proper occlumency, they’d still have to put in the two-hundred odd hours it takes to learn what would be a very circumstantial spell that apparition could replicate in many circumstances. And then there is the final killer.”

“Which is?”

“Switching spells are classified as transfiguration magic. And transfiguration is not permitted in international standard rules duelling.”

Ginny’s jaw dropped. “For such a stupid reason?”

Harry nodded. “Quite possibly.”

“And aurors?”

“—Carry huge ass iron shields with them that levitate from their arms as a protection against certain dark spells such as Avada Kedavra. Because they’re not touching them, they wouldn’t be counted as clothing for the switching spell and would probably be left behind.”

Ginny leaned back.

“This is all speculation, of course. We don’t know that’s why no one’s ever done it. Hell, we don’t even know its not impossible. It’s just Voldemort’s theory after all. It could be total rubbish.”

Ginny tilted her head. “Do you think it’s rubbish?”

Harry cast his gaze into the distance. “I think its worth a shot. The rewards far outweigh the risks. We’ve got to have you doing something. I don’t have the time and I believe this is the best thing to try.”

Ginny nodded. “That’s good enough for me. Okay. Let’s do it.”

“Right. The first step is switching two objects like normal without a wand.” Harry motioned her to sit herself in front of him, back against his chest, which she did.

“Now, feel this, and take note …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny stirred the cake batter, bored. Bored, bored, bored. She put the spoon down, looked around furtively, and dropped into her occlumency. She tried to pool intent to switch, but found it tough going. The spell just didn’t want to form. She knew this feeling. She’d felt it before when she couldn’t get first the stunner, then the shield, and then, the stinger. There was nothing for it, but put in the hours, and keep on slogging away.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Try again, Ginny?” Luna extended her hand to her.

Ginny looked up into Luna’s tired but glowing face. She still couldn’t beat Luna, but she prided herself that she now got the blonde witch out of breath. “No, I think we should rest for a bit before we have another go.”

Luna hauled her up and bounced up and down a bit. “Okay, Ginny.”

They sat down on the ground, fallen leaves all around them, and passed a bottle of pumpkin juice between them.

The sky night was clear of clouds. The stars shone through. Owls hooted. The chilly wind rustled the leaves.

“Luna?”

“Yes, Ginny?”

“Do you talk with Alexandra Black much?”

“Oh, yes. We are quite close friends.”

“Really?” Ginny looked at her friend in surprise. “Why didn’t you say?”

Luna put one small finger on her chin. “Well, we have only recently started seeing each other again. She invited me over for her birthday party. I think she wanted to know if Harry was trying to marry her.”

Ginny spat out her juice and choked. “W-what?”

“Harry has been courting her as Lord Slytherin. He wants her to join our little group. I think she was somewhat confused.”

Ginny stared at the ground, face flaming red. “S-so Harry doesn’t want to …”

“Oh, I have no doubt he does. But, you know Harry. He is all about long term plans, with short term goals, which is good. World conquest requires both.”

Ginny squirmed. She half-wanted to ask what Harry thought about her, but she had a feeling that if she asked, she would get what could only be described as an ‘honest’ answer, and she didn’t feel she could handle the embarrassment. The phrase ‘world conquest’ also bounced around in her head like a gob stone in a bludger. “S-so,” she said instead, “Does Alexandra know? About Harry being Lord Slytherin and from the future and everything?”

Luna shook her head. “No, she does not. If you are going to talk to her, make sure you refer to Harry as Lord Slytherin, our lord, or, if there are others around, just ‘our teacher’. She does know Harry Potter exists, and that he is being taught by Lord Slytherin, but that is all she knows.”

“I see.”

Luna rose from the ground. “Are you ready for another round, Ginny?”

Ginny nodded. “Sure.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny let the magic flow through her, again. Let the magic pool in her, again. Focused her intent on the desire that the stone in front of her, should be over there, and the stone over there should be here. She pushed it into her hands. The spell died.

Her shoulders slumped.

Harry looked up from where he was doing paperwork at a mahogany desk on the other side of the small, Aztec stone room. ‘Ninety percent of paperwork is thinking,’ he’d told her months ago when she’d asked about the impossibility of doing paperwork in a dream. “Did you manage to keep your intent intact through the post-middle phases?” he asked.

She nodded.

Harry smiled. “Well, that’s something.” The desk vanished. “C’mon! I’ve got a surprise for you.”

Ginny perked up and followed Harry out of the pyramid.

The sounds of songbirds hit them as they stepped out into the open air. There in the courtyard, on either side of the several massive buildings that made up the Aztec temple complex that they’d made their dreamland training base for the last few months, were six, hundred-foot-tall quidditch hoops.

“Harry!” Ginny leaped up and hugged Harry.

Harry grinned. “I thought we’d have some fun with mid-air duelling since you’re doing so well.”

Ginny smirked. “Sure I am, Mister Time-traveller. And it has nothing to do with the fact that today was the first Hogwarts Quidditch match, does it?”

Harry smirked back. “I can’t imagine how you could possibly suggest such a thing.”

Two Nimbus Two-Thousands appeared in front of them.

Harry swung a leg over one of them. “I’m pretty sure I’ve got the physics right.”

Ginny scrambled to mirror his actions, grinning like a loon all the time. “Only pretty sure?”

“Well, I guess we’ll find out!”

And they shot into the sky, laughing and cheering all the way.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny sat with her hands under her chin, listening to Lady Lily drone on and on about muggles, the ministry, how the obliviator squads worked, and how they prevented muggleborn parents from spreading knowledge of the magical world.

So boring.

She slipped into her occlumency and idly started pooling magic in her body, feeling it slosh around and wildly form little eddies and uncontrolled streams. She withdrew her hands from under her chin, reached under the desk, out of sight of the front of the classroom, and started crafting intent to switch. She was getting better at it. She’d put in a good hundred hours over the last two weeks, snatching practise time whenever she could, just like now, and she could start to feel the results.

She pushed the spell through her system, up into her hands and held it there. It felt solid. Not solid enough to let loose, but solid enough for the next phase. She firmed her jaw while Lady Lily turned and wrote a particular point out in large capital letters on the black board. She pushed and felt the tips of her fingers start to tingle.

Yes.

She pushed a bit more.

Yes.

She pushed a bit more and … No! Her heart lurched. Out of the corner of her eye, she caught someone watching her from the other side of the back row.

The spell died, starved of intent.

She glanced to the side and quickly looked away from the narrowed gaze of the Black Heiress who was now staring at her the way a hawk stares at a mouse.

As soon as class ended Ginny bolted for the door, but Alexandra followed her.

“Weasley!”

Damn. Ginny stopped halfway down the Potter Manor stairs. “Yes, Black?”

Alexandra caught up with her and pinned her with her violet stare. “You’re being taught by ‘him‘, aren’t you?”

Ginny panicked. They were in the middle of Merlin damned Potter Manor and this was where the girl wanted to talk?!

“You are aren’t you?”

“Not here!” Ginny hissed. She grabbed the Black Heiress by the very expensive robes and dragged her down the remaining stairs, out the main doors, out across the garden, and into the small copse where John had sometimes brought her and Ron, and which powered the Potter Manor wards.

She looked around furtively. “Right, what is it?”

“You’re being taught by him, aren’t you.” Alex said, as though they’d never stopped their original conversation.

“That depends on who him is.”

Alexandra lowered her voice to a whisper so low Ginny had to lean in to hear.

“Lord Slytherin.”

Ginny leaned back and regarded the Black Heiress. Harry was courting her as Lord Slytherin. He wanted her to join them. She was also Luna’s friend and, quite apart from anything else, she was probably going to have to spend the next seven years sharing a dormitory with her.

She slowly nodded.

Alexandra breathed in sharply. “I knew it!” she whispered. “That exercise you were doing in class. You were practising wandless magic, weren’t you?”

“Are you practising wandless magic?” she asked, eyes still narrowed.

Alex nodded. “Luna’s teaching me.”

Ginny relaxed somewhat. “Oh. Well, if Luna’s teaching you, you must be doing quite well.”

Alex shifted her weight, clearly uncomfortable. “Well, I’d like to say I am, but I’ve never beaten her once.”

Ginny scoffed. “You mean in a duel? No kidding. I can’t beat Luna and I’ve been busting my ass trying to.”

Alex’s eyes started to sparkle. “Duel me, then.”

“I’m sorry?”

“Duel me!”

Ginny nervously looked around the woodland clearing. It was probably okay … She turned back to the excited witch in front of her. “Well, okay then, but just this once. We can’t risk making this a regular thing. Not here.”

“Fine.” Alex turned and made her way back to the other edge of the clearing, expensive robes fluttering around her ankles in the wind.

Ginny took a deep breath and drew herself into her own mind. Calm. Focus. Magic. Pool it. Wield it. Command it. She closed her eyes for a moment and then opened them again. She looked around and saw a particularly large oak leaf on the ground. She picked it up and called out to her opponent, “When the leaf lands, we start.”

Alex nodded, clearly also bringing herself into focus.

Ginny saw the witch’s fingertips start to glow red.

She held the leaf between thumb and forefinger, took a deep breath, and regarded her opponent. Just like a normal duel—Dodge to the sides, pound magic into her shields, break them down, dart away, swat anything that makes it too close, rinse and repeat as many times as needed to win.

She threw the leaf into the air.

Both pairs of eyes followed the leaf’s descent.

The leaf hit the ground.

Ginny leaped to the side, shot off her chain, shielded, turned on her heel, not waiting to see the result, and dashed away, all the while straining to feel the first cast, leaped behind a nearby tree, and waited.

And waited.

And waited some more.

Eventually, tired of waiting, she poked her head around the tree.

There, laying on the ground, exactly where she’d started the duel, was the unconscious form of Alexandra Black.

Ginny stepped out from behind the tree and cautiously walked towards the Black Heiress. She wiggled her fingers and stared at them in disbelief. Holy Merlin.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And when I looked back, she was down!” Ginny bounced on her feet in front of where Harry sat, her eyes twin shining beacons.

Harry’s smile could only be described as amused.

“Ohh, it just feels so good to be the one laying the smack down instead of being Luna’s chew toy! Hah!” She punched the air and spun around on one foot.

Harry slowly got to his feet. “So, you ready to go to the next level on project ‘lay the smack down on Luna’?

Ginny grinned. “Yes! I swear I almost had it before Alex interrupted me in class.”

“Okay. Go ahead then.” Harry motioned to the many stones that lay around them and stepped away.

Ginny’s face firmed. Right. She locked her gaze on a nearby pebble, identical to the black one Harry had used before. Focus. Feel the magic pool, form the intent, push it to your finger tips. She cast her gaze around and spotted a similarly identical white pebble a little way off. The spell danced at the edge of her fingers and she knew. The spell surged and she felt the pull in two directions at once, one to the black pebble here, the other to the white pebble there.

She blinked.

The black pebble was there. The white pebble was here.

She’d done it. Her heart soared. She let out a happy sigh.

“Well done, Ginny.” Harry smiled and they spent the next hour making fine adjustments to her technique.

Ginny couldn’t stop grinning. If she felt good about having wandless magic before, because not even Bill or Charlie could do it, it was nothing to knowing she could now do something that not even Harry could do. Her very own secret weapon. Or, it would be, if she could get the next stage to work. Then she could beat Luna, or perhaps, as Luna might prefer, ‘conquer’.

Ginny grin turned bemused. “Harry?”

“Yes, Gin?”

“Do you want to conquer the world?”

Harry briefly stilled where he’d been idly kicking his feet against the stone pillar on which he’d sat, himself before continuing again. “I wasn’t planning to,” he said, his voice sounding as amused as he looked.

Ginny grinned impishly and hopped up next to Harry. “The other day, Luna said, ‘World conquest requires long term plans and short term goals,’ and that you do both.”

Harry raised an eyebrow. “Did she really? That’s … interesting.” He looked off into the distance. “You know that dominating magical Britain was always the plan. Whether through political, economic, or magical means doesn’t matter so much. Vanquishing Voldemort and securing the future of those we care for against the wolves of our world who would seek to subjugate us for their own pathetic ends … that’s not something that can be done from a position of weakness.” He looked back at her and gave a small smile. “ ‘Conquest’ still seems like quite a strong word though.”

Ginny smirked. “I thought you also wanted revenge?”

Harry smirked back. “Yes, that too.”

“And the world?”

“So long as the world leaves us alone, I don’t much care.”

“And if it doesn’t?”

Harry’s eyes hardened. “Then I will burn a path to those who threaten us—who wish us dead or enslaved … and tear them apart so they can never threaten us again.”

Ginny shivered, met Harry’s gaze and saw ten years of hell. She saw her own death. She saw a world ruled by the dark lord. Of course. That’s why she was doing all this. It wasn’t as though it had much to do with her dream of playing professional quidditch.

She firmed her jaw and nodded.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Luna rolled happily on the leaf strewn ground after one particularly hard duel.

Ginny watched her. The discrepancy between the witch when she relaxed and when she duelled was disconcerting to say the least. “Luna?”

Luna stopped rolling in the leaves, blew her hair out of her eyes, brushed away a stray leaf, and slowly turned to face her. “Yes, Ginny?”

“Why did you say that Harry wants to conquer the world?”

“I didn’t say, ‘Harry wants to conquer the world’, Ginny.”

“Yes, you did!”

“I said it’s good that Harry could conquer the world.”

Ginny blinked. She wasn’t sure where to even begin with that comment. “Why?”

Luna smiled. “Harry might need to. It would be an awful shame if he needed to and couldn’t, wouldn’t it?”

Ginny hesitated. “I suppose …”

Luna rose from the leaves, brushing herself down as she went. “Come on, Ginny. Enough talk of Harry conquering the world and making you queen of the Amazons. We’ve still got lots to do. And Mum baked a pie earlier. There’s still some left.”

Ginny watched Luna walk off.

Huh?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny felt the magic pour through her.

“Now, this next bit is extremely tricky,” Harry said, holding her arms with his own. “The idea is that you shoot only half of the spell while keeping the other half inside yourself, but still realising the spell in its entirety.”

Ginny’s head swam. Complexity piled on complexity. What she’d struggled with in September now seemed child’s play compared to this.

“You know the feeling you get when you swat spells? When the magic feels half in and half out? It should, in theory, feel something like that.”

She pushed the switching spell to the very tips of her fingers. She tried to fire it and hold it at the same time, but the spell died and putted out. Damn. She scowled.

Harry squeezed her gently. “Again.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny stared at the stone of the other side of the Burrow’s orchard, willing herself to switch places with it, pooling her intent with her magic, and trying to loose it and keep it at the same time.

The crisp November air rustled the few leaves she hadn’t yet raked onto the compost heap.

Ginny tried one last time before dinner.

The spell died.

Damn.

Oh, well. Her eyes hardened. Soon. Soon, she’d master it.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ginny hurled the pebble at the Aztec wall. “This is SOOOOO annoying!”

Harry smirked.

“All month! All freak’n month! And I’m still no closer! ARGHH!”

“No one ever said spell discovery was easy.”

Ginny grumbled, picked up a twig and switched it for the pebble she’d just chucked away.

Harry’s face firmed. He nodded. “Again.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Ginny, we need a half dozen eggs, the hens were short this morning.”

“Yes, Mum,” Ginny said, and made her way to the back of the muggle shop, glaring at every cardboard box now that she was out of sight.

She found her quarry, all lined up muggle style on the shelves.

She scowled, generally annoyed at everything that wasn’t a successful self-switching spell, which included what sat in front of her. Eggs. Damn eggs sitting there so smug and in boxes.

As she had for seemingly every waking moment she could for the last month, she pooled her magic, and went through the motions,

She mentally picked out an egg.

She threw the spell.

She held the spell.

She both threw the spell and held the spell.

Her eyes widened in shock. Her heart leaped. It worked!

Immediately and without thinking, she actualised the rest of the spell, and realised, to her horror, and a split second too late, that she was about to switch with an egg, on a shelf, in an open cardboard box, in a muggle food shop.

Her view point shifted and she felt a hammer like force smack into the top of her head. The world fell down around her and a massive crash announced the depositing of several shelves of tins, boxes and bags, along with the shelves themselves, onto the floor. She fell with it, hard.

“Ginny!” Molly Weasley appeared as though by magic and immediately started helping her out of the wreckage. “Ginny, what happened? Are you alright?”

Ginny nursed her head and frantically looked around. Several customers were staring, looks of utter shock on their faces. One whispered to another, “Did I just see that girl teleport?”

“I—” Merlin, this was embarrassing. “I had an accident, mum.”

Molly Weasley goggled. “At your age?”

Ginny nodded.

Her mum looked around, business-like, pulled out her wand, and surreptitiously fired off a spell that Ginny knew would alert the obliviator squads.

They left just as a pair of wizards in waistcoats and flatcaps entered, nodding to her mum as they passed, both whistling jaunty tunes.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

That night, after being fussed over for several hours, Ginny found herself back at The Rookery, once again, for what seemed the thousandth time, facing off against Luna.

Fire burned in Ginny’s eyes.

“Begin!”

The duel started as their duels always did, with Ginny charging forward, closing the distance and swatting away every spell that came her way. Luna countered as she always did, with shields and swatting of her own. The closer they got to each other, the more frantic the swatting got and the more Luna had to rely on her shields. Ginny was just faster like that.

Soon they both started to tire.

Ginny retreated in a hail of stunners and stingers.

Luna chased, but never quite managed to catch up.

They both reset, and they both started at it all again. This would go on and on until one found an opposing. A tiny sliver in their opponent’s armour to sneak a spell through, and that one was always Luna.

But not this time. Ginny grinned from behind a tree. This time, that sliver would be a Merlin-damned gaping hole, and Luna wouldn’t know what hit her.

Ginny dived out from behind the tree and sprinted towards the other side of the clearing, Luna close on her heels.

She passed a stone on the ground, pooled her magic, formed her intent, and fired the spell, still running at full tilt. The spell connected, Luna passed the stone a few seconds later, and Ginny felt the spell catch. Her hand glowed red. She felt a little yank and Luna’s back popped into view in front of her. She loosed the spell and had just enough time to catch the look of utter shock that appeared on Luna’s slightly turned head.

The stunner hit. Luna’s face blanked, and the witch who’d gone undefeated for the whole damn semester, the witch who’d kept her learning trick after trick and still staying one step ahead of every single one of them, fell, with a quiet thud, onto the leaf padded ground.

Ginny panted. She stared. She bent over double, hands on her knees to support herself. She’d won. She’d won. Ginny sucked in huge gulp of air. She’d damn well won! Ginny straightened her body, raised her fists to the sky, and let out the loudest, most ferocious, and most triumphant war bellow that her ten-year-old girl’s throat would give her.

Then she cast a finite on Luna.

“Wow! Ginny!” Luna bounced up and tackle-hugged her.

Ginny stumbled backwards, just managing to keep her balance.

“That was amazing! What was that?!” All dreaminess had gone from Luna’s eyes, replaced with nothing but sharp enthusiasm. “It wasn’t apparition. I’d have heard the crack! You didn’t silence yourself either! And the Rookery has key-in apparition wards anyway!”

Ginny couldn’t help but grin. “If I tell you, will you promise not to suddenly learn it in less than a week?”

Luna pouted. “Fine.”

One hour later, Ginny was sorely regretting telling Luna how the self-switching spell worked. “HOW?” she cried, crawling on her hands and knees from where she’d just been awoken from losing yet another duel.

“It’s your face, Ginny. And the way the your fingers move. I can see when you’re going to switch just before you do it.”

Ginny groaned.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Disillusionment,” Harry said.

“Disillusionment?” Ginny asked, mischief dancing in her eyes.

“Disillusionment,” Harry repeated.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The shrill voice of Molly Weasley sounded through the Burrow. “Ginny! Ginny where are you? We need to get to the Alley before everything closes! They don’t open on Sundays and we won’t have time before the portkey for Romania leaves on Monday!”

An almost invisible Ginny quietly sniggered and crept back up to her bedroom from where she’d been secretly training in the backyard. She dropped her disillusionment and poked her head out the door. “I’m here, Mum!”

“Oh!” her mum said, looking more than a little flustered. “Good, then.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“HOW?!” Ginny beat her still almost invisible fists on the ground in rage and frustration.

Luna smiled dreamily, brought her hands to her ears, and flicked them back and forth.

“Right,” Ginny muttered into the frosty late December ground, “guess it’s going to be silencing charms next.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The next night, Ginny lay awake in bed, staring at the ceiling and thinking. She wished she could go to the Winter Festival at Greengrass Manor, but her parents were taking her to Romania to visit Charlie. It wasn’t that she wasn’t looking forward to seeing her second eldest brother again, she was. But, well, she had seen her mum packing four separate Ginny Weasley sized coats into her old expandable trunk. Cumbria wasn’t that cold.

There was also the fact that she still hadn’t completely forgiven either Bill or Charlie for ignoring her last summer and pushing Harry so far that he actually suffered a panic attack strong enough to briefly knock out the Burrow’s wards.

That Charlie had supported their parent’s decision to confiscate the broom Harry had gifted her rankled even more, especially given Charlie’s own history with Quidditch. She’d like nothing more than to blow off some steam in the nighttime skies around the Burrow.

Ginny stared at the ceiling some more. She frowned and sat up in bed and stared at an empty patch of bedroom wall. But … now … if she could … Her eyes narrowed. Yes.

She quietly slipped out of bed, opened her door, slipped through the magic trip wires with barely a second thought, moved as silently as she could without magic to the trapdoor to the attic, carefully opened the door, stunned the ghoul, turned and regarded the ward around the trunk that she’d found before.

She closed her eyes, opened herself to magic, and let the intent caress her skin her like a Luna-hurled stunner to be instantly swatted away. It felt like … a key-in perimeter ward? A key-in perimeter ward … and something else … a motion detection area ward … a motion detection ward that worked by. … Ginny tilted and rolled her head as though trying to hear something a long way off. … It worked by ‘seeing movement.’ The trunk itself … had no magic.

Ginny bit her lip, turned, thought about the distance between here and her bedroom, and the chance that she could make it back without bumping into her parents if something went wrong.

She turned back to the ward. Her jaw firmed. She looked around, picked up a hat from a nearby hatstand, disillusioned it, and, standing right next to her escape route and holding her breath, frisbeed the almost invisible hat past the perimeter ward and into the motion detector ward.

Nothing happened.

She let out her held breath. Stage one was successful.

Ginny walked towards the ward line and allowed herself to also fade into the background.

She focused on the hat … and switched, bringing herself forward a whole few metres closer to the trunk and depositing the hat back where she’d been standing.

Again, nothing happened.

Right. Next step.

Ginny walked forward as carefully and as slowly as she could manage. She wasn’t completely invisible after all. She reached the trunk and suddenly realised there was a problem. She couldn’t just open the trunk lid without triggering the motion detection ward.

Ginny chewed her tongue.

But, she couldn’t just disillusion the trunk either. That would surely also trigger the ward. But … —She stopped chewing her tongue and started on her cheek— … But maybe she could slowly disillusion the trunk, just a tiny bit at a time.

She reached out, placed her hands on the trunk and slowly, ever so slowly, applied one disillusionment charm after another, each one just a bit stronger than the last, each time waiting a good amount of time before casting again.

Eventually, the trunk was noting but a mirror of the background, an outline in the air.

Ginny fingered for the lid and opened it just a crack. The disillusionment held, shielding the trunk’s contents from the ward without actually carrying over. She opened it a bit more, peeked in and had to stifle the instinct to breathe in sharply and shout in triumph.

She snatched her tiny, limited-edition Nimbus 1700 from the bottom of the trunk, closed the lid, slowly dispelled the charms, worked herself back through the area ward, switched herself to the other side of the key-in perimeter ward, used a disillusioned umbrella to retrieve the hat, tiptoed back down the stairs, into the kitchen, out the back door—slipping through the other set of trip lines as she went—down to the orchard, gave her broom the magical once over, un-shrunk it, mounted up, and shot into the air, grinning like a madman, and letting happiness surge through her body.

Her parents would never know. Oh, they’d find the broomstick gone when they next checked, but they’d have no way of suspecting it was her who had done it. She’d deposit the broom in Harry’s fidelius charmed secret passage way when she was done. She sure wasn’t stupid enough to hang on to it—she’d learned that lesson well enough. But it was back in her possession again, and that was what mattered.

Ginny did a loop in the air, still under disillusionment, and soared upwards towards the moon.

She’d get cold soon, but right now, she felt she could weather an Arctic snow storm, she was that happy. The last four months had been almost nothing but hard, hard work and soon she’d be back at it, but for these few, precious moments, she was going to enjoy herself, just like Harry surely was at the Winter Festival.

—End of Chapter Twenty-four—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: Wow, that was a lot of Ginny. I hope you enjoyed, because we won’t see her again until the start of book three (year two).

Next chapter: Alexandra and Luna being very bad girls.

A/N: Gah. This chapter was late—That’s annoying. I wasn’t able write for the whole of last week because life got in the way, and then, what I thought was going to be a short 7,000–8,000 word chapter, wasn’t. As I’ve said many times before, I suck at estimating word length.

Anyway, it’s out now. Yay!

As many of you know, when my schedule messes up, I currently let people know using twitter, but I appreciate that not everyone uses or likes twitter. I’m working on an alternative solution that will both allow me to keep you updated, and also allow me to post relevant content that doesn’t currently meet fanfic dot nets publication guidelines.

A/N: Just so everyone knows. I currently do not consider anything in cursed child as canon and stuff that happens in there doesn’t happen in this AU. Just putting that out there.

Necromancy for Fun and Fun - Part One

[Warning: This chapter contains strong and potentially offensive language]

[August 5th, 1991—The day after Alexandra’s tenth birthday party]

In a dusty corner of a dusty library, a pair of bright violet eyes were glued to the occasionally turned pages of a colourful book.

And then, the boy who lived swept down on the foul beast and sliced it in two.

“Hah!” the boy who lived shouted. “Your foul magics won’t help you this time!”

The black witch of the north cackled. “Oh, you think so, do you? You haven’t even seen one-tenth of my true power!”

And then, the black witch of the north drove her staff of supreme evil into the ground, which started to shake terribly.

“What is this?!” The boy who lived was startled. He’d never seen such evil before.

“This! This is my TRUE POWER!” And from the ground emerged a dragon, and the boy who lived could see that it was undead because its skin was yellow and flaky and bony and yet it still moved.

“Do you see, boy who lived?” the black witch of the north cackled. “You cannot possibly hope to defeat such evil! Now, bow before me!”

“Never!” The boy who lived got shakily to his feet. “I can defeat you! Because I have my friends!”

And the friends of the boy who lived all gathered round him.

“Use it now!” shouted Maldeve.

“Yes!” shouted Vivian. “The ancient artefact! It’s the key to defeating the black witch of the north!”

And the boy who lived pointed the ancient artefact of Zak’ra’na’fu’si’ta’dul at the huge undead dragon and the power of friendship rushed through them all, hit the foul dragon, which let out an evil cry of rage, and dissolved into nothing.

“NO!” The black witch of the north cried. “This cannot be! I cannot be defeated by—”

Wham! The book hit the nearest bookcase and dropped to the floor, face down, still open, its colourful front cover showing a boy of no more than six standing on the head of a dragon and holding a sword. A startled Amethyst jumped up and fell from where she’d been sleeping, landed lightly on the floor, righted herself and looked around, dart like, for whatever threat had awoken her.

Alexandra Patricia Black, wearing a long night dress and a frown, folded her arms and glared at the fallen book. That was how the ‘boy who lived’ took down a seventy foot long undead dragon? What a cop out. He should have been a greasy stain on the castle floor! The black witch of the north should have won! She’d been better prepared, better armed, better manned. She’d had a whole army of skeletons in book four. Where had they been?

Still grumbling, Alex hopped out of her armchair, snatched the book up, carefully gathered a mewing Amethyst in her arms, made her way out of the library, and down to where breakfast was being served.

“Morning, sleepyhead.” Lord Sirius Black hastily buttered a slice of toast while she slid herself into one of the high back chairs and spooned herself a boiled egg from a large silver bowl filled with sand.

“Been up for ages,” she muttered, depositing the cute black kitten and tapping the egg with a convenient silver spoon.

“Oh? Doing what?”

She held up the boy who lived adventure book in her other hand. “In the library.”

A brief look of concern flashed over her father’s face before settling back into its usual jaunty demeanour. “Just so long as you’re staying out of those areas.”

She mentally rolled her eyes. “Yes, Dad.”

Her father swallowed another bite, grabbed two more slices of toast, and stood up. “And you enjoyed your birthday party yesterday?” He moved to the hatstand and started putting on his cloak, both slices of toast now held in his mouth.

“Yes, seeing Luna again was nice. I’ve missed her.”

Her father grunted something that she couldn’t quite make out.

“I was thinking of inviting her around again sometime?”

Lord Black looked around, patting his pockets and frowning.

Alex tilted her head and put on her best puppydog face. “It’s been kinda lonely over the summer, otherwise.”

Her father stopped looking around and briefly focused on her. “Oh. Oh, yeah, yeah, sure, okay then—have you seen my badge anywhere?”

Alex smiled brightly. “Kreacher!”

Lord Black groaned.

“Honoured Bastard Mistress called?”

Alex’s smile became rather wooden.

Her father looked resigned.

“Find Lord Black’s auror badge.”

“Yes, Honoured Bastard Mistress.”

A few moments later, her father briskly walked to the floo, auror badge in hand.

Alex spent a few more minutes finishing breakfast before heading back up to the library. She slid the offending boy-who-lived adventure book back between its dozen or so fellows, carefully extracted Volumes I,II, and III of The Light Side of the Dark Arts and made her way to the nook that held her Grandfather’s portrait.

“So, he got you another gift, mmm?”

Alex shifted uncomfortably, holding the book up for inspection. “He did. And Luna gave me a black kitten.”

“Well, make sure you send a couple of owls to thank them both.”

Alex nodded.

“And,” Portrait Orion Black stroked his beard. “You’re now ten years old. That’s a very special age for a daughter of the house of Black.”

Alex hesitated. “It is?”

“Oh, yes,” he continued. ” You’re off to Hogwarts in a year’s time, and now’s the time for you to learn about the Black family magic.”

Alex’s eyes widened. “Really?” Her face broke out in a massive grin.

Orion Black smiled back warmly. “Yes, really.” His smile faded. “I advise against you telling my son that I’ve spoken to you of this though. He never bothered learning when he was younger, despite my and your grandmother’s best efforts, unlike your late uncle.”

Alex snorted. “Why am I not surprised?”

Orion Black nodded and then told Alex exactly what she needed to do to find the secret section of the Black Library that held the Black family magic. Alex thanked her grandfather and left.

“Kreacher!”

Kreacher popped in front of her, all pointed nose and ears, mean eyes, and yellowed teeth. “Honoured Bastard Mistress called?”

“Yes. Please get me a sharp knife and a healing potion.”

Moments later she held a wickedly sharp looking knife and a healing draught.

She nodded and turned back to Kreacher. “You are not to know where I am, or what I’m doing, for the next thirty minutes, understood?”

Kreacher grinned and rubbed his hands together. “Honoured Bastard Mistress is being sneaky again. Kreacher understands, Honoured Bastard Mistress.”

Kreacher popped away.

Alex nodded to herself. When she’d been five, she’d taken to asking the elf to pop her just outside her then friends houses. A confused Sirius Black had randomly asked Kreacher where she was and blew a fuse when the elf had been forced to tell him. Since then, she’d always been very careful to make sure the elf didn’t know anything that could get her into big trouble. That included rituals, dark magic, and anything to do with Lord Slytherin.

She padded across the library until she faced a bookcase that looked just like every other bookcase, took a deep breath, sliced open a cut on her palm and winced. It hurt. No, it really hurt. Tears forming in her eyes, she smeared the blood across the spine of the book titled Alchemic Transmutation Volume VIII—Maintaining Purity. The bookcase shivered, the books leapt from their shelves, woodwork slid and reformed itself, and in moments the bookcase become an archway of books, framing a solid looking door, also made from books.

Alex drank the healing potion and a wave of relief washed through her, pooled in her hand, and within moments, the cut was as though it had never been. Thank Morgana. She grasped the door handle, which looked to be made of two ornate looking book stoppers, and pushed.

Darkness greeted her. She stepped through in worshipful silence. The room was tiny. There were only two book shelves on either side of her and barely enough space from two people to comfortably move around in.

These books contained the Black family magic. The magic that only Blacks and their immediate families could cast, or that the family wanted only Blacks to be able to cast. It was part shrine, part incubation chamber and clearly hadn’t been accessed in many years.

Alex idly wondered how many of the spells on the shelves had become actual Black family magic on her birth. The rule of three said that for a new spell to become family magic it had to pass through three generations of heirs without being used by any not of the family’s blood. She was sure that her own father hadn’t invented any spells that he hadn’t immediately shared with the Lord Potter at least.

When she eventually had children … one day … a long, long time in the future … they wouldn’t be getting anything new from their grandfather.

She sniffed bitterly and reached for an interesting looking tome named The Dendromancer’s Doomsday Book.

Wings flittered.

Alexandra stiffened.

Something had moved just outside her field of vision.

Then, suddenly, something grabbed her long black hair and started yanking it backwards.

She cried out, felt a small bite on her leg through her thin nightdress, heard a cacophony of little angry shouts, stumbled towards the door, grabbed at whatever was yanking on her hair, kicked off the thing on her leg, saw a little blue something fly into the wall, half fell through the door, slammed it shut behind her, flinched as she felt the thing in her hand bite down hard, and smashed it against the nearest bookshelf in retaliation. The thing smushed under force of her ritual empowered attack, sending blue gunk everywhere and all over her hand in particular.

Alex gasped for breath, her heart now beating a million beats a minute. Doxies! She gently cradled her bit hand, felt the bite on her leg rapidly turning enflamed, and glared at the now closed book-like door to the secret chamber of Black family magic. Damn it! She stamped her foot in frustration. Now what was she supposed to do? She needed to get this treated, but she couldn’t ask Kreacher. He was under orders to tell her father if she got hurt. She couldn’t go to St. Mungo’s for the same reason.

But … there was someone who might be able to help. Alex’s jaw firmed. She hated this, but there was nothing else for it. She darted downstairs, zipped to the floo, threw some floo powder into the fireplace, ducked her head into the fire and shouted, ‘The Rookery!’

The living room of the Lovegoods faded into view and a regal and dignified looking man bearing more than a passing resemblance to Lord Malfoy crouched down to her eyesight and asked, “Do you know the meaning of life, young lady?!” in quite a loud voice.

Alex panicked. “I, what?”

The man crouched closer. “Is it more important to rule or to serve?”

Alex sneezed on a bit of wood ash and resisted the urge to back off. “That’s like asking if its more important to breathe in or out!”

“Then do you rule a master through servitude, or serve a follower through leadership?”

“Either! It doesn’t matter! Do whatever is needed!”

“Good.” The man stood back up, suddenly all formality and politeness. “I am Xenophilius Lovegood, Head of the Ancient and Noble House of Lovegood. How may I serve you?”

Alex hesitated. “I—”

“Alex!”

Luna bounded into view and skidded to a halt in front of her. “You’re here! Oh, don’t mind Daddy, he just gets a kick out of being all mysterious.”

Lord Lovegood smiled and stepped back a few paces.

Alex suddenly realised her knees were starting to ache and both her leg and hand were flaming quite magnificently. “Ah, I … Lord Lovegood? Could I maybe speak to Luna in private for a few moments?”

Lord Lovegood nodded and retreated.

“Luna, I got bit by a doxy and I can’t go to the hospital. I can’t let my Dad find out about this!”

Luna’s eyes widened slightly. She nodded slowly. “One moment, Alex, I think I might have just what you need.”

Luna left and soon returned with a bright blue potion in a tiny bottle. “Here it is.”

“What is it?”

“It is anti-doxy bite potion.”

Alex looked at the blonde haired, gray eyed witch, incredulity seeping from every pore on her young face. “You had this just lying around?”

Luna’s face remained as dreamy as ever. “It is very important to be prepared for anything that might happen, and me and Daddy do go hunting occasionally.”

Alex stared at Luna for another moment before shrugging, opening her mouth wide, and making an ‘Ahhhhhh’ sound.

Luna tipped the potion in, not letting any liquid fall off her outstretched tongue.

Alex snapped her mouth shut, gulped it down, and immediately started to feel a reduction in soreness in her leg and hand. She let out a sigh. “Thanks, Luna.”

“That is quite all right, Alex. Would you like to start occlumency training now?”

Alex’s hesitated, briefly thinking back to her as yet unexplored birthday inheritance, and then remembered that, for the time being, she had no way to get to it. Then she thought back to what had happened yesterday, when Luna had blown through her occlumency barriers like they were tissue paper, just because she’d gotten special lessons from Lord Slytherin. Lessons that she could have had, but had thrown away in a fit of childish arrogance. Her eyes firmed. “Yes.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

If Alex thought that Lord Slytherin’s special lessons would be easier than her previous occlumency lessons, then she was sorely mistaken. She’d never ever done anything so hard. Everyday, for hours and hours, Luna ripped through her head like a hurricane, destroying everything in her path and building it back up as she went. Her brain ached and she went to bed every night exhausted, only to wake up the next morning with a thumping magical toxin hangover—a hangover that she somehow had to hide from her father, every single day.

August came and went and soon enough September the first rolled around.

“How much longer are we going to do this?” Alex groggily asked a faintly smiling Luna. They were sitting opposite each other on Alex’s bed.

“A few more months yet. Your body should be getting used to the magic soon and you won’t feel so bad in the morning.”

“Good.” Alex clutched her head. “I feel like … horrible.”

“Here, drink more water.”

Alex grabbed the offered bottle and gulped it down.

“You know, Alex, you are doing quite well. I think we’re ready to start on wandless magic, although we do still have to continue on with the occlumency for a while yet.”

Alex raised her head to look at the annoyingly chipper vision in front of her. “Eghhh … do we have to? I still don’t see the point of learning wandless magic.”

“Oh, Alex.” Luna shifted closer and took her unresisting hands in hers. “There’s so much to look forward to once you learn wandless magic. It’s not just about casting spells without a wand. You’d be missing out on so much.”

“Like?”

“Well, there’s magic sensing, and all the girls are going to become Animagi the year after next, and it does give you a last line of defence if you lose your wand. I love knowing that if any boy tries anything with me, even without a wand, I can still swat him away like the annoying pest he is.”

Alex frowned. That did sound attractive, although the point was fairly moot since she had a boy’s strength anyway. She’d never wanted to be an animagus before. It was something her father had done and, therefore, not something she’d wanted to do, but if it was with a whole bunch of other girls. … ‘All the girls’? Alex frowned and opened her mouth.

“And then of course, there’s the fact that wandless magic is sort of the badge of honour for those Lord Slytherin trusts.”

Alex slowly closed her mouth. Oh. She opened it again. “So, it’s like a test?”

“Alex, with Lord Slytherin, everything is a test.”

Alex’s eyes widened. Oh, damn. It was just like last time, when she’d turned away Harry. Damn damn damn. She shook her head. Her violet eyes firmed.”Right. Let’s do it then.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex sat alone in the Black Library reading a book from one of the sections her dad had forbidden her from entering. Her eyes widened as she skimmed the pages.

And of all the necromantic arts, the most basic, nay, the most elemental, is the raising of a magical being under the binding of the raiser. The raised, known as inferi, will obey the will of the raiser to a certain degree in the large numbers, and to a greater degree in the small numbers. A total control can be attained over a single inferius through a method similar in the practise to that most potente of all dark mind magics, the imperius curse.

Images of mighty undead dragons flew through Alex’s mind.

The ritual required to raise inferi requires a moste powerful wizzard and much practise and deliberations. The ritual in the first phase animates the corpse, and reconciles its core with that which has passed on. The ritual in the second phase binds the now animated corpse to the wizzard’s will, but only in so much as the wizzard be powerful and the corpse be fresh. If the wizzard fails in this phase, beware, for the beast will run riot across all in sight until the ritual’s magics run down and die out. The ritual in the third and final phase opens the now inferius’ core to the aether and allows the being to exist apart from the now master’s magic.

So you needed a magical core to be an inferius? Didn’t that meant that muggles couldn’t be inferi? She looked back and forth across the book but couldn’t find anything that might confirm or deny her question, although many pages seemed to have conspicuous burn marks all over them, including several passages that dealt with the ritual itself. She re-read the passage again.

‘A moste powerful wizzard and much practise and deliberations …’

Alex sighed. If there was one thing that her lessons with Luna had driven home, it was that she was ‘behind’. She’d unwittingly rebuffed Lord Slytherin and was now in a position of having to prove herself if she wanted what her friend was already getting. This sounded like just the thing to prove she was more than ready to learn more. She was sure she was powerful, but it wasn’t as though she had a horde of people ready for her to … practise … on …

A lightbulb went off in her head. She grinned.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex let the magic swirl through her, trying to feel what Luna called the ‘intent’ of the spell. It was supposed to feel like water running through her, condensing at a point about half way from her navel to her chest. No matter how much she tried she just wasn’t getting it, but she swore if it was the last thing she did, she was going to figure this out.

Luna smiled at her from the opposite chair. “You’re doing a lot better now that you’ve collected some kerfuffling scribblebugs.”

Alex unclenched her determined fists, un-scrunched her face, and smirked at Luna. “Naturally, now that I’ve found some annoying pests to swat.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alexandra watched suspiciously as Ginny Weasley, the chief worshipper of John Potter, the boy who lived, walked up to the front of the classroom, picked up the dark magic detection device that the Lady Potter, who was not her god-mother, despite her father being John Potter’s god-father, had left there, and waved it over herself.

Odd.

The red-headed witch then proceeded to just stand there with her back facing the class, holding the ring-topped black rod up to her face. She stood there, unmoving, for a whole minute. Alex timed it on the wall clock.

Weasley then spun around, face aglow with satisfaction and happiness and almost danced back to her seat.

Alex narrowed her eyes. What was Weasley up to?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Your fingers are glowing red, Alex. That’s a good sign.” Luna’s calm voice washed over her.

Alex focused and felt the spell reach the very tips of her fingers. She opened her eyes, looked straight into Luna’s, raised her hand, and loosed the stunner.

Luna instantly shielded, serenely smiling.

Alex’s heart leapt. “I did it! Hah! Yes! No one can stop me now!” She jumped up, pumped her fists in the air, almost lost her balance, and jerkily spun on one leg to keep it. She reddened. “Err, you didn’t see that.”

Luna continued to smile. “It’s okay, Alex, you don’t have to feel embarrassed around me.” She stood up and swung wildly on one foot before loosing her balance and falling back over on her bum. She pouted. “Owie.”

Alex couldn’t help it. She giggled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex approached the Black magic section of the Black Library holding a box. In this box were two dozen unbreakable jars, bought from Diagon alley the other day. This time, she was ready.

She put the box down, placed her hand on the correct book, and waited as the library’s magic recognised her as a previously accepted daughter of the house of Black. The bookcase resolved itself in a swirling of books and wood into the door. She opened it a crack, brought a stunner to her fingers, and crept over the threshold.

Something angry rocketed out of one of the shelves and towards her in a blur. Without even thinking, she released her stunner, and, by sheer luck, hit the thing before it reached her face. It fell to the ground and she snatched it up.

Her movement seemed to alert all its fellows. They took to the air to defend their downed comrade in a small swarm of scowling blue wings and bodies.

Alex leapt back through the door, slammed it behind her, dumped the unconscious doxy into one of the jars, and screwed one of the air-hole ready lids on tightly.

There. She nodded, grim faced and sweating. Test subject number one.

Alex brought another stunner to her fingers, opened the door another crack, and caught another bolting doxy clear in the chest with her second stunner. She slammed the door, dumped the second doxy into another jar and again screwed one of the lids on tightly.

Test subject number two.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The sun was bright and the day was young.

Alexandra stepped out of the Diagon alley public floo point, furtively eyed the early morning shoppers, and darted towards the nearest public toilet, careful not to jostle the contents of her shoulder bag.

Once safely ensconced, she pulled a green coloured potion out of her bag.

‘Next time, use one of these.’ Lord Slytherin had said.

Alex faced the bathroom mirror, popped the bottle’s cork, swigged the complete small dose, and watched with awe as her whole body changed. She grew taller, her face matured, her hips widened, and a sudden weight on her chest alerted her to the fact that, well, she now had one.

“Magical Merlin,” she whispered, eyes wide, hands lightly tracing the lines of her new grown-up face. She tore her gaze away from her reflection and looked around. Everything suddenly felt smaller. It was disconcerting. Alex reached for the bathroom door, opened it, pulled up the hood on her robes to hide her face, stepped outside, and started walking down the alley.

She shifted uncomfortably as she walked, and it wasn’t just her getting used to her new body anatomy. All the grown-ups around her suddenly seemed … less grown-up? It was difficult to put her finger on what had changed, but the change was there. People were looking at her differently, too. No one was paying her any attention. Or rather, people were paying her attention, but the attention felt different. Not so much, ‘what are you doing and will I to have to do something about it?’ so much as ‘I see you and acknowledge you, but won’t do anything unless you do something first.’

It all felt very different, while at the same time, being very similar. That was, until she passed a tall wizard in his twenties, whose eyes fixed on her half hidden face and didn’t leave until she’d passed, and even then she swore she could feel his lingering gaze as she continued on.

Alex self-consciously adjusted her self-adjusting robes and ducked into Flourish and Blotts, where she proceeded to buy a book to be sold only to those of age, and felt a little thrill of forbidden triumph as she left.

It had worked. She grinned. Now she could go buy stuff she needed for her experiments. Experiments that it was critical stayed secret. She was almost certain Lord Slytherin wouldn’t mind what she was doing, in fact, she hoped he’d be impressed, but she wasn’t so sure about Luna. She liked Luna—it was difficult not too, but the girl had been raised in a then light family, and felt … too innocent? Yes, that was it—too innocent—too naive. She could still remember years ago when she and Luna had occasionally played ‘light vs dark’ with John Potter and Ronald and Ginny Weasley. It had always been a four on one affair. Luna wouldn’t understand and Alex really didn’t want to lose her as a friend. As for her father, Lord Black, the chief auror, the ‘hammer of the light’ … she shuddered, the less thought about what he’d think, the better.

Alex made her way to the mouth of a side alley, checked that no one was looking, produced an ornate looking green and black mask, attached it firmly to her face, and started down the dark and forbidding shop fronts of Knockturn Alley. Her gaze trailed down the shop fronts as she walked, one by one, each one like a little mystery to be solved.

One shop window held nothing but a single black, velvet pillow on which rested a single, bone-like wand that looked disturbingly like certain illustrations she’d read—with horrified fascination—in certain ritual books of wizard-only spells. Fighting down a blush, she tried to get the images out of her head and concluded that the shop was probably for wand modifications.

The next shop window held the top half of a stuffed, fully-grown troll holding a battle-axe. A glance inside revealed many other stationary and vaguely humanoid shapes, the horrifying highlight of which, had to be the row of house elf heads on plaques behind the un-attended shop counter. The shop sign proclaimed itself as ‘The Helping Hand’.

Alex shook her head, continued down the alley, and detoured around a pair of twenty-something witches loitering outside the next shop front, smoking muggle cigarettes and looking bored. The shop window itself was blacked out and didn’t seem to be much of anything. The shop sign featured only what looked to be a nailed-up, dead, dried, and flattened snake skin. She couldn’t for the life of her think what might go on in there.

Finally, Alex found herself outside a shop front that held a collection of half skull dribbly candle holders. Now, this looked like what she was looking for. She pushed the door open, causing a little bell to tinkle, and stepped into the far darker room beyond, filled with crates and barrels and open boxes containing what looked to be half a magical zoo.

“Mornin’ Madam.” A stout little man wearing a black robe with a pointy collar and a goatee emerged from a back door and gave her the once over. “What can I do for you?”

Madam.

Alex mentally smirked, produced a parchment from her robe pocket, and handed it over to the man. “I am looking”—whoa—“for everything on this list.” That was how she’d sound when she grew up?

The wizard took the list with a curious look at her masked face and inspected the parchment. He rubbed his goatee and grunted. “Well, this shouldn’t be too difficult. We’ve most of this in stock. I’ll need to talk to Steve a few shops down about the chicken blood though.” He gave her a sideways look. “Yeh can wait a few minutes, right love?”

Love. Ack. “Yeah—Yes! I mean, that is not a problem.”

The wizard gave her a strange look and left the way he came.

Alex mentally smacked herself. Get a grip! It wasn’t as though this was anything that different to what she was used to—just grown-ups treating her as an equal instead of as a walking glass statue with the IQ of a kneazle and the self preservation of a disobedient house elf.

Not long later, the wizard returned. She paid for the goods and left the shop, carrying everything in several large bags, and wishing she had one of those cool shrinking trunks.

Alexandra spent the rest of the day walking around the alley, checking out all those little nooks and shops that had barred her as an almost ten year old, and asking all those questions she was sure would’ve been frowned on before. In particular, she learned that even with her rather generous allowance, she’d never be able to afford a shrinking trunk any time soon, and, rather embarrassingly, Gringotts were not in any way fooled by her ageing potion.

Eventually, she made her way back to the bathroom she’d started her day in, glad to take the ageing potion antidote, and looking forward to getting home to change into something a bit less constricting. Her chest was really quite sore now. How in Morgana’s name did grown-up witches go around with these things rubbing against their robes all day?

Alex left the bathroom and headed for the floo.

… Oh, and she still couldn’t get those damn wizard-only rituals out of her head.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

It was one week later.

Her father had left for the day and Alex was sure he wouldn’t be back for quite a while.

In other words, it was time to get down to business.

She barricaded herself in one of the many empty rooms of the house, furtively unloaded her many doodads onto the room’s only table, and placed the book that contained the inferi ritual next to them, open to the mildly burnt ritual description page.

Take a pint of chicken blood or as much as needed for the size of the subject to be raised—the larger be the subject, the larger will need be the deathly hallow.

She pointed to the large jar of red liquid she’d bought earlier in the week. Check.

Take the dowel and place it at the tip of the deathly hallow, that it be pointing parallel and on the line of the symbol of death.

She pointed to the simple wooden rod on the table. Check.

Next, be the stone, to be placed on the leftmost side of the hallow, at the bottom most point.

She pointed to the pebble that she’d found in the garden and washed earlier this morning. Check.

And finally, you must place a cloak at the one remaining triangle tip, taking all efforts to ensure that it be not contaminated with residue magics from charms, enchantments, or runes, lest the ritual fail and the results be really very bad.

Alex tapped the buckle of the cloak around her neck. It was the only item of clothing she had that she knew contained no magic and as such, was the only piece of clothing she now wore. She’d even taken off the black butterfly hair ornament that Susan had given her for her birthday. She suspected that her socks might not be charmed or enchanted with anything, which would be nice as the floor wasn’t exactly warm, but she wasn’t about to take that sort of risk.

She glanced down at the book again. The next paragraph was kinda burnt, but she was certain it was a warning not to interfere with external magic until the ritual was complete—Something she’d already read many times before. She continued on.

Once all these have been placed you shall take your dead subject and place it in the centre of the hallows. You shall then channel your magics into the blood painted deathly hallow and speak thusly:

‘Death who takes all, through the power of wand, stone, and cloak, hear your humble servant.’

You shall then wait for the deathly hallow to glow with the magics of death.

You shall then take your sickle or scythe and plunge it into the corpse of your subject, and channel your magic through the reaper’s tool into it, at which point you shall recite the following passage:

‘Death who takes all, I offer you back that which the three brothers took. To raise this container of a soul that you now possess. To bind its magic back to the aether, and to your humble servant.’

You shall then step out of the deathly hallow, wait for the magics to finish and begin your efforts to subjugate your newly raised inferius to your will.

Ah, yes. This bit had caused her quite a bit of headache. It had taken all week to track down a book that explained exactly how she was supposed to actually do that last part. Apparently, it was all about overwhelming the target’s magic with your own, at least for long enough to cement the bond, which is presumably why the book said the ritual took a ‘most powerful wizzard‘. In any case, she was glad she’d listened to Luna and learned the basics of wandless magic or this bit would’ve been impossible without a wand.

Alex pointed to a large tin next to the pebble on the table. Mrs. Skower’s All Purpose Magical Mess Remover? Check. Scrubbing brush and broom? Check. Hand sickle? Check. And finally—she pointed to the last item on the desk, an unbreakable jar in which a furious doxy pounded the glass with all four arms and made occasional evil finger gestures at her. She narrowed her eyes. One disgustingly obnoxious magical creature? Check.

And now all she had to do was follow the instructions.

Ten minutes later, a completely naked Alex channelled her magic into the macabre blood symbol on the floor, in the middle of which lay one now very dead doxy, and spoke the first words of the ritual.

The hallow started to glow deep red.

Alex’s heart leapt. She thrust her sickle into the doxy’s still warm body, let out another pulse of magic, chanted the ritual words, stepped back out of the ritual space, and waited.

Moments later, the cloak, dowel, and stone all started to glow as well.

Alex felt her heart beat in her chest.

Finally, the doxy started to glow. Magic swirled around the room, rushing past her and sending tingles all through her body.

A grin spread across her face. She leant forward …

… And the deceased doxy exploded, sending blue gunk all over the room in general and all over her in particular.

Alex stared. Damn. She frowned. That … wasn’t supposed to happen.

She straightened, wiped away as much of the entrails from her person as she could, and chewed her lip. She must have done something wrong.

She cast her gaze to a nearby shelf where several other doxies watched her, furiously chattering and chittering and banging their enraged tiny fists on the walls of their glass prisons.

It looked like there would plenty more library time for her in the near future.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

A few days later, Alex was feeling very silly and very stupid.

Grimmauld place was a magical house. The magics that swirled in the very air were far greater than the paltry enchantments she’d been worried her clothes might contain.

A few years ago, she’d done a ritual to give herself the strength of the male she could have been at the cost of her ability to taste sweetness. That the house hadn’t affected that ritual was a minor miracle. She shuddered to think of what could have happened to her if it hadn’t gone well, given what happened to the doxy in the ritual she’d just failed to complete.

Her latest trawl through the library yielded the depressingly basic titbit that traditional magic houses usually contained a ritual room—a space built so the inherent magic of the wards were suppressed while still being inaccessible to the outside world. It had been the work of a moment to walk into the Black magic section of the Black Library and find a floor plan of the house, which, lo and behold, showed her where the ritual room was.

Which is how Alex now found herself, naked and shivering, in the basement of Grimmauld place, surrounded by old stone walls covered in complex runic arrays, and standing on a perfectly flat slate floor, ideal for chalk and paint and, well, blood—glowing blood—glowing red like an angry red star.

She stabbed the second dead doxy with her wickedly sharp sickle, sent a pulse of raw intent through the curved blade, chanted the second ancient set of ritual words, stepped back out of the deathly hallow, and watched.

The deathly hallow glowed red.

Alex narrowed her eyes.

The dowel, stone and cloak all glowed.

The doxy glowed … and then exploded.

Alex groaned and wiped more doxy bits off her pale skin. Back to the library again.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

It was the weekend, and Lord Black was at work.

Alex stood in a dark corner of the Black Library, flipping through Ritual Troubleshooting - What to do When it All Goes Wrong, and waiting for Luna to finish lunch at the Rookery so they could do stuff together.

And if you are still experiencing problems, you might consider using a virgin as the ritual performer, as the act of intercourse subtly alters a witch or wizard’s magic in ways that can adversely affect some rituals.

Alex felt her cheeks warm up. That … wasn’t an issue for her.

Some rituals are affected by the phases of the moon, and can only be done at full, or new moon. The prevalence of this consideration is mostly restricted to fertility and life rituals.

So, again, not relevant.

Make sure to double check and triple check yourself for any and all possible external magic that you may be carrying with you into the ritual. Sometimes there are things that we carry around with us all the time that we forget about. The most common types of magic accidentally brought into rituals are small items of clothing, potions taken earlier in the day, charms still lingering on one’s person, and magical jewellery such as hair ornaments, necklaces, and rings.

Rings! Alex’s eyes widened. Damn! Damn damn damn! She looked down at her right hand, thought about her noble house ring, and watched it materialise on her index finger in the shape and crest that marked her as the heiress of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Black. She was so stupid! That must be it! Just because she kept it invisible and untouchable most of the time, that didn’t mean it wasn’t there in magic, did it? She hesitated. Or did it? She wasn’t actually too sure, but that didn’t matter. She just had to take it off and try the ritual again to know.

Alex nodded, replaced the book in the shelf, and headed for the basement. She still had a little while before Luna arrived and she really wanted to get this sorted out.

A few minutes later, she stood again in the ritual room, but now that she was here, she felt a lot less certain.

Taking off her noble house ring felt … wrong. It had protected her ever since her father had shown her how to call it when she’d been just four years old. She fingered the ring and traced the black crest on the front. Her jaw firmed. But if she didn’t do this, then she’d never know, and it wasn’t as though it would be for all that long. She closed her eyes, willingly accepted the removal of her ring without outside compulsion or persuasion, and slid it off her finger.

She looked at the tiny ring of silver in her palm, placed it carefully on the table top, and shivered. Merlin, she felt so … vulnerable. Without her ring, she might as well be a muggleborn, totally at the mercy of the first idiot to catch her off guard with a confundus charm, love potion, or obliviate.

She gently shook herself, formed up the ritual lines, carefully placed the stone, dowel, and cloak at the triangle’s corners, pulled off her robes and underthings, deposited them in a neat pile by the doorway to the rest of the house, turned away from the door, reached for the shelf nearest her, stunned another of the jar contained doxys, pulled out the horrible little thing, stabbed it through the chest with her sickle, and placed it, still bleeding, in the middle of the ritual space.

She stepped back and waited a few minutes to be certain the multi-armed blue pixie thing was dead, occasionally shivering in the cool basement air, and feeling far more naked this time than she had the last.

Okay, that should be long enough. Alex stepped back into the deathly hallow, put her finger to the blood drawn symbol, and pulsed her magic into it.

She took a deep breath. “Death who takes all, through the power of wand, stone, and cloak, hear your humble servant.”

The deathly hallow started to glow, blood red and angry. The shadows moved across the small room. Her own shadow lengthened, and was joined, moments later, by someone else’s.

Alex froze, heart leaping into her throat, dread flooding her body.

She turned her head, sickle shaking in her hand.

In the doorway, stood Luna, as naked as she, and not smiling.

Alex gasped. “Lun—”

Luna moved fast, covering Alex’s mouth with a hand and stopping her from finishing whatever shocked words she’d been about to say. The blonde shook her head, eyes sharp, mouth one thin line.

Alex found herself turned around and gently but firmly pushed forward towards the ritual space. She looked behind her again to see naked Luna making a ‘get on with it’ gesture. She gulped, knelt down, raised the sickle in an unsteady hand, thrust it into the dead doxy on the floor, and pulsed a shot of magic into it. She stood back up on weak legs and took a single, long, shaky breath. “Death who takes all, I offer you back that which the three brothers took.” Her voice trembled. “To raise this container of a soul that you now possess. To bind its magic back to the aether, and to your humble servant.”

The dowel, stone, and cloak all glowed red. The Doxy started to glow and then, exploded.

The red glows all faded away.

Alex whirled around, now covered in doxy gore. “Luna, I swear, this isn’t—Oomph!”

Luna tackle hugged her, forcing Alex to step backwards or lose her balance.

Alex’s heart was beating a mile a minute. She stiffened, unsure what to do with her now extended arms, one hand still holding the ritual sickle. “Luna? I don’t … Luna?”

Luna body shook against hers. “Stupid, Alex.”

“Luna?”

Luna leaned backwards and glared at her. “Stupid, Alex! Why didn’t you tell me?”

Alex flinched. “I didn’t think you’d like it.”

Luna’s glare softened “Oh, Alex.” It hardened again. “I don’t like many things, but the biggest thing I don’t like at the moment is that you’ve taken off your noble house ring!” She pointed to where her ring still lay on the table.

“I …” Alex looked at her feet. “… I thought its magic might be interfering in the ritual.”

“Put it back on!”

Alex scrabbled to do so, but found it difficult. Luna refused to let go of her. Soon it was back on her index finger, where she knew it belonged.

“Alex,” Luna continued, still firmly hugging her and paying no attention to the doxy remains still splattered all over her. “the Albion magics don’t interfere in rituals. If they did, no one would be able to do any rituals in the entire country.”

Oh. She stood in Luna’s arms in silence, afraid to say anything more. It seemed impossible that Luna hadn’t spotted what kind of ritual she’d been attempting.

“Alex?”

She took a shuddery breath. “Yes, Luna?”

“Why are you doing a necromancy ritual—”

Oh, Merlin.

“—without a central foci?”

…

…

…

Wait, what? “Huh?”

Luna turned and pointed to deathly hallows on the slate floor. “All necromancy rituals that use the deathly hallow as their ritual symbol use a central foci.”

The burnt paragraph!

Alex leaned back in shock. “How … how do you know that?”

“I know all about the deathly hallows.”

“But, your family is … was … light! The Lovegoods were light for generations.”

Luna smiled softly. “Stupid, Alex. We were politically light, not magically. We Lovegoods have been hunting the hallows for hundreds of years. ‘The last enemy to be defeated is death?’ That’s not just the motto of the Peverells, but of necromancers everywhere.”

Alex’s eyes widened. “You’re a … ?”

Luna shook her head, causing her little radish earrings to swing wildly about her ears. “I’m not a necromancer. Neither are my parents or my grandparents. I had a great great uncle who was, but he was the odd one out.”

Alex sighed. She relaxed slightly, dropped the hand sickle on the table, and wrapped her arms around her friend. “Luna, I’m sorry I didn’t tell you about what I’ve been doing.”

Luna’s grip on her tightened. “Stupid, Alex. I’m here. I’m your friend. I’m not going to run away because you’re practising necromancy. But what you were doing was just so dangerous. Anything could have happened to you. I know you want to prove yourself to my future lord, but, please, Alex, promise me you won’t try any more rituals without me?”

Alex’s insides clenched. Guilt, which had been starting to settle, reared its ugly head once more. “Yes, okay. I promise.”

Luna leaned back, gazed into her face, and smiled, her face returning to something more recognisable as the dreamy, unconcerned witch who worshipped pudding and hunted myths and legends. “Thank you, Alex.” She stepped backwards. “Shall we go get washed?” She wrinkled her nose. “You are really icky.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“So, you think you’ll have a copy that doesn’t have the burnt bit?” Alex asked.

Two baths and a floo trip later, Alex and Luna descended into the Rookery’s basement, where, according to Luna, most of the really Lovegood stuff went on.

“I think we might,” Luna answered, now leading the way down a short corridor. “Ah, here it is.”

Alex looked up at a huge, curved, mahogany door, carved with all kinds of magical creatures, from dragons to nifflers. It was certainly different.

Luna opened the door and they both stepped in.

Alex looked up again and breathed in sharply. The library was small, round, with a circular stair case, just like Luna had described. And also, just like Luna had described, the book shelves around the edge stretched upwards, all the way to infinity.

Luna smiled at her. “Do you feel like you’re going to fall up?”

“Yeauhg.”

“When I was six, I tied a letter to a balloon in here and let it go.”

Alex tore her gaze away from the disconcerting view. “And?”

“It never did come back down.”

Alex bit her lip. She had to know. “What did the letter say?”

“It said, ‘Don’t jump.’ ”

Alex blinked.

“Well, I thought that the library might go on forever. But then I thought that maybe it didn’t, and maybe there were people who lived at the very top. But then I thought that maybe the people who lived at the very top might think that the library went down forever, when, in fact, it doesn’t.”

“Ah.” Alex looked around, trying not to think too hard about people living in an upside-down rookery in an upside-down world. “So, where would this book be then?”

Luna frowned. “You know, I’m not sure. We did have a bit of a move around a few months ago …” She turned, leaned out of the door and screamed, “DAD! WHERE ARE THE NECROMANCY BOOKS?”

Alex goggled and a faint voice bellowed back, “Sixth floor! Right hand side! Between the books on demonic summoning and the muggle physics section.”

“THANKS!” Luna turned back and beamed.

Alex fought down her urge to throw something as she followed Luna up the stairs.

“Now, let’s see.” Luna trailed her finger along the books. “Ah, here we are.”

The collection wasn’t nearly as large as the Black Library’s. Alex stared. Whereas the Black Library had a whole row of shelves dedicated to the magic of death, here, there were only a dozen individual books, but those dozen were large tomes, thick and uniform, with expensive leather bindings, and each one had the sign of the deathly hallows imprinted on the spine.

They each pulled out a book and got to work.

It didn’t take too long for Alex to find what she was looking for.

Make sure that your central foci be of high quality and possessing absolutely no cracks. The Inferi are soulless beings that do not live and yet are once again touched by magic. In this respect, they much resemble the victims of those darkest of creatures, the dementor, and, as such, it is fitting that the central foci for the inferi ritual be taken from said creature. Acquire yourself a stake, sharpened from a dementor bone, that it may serve you well for all your future raising, and place it on the point in the deathly hallow where the circle meets the bisecting line most highest.

Alex thumped her head on the open book, and rolled her forehead around on the pages. She really was an idiot.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The sun was bright and the day was young.

Alexandra and Luna stepped out of the Diagon alley public floo point, furtively eyed the early morning shoppers, and darted towards the nearest public toilet, careful not to jostle the contents of their shoulder bags.

Once inside, they both pulled out green coloured potions from their bags.

“Bottoms up,” Luna chirped and swigged the bottle in one long gulp.

Alex downed her own dose and soon found herself, once again, regarding her grown up self in the mirror. Something grabbed her around the chest. “Gah!”

“Will you check out these!”

“Luna!” She grabbed the inquisitive hands and easily pulled them away. “What are you doing!” She turned around to face her assailant.

Luna smiled brightly, looking like a slightly more youthful version of Lady Lovegood. “I’m feeling your boobies, Alex, couldn’t you tell?”

“Well, don’t!” She reddened. “How would you feel if I grabbed yours?”

“Would you like to?” Luna pressed them together.

Alex yelped. “No! Just, c’mon. We’ve got stuff to do.”

Luna pouted and they soon found themselves walking down Knock-turn Alley, masked (Luna’s was blue as opposed to her own black one), hooded, and attracting more than a good bit of attention from the local wildlife, although it mostly backed off when Alex flashed glowing red fingers in their general direction.

“Oh, I was wondering if I’d ever see you again,”—the stout little shop keeper of the ritual supply shop finished filling a box labelled ‘phoenix ash’—“and you’ve brought company.” He nodded at Luna who was inspecting the massive skull of some ancient magical monster.

Alex adjusted her mask. “We need a stake made from a dementor bone.”

The shopkeeper sucked his breath in between his teeth. “Not asking for much this time, are you?”

“Can you do it?”

“No.”

Alex’s shoulders slumped.

“But I might know of someone who might have one and might be persuaded to part with it for … for the right price.”

Alex frowned under her mask. Something about the way the man had said that last bit felt wrong, but … “So, who is this wizard?”

“Unfortunately, I can’t just give you his name. But I can point you in the right direction and let him know to expect you.” He paused. “Who should I say is coming to visit?”

Alex looked towards Luna who gave a small nod. She turned back to the shop keeper. “Blue Mask and Black Mask.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The lighthouse was tall and white and jutted out from the land like … like … like something Luna would undoubtedly have no problem thinking about. Alex shook herself and jogged to catch up with the dreamy blonde who was now standing at the edge of the cliffs, arms outstretched, letting the sea wind blow her hair and silken robes all over the place.

“Are you done?” Alex asked, panting slightly from the effort.

Luna turned back around. “Yes. I was just enjoying the view. It’s amazing to think what might be out there.”

“What? The sea?”

“Yes. So much gets lost down there.”

Alex blinked. “I guess.” She shook herself again. “Shall we?”

Luna nodded and they made their way along the coast to where the lighthouse stood hard and firm against the elements, proud and erect. Alex shook herself so hard her mask slipped, forcing her to re-adjust it. Morgana damn this body!

Alex knocked on the front door, which was opened by a tall, bald, middle-aged man in a long black robe with large, pointy, upturned collars.

“Well?” the man asked gruffly.

“We’ve been told you will be expecting us and that you might have a dementor bone stake for sale.”

The man looked her and Luna over. He smiled a smile of sin and vice. “Blue Mask and Black Mask. Heh. Come in.”

The moment Alex stepped over the threshold, a much older looking ghost dressed much the same as the man swooped into the room.

“Oh my, those two curvy fuck toys look like they need a good dicking!”

Alex stilled, too shocked to move.

The man turned back. “Ignore my master, he’s been like that for years.”

Alex’s brain started to reboot. “Master?”

Luna had stepped past her and was now inspecting various objects around the chintzy sitting room they found themselves in, busily ignoring the ghost who was now hovering in front of her and making kissy faces.

“Yes,” the man drawled, “a dark wizard obsessed with life and death to such a degree that he performed a ritual to ensure he became a ghost when he died. Of course, now he has to deal with an eternity with no body, which, apparently, he misses.”

“Damn yes I miss it!” The dark robed ghost carelessly floated through Luna causing her to shudder. “Especially when two hot things like you turn up.”

Alex was starting to really hate this place. She turned back to the live one. “The sharpened dementor bone, how much do you want for it?”

The wizard scratched a point on his bald head. “Well, that’s tricky. See, I don’t really have much need for money, got enough of it already.”

Alex hesitated. “Then what?”

The wizard grinned. “Seeing my master go through what he did made me a lot more philosophical about life. You’ve got to live for the now, grab it while you can, and all that. It may be too late for my master, but it isn’t too late for me.”

Alex frowned, confused. “What?”

“He’s suggesting,” and Luna’s voice now sounded about as dreamy as a steel bar, “that we have sex with him in exchange for the stake.”

Alex flushed indigently. “Hell no! I’m not going to do anything like that!”

“I’m inclined to agree with you.”

The man leered. “Well, the way I see this, you can accept my offer, we all have a roaring good time and you get the dementor stake, or …” he flicked a wand into his hand “… I’ll take what I want anyway.”

Silence.

The world slowed.

Alex’s eyes widened. The man raised his wand and fired something purple towards her. She hadn’t even moved an inch before something invisible slammed into her from the side.

The world sped back up and she found herself flying straight out of the lighthouse’s front door,

The door slammed shut.

Alex tumbled.

Pain.

She slid to a stop.

Her hands, knees, thighs, and shoulders burned. She ignored it and struggled to her knees.

Luna!

Bangs, thuds and cries of pain came from the lighthouse.

She forced herself to her feet.

The lighthouse went quiet.

No!

She stumbled forward for the door, brought a stunner to her fingers, flung open the door, and charged inside. Her eyes widened and the stunner died on her fingers.

“Hello, Black Mask,” Luna said dreamily. “That didn’t hurt, did it?”

Alex’s jaw dropped.

The would be rapist was tied up in a chair, bound, gagged, and struggling helplessly. The ghost was nowhere to be seen.

“N-No, Blue Mask. I’m fine.”

“Excellent.” Luna beamed. “Now, then,” she turned to the still struggling man in the chair and leaned in close to his face, “let’s see if the bad man can be helpful.”

The man’s eyes fixed with Luna’s blue-mask eyeholes. He started convulsing in the chair, moaning into his gag, and Alex couldn’t help but remember when Luna had battered down her own occlumency barriers at her birthday party.

A few seconds later, the man conked out and Luna straightened. “The stake is one floor up on the bedroom desk. There are no defences around it.”

Alex nodded and made her way upstairs while Luna covered the bald pervert. She opened the door and found the old ghost hovering over the bed.

The ghost sniggered. “Vicious little fuck toys. Damn, I so wanted to watch my apprentice fuck your beautiful, creamy—”

Alex forced down the rising bile, grabbed the bone-made stake on the desk and bolted for the door. The faster they got out of here, the better.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alexandra Black, now back in her good-old-young body—a body that didn’t have to deal with perverts or rapists or even its own damn mind constantly shoving embarrassing thoughts at her every second of its existence, pulsed raw magic into the ritual hallow and took a deep breath.

“Death who takes all, through the power of wand, stone, and cloak, hear your humble servant.”

The deathly hallow painted on the floor in chicken blood started to glow. Alex raised her hand sickle and stuck the blade into yet another dead doxy. On the other side of the room, Luna silently watched.

“Death who takes all, I offer you back that which the three brothers took. To raise this container of a soul that you now possess. To bind its magic back to the aether, and to your humble servant.”

Alex stepped out of the hallow’s boundaries.

The dowel, cloak, and stone all started to glow.

The doxy started to glow.

The magic swirled through the space, met the dementor bone stake laying towards the centre of the hallow, rushed to the pointed tip, and arced a tiny and silent bolt of lightening towards the doxy.

Alex’s eyes narrowed.

The doxy’s eyes glowed yellow.

Right. Now, Alex, focus—All your will power.

Alex stepped forward, let her magic flow out of her and over the doxy.

The doxy made to move, but stopped, clutched its head, and let out a silent scream.

Moments later it was all over. She may not even be a Hogwarts student yet, but the tiny doxy was nothing in comparison.

The inferius doxy flittered over to where she stood, and, with a simple mental command, stood to attention on her shoulder.

Alex grinned. It was official. She was a necromancer.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The Black Witch of the North crossed her legs on her throne and imperiously surveyed her court. On the right hand side, her most fearsome warriors, commanded by General Teddy ‘one-eye’ Fluff and Wolf Plushy Bark-a-lot, stood assembled and ready to lay waste to her foes. On the left hand side, her most trusted political and magical advisers, Merlin Dolly and the ever faithful Metamorph Dolly, sat ready to give complicated and complex advice on all kinds of important things.

On her lap, lay her loyal and vicious beast, Amethyst the Panther, currently shrunk down to the size of a ten week old kitten and purring under her scratching fingers, but ready to grow to full size and pounce at a moments notice.

And around her, like whelps around a mother dragon, flittered her brand new bodyguard—the doxy trio, the most feared elite combat unit this side of the veil.

The Black Witch of the North leaned back in her throne and laughed. “Muhahaha! Now no one can stop me! Not even that accursed Boy Who Lived!”

Just then, the door to her throne room banged open and a lone witch entered.

“What is this!” she demanded. “Who dares barge into my throne room unannounced?”

The intruder smiled brightly. “I am Gray Witch Radish Rings. I am here to guide you, Black Witch of the North.”

“Guide me?! I need no guiding! I am more powerful than you can ever hope to imagine! Did The Boy Who Lived put you up to this?!”

“Oh, I do not serve him. I serve a power far greater and far, far more handsome.”

“Enough of this foolishness! General Teddy! Attack!” The Black Witch of the North jumped up from her throne—causing Amethyst to jump down and scamper away—picked up General Teddy and threw him at Radish Rings who stepped to the side and let the General sail past her.

“What?! You defeated my best general!” She scowled. “No matter. General Wolf! Attack!”

General Wolf joined General Teddy on the floor behind Radish Rings.

“You see, Black Witch of the North?” Radish Rings smiled her dreamy smile. “You still have much to learn.”

“No! Enough is enough! You will now face my true power!”

The merciless doxy trio flittering around her head zoomed forward towards Radish Rings. The gray witch’s fingers all glowed white and all three inferi were banished away and pinned against the wall by an invisible force.

The Black Witch of the North fell to her knees. “No. It’s not possible. What power is this? How can you possibly do these things?”

“I have these powers because of the power I serve.” Radish Rings released the inferi from her wandless banishing spell and the undead fairies zipped back to their mistress.

“And, what power is that?” The Black Witch of the North got to her feet and stepped towards Gray Witch Radish Rings.

“My lord, of course. The Gray Lord—Lord Slytherin.”

“Lord … Slytherin …” The Black Witch of the North tried the words on her tongue for taste. “And this Lord Slytherin wishes to … guide me, does he?”

“Yes!” Radish Rings jumped up onto the throne room bed and bounced up and down. “Prove yourself worthy to my lord and he shall grant you ultimate power!”

The Black Witch of the North’s gaze firmed. She turned away and pumped her fists down hard. “Fine! I will prove myself to Lord Slytherin!” She whirled around at Radish Rings again. “But, you’re going to help me, Gray Witch!”

“Yay!” Luna jumped off the bed and hugged her. It really did feel kind of nice.

—End of Chapter Twenty-five—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: This is the end of Part One. Part Two will be released on Tuesday, September 20th!

I’m splitting this chapter into two parts because A) It’s already 20,000 words, and B) I’m a bit behind, but I don’t want to push back the release any more.

Necromancy for Fun and Fun - Part Two

Alex woke up and groaned.

Her early morning headaches weren’t quite as bad now as before, but they still sucked. October was drawing to a close and she and Luna spent most of every day practising occlumency and wandless magic. She’d just about got the shield charm down and Luna said they’d soon be moving onto the stinging hex.

What Alex really wanted to learn though, was the banishing charm. She’d seen it used three times now—Once when she’d first met Harry and twice when Luna used it on her at the lighthouse and against her inferi doxies, now kept in jars hidden behind the portrait of her grandfather.

She rolled out of bed, still clutching her head, and made her way downstairs for breakfast. Her father had already left for work so she didn’t have to worry about him worrying about her.

Fortunately, she was starting to feel a bit better by the time school rolled around, which was just as well, because what greeted her in the classroom blew her mind even more than the toxins did.

“What the hell is this?” she shouted, spotting the front page of the Daily Prophet laid out on the table. She snatched it up and skimmed the article.

HOGWARTS TROLL DEFEATED BY FIRST YEARS!

Unbelievable.

She stormed out of the classroom. If Greengrass and this muggleborn Slytherin vassal witch were already doing stuff like that then just how far behind was she? Damn it! Why oh why hadn’t she accepted Harry’s offer? Practising with Luna was great and all, but …

She stopped, halfway down the stairs. Wait. She shook her head. She was being silly. Of course Greengrass and the vassal were ahead of her, they were a year older than her! She shouldn’t be comparing herself to them. She should be comparing herself to people her own age … people like Luna.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Try again, Alex?”

Alex groaned, accepted Luna’s hand, and got shakily to her feet. “I swear I almost had you that time. If I had just gotten through that last shield …”

Luna smiled. “I’m sure you would have, Alex.”

Alex narrowed her eyes. “Again then.”

Luna nodded and they faced off against each other again.

“Start!”

Alex brought a bright red stunner to her fingers and loosed it at Luna.

Luna cast a shield to block it.

Then, Luna brought her own stunner to her other hand and cast it at her.

Alex just managed to side step it, but it had been a close thing. She’d already half formed her second stunner and decided this would be the perfect time to unleash her surprise weapon. She sent a mental command to her inferi minions to swarm Luna.

Luna’s eyes widened slightly, red stunner also half formed on her fingers, as the three undead doxies emerged from their hiding places around the Lovegood orchard and attacked her en mass.

Alex grinned and let loose her stunner. It ran straight into another of Luna’s shields and Luna cast her own stunner straight at her, completely ignoring the three doxies that were now pulling the blonde’s hair, scrabbling on her robes, and scratching at her legs.

The last thing Alex thought before she fell unconscious was that doxy inferi really kind of sucked.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex and Luna sat on twin beanbags that Luna had dragged over from the Rookery to the Black Library, relaxing and reading and taking turns at petting a purring Amethyst.

Alex sighed. “Luna?”

“Yes, Alex?”

“I think I need to practise inferi raising on something bigger.”

Luna lay aside her book. “Because your doxies aren’t good in combat?”

Alex nodded.

“But they are good at intelligence gathering and infiltrating hard to get at places.”

Alex nodded again, more slowly this time. “Yes, but still.” She frowned. “It’s not as though I know where to get something bigger to practise on though, so I guess it’s useless anyway.”

Luna put a finger to her chin. “Maybe not. Dad is the second largest donator to the department of the regulation of control for magical creatures, so we do have certain privileges.”

Alex perked up. “You’d do that for me?”

“Well, I’d have to ask Dad first, but of course.”

Alex grinned. “Thanks, Luna. You’re the best.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Thank you for agreeing to do this, Lord Lovegood.” Alex curtseyed in her plain and completely unmagical robes.

Luna and Lord Lovegood, by contrast, were both dressed in identical beige trousers, long sleeved shirts, and matching safari pith helmets.

“Don’t worry about that, young lady. It’s about time for their culling anyway and it is my license. Just make sure you stay behind me at all times. These critters can be rather tricky if you don’t know how to deal with them.”

Alex nodded uncertainly, eyeing the long metal and wood device that Lord Lovegood had casually slung over his shoulder, and which had been introduced to her as his pre-1964 Winchester Model 12 Shotgun.

“Just don’t tell anyone about it,” Lord Lovegood said with a wink, indicating the weapon.

Alex hurriedly nodded and soon found herself in a small boat, bobbing offshore of a heavily warded Scottish island.

“Hang on!” Lord Lovegood shouted and she felt the squeeze of a side along apparition.

They landed on soft ground and Alex instantly regretted wearing robes, not that she had any clue about what else to wear.

She and Luna kept a few steps behind Luna’s father and he soon held up his hand, indicated that they should stop.

He readied his weapon and shouted. “Oi! Ugly! Over here!”

Something large, hairy, and five legged bolted for him from just around the next hill. There was an ear-shattering BANG, and the thing skidded to a dead halt right in front of him.

“Hah! They never learn.” Lord Lovegood leaned over the corpse and Alex stepped forward to inspect it.

“Quintapeds are highly magically resistant.” Lord Lovegood continued. “And they’ve never faced anything except wizards since the ministry made the island unplottable and warded it. So they see a wizard on his own or with just a few others and they immediately think he’s easy prey. Hah! Not this wizard!”

He nudged the quintaped with his shotgun. “I suggest you get on with your project then, Miss Black. Best not to hang around.”

Alex quickly nodded and soon she and Luna had the ritual space prepared around the dead class XXXXX beast.

She spoke the words, channelled the magic, thrust in the sickle, spoke the next words, channelled the next bit of magic, stood back and prepared herself.

The quintaped scrambled back to life, eyes glowing a deep purple.

Alex focused her magic and sent it out to engulf the beast.

The quintaped halted it’s skittering movements.

Yes.

Alex felt a huge overwhelming pressure all over her body and the connection to her magic snapped.

No!

The undead quintaped turned and bolted towards her in a flurry of legs and a snapping of teeth.

She took a desperate step backwards and tried to bring her magic to her fingers to defend herself from the rushing onslaught of meat and jaws, but she knew it was already too late.

The beast leapt.

And from behind her, Lord Lovegood’s shotgun barrel was thrust forward, impaling the quintaped in its wide open maw, letting out another earsplitting ‘BANG!’, and exploded the beast’s head in a fine mist of gore.

Alex fell backwards and gazed in horror at the spot where what remained of the quintaped now lay. That had been far too close. She felt Lord Lovegood place a comforting hand on her shoulder. “Bit more practise on less dangerous things first, I think, yes?”

Alex gulped and nodded shakily. That hadn’t been anything like when she’d subdued the doxy. The doxy had been easy. This hadn’t. This had felt like she was trying to push a tendril of her magic against an octopus of magic, tendrils all over the place, chaotic and uncontrollable. “Yeah. Practise. Yes.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Heiress Black,

I hope this owl finds you well. It’s been quite a busy few weeks as you’ve no doubt seen. If I had my wish, none of the witches involved would have had to face the troll, but the event does highlight one of the reasons I take an interest in the ability of those in my sphere to defend themselves. Our world is not as safe as those in power might wish us to believe and if we do not take responsibility for our own well being, or allow others to take away from us that responsibility, we will be at the mercy of those who are not so complacent.

It’s good to hear about your continued practise of occlumency and wandless magic with Luna. I hope you continue.

I’ve attached something that you might appreciate. Copies of the troll fight are quite easy to come by, but I’m not sure if you were able to. I can’t imagine your father would just leave that kind of thing lying about.

Yours,

Lord Slytherin

Alex re read the parchment one last time while she and Luna waited for their appointment slot in Michelle McLaggen’s Memories in Diagon Alley. She bounced her knee up and down and tapped the low table next to the settee they sat on. Luna hummed quietly. The space was set up like a waiting room and on the far side of the room, a partition separated the pensieve room from the rest of the shop. A half dozen other customers were also waiting.

“Alright girls,” said the middle aged woman behind the counter, addressing them. “Your turn.”

Alex and Luna stood up.

“But just the fifteen minutes, mind you. Don’t make me come in there and get you.”

Alex rolled her eyes and Luna nodded. They walked into the room next door, covered from floor to ceiling in moving pictures of famous moments throughout wizarding history. Alex opened her bottle of silvery liquid, poured it into the plinth bound pensieve in the middle of the room, and they both dived in.

Alex watched in awe as the Vassal, Hermione Granger, a muggleborn(!), dove straight into the bathroom and summoned the screaming girl out of the way of the descending club. She yelled in fright when the troll tried to flatten the Indian girl but was again stopped by Granger, this time by shattering the troll’s weapon.

By the time Granger and the Greengrass Heiress both transfigured random pipes into swords, she was cheering, and when one of the other girls shielded Greengrass from a thrown rock, she was convinced. These were the people she wanted to hang out with.

The memory ended with John Potter being a complete dumbass, although, dumbass or not, Alex couldn’t deny that the boy who lived was very powerful. Was Harry also that powerful? They were twins after all.

Luna didn’t say much, but Alex was sure the smiling blonde was just as fascinated as she was enthralled.

They watched the memory three more times before the woman from the counter came to kick them out.

Alex dashed back home. She had another owl to write.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex surreptitiously watched Weasley from the other side of the classroom.

The red haired girl was up to something and had been for a while now.

Alex doubted anyone else had spotted it, but they hadn’t spent the last few months practising wandless magic with Luna.

Still, Alex hadn’t been sure. At least, not until Weasley had unknowingly let her see glowing fingers under the desk.

“Weasley!”

Weasley turned around on the stairs where she’d been trying to get away. “Yes, Black?”

Alex caught up with her. “You’re being taught by him, aren’t you?”

Weasley seemed to panic and a few minutes later, in the small copse surrounding the Potter Manor, Alex got the truth out of her. Weasley was being taught by Lord Slytherin, or at the least one of his other students.

“Duel me!”

Weasley looked nervous. “Well, okay then, but just this once. We can’t risk making this a regular thing. Not here.”

Alex nodded. “Fine.” She turned around and walked towards the other end of the clearing. She smiled. Here at last was a chance to really test herself. She turned back around and brought her stunner half-way to her fingertips. If Weasley also couldn’t beat Luna then she was sure she could beat Weasley.

Alex watched the leaf slowly fall to the ground and smirked. Weasley wasn’t even pre-loading her spells.

The leaf hit the ground, she made to cast her stunner, and THREE WHOLE SPELLS shot towards her. She gasped, made to move, got hit, and blacked out, hitting the ground with an un-ceremonial thud.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex barged into Luna’s bedroom sat down on the edge of the bed, folded her arms and sulked. “You’ve been going easy on me.”

Luna looked up from where she sat, cross legged, on the bed. “Alex?”

“I just duelled Weasley and she said she can’t beat you and then she pounded me into the dirt.”

“Alex, I have not been going easy on you.”

Her voice rose an octave, anger starting to show. “Then how do you explain—”

“Alex, I have not been going easy on you, I have been teaching you.”

That brought her up short.

“Me and Ginny have been duelling each other for over a year. If I just pounded you into the dirt every time we duelled like Ginny did, you would never have time to get better, just like with the quintaped.”

Alex slowly deflated again. “A year …” she almost whispered.

“Yes,” Luna said, scooting down the bed to sit beside her. “And you will get better like that too, but you have to be patient and listen to me.”

She suddenly felt rather small. “I-I’m sorry.” She fiddled with the hem of her robes. “It’s just so frustrating knowing how behind I am.”

Luna smiled softly. “That’s okay, Alex. Me and Ginny are probably the only people our age you’re behind.”

Alex stared at the wall.

The two of them sat in silence for a moment.

“Um, Luna?”

“Yes, Alex?”

“I understand if you don’t want to, but …” She hesitated. “But could we learn the banishing charm next instead of the stinging hex? It’s just that it was so cool when you and Harry used it and I really want to know it too.”

Luna tapped her chin and looked thoughtful. She smiled. “We can do that.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Heiress Black,

Regarding the memory of the troll fight … You’re most welcome. I’m glad you enjoyed watching it.

As for your question about my ability to guarantee places in Slytherin House … The method Hogwarts uses to place students takes into account the wishes of the student in the placement. So long as you choose to go to Slytherin, the sorting will place you there, although it may try to persuade you otherwise if it sees sufficient non Slytherin qualities in you. I personally have no doubt you will end up in my house.

I also have to thank you for your willingness to occasionally look through the Black Library for me. I actually have a project that I’m working on right now that could use such assistance. I am friends with a rather special ghost who is currently bound to a certain tree in Wales. I’m looking for a method to rebind her to something rather more portable, possibly a cutting of the tree, possibly something else entirely.

I’ve no idea if you can find anything, but if you can it would be most helpful.

Yours,

- Lord Slytherin

Alex re-read the owl again and again. This was it. This was her chance to prove herself to Lord Slytherin.

She dashed from her bedroom down to the library, and immediately headed for the section towards the back—the same section she’d originally found the book with the inferi ritual. She perused the first book on the shelf. No luck. She tried the second. Nada.

Several hours later, Alex felt tired, grumpy, and was no closer to finding anything that could help.

“Why don’t you check the Black family magic section?” her grandfather replied when she asked him.

Alex winced. She’d spent so much time in here with Luna, or else practising occlumency and wandless magic, that she’d barely looked through the Black Magic in the several months since her birthday.

The hidden Black family magic section was almost as dusty as when she’d first opened it, although now obviously free of doxies.

Alex read up and down the shelves. Her finger fell on a dusty tome in burgundy leather. Spirit Necromancy—Ghosts, Poltergeists, Shades, and Paintings. Alex grinned.

She was just about to leave when her eyes fell on something else. The Dendromancer’s Doomsday Book—the book she’d tried to read before the doxies first attacked her. Curiosity getting the better of her, she carefully slid it out, opened it up, and her eyes went wide. Thousands of tiny entries filled the pages. The book was a magically updating record of all the magical trees in the country. She bit her lip. Oh, magical Merlin, the things her family must have been able to do with something like this!

A lightbulb went off in her head. The things she could do with something like this, now.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The weather outside was getting colder, but Alex and Luna hardly noticed, buried as they currently were in their twin beanbags in the Black Library.

“Luna?”

“Yes, Alex?”

“I was thinking …”

“Gooood.”

Alex snorted. “I was thinking, magical trees have magical cores, don’t they?”

“They do.”

“And trees can’t move, can they?”

“Some trees can—like the whomping willow.”

Alex struggled out of her beanbag’s death-grip to sit upright and look over to where Luna was still buried and staring at the ceiling. “Right, but they can’t move across the ground.”

“No, they are rooted in place.”

“So, what if the inferi ritual worked on magical trees?”

Luna didn’t say anything.

“I mean, if it did work, then I could keep trying to subdue it for as long as needed without having to worry about it attacking.”

More silence.

“Luna?”

Luna struggled out of her own beanbag, a small smile on her face. “It might work. I’ve never heard of inferi trees before, but if it does work, it would solve your problem.”

Alex nodded happily.

“But, Alex, how are you going to find a dead tree? I don’t think that killing a tree for practise is a good idea. Killing trees is bad.”

“Oh!” Alex rolled over on her beanbag and stretched out to reach behind it. “That’s not a problem. Look at this!” She handed the The Dendromancer’s Doomsday Book over to Luna.

Luna started reading it and her eyes went wide. “Wow, Alex, this is amazing.”

“I know, right?” Alex beamed. “So, can we do it?”

Luna smiled. “Yes, I think we can.”

Alex grinned.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lord Slytherin,

Success! I spent ages looking through the Necromancy section of the Black Library (I practically know it like the back of my hand now) and I found a ritual that can do what you asked, but the ritual is Black family magic so only I can do it. Is that a problem? I do feel I’m qualified for it. I can sneak out at some point if you need it. My father would never notice.

Respectfully,

Heiress Alexandra Black,

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alexandra Black stood in the Black library and shook with rage.

Heiress Black,

That sounds wonderful. I suggest we meet up some time soon to discuss this further.

However, while receiving your news is welcome, something has come up which disturbs me greatly and which directly concerns you. I’ve received intelligence from a reliable source that your father may be considering purging the Black Library of all books that he considers ‘dark’. I don’t need to tell you what a loss that would be to our culture and our world’s hard earned understanding of magic.

I don’t believe he is planning to act immediately, but knowing how much you value your library, this isn’t a situation that I could just sit on.

I believe your father still brings you to the Winter Festival at Greengrass Manor? That would be a perfect opportunity for us to meet and to talk about both these matters. I also shouldn’t need to say that if I am to help you, as you are currently helping me, then our knowledge of your father’s intentions must remain absolutely secret.

Yours,

- Lord Slytherin

She gripped the parchment in front of her so tightly her fists went white. How could he? Her own father! Didn’t he appreciate the fifteen hundred years of history in this room? He was supposed to be Lord Black! He was supposed to protect the family legacy, not tear it apart. If she could be Lord Black, she’d rather die than let someone defile their ancient library!

She reread the owl again. If it was true, and she had no reason to doubt that it was, then this was the last straw. Her eyes narrowed. She wouldn’t let her father get away with it. No, not if she could do anything about it and it seemed Lord Slytherin didhave an idea about what to do about it.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Can you believe it?!” Alex paced the room in her nightdress while Luna sat crosslegged on the bed, scratching a purring Amethyst behind the ears.

“I mean, how could he?!”

Luna’s face was completely unreadable.

“Gah! I just want to—”

“—Alex.”

Alex paused, mid rant.

“You told my lord you could do something that you’ve never tried.”

“Huh?”

“The ghost binding ritual. Have you ever done it?”

Anger drained out of her. She felt her ears heat up. “Um …”

“You remember what happened to the doxy when you didn’t do the inferi ritual correctly? What do you think my lord would think if that happened to his friend?”

Alex paled. “I … I didn’t think …” She gulped. “So … we try it, first?”

Luna’s expression slowly morphed into a smile. “I think that would be a very good idea.”

“But where are we going to find a ghost? And one who won’t mind us doing tests on them?”

Luna tilted her head to one side and hummed. “Oh, I doubt we’ll find one who’ll let us do it willingly.”

“Then what are we going to do?”

“Well, obviously, we find a ghost who we don’t mind forcing and perhaps accidentally destroying.”

Alex frowned. “But who …” Her expression turned into one of sickening horror as realisation dawned. “Oh no! Hell no! I’m not going anywhere near him again!” She shook her head violently causing her long black hair to fly all over the place. “Absolutely not. No. No way. Not a chance.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The rain pattered on Alex’s hooded head as she and Luna, already under the effects of ageing potion, crept towards the lighthouse in the dead of night.

“Really, you’d think someone who ‘had no need for money’ would have some decent wards, wouldn’t you?” Alex muttered, trying to ignore the feeling of dampness creeping in through her thick, specially bought, non-enchanted robes.

“Maybe he just saves all his money for other things?” Luna suggested in a voice far too cheerful for the weather.

“What other things?”

Luna put a wet finger on her blue mask where her chin would be. “Maybe on whatever goes on in the shop with the snake skin nailed to the sign?”

Alex looked at her sharply. “And what does go on in the shop with the snake skin nailed to the—” But Luna had already moved ahead, and by the time Alex caught up with her, they were right up against the lighthouse’s door.

“Banishing spells on three?” Alex whispered.

Luna nodded.

“One, two, three.”

BOOM! The door flew off its hinges and sailed through the lighthouse’s living space taking some of the furniture with it. There was an alarmed shout from the above floors and moments later, the would be dark wizard rapist, wearing only a dressing gown and a floppy nightcap, hastily descended the steep lighthouse stairs, wand in hand, took one look at her and Luna in their robes and masks, fingers already aglow, made a little squeaking noise, and apparated out with a loud crack.

“Go!” Luna shouted.

Alex made a beeline for the stairs and charged into the bedroom.

“Hi, pervert ghost.” She reached into her bag.

“Oooo it’s the curvy fuck toys, back again!” The ghost cackled and rubbed his hands together, “and what can I do for the curvy—”

Alex drew out a knife and a silver pendant in the shape of the deathly hallows that Luna’s dad had leant them.

The ghost stopped in mid cackle.

Alex slashed a gash in her hand and flung some of the resultant blood at the shocked ghost. “Death who takes all, through the power of the deathly hallows, hear your humble servant.”

“What are you doing?!” the ghost shouted. It made as thought to move, but Alex knew it now couldn’t—not until she was finished.

“Death who takes all, bind this spirit to your servant’s person, that they may serve your—” There was a small explosion from downstairs that shook the room. “—servant as your servant serves you.” Heart pounding, she held up the deathly hallows to the still protesting ghost, and channelled her magic straight into the pendant.

The pendant glowed silver and ethereal chains leapt from the pendant, wrapping themselves around the ghost.

Alex’s heart leapt. It worked! And through the ageing potion too! She turned and ran back down the stairs, unceremoniously dragging the shouting and cursing ghost behind her.

Luna turned to her from the middle of a small pile of rubble that used to make up a bit of one of the walls. “I have a stone.”

“I have a ghost!”

“Then let us be away from here.”

And be away from here they did, all the way back down the path to where they’d stashed a pair of broomsticks, up into the air, and across the country side as fast as they could, all the way back to the Rookery, one very unhappy ghost trailing behind them like a small silvery comet.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Well, this is all very interesting,” said Lord Lovegood, currently wearing a mask as blue as Luna’s. “I don’t think I’ve ever interrogated an evil dark wizard before, especially a dead one.”

Lady Lovegood nodded from under her equally blue mask. “Indeed, just be sure you two girls don’t spend all day in here and come up if you want any of the pie I’ve baked.”

The now inexplicably purple tinted ghost looked up groggily from where it hovered unsteadily in the middle of the Lovegood’s ritual room—not that it knew that. “Pie?”

Alex sent another pulse of magic into the deathly hallow painted on the floor and the ghost flinched back.

Luna hummed cheerfully, “Thanks, Mum!”

The two adult Lovegoods nodded and left them.

In the last few weeks, she and Luna had tried binding, rebinding, unbinding, controlling, forcing to speak truthfully, seeing through the ghost’s eyes, making the ghost solid, conjuring ghost like objects for a ghost’s use, forcing it to speak only ancient Greek, changing its colour, and now causing controlled pain. They’d gotten the binding, rebinding, unbinding, and colour change rituals to work, but the other rituals, except for the pain ritual, were missing something.

The old ghost had been unbearable, constantly spewing out stuff that Alex was certain young witches shouldn’t be hearing, and some of the stories he told them of his life made her want to hurl.

Luna moved to stand beside her. “I think he’s been about as much use as we can expect, Black Mask.”

Alex nodded. “Soo … we try the final ritual then, Blue Mask?”

“Yes.”

The ghost looked up. “F-Final ritual? Fuck Toys?”

Alex and Luna set the room up the exact same way they would for an inferi ritual, the major difference from the last time being they now wore their specially bought, non magical clothes. No way beyond the veil were they going to strip down in front of this thing.

Alex stepped forward and sent a pulse of magic into the deathly hallow on the floor. “Death who takes all, through the power of wand, stone, and cloak, hear your humble servant.”

The deathly hallow started to glow red.

The ghost tried to speak, but all that came out was a strangled choke.

“Death who takes all, I grant you that which has been trapped on the in-between. The soul of a wanderer, held back from your embrace, now to return to the eternal river that lies beyond the veil.”

Her magic swirled around her.

The room got noticeably colder.

The ghost opened its mouth in a silent scream—the deathly hallow glowed brighter than Alex had ever seen—and the ghost evaporated in a swirl of ephemeral mist.

The room was quiet.

Luna brushed her hands on her robes. “Thank Merlin. If I had to hear him say, the F-T word one more time …”

Alex turned to face her. “Yes?”

“… Then I’d be forced to hate myself when I finally start saying, ‘fuck toy,’ and that would be horrible.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“So, let me get this straight.” Portrait Orion Black leaned back in his painted high-back chair. “Lord Slytherin has heard word that my son is planning to destroy most of the Black Library?”

Alexandra nodded.

“And he says he has a plan to stop that?”

Alex nodded again.

“And you’re going to meet up with him at the Winter Festival to talk about it?”

Another nod. “That, and the ghost Necromancy thing.”

“Mmmmm.” Her grandfather pursed his lips. “Well, as much as it pains me to say it, that does sound like the kind of thing my son would do and I don’t need to say that even were the threat small, we cannot let any threat to the library stand.” He stroked his beard. “On the other hand, you must be careful. Slytherin could well be using the opportunity, whether real or made up, for his own ends in such a fashion that might not be in the best interests of House Black. Do not allow yourself to be trapped.”

Alex straightened and nodded.

“Having said that,” Orion continued, “Slytherin is going far out of his way to get in your good graces—”

“But he still won’t teach me,” Alex couldn’t help butting in.

Orion sighed. “Child, you cannot expect a Lord to just drop everything he’s doing to personally teach you.”

“He’s teaching Weasley,” she muttered.

Orion raised an unimpressed eyebrow. “The one who laid you out without even meaning to?”

Alex grumbled under her breath.

“There are only so many hours in the day. Priorities have to be made. If the Weasley girl is more advanced than you, obviously he wants to spend his limited time on her.”

“But … but if he is … you know …” She blushed. “Talking to me because of that, then shouldn’t he at least meet me in person?”

“He should. But that is not the point here. Regardless of your personal feelings on the matter, Slytherin is doing far more for you than you currently appreciate, and if he can protect the Black library when both yourself or I cannot, then you will be even more in his debt. Do you think your friend, the Lovegood girl, would be able to teach you if she hadn’t already been taught be him?”

“I guess not.”

Her grandfather leaned forward in his chair. “You should look for some way to balance things out a bit.”

Alex opened her mouth.

“I know you’re helping him with his ghost friend,” he quickly added, “and that is a good start, but you should find something else too, preferably something that benefits both of you.”

Alex thought for a few moments, then slowly nodded.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex and Luna leaned over a table in the Black Library, going over the details of their plan one last time. The Dendromancer’s Doomsday Book was on the table, open to a page that listed all the magical trees and their current states in the county of Cumbria. One line read, ‘Whomping Willow, Died—17th May 1990—Greengrass Forest Hilltop’

Alex jabbed a finger at a parchment with lots of scribbles on it. “The wards around the manor will always track us, so the Winter Festival is the perfect time. Yes, we’ll be there, but so will several hundred other witches and wizards.”

Luna nodded.

“Once the main part of the ritual is complete, I can practise subduing the tree until I’m magically exhausted, or at least fifteen minutes.”

Luna nodded again.

“And once I fail to bring the tree under control, we’ll just blow leaves over it and get the hell out of there. The ritual magics will run down quickly, and so long as no one pumps more magic into the ritual—and who’d be dumb enough to do that—it’ll all be fine.”

Luna nodded yet again.

“And before you know it, the blood will all be washed away and no one will be any the wiser.”

Luna smiled. “That’s the plan.”

Alex grinned. “And if it goes well, we can make it a regular thing. I’ll soon have the knack of it, and you can have some Five-X magical creature duelling partners.”

Luna’s smile widened. “Just no dragons, Alex, we don’t have anywhere to put them.”

Alex pouted.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex sneaked around Grimmauld Place, poking her nose into the various storage rooms and having a general good root around.

Something to balance things out. Something that could benefit both her and Lord Slytherin …

She reached into one paper lined box and drew out what looked to be a pair of hand mirrors. One of her father’s many Hogwarts stories came, unbidden, to mind. She smiled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The mist engulfed Greengrass manor and the surrounding forest in a perpetual obscuring charm. Alex stomped her feet in bring some warmth to them and hefted the huge bag she had slung over one shoulder. She’d been waiting for ages. If they didn’t get a move on, the hunt would start and they’d never be able to get out of the forest in time.

“Hi, Alex.” Luna appeared out of the mists.

“Luna! Where have you been?”

Luna smiled. “Manor shopping with my lord.”

“Manor?” Alex said, startled. “He’s buying a Manor? Where?”

“The manor is not built yet. My lord says it won’t be done until next Winter Festival. It’ll be on an island off Scotland. It’s beautiful and has this wonderful hill you can roll down.”

Alex took in Luna’s slightly ruffled appearance. “Yeeeesss, I can see that …” She straightened and looked around. “So, are you ready?”

Luna smiled brightly. “Yep! I just finished getting our permits.”

Alex stilled. Dread trickling into her stomach. “Permits?” Her voice rose. “Luna, did you tell Greengrass!?”

Luna tilted her head. “Of course I did, Alex. Daphne is my future sister and these are her family’s lands.”

“But! But!”

“Alex,” Luna said in a soothing voice, stepping closer and hugging her.

She stiffened.

“It’s okay, remember? We’re all going to help each other and it’s all going to be okay. You just have to trust us, okay?”

Alex hesitated before relaxing. “O-okay, then, I guess.”

The two of them mounted a pair of broomsticks, donned a pair of masks, swigged a pair of ageing potions, took off into the air, swiftly identified the correct hill, and landed, now as Blue Mask and Black Mask.

Blue Mask patted the trunk of the dead whomping willow. “Big fella, isn’t he?”

Black Mask didn’t reply as she was already clearing the area around the tree and getting ready to paint the huge deathly hallow needed from her shoulder bag of chicken’s blood.

Soon, they were ready. The sacrificial cloak, dowel, and stone were placed at each of the three triangle points and the dementor stake pointed up near the middle.

Alex took a deep breath, stepped into the hallow, shot a pulse of magic into it, and raised her ritual sickle. “Death who takes all through the power of wand, stone, and cloak, hear your humble servant.”

The clearing grew noticeably colder, even more so than the already December cold Cumbrian air. She shivered. Thank Merlin they now had special ritual robes. Doing this naked didn’t bare thinking about.

The Deathly hallow started to glow red.

She walked all the way into the centre and stabbed the bark with her sickle. It embedded itself in the thick trunk. “Death who takes all, I offer you back that which the three brothers took. To raise this container of a soul that you now possess. To bind its magic back to the aether, and to your humble servant.”

Alex scampered back outside of the deathly hallow to where Luna stood, coiled and tense, well outside the range of the whomping willow’s branches.

The dowel, stone, and cloak started to glow, magics rushed through the clearing, the dementor bone arced a bolt of silent lightning, and the tree gave one massive creak. The cloak, wand, and dowel all evaporated.

Alex readied herself, bringing all her magical powers to her command, ready for the dominance battle with the huge tree, a battle she knew she would lose, but not without testing herself to her absolute limit first.

A pair of steaming blue eyes snapped open like two portals into the realm of death.

Alex gulped

A growl like a hellhound crept up her spine and froze her to the spot.

“Black Mask,” Luna prompted.

No! She shook herself, thrust out both hands in front of her, and released her magic to intermingle and bind with the whomping willow inferius in front of her. The inferius tree’s magic smashed back into her like a battering ram.

She dropped to one knee.

“Black Mask!”

She struggled. So strong. Just so, so strong.

A branch smashed into the ground just in front of where she and Luna stood.

But she would NOT be stopped just like that. This was probably the only chance she’d have to practise this for weeks if not months. She forced herself to her feet and glared at the wall of flailing branches and twigs in front of her.

Their magics continued to fight each other. There was no contest. The whomping willows magics were far too strong, but so long as it couldn’t get to her, it made no difference.

She winced as a particularly strong wave of magic pushed against her.

There was a massive rumbling noise.

Alex felt the ground move.

The mass of branches in front of her raised to reveal the trunk again.

One massive root wrenched itself out of the ground.

“Oh, that isn’t good,” Luna whispered.

The roots continued to dislodge more and more earth and one massive tree like foot steeped out of the ground.

“Yeah, definitely not good!” Alex shouted.

Luna ran.

Alex abandoned her magic dominance battle and dove to the side just as another branch slammed where she’d just been standing. She scrabbled to her feet and made it to the other end of the clearing.

The inferi tree slowly turned to her and took one massive step forward.

“Black Mask! Broomstick! Here!” Luna chucked her her broomstick.

She barely caught it and moments later the two of them zoomed into the sky, leaving a furiously pissed off inferi tree behind them.

The both caught their breath.

The tree bent upwards to look at them in the sky and growled.

“The dementor bone,” Alex said.

They both looked down at the deathly hallow painted on the ground, now devoid of cloak, dowel, and stone, but very much still containing the stake.

“I’ll distract it, you grab it?” Luna suggested.

Alex nodded. “And the sickle.”

“Yes.”

One horrible dive later, in which Alex was sure she was either going to crash or end up tree food, she’d snatched back the dementor bone, and the dislodged the sickle from an enraged tree, which could do nothing to reach her, so close was she to the trunk.

She and Luna sped back into the air.

The tree snarled at them, apparently frustrated by the fast moving pests. Eventually, it moved back to where they’d first found it, replanted itself back in the ground, and slowly closed its eyes.

They waited, but it didn’t seem inclined to move any more.

Alex gazed at the now dangerous patch of forest with a worried expression. “That really didn’t go like we wanted. I barley got twenty seconds of practise.”

Luna shrugged. “These things don’t always work out,” she said, sage like. “The important thing is that no one catches us.”

Alex nodded and moments later the two of them had banished a bunch of leaves over the blood and retreated back across the forest canopy, back towards Greengrass Manor.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex wasn’t in a particularly good mood after the inferius tree failure. She grumbled her way through the festival avoiding every cheerful face and laughing family. The stall keepers were the worst though, always calling out to her in some misplaced attempt to cheer her up from whatever trivial concerns obviously befell ten year old witches, which, even if she wasn’t doing certainly illegal Necromancy experiments, was a stupid assumption to make. Obviously, none of the middle aged wizards calling out to her had ever been a ten year old witch in Magical Britain.

She dodged past one particularly insistent stall keeper who wanted her to, “turn her frown upside-down,” while pointing to a sign that read, ‘THE WINTER FESTIVAL MIRROR OF ERISED—[NOT THE REAL ONE] FOUR KNUTS!’ (£0.36). So focused was she in getting away from the man that she wasn’t paying attention to where she was going.

She ducked around a corner and, suddenly, there he was.

Her eyes widened.

Tall and dignified, all long black and silver robes, emerald green mask, and …

… And coiled fluffy snake.

“Ah. Good afternoon, Heiress Black,” Lord Slytherin said, giving her a respectful nod.

“L-Lord Slytherin.” She dipped into a hasty curtsey, but she also just couldn’t tear her eyes away from the fluffy snake which was still coiling around Slytherin’s chest and hissing.

“Mmm?” He seemed to realise what had her attention. “Oh, take no notice of her. A gift for Daphne. You’re going to protect her from all the nasty things that dare try and hurt her, aren’t you?” He sounded highly amused and she realised he was talking to the toy snake. He then hissed something and the snake let out what Alex could only think of a kind of snaky, hissing, laugh.

Alex shivered. Parseltongue. Of course, he was Lord Slytherin after all.

Lord Slytherin turned back to her. “Behind the stables in five minutes you will find a trunk. Knock seven times.” He then vanished. Not apparating—there was no crack sound—just becoming a shimmer in the air, which then almost instantly become nothing.

Alex blinked.

Five minutes later, she found herself behind the stables and there was indeed a trunk. She knocked seven times, the trunk lid opened, and she climbed inside what seemed to be a well appointed, if rather small, sitting room. Lord Slytherin sat in the far most high back chair, still wrapped in the fluffy snake.

The lid closed behind her.

“What if someone finds the trunk?” she asked.

“They would have to subdue our mule first and then riffle through her pockets.”

Alex sat down in the chair opposite Lord Slytherin. “Mule?”

Slytherin reached behind him and extracted one can of orange juice and one can of something she’d never seen before. “Luna, in this case.” He tossed her the unidentified can. “I believe she wanted to, ‘win all the chocolate frog racing races’, because ‘they all deserve to win.’ It’s a blessing none of the stands offers pudding as a prize or we’d never get her away from it.”

Alex snorted despite herself and inspected the can. “Bubbled water?”

“I thought you might appreciate it.”

Alex carefully popped the can and took an experimental sip. “Not bad.”

“Personally, I can’t stand it, but then, I still have my sweet tooth.”

Alex felt a pang of loss, but quickly squished it.

Slytherin took a sip of his own and the mask moulded itself around the can in a way that Alex found strangely creepy and awesome at the same time. “So,” he began, “I’ve been hearing snatches of what you’ve been up to from both yourself and Luna. But Luna also thinks you should be the one to give me the full details because, ‘She’ll want to tell you in person.’ ”

Alex hesitated. Then Luna’s words from before came back to her and she began to tell Slytherin everything. From the doxies, to their ageing potion adventures, the dementor bone, the successful inferi raising, and the failed quintaped expedition.

“Did you consider tying it up first?”

Alex gaped. She then blushed harder than she’d ever blushed before. That would completely solve her training problem.

“In case you can’t tell, I’m smiling right now,” Slytherin said, and Alex could hear the smile in his voice.

“Anyway,” she mumbled, not meeting his maskly gaze, “We then kidnapped that horrible ghost from before and tried out all the ghost rituals in the book I have on him.”

“And they worked?”

Alex straightened a bit. “The one’s you need work.”

“Excellent. Can you slip out of Grimmauld Place three nights from tonight?”

Alex nodded.

“Great. Harry and Daphne will meet you at the local park and escort you to the graveyard where Angelystor resides.”

Alex nodded again. She’d be ready. She hesitated. “Ah, Lord Slytherin?”

“Yes?”

“I … that is, my Grandfather, that is, the House of Black … although also me …” Merlin how could giving someone something be this embarrassing? “We wanted to thank you for your offer to help with protecting the Black Library and give you this.” She reached into her bag, took out one of the communication mirrors, and handed it to Slytherin.

“What is it?” Slytherin asked, sounding curious. He turned it over in his hands.

“It’s a communication mirror. I have the other one.”

Slytherin whistled. “Wow. You know, the last union of family magic that could make these was hundreds of years ago.”

She hadn’t known that. “I thought you could use it. You know, if you needed it.

Slytherin placed in on the table in between them. “Thank you, Alexandra. If I have need of it, I will certainly make use of it. Would you mind if I asked a few friends of mine to take a look at it, too? There may well be interesting things to learn from it.”

“I guess not.”

“Right. Then, shall we move on to our main point of business?”

Alex’s eyes hardened. “The Black Library.”

Slytherin nodded. “Do you know what the fidelius charm is?”

She nodded back. “Luna told me.”

“The easiest way to keep the library safe is to have me cast a fidelius charm around the Black Library and make you the secret keeper.”

Alex eyes brightened. “That’s brilliant! Then he’d never even be able to find it!”

Slytherin nodded.

Alex’s face fell. “But, how would you get into the house? I can’t let you in and my father certainly wouldn’t allow it, and even if he did and you came back later, the wards would still say that you’ve been there, and I’m pretty sure using such a charm on someone else’s property is illegal.”

Slytherin sat back in his chair. “That’s where it gets tricky and there’s no safe way to do it. There are easy ways, but they’re not safe.”

Alex leaned forwards. “What are those ways?”

“The easiest way is for you spend a few months memorising every inch of the library with your occlumency, if its good enough. Then I place you under the imperius curse and cast the charm for you.”

Alex paled. The words of her Grandfather came back to her—do not allow yourself to be trapped. “I … I don’t know if I’m comfortable with that.”

“Like I said, the easy, but unsafe way.”

“What’s the hard way?”

Slytherin shrugged. “Smuggle every single book out of the library over the next few months without your father noticing. But then you have to place the library at risk from outside parties. Probably myself, and I wouldn’t recommend you do that.”

Alex hesitated. That had been a very honest recommendation.

“Of course, you take a risk with the imperius-fidelius method too. I might make myself the secret keeper rather than you.”

Alex shifted in her seat. “Are there any other methods?”

Slytherin started counting off on his fingers. “Use your occlumency to memorise every single book in the next few months and then write them all out again later …”

Alex blanched. Not possible.

“… Persuade your father not to get rid of the books …”

Urgh. If she tried to do that, he’d probably just speed up his plans.

“… Arrange for your father to have an accident …”

She looked at Slytherin in horror.

“… Which obviously isn’t an option, but I’m just listing them all off …”

She nodded quickly

“… Arrange for your father to fall in love with someone you control and indirectly control him through her …

She snorted. That wasn’t happening.

“… Have a law passed that somehow makes his course of action against the law, which as head auror he’d be forced to comply with …”

She raised her eyebrows.

“… Not a chance …”

Her shoulder’s fell.

“… Infiltrate the ministry department that he’d give the books to, probably the department of mysteries, and have your agents give the books back to you once your father handed them over …”

Magical Merlin, this was getting ridiculous.

“… Find a place in the house that your father doesn’t know about or can’t get in and move the books there instead …”

The Black Magic room! Oh … but her father did know about it, he just never went there. She scowled. Plus, it was too small.

“… Learn the fidelius charm yourself …”

She perked up. “Could I?”

“Unlikely.”

Her shoulders drooped again.

“… Learn to throw the imperius curse, so that you don’t feel uncomfortable having it cast on you …”

Her mouth made a small o.

“… Which requires someone to repeatedly cast the imperius curse on you so you can learn to throw it …”

Her mouth snapped shut. Well that was useless.

“… Buy several dozen library trunks, transfer the Black Library to them, and then hide them somewhere, maybe even somewhere as simple as your bedroom …”

“I don’t have the gold to do that.”

“… I do. But I’m not dumping tens of thousands of galleons just because you’re a bit squeamish about the imperius …”

She pouted.

“… I’m not even sure if the family that makes expandable trunks even has that many for sale, or would agree to make that many to order …”

She frowned.

“… We could also full out assault Grimmauld Place, tear down the wards with brute force, and I’ll cast the charm in person …”

She shook her head violently.

“… I’m smiling again …”

She scowled. “I know, I can hear it.”

Slytherin sighed dramatically “… The other option is to put up some kind of defence that isn’t the fidelius charm, but that has exactly the same problem as casting the fidelius does …”

Alex stared at Slytherin’s unmoving mask for a few more moments before dropping her head. “So, no other methods then?”

“Well, I did tell you the best … one … first …” Slytherin stalled. “Oh.”

“What?”

Slytherin laughed, a deep dark laugh. “Oh, I’m being dumb.”

Alex looked up at Slytherin in surprise. “What?”

“Wait just a moment.”

They waited.

Then, suddenly, the trunk lid popped open and Luna stuck her head in. “You called, my lord?”

“Luna, do you mind me casting the imperius curse on you?”

Luna beamed. “Nope!”

Slytherin grunted. “Problem solved.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Alex checked she had everything one last time, snuck out of her room, crept down the stairs, tiptoed past her Grandmother’s portrait, quietly opened the front door, slipped out into the night, down the street, across the road, and into the small park where she’d first met Harry Potter over a year and a half ago. And sure enough …

“Potter.” She nodded to him before turning to his companion. “Heiress Greengrass, I am Heiress Alexandra Black, of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Black, I believe we have met before.”

Greengrass smiled. “Yes, I remember. And since you already know who I am, and we’re all working together, I suggest we drop the formalities for tonight.”

Alex hesitated. “Okay. I mean, you’re the leader, after all.”

Greengrass smirked. “Leader, mm? I like the sound of that.” She turned to Potter. “What do you think, Harry? Does ‘Leader’ sound like a good title for me?”

Potter gave her an amused look. “If you like.”

Alex looked back and forth between the two in front of her. Was she missing something here?

Potter then pulled out a trunk from his pocket and expanded it.

Alex eyed it with envy. She could see it had multiple compartments and must have cost a small fortune. She was the heiress of one of the wealthiest families in the country and she didn’t have a trunk like that.

“All in,” Potter said in a cheerful voice.

Greengrass climbed in without missing a beat and she hesitantly followed a moment later.

Halfway down the stairs, Alex did a double take. It was just like Slytherin’s sitting room trunk from the Winter Festival. No, it was Slytherin’s sitting room trunk. Huh. Figures it wasn’t Potter’s. She carefully lowered herself into the chair opposite Greengrass, mindful of the graceful way the blond carried herself.

On the table in-between them sat a small tree cutting in a pot.

The trunk lid closed.

“So, Potter is our mule?”

Greengrass shrugged. “I can’t confirm or deny that.”

She frowned. “Why not?”

She suddenly felt a terrible squeezing sensation that instantly loosened again.

“That’s why.”

Alex gaped. “That was apparition, wasn’t it? Potter can’t apparate! He’s only a year older than me!”

They squeezed again and again she was glad she’d had dinner a while ago.

“You are correct, Black. Harry is only a year older than you. That’s why suspecting he can apparate makes no sense.”

They squeezed again.

“But he’s doing it now!”

Greengrass smiled. “I’ve no idea why you’d think that.”

Alex sat and stared at the future Lady Slytherin as they obviously chain apparated across the country.

After a few minutes Alex found her voice again. “You and Potter seem quite close.”

“We are. Although that isn’t public knowledge and my lord is trusting you not to tell anyone.”

Alex quickly nodded. “And Lord Slytherin doesn’t … mind? You and Potter being close, I mean.”

Greengrass smirked. “My lord often treats Harry as his own flesh and blood.”

Alex scrunched up her face. “Wouldn’t that mean that Potter is like your son?”

Greengrass’s eyes widened and she let out a snort that turned into a choke when something went down the wrong way. “Huack Kuh kuh … Oh, wow, that is wrong on so many levels.”

“It is?”

Greengrass waved dismissively. “Never mind.”

It was then that the trunk lid opened. “Alright, girls. We’re here.”

Alex climbed out into a graveyard and in the corner stood a tree that looked older than her own house.

“Easily twice as old,” Potter said when she voiced this thought. “And this is my good friend, Angelystor.”

They greeted each other, and Alex couldn’t help think that this ghost was far nicer than the last one she’d met. Greengrass seemed to think so too, and the two immediately hit it off, happily chatting together while Alex went about setting up the ritual.

Eventually, it was time to add the item they would be rebinding the spirit to. Potter descended into the trunk and reappeared with the tree cutting in the pot. He placed it in the centre of the ritual space and stepped back. “Okay, Alex,” he said, drawing himself back to be level with her. “We’re all counting on you now.”

Alex swallowed and turned back to the ghost, now waiting patiently, if somewhat nervously, in the middle of the bloody deathly hallow. She closed her eyes. She could do this. She had to do this. This wasn’t like what she’d done before. This time, people were relying on her. She would show them—show Lord Slytherin—show the world—what she was capable of.

Alexandra Black focused all of herself to the task at hand, raised her hands and, with steady and sure movements, slowly began the ritual.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The next morning, the Auror section of the Department of Magical Law enforcement was just getting down to the day’s business.

Chief Auror Lord Sirius Black jerked back an inch in response to a thick document landing on his desk.

“Updates to the search lists, Chief.”

Sirius thanked the man and started perusing the parchments. There always seemed to be more and more going on these days. He flipped to the new additions section and stared.

“Blue Mask and Black Mask?” he muttered. “Wanted for questioning by the spirit division of the Department for the Regulation and Control of Magical Creatures in relation to the disappearance of one Edgar Hawthorn, a ghost—twenty years dead.”

The disappearance had been reported by a wizard of questionable moral character whose apparent distaste for the ministry was only just overcome by his fear of the two witches who’d twice broken into his lighthouse—although he’d refused to give the memory of the first break in.

He looked at the moving photograph, lifted from the wizard’s memories. There was something hauntingly familiar about the two women’s figures that Sirius couldn’t quite put his finger on, but it made his palms itch and the last time that happened he’d almost ended up dead.

Disappearing ghosts? He idly chewed his quill. … Dead monster trees … He groaned. It looked like they had at least one rogue necromancer on their hands … and they weren’t working alone.

—End of Chapter Twenty-six—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: To all those who disliked the last four chapters and who want me to write only Hogwarts chapters, I have only one thing to say—tough.

A/N: To all those who dislike the fact that we are where we are and are counting 220,000 words … My apologies for being slow, but we’re not speeding up. This thing is going to be long.

A/N: To all those who post long juicy reviews extolling your likes, dislikes, feelings and opinions on Harry and the girls, on their adventures and misadventures—even if I might disagree with you—who tell me you wait for each new chapter with bated breath, or excitement, or even mere mild contentment in the belief that I am about to bring you a small extra sliver of entertainment—I love you all. To the other 14,000-ish who (might) do the immediate above, but don’t post reviews—I really like you too :)

What Goes On In Knockturn Alley

[October 3rd 1991]

Knockturn Alley.

The very name conjures up images of darkness and shady dealings—of forbidden things hidden away from where common, law-abiding witches and wizards choose to travel.

The shops of Knockturn Alley often didn’t advertise their wares. Not because they were necessarily illegal—although they sometimes were—but rather because most people liked to pretend that the wares in question didn’t exist.

The sky was dark and cloudy—the crescent moon, barely visible. A light drizzle fell on everything, splattering against cobblestones and pattering off of windows. It fell on the many signs that lined the shops, and on one sign, it ran down a dried and flattened snake skin nailed to the otherwise empty wood.

A robed and cloaked man exited from the snake skin adorned shop front, let out a satisfied breath, and slowly walked off down the wet and dripping alley.

In the upper floors of the shop, in a small and simple room, a slight figure with shoulder length, blonde hair and watery, blue eyes sat on a messy bed, arms wrapped around her knees, knees pressed against her chest, shivering against the cold seeping into her now sweaty body, naked, but for an ominous silver collar around her neck.

Clothes lay strewn over the floor. A torn slip of women’s underwear hung on the back of a chair. An empty potions bottle sat on the tiny window desk, next to a small pile of coins.

Suddenly, the girl on the bed started to change. Her hair slowly shifted from blonde to brown, keeping its straightness, but lengthening down to the small of her back. She seemed to gain a few years, maturing from a possible sixteen or seventeen year old to a very definite early twenties. Her form filled out somewhat, from petite to curvy, although her height remained the same. And finally her face changed, becoming softer, rounder, with a button nose, a dainty chin, and two still wet eyes, one staying blue, the other turning hazel.

The girl shivered again and tried to banish the feeling of unwanted hands all over her. Food would be served soon. She should at least get a shower before then.

The girl shuffled to the edge of the bed, stood up shakily, stepped over to the desk, picked up the empty bottle of polyjuice potion, and dropped it into the nearby bin.

She then collected the coins and counted them out. One sickle, eight knuts (£3.80). Not a great tip, but better than a smack around the face, which is what she sometimes got. She moved back to the bed, lifted up the mattress, and added the coins to her secret pile of bronze and silver. No gold of course. She knew galleons existed, but she’d never actually seen them before. Her secret stash was small but growing, and after almost three years, was starting to close in on her target of seven galleons … enough for her very own wand.

She lowered the mattress and looked blankly at the wall.

A knock sounded from the door. She instinctively flinched away and covered her chest.

“Clare?” a voice from the other side of the door called. “Food’s ready.”

Clare relaxed and lowered her arm. It was just the madam. She called out. “Wait. Can you repair something?” She reached over and snatched the torn pair of knickers from the chair as the door opened.

The madam was a larger, older woman, who’d taken over when the last manager had disappeared in mysterious circumstances. The woman sighed. “Again?”

Clare nodded.

The madam took the ruined knickers, tapped them with her wand, and returned them to her, almost good as new.

“Thank you.”

The madam nodded. “Now get a wash, dear. You’ll need it.”

Clare stilled. “Why?”

“You have another appointment after dinner.”

Clare’s shoulders slumped.

The madam folded her arms. “None of that. Now, go get ready. Go on.”

Clare nodded, resigned, closed the door, threw on a bathrobe, exited her room again, padded down the hall to the shared bathroom, grabbed a quick shower, careful to wash the skin under her silver collar, went back to her room, pulled on her now repaired underwear and plain black robe, and joined the other girls downstairs at the tiny table in a cramped back room of the building.

Jessica, Rachel, and Caroline had all suffered the same fate as her, although she was the only one who wore a collar. She’d been the only one foolish enough to try and break the International Statute of Secrecy.

They chatted and ate for a few minutes, Rachel giving the newer Caroline tips on how to handle older wizards. “They love it when you ask them to show you some magic and then praise their power. They love having their ego stroked.”

Clare was just reaching for a second bread roll when the madam stopped her.

“Don’t eat too much, dear. I understand your client is bringing food with him.”

The other girls looked up.

“Oh, one of those clients.” Jessica muttered. “Lucky.”

Rachel snorted. “Maybe. The last one who brought me food ate most of it himself.”

Just then, the back door opened and an older wizard they all knew, but rarely saw, walked in. The chatter instantly ceased and all the girls averted their eyes down to the ground.

The man moved over to the madam.

Clare stared at the floor boards.

“A word in private, Madam Cakeworth.” The voice was calm and cruel and caused Clare to suppress a shudder.

“Yes, my lord,” the madam quickly answered and the two left.

“What’s he doing here?” Jessica whispered, looking worried.

Rachel shrugged.

Caroline shivered. “I don’t like him. He’s creepy.”

Jessica looked at Caroline sharply. Her voice turned deadly serious. “Don’t say that, Carol. Don’t even think it. Some of them can read minds, you know.”

Clare grimaced. The people who ruled the wizarding world were scary. She’d only ever met two of them, but had no wish to meet any more. They were deceitful, evil, and ruthless.

The back door opened again and the lord walked through again, accompanied by another man. Clare caught a hasty look at the one she didn’t know—tall and poised, with long blonde hair, aristocratic features, and holding a silver snake topped cane.

The wizard glanced at her and she instantly averted her eyes.

She heard the door close and looked up. The two men had gone.

The madam bustled back into the room looking flustered. “Clare, in here, please.”

“M-me?” She stood up. The other girls gave her weary looks.

“Yes. C’mon now.”

Her mind raced as she shuffled into the back room the two wizards had just vacated. Was she in trouble? Surely things couldn’t get any worse, could they?

The door closed behind her.

The madam turned to her. “Your next client will be here in thirty minutes. You will have no polyjuice.”

She blinked, shocked. No polyjuice? She’d only ever had one client who she didn’t use polyjuice with—a regular, much older wizard called Robert Volf. “But,” she started, “I thought I wasn’t allowed—”

“This client is somewhat different. I don’t know the specifics, but he is one of the most powerful wizards in Britain.”

Clare’s heart sped up. Dread seeped through her.

“You are to do anything he asks of you, understand? Any request at all.”

She swallowed and nodded.

“And you’re to look your best.” The madam looked her over. “I’ll go through my wardrobe, find something appropriate, and we’ll resize it the best we can.”

She nodded again and left to get ready.

Twenty minutes later, Clare sat inspecting herself in front of her room’s dresser mirror, adjusting a cloth wrinkle here, brushing back an errant hair there. The robe she now wore was more like a dress than a robe, and if it didn’t have a hood, would have certainly passed for one. The madam had attached an emerald pendant to the front of her silver collar, turning it into a kind of jewelled choker.

She tried to keep her mind off the upcoming appointment, but wasn’t having much luck. The closest client she’d ever had to a lord before had been Mister Volf, who, as the man constantly told her, was a pureblood from a family dating back over a thousand years. This man, by contrast, would almost certainly be an actual lord—And magical lords were dangerous.

Eventually, there came a knock from the door.

Clare stood up and demurely waited for the man to enter.

The door didn’t move.

She frowned.

The knock came again. Clare jumped, heart racing and quickly opened the door herself. “I’m sorry, I didn’t—”

She stared up into a black and emerald mask.

“—Realise,” her voice slowed. “Most people just … come in.”

She hastened to stand back and the masked man took a step forward.

“That’s quite alright, Miss Cooper.” His voice was deep and rich, much like the clothes he wore. “I try to make it a point to respect the spaces of those who are not my enemies.”

Clare took another step backwards, dipped into the lowest curtsey she could and used it to hide the gulp from a suddenly too dry throat.

The man stepped forward and reached out a hand, palm up.

She took it, hesitating only slightly.

The man then silently lead her through her own little room to the window. He drew back the curtains and looked down into the alley beyond. “No watchers that I can see,” he murmured. “I was sure they’d have posted someone.”

“Sir?”

The man closed the curtain again and turned back to her. “Oh, my apologies, Miss Cooper. Please allow me to introduce myself. I am Lord Slytherin of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin.”

So he was a lord. “I-I’m sorry, my lord.”

The mask tilted to the side. “That’s quite alright, Miss Cooper.” He let go of her hand, walked back to the still opened door, closed it, produced a wand—seemingly from nowhere—and waved intricate patterns over the now shut woodwork. “There.” He turned back to her. “Now we don’t need to worry about being disturbed.”

Clare tried to smile as though this was the best news she could have possibly received.

Slytherin stepped into the middle of the room, reached into his pocket, brought something out, and reached down to place it on the ground.

Clare’s eyes flickered uneasily to the now closed and presumably locked door, looked back, and did a double take when the thing the lord had taken out of his pocket had turned into a large wooden trunk.

Magic.

“I was told you wouldn’t have eaten?”

She shook her head.

“Well then,” he walked over and offered her his hand again. “I’d like to invite you to join me for dinner with two close friends of mine.”

Her eyes widened slightly. Two other people? “I …” The madam’s words came back to her, ‘do anything he asks of you.’ She swallowed. “I understand, my lord.” She took his hand.

He lead her over to the trunk and, to her utter shock, down into the trunk!

Magic.

The trunk held a small room about as big as the room she and the other girls usually ate in. The walls were wood panelled, torches flickered green light across the space, and a small table in the middle of the room already sat two other people. One thing leapt out at her … the room didn’t have a bed.

“Miss Clare Cooper,” Slytherin intoned, “allow me to present two dear friends of mine, Daniel and Emma Granger.”

Emma Granger stood.

Clare was taken aback. The witch was dressed in a blouse and blue jeans. She hadn’t seen anyone dressed like that since her last escape attempt almost a year and a half ago.

Mrs. Granger extended her a warm hand, which she shook. “Pleased to meet you, Clare, and so is my husband.”

Daniel Granger nodded to her, smiling just as warmly, and dressed much the same as his wife in jeans and a button up shirt.

She and Mrs. Granger sat down and she looked at the table for the first time. The cutlery was silver. The glasses were crystal.

Clare felt lost. This whole situation was just too different from the script she’d followed for the last three years.

The masked lord behind her cleared his throat. “I’m going to go sort out dinner—should be ready in five or ten minutes—The bar’s all yours, Dan.” He then left them.

Daniel Granger grinned, stood up, and started pulling bottles off the nearby cabinet.

Emma leaned forward and smiled. “I hope our lord didn’t intimidate you too much?”

“Ah, no, not at all,” she lied.

“Slytherin can be quite a scary person, but he has a good heart.” Emma hesitated. “At least, to those he considers his friends.”

Clare nodded and hardly noticed when Daniel Granger poured her a shot of some orange coloured liquid.

“So,” Emma continued, “how much do you know of what this is all about?”

Clare blinked. “All this?” she looked around. Clearly something different was going on. “I don’t really know anything.”

Emma nodded. “Well, I’ll leave the details to our lord to tell you when he gets back, but I will say we might have need of a valuable service you can provide, and, if we’re a good fit, we might like to make you an offer.”

Clare’s mind raced. A ‘valuable service’? There was only one kind of service she knew she could provide and she didn’t really like providing it. On the other hand—she thought of the small pile of silver and bronze under her mattress—if the offer was good enough, she might be able to have enough money to finally buy a wand.

She wrung her hands in her lap under the table. “What kind of offer?”

Emma smiled. “Later. Why don’t you tell us a bit more about yourself?”

Clare grimaced. “There isn’t really much to tell. I’m a prostitute.”

Emma’s smile didn’t falter. “We know that, but how did you become one? I’m sure our lord knows every single detail, but we don’t.”

Clare’s shoulders dropped.

Daniel Granger finally sat back down after messing with the bottles and glasses at the drinks cabinet.

Clare grabbed the glass of orange liquid beside her, took a sip, and felt a heat pass through her body and up her throat. It wasn’t as though she had any dignity left to lose. She put the glass back down. “I’m a muggleborn—never knew about the wizarding world—parents were convinced there was a perfectly rational explanation for all the weirdness that happened around me. Anyway, when I was eleven I received my letter for Hogwarts. I was so happy—it answered all my questions.”

She took another sip of the orange liquid.

“But then my parents poured water on that dream—didn’t let me go—refused to listen to the witch they sent around—said it was all a lot of silliness and that I was going to go to a normal school and get a real job.”

She looked up. Dan and Emma were listening attentively.

“And that’s what I did—or tried to do, at least. Did well on my GCSEs and was half way through my A-levels—I guess you don’t know what they are—but I never stopped thinking about the magical world—about the world I could have gone to.” She paused. “I was seventeen when it happened,” she said with a noticeable hint of bitterness.

Emma’s smile had faded by now. “What?”

“It was summer—I’d just reached my birthday and was looking to make some summer pocket money—to help me when I went to uni, you know?—and this man had what looked to be a great part time job offer. I wasn’t paying too much attention to the contract, although it wouldn’t have helped much even if I had, I guess.”

Clare sighed. “I was tricked into signing an immigration contract. The kind of thing a muggle born signs when they want to completely move to the magical world and leave nothing behind in the non-magical world. The moment I signed the contract I was stunned and locked away for a week while the immigration company did their work. When I was let out I found my identity had been completely erased—no records—no papers—no memories. My parents, my friends, my family, anyone who’d ever known me—none of them had any clue who I was.”

Both Daniel and Emma Granger were now wearing identical looks of disgust.

“I know, right? And then I learned the worst bit. The price of the service I’d been tricked into purchasing was far over what I could afford to pay. They tricked me, not only in erasing my family’s memories, but they made me pay for it! Or they make me pay for it, rather. The repayments are far higher than I can make anywhere with no magical education—The person who set the whole thing up—I still don’t know who did it—they sold my debt to this place. The owners now set both my repayments and my wages. That’s how I became a prostitute. I have literally no other choice.”

Daniel and Emma Granger’s faces were grim.

“And the collar?” Emma asked.

Clare deflated from her righteous rant. “That was me making a bad situation even worse. I’d tried running away before—once or twice—but I never got very far. Then, one time, I got all the way to a non magical police station. I tried to tell them everything. Everything about magic, about the situation I’d been forced into, about the people who go around erasing people’s memories.”

Clare snorted.

“I’m sure they thought I was crazy, but it didn’t matter. The moment they made the official report, the obliviate wizards turned up, and I woke up in a ministry holding cell, waiting to be tried for a medium class breach of the International Statute of Secrecy. The wizards who owned my debt turned up at the trial and persuaded the court to release me into their ‘care,’ which the court agreed to, but only under the condition that I wore this.” She tapped the collar. “It’s keyed to the wards and I can’t leave without permission. This isn’t Azkaban, which I’m grateful for, but I’m still a prisoner.”

Silence filled the room.

Eventually Emma spoke. “What would you do if you weren’t in this situation?”

Clare shuffled her feet under the table. It dawned on her just how much she was telling these virtual strangers. “Buy a wand and go to magic school, but I don’t know if that’s even possible—They may not take people like me.”

Dan and Emma shared a look.

The trunk lid opened and the masked lord climbed back down the stairs.

Clare looked down at the table.

“Wow,” Slytherin said, “heavy atmosphere.”

A plate of steak and potatoes was placed in front of her and her mouth began to water. She hadn’t eaten food like this in over three years.

Slytherin sat down at the one free space and took off his apron, which she realised with a jolt on incongruity said, ‘I must break Gamp’s law because my food is magic.’ She didn’t get the joke but it was clearly supposed to be humorous and totally didn’t mesh with the ultra intimidating visage of the powerful masked magical lord.

They started eating.

Slytherin glanced at Emma and Dan who both nodded at him.

“So,” Slytherin said, causing her to instantly focus on him, “we have a problem—several problems, actually—and we’re hoping you’d be able to help us with them.”

She paused with a slice of stake halfway to her mouth. “My lord, I’m sure I’d be willing to help in any way I can, but I don’t see what you could possibly need my help with.” She paused. “Apart from the obvious, I mean.”

Slytherin waved a vague hand holding a fork. “Well, you can rest assured, Miss Cooper, that it is not the obvious.”

Some part of Clare that she didn’t know she’d been holding tense, relaxed slightly.

“Dan and Emma recently sent their daughter off to Hogwarts. Before they did that, I had quite a number of powerful wards installed at their home. Their daughter, Hermione, was charging those wards, but now that she’s away, the wards are powered only by a small number of magical plants in the garden—not nearly enough to maintain the wards at the levels we’d appreciate.”

“—Wait,” Clare said, shocked. She gestured to Dan and Emma. “You’re both muggles?”

Dan and Emma nodded, smiling.

Whoa. That was unexpected.

“Dan and Emma are also doing work on several magical projects—runes, enchanting, product development, etc—that do need a magical person to activate, or cast a spell for, and we’re hoping you’d be able to perform this role as well.”

Clare felt her heart sink. “But, I don’t know any magic.”

Slytherin bit into a piece of roast potato, the mask moulding itself around the morsel in a strangely hypnotic manner. He swallowed. “Don’t worry about that—that’s something I’ll handle.”

Clare took another sip of the orange liquid. “What about …” she hesitated before tapping the collar around her neck.

“Ah, yes. This morning, I purchased an option on your debt for the next two weeks. If we decide we want to go ahead, I’ll activate the option and buy your debt. Then we go to the ministry and get the official stamp to move your prison to Dan and Emma’s house.”

She bit her lip. “And I wouldn’t have to have sex with anyone to pay off the debt?”

“No.”

Clare looked down at her half finished meal. It sounded too good to be true. But on the other hand, she was really only trading one master for another. At least she knew her current one. She narrowed her eyes. She knew he was a vicious pimp who forced her to have sex to pay off an unfair debt.

She looked up at the masked man across the table from her. Was this man who hid behind a mask likely to be any better? Oh sure, it was all happy promises and rainbows now, but she knew how these people played their games. They made promises for breakfast and broke them for tea … and then fucked you for supper.

Slytherin tilted his head. “Take your time, Miss Cooper. I suggest you think on it. We’ll all get together again in a week and you can decide then.”

Clare nodded slowly. Yes, she’d think on it.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The next week passed and, apart from one disgusting client who had her polyjuice into his own daughter, nothing special happened. She was booked every night and spent the days asleep or else pondering Lord Slytherin’s offer.

The other girls thought she was mad for even considering not taking him up on it. “This is your chance, Clare! You HAVE to do it!”

But Clare still wasn’t sure. How could she know she wouldn’t be even worse off after she agreed? Wizard lords couldn’t be trusted. The only reason she wasn’t instinctively turning it down was that Lord Slytherin seemed to be giving her the choice. After all, he could have just bought her debt without even asking her.

Her indecision, however, was about to be given a serious kick in the teeth when Slytherin’s promised day of return came. She was in her room, in the middle of the afternoon, entertaining her only non-polyjuice client, Mister Volf, all balding head and potbellied belly, when the man, who looked old enough to be her grandfather, tried to cast a spell of some sort while she was on top of him. A sudden motion from her caused him to jerk back and instead of whatever he’d hoped to happen, an angry stoat popped out of nowhere, bit him on the arm, and caused him to drop his wand, which clattered away across the floor.

“You idiot!”

The stoat disappeared.

She flinched and tried to apologise, but it was no use. He slapped her across the face, pushed her off of him and got dressed, muttering about worthless mudblood whores.

That might have been par for the course, if it hadn’t been for the madam calling her in later saying that Volf had demanded compensation for a scratch on his wand and the bite on his arm.

“We’ll have to take it from your wages, I’m afraid.”

Clare’s heart sank. “But what about my repayments?” she asked, desperately, “Will they be lowered?”

The madam looked at her with sorrowful eyes. “No, dear. You’ll have to make up the difference from your tips. I know you have a secret stash—all the girls do.”

Her heart sank lower. “How much?”

“Three galleons (£150).”

Three whole galleons. That would wipe out everything she’d saved for the last year—over half of everything she had. She trudged back up to her room, shut the door quietly behind her, collapsed into her still messed up bed, put her pillow over her head, and cried tears of frustration into the sheets and all over her plain black robes.

Half an hour later, Clare hadn’t moved from where she lay.

A knock came from the door.

She didn’t bother to look up or even take the pillow off her head. “Come in!”

She heard the door open.

“Is this—” started a familiar deep and rich voice.

She jerked up.

“—a bad time, Miss Cooper?”

She scrambled off the bed and tried to wipe the tear stains away from her face. “N-no lord, I’m sorry.”

Lord Slytherin inclined his mask. “No worries.” He reached into his pocket and produced his tiny trunk. “Shall we?”

She nodded, and together they descended into the now unshrunk trunk.

“Clare!” cried Emma Granger from inside the trunk. She rushed over to her and took her hands in hers. “Have you been crying? What happened?”

Dan Granger stood up and shook Slytherin’s hand.

Clare tried to wave it off. “It’s nothing, don’t worry about it, I’m fine.”

Emma looked unconvinced, but didn’t drill down any further. They all sat around the same table they’d eaten at the previous week.

Clare fiddled with the cuffs of her robe. She looked nervously from the Grangers to Lord Slytherin. Finally, she took a deep breath as thought getting ready to step off a cliff and into a deep an unknown sea . “If I accepted your offer … what would my repayments be?”

Daniel and Emma Granger smiled.

Thirty minutes later, Clare watched, heart racing, as Lord Slytherin put quill to parchment and signed into magic his decision to buy her debt. The parchment glowed white for a moment, then vanished.

It was done.

Lord Slytherin stood up, produced his wand, and tapped her collar. It flashed green. “I’ve granted you a leave of absence from the containment wards. We have an appointment with the ministry.”

She looked up, startled. “So quickly?”

“Yes.”

The walk down Knockturn Alley felt surreal. It was the first time she’d been outside since her sentencing.

Dan and Emma walked at her sides and Lord Slytherin strode ahead, parting the crowd like a prophet parting a sea. She couldn’t help but notice the mixed looks of nervousness and fascination that Slytherin seemed to garner as they moved from Knockturn Alley and into Diagon. A group of children gaped and pointed and an older witch actually yelped and ducked back into the shop she’d just left when she spotted him. Just what had she gotten herself into?

Soon enough, they’d reached what looked to be a fireplace, complete with chimney in a random wall section of the Alley. After a quick explanation of what a floo network was, Clare found herself tumbling out of a fireplace and into a large indoor space where dozens upon dozens more witches and wizards walked and milled.

“Welcome to the Ministry of Magic,” Slytherin said, appearing behind her. “I don’t suppose you’ve seen it from this side, have you?”

She shook her head and tried to fight down her unease. The last time she’d been here hadn’t been fun. They made their way through the hallway and past a massive statue of a wizard and witch surrounded by a centaur and two very different little knobbly creatures.

Slytherin stopped briefly to have his wand checked and they took an elevator down several floors.

Everywhere they went, wizards and witches stared and whispered.

“Lord Slytherin! My dear chap!” A shorter, plump wizard wearing yellow and black stripes bounded over to them. “I’ve been meaning to ask you for a chat for ages!”

Slytherin managed to extract himself from the man with a promise for a later talk and they soon found themselves in a waiting room. The secretary stood up from behind her desk. “Court room six, my lord.”

Clare had to suppress a shudder as she walked into the court room. It was exactly like the room she’d been tried and sentenced in. Small, with a row of benches around the main entrance and a raised table on the far side of the room, in which sat an ancient witch. A court scribe sat in a lower chair. Other than that, they were alone.

“Ah, Lord Slytherin,” the ancient witch stated. “I don’t suppose it would be too much to ask for you to take off your mask?”

“My deepest apologies, your honour.”

The witch sighed. “Very well then, let’s get this sorted out shall we?”

Clare was shocked at how easy it was. Slytherin stood there and gave some reasons about why he wanted to move her from her current prison to a new one, managed by his vassals, the House of Granger. The judge, who the court scribe had identified as a Madam Marchbanks, listened and added a few stipulations of her own, which Slytherin agreed to, and they came to an accord.

“One last thing, your honour,” Slytherin said.

Madam Marchbanks raised an eyebrow.

“I wish for my debtor to have the opportunity to attend Madam Goose’s Home for the Magically Gifted.”

Clare’s head shot up.

“Obviously, this would require Miss Cooper to be out of the primary containment wards for longer periods of time than stated in the original sentence. I have already spoken with the school’s administration and they are willing to key Miss Cooper into a separate set of containment wards at the school on your honour’s approval of an alteration to the sentence to permit a secondary confinement location.”

Madam Marchbanks rested her chin on her knuckles. “And what does Miss Cooper think about this?”

Clare looked nervously from Lord Slytherin to Madam Marchbanks. She swallowed. “It sounds too good to be true.”

Madam Marchbanks smiled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And this is the garden.” Emma Granger flung open the double doors and stood back, obvious pride in her face.

Clare walked out and gazed around her. Plants grew everywhere. That was about all she could tell. “It’s very … green,” she commented, feeling rather lame. “What are they all for?”

Emma shrugged. “Most of them, I’ve no idea. I just know they’re magical. Those ones though,”—She pointed to a patch of what looked like cabbage size clover—“They’re healing herbs that our Hermione asked us to grow when she heard we were starting a magical garden. She’s taking healing training, you know. Youngest healer trainee in magical history.” She beamed.

Clare smiled faintly back. She’d already been taken on a quick tour of the house after being keyed into the wards and had felt the difference between her old and new prison instantly. The Granger’s home felt like a … well … a home, little different from the home she’d grown up in—Although there were some important differences.

She walked back into the house and glanced at the TV.

“Oh, yes,” Daniel Granger had said when she’d picked up the remote and tried to turn it on. “That hasn’t worked since we activated the wards a few months ago. After a few weeks, the kitchen appliances failed, and now we can’t even get the electric lights to work.”

Clare looked around at the numerous candles that lit the otherwise darkened room. That two non-magical parents would go so far to join the world that their daughter had suddenly found herself in … she couldn’t help but feel a touch of sadness. How different her life might have been if her parents had done the same.

Emma joined her side again. “It’ll be a lot brighter once we get the magical lighting set up.”

She gave Emma a wistful smile. “No magical TV? I never saw one before.”

Emma sighed. “No, they don’t have that. They have magic radio though.”

“So, what do you do with your free time then?”

Emma grinned at her. “Reading, mostly. The library’s getting quite big now, which is good for you, what with school and all.”

Clare’s heart skipped a beat. She’d been trying not to think about that. She still didn’t want to believe that what Slytherin had talked about to the judge was actually going to happen until she was there. The disappointment would kill her otherwise.

They walked up the stairs again and Emma handed her a slip of parchment on which the words, ‘the Granger’s secret magic testing room is located next to bathroom on the second floor.’ Suddenly, a door appeared where before there had been none. Clare’s eyes opened wide.

“The special room for you to use your wand in without getting caught by the ministry. Normally, they wouldn’t be able to track you, because you are of age, but this area is almost all muggle, so even if they can’t detect what spells are being used they can tell magic is being used. It raises flags. Of age, unqualified wand use is a legal gray area. Best just to pre-empt all possible problems.” Emma said, seeming to guess her question.

Clare nodded dumbly.

The last part of the house was the garage, which contained nothing but a massive machine covered in a see-through plastic sheet on a wooden pallet. The huge cardboard box it probably came in sat folded up in a corner.

“And what is that?” she asked.

“Milling machine,” Emma answered. “One of Dan’s new toys that we bought with the proceeds from selling the dental practise. We’re planning to use it to prototype new magical stuff. It’s going to be amazing how small we can make the runes with something like that.”

“But,” she pointed to what was obviously a computer attached to it. “If the TV doesn’t work because of the house’s magic, surely that won’t.”

Emma grinned at her. “Yes, funny that.”

“What?”

“Well, the wizards we’ve all talked to say that electricity can’t work around magic, because the magic interferes with it, and that we should just give up trying to find a way to make it work because no one’s ever found a way.”

“Well?”

“Well, I was reading this book on different types of magic and there’s this one type called ritual magic that’s mostly only used by the ministry and the older families. The description said that, ‘Ritual magic is extremely sensitive to outside magics,’ and, ‘it is critical to perform in a zero or near zero magical environment.’ ”

Clare watched her expectantly.

“But old families all live in equally old and magical houses, so how do they do their rituals? Turns out they have this thing called a ritual room that mostly insulates the room from the ward’s magics.”

Clare’s eyes widened. “And you think …”

“That all we have to do is have a ritual room built in here, stick all our electronics in it and BAM, electricity inside a magical house!”

Clare looked around the garage and bit her lip. “Can we put a TV in here?”

Later that night, Clare lay awake in her new bed in the Granger’s guest room. She was certainly much better off now, but she had no illusions about Lord Slytherin. To Slytherin, she was a magical generator. A thing that protected his investment in the Grangers, nothing more. As soon as Slytherin had no more use of her, or she became inconvenient, she’d be sold on again.

It would be a long time before she finally got to sleep that night, without the familiar scary sounds of the Knockturn Alley only a thin wall away.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

October passed in a whirlwind of activity. The very day after Clare arrived in Crawley, a snooty representative from the muggle liaison office had turned up and, after angrily shouting about illegal wards and all the trouble they were in, had quickly backtracked when she’d checked the Granger’s status as Vassals of the House of Slytherin and found that, yes, they did have the legal right to them.

The representative had then got to the point of her visit … asking Dan and Emma how they were settling in to their place on the edge of the Wizarding World, and was promptly catapulted into the nearby park when she’d attempted to use legilimency on Emma.

“They want to make sure muggle-born parents aren’t meeting each other and organising, you see,” Emma told a shocked Clare after they’d sent Hedwig to the probably irate representative with a note apologising for her unceremonious removal from the property, but that they took a dim view on magical attacks and that she could check all the other muggle-born parent’s minds if they wished to ensure they were being good little muggles.

The week after that, a female goblin who turned out to be the daughter of the Granger’s bank manager oversaw a small army of tiny aliens called house elves in the building of a ritual room in the garage. Apparently the house elves were owned by a Lord Parkinson who was a not-actually-proven-but-totally-was-a-death-eater.

“Doesn’t that worry you?” she’d asked Dan.

Dan had shrugged. “If you make it a policy to have no dealings with ex-death-eaters you’ll never get anything done. We know he’s untrustworthy, so we don’t trust him. That’s why we work through the Boneslicer clan.”

She’d spent the next week thinking about how a clan of literal bloodthirsty bankers was apparently more trustworthy than yet another member of the wizarding world’s aristocracy.

While she worried about this, the Grangers, who she was really starting to warm to, had a floo installed, put up the magical lighting, given her a magic ring, and spent hours and hours getting her to do everything from picking up broomsticks by shouting ‘UP!’ to opening chocolate frog packets. It was amazing that, even without a wand, there were so many things she could do that Dan and Emma couldn’t. When they tried to open a chocolate frog packet, they just got a normal frog shaped chocolate. Apparently, this was because the enchantments and runes in the chocolate packaging drew an almost unnoticeable amount of magic from the wizard as they opened it to power the animation charm.

Eventually, the day Clare had been waiting for but never dared to believe would come had arrived.

It was Saturday, November the 2nd and on Monday she would be going to magic school for the very first time.

She arrived from her guest-room bedroom for breakfast to find Dan and Emma at the dinning room table, both gazing fiercely at a copy of the Daily Prophet, Emma hanging over Dan’s shoulder.

“Is everything okay?” she asked, sitting down.

Dan’s head shot up. “Yes. Yes, it is, thank god.” He chucked the paper at her. “Look at that!”

She looked. A huge two legged monster widely swung a club around while five young girls fought it to a stand still.

Dan jabbed his finger at one of the figures. “That’s our Hermione!”

Clare’s eyes widened. “She’s alright?”

Emma let out a shaky breath. “Yes, thank heavens. If Harry hadn’t been giving her those extra lessons … I don’t want to think what might have happened.”

“Harry?”

“Her friend from before school. They both go to Hogwarts.”

Clare looked at the paper again. “This happened on Halloween and you’re only just now finding out about it?”

Emma moved out from behind Dan and sat down opposite her. “Hermione sent us an owl yesterday, but hearing about it in a letter and seeing moving pictures are two totally different things.”

Clare nodded and looked at the paper again. This was the sort of thing first years at Hogwarts got up to? That changing pipe into sword spell was amazing, and those shields, and those other spells. She bit her lip. She didn’t want to say anything for fear of looking inconsiderate, but suddenly, going to magical school seemed even more amazing than she’d ever imagined, even during all those slow and boring middle and high school years.

The three of them soon finished breakfast and, when the containment wards allowed it, made their way through the floo to Diagon Alley.

“What do you mean, ‘I already have a vault’?”

The goblin teller looked at Clare like she was stupid. “I meant what I said, human.”

She looked to the Grangers who shrugged. “Ask for a blood confirmation if you’re not sure,” Dan suggested.

Apparently, there wasn’t a mistake and she did in fact already have a vault, although she couldn’t begin to imagine how. She carefully deposited her remaining two and a half gallons of silver and bronze and made her way back to the wild cart ride.

Clare’s heart flew as they shopped for new robes, and cauldrons, and potion supplies, and all sorts of other things. Slytherin was paying and she was determined to take maximum opportunity before she’d inevitably be kicked to the curb.

She happily zipped up and down the rows of books in Flourish and Blotts, picking out her very own copies of all the books she’d been perusing in the Granger Library over the last month.

Dan and Emma didn’t let her monopolise all the enthusiasm either. They left the book shop with wide smiles and carrying a few choices of their own including, ‘The 1991 guide to known family magic,’ and ‘Patent law and family magic,’among a small pile of other books.

Finally, Clare found herself in front of the shop that she’d dreamed of for seven years, and despaired of never seeing for three—The wand shop.

Clare stepped into the dark and dusty shop followed quickly by the Grangers.

“Good morning,” came a soft voice from right beside her that made her jump.

“G-good morning,” she said, but the old man’s eyes had already left her and were scanning Dan and Emma behind her.

“Ah,” the man said, smiling. “You must be Mister and Mrs. Granger, of the House of Granger, Vassals of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin. Am I right?”

Clare turned and saw Dan regard the man with wary eyes.

“We are. And you must be Mister Ollivander, the oldest member of the oldest family in Britain—the only family that holds the title of Most Most Ancient.”

The man chuckled. “Indeed. 402 BC. I wonder if we can hold on for another one hundred some odd years … maybe the Albion magics will upgrade us again to Most Most Most Ancient. We’d have to re-order our calling cards again.” Mister Ollivander turned away from them and started pulling boxes out of the many shelves. “And you are, if I may say so, the most surprising muggles I’ve ever met. A good fit for an equally surprising daughter.” He turned back to them with a pair of boxes in his hands. “It would seem, that anything to do with Lord Slytherin is automatically surprising … so maybe I should just stop being surprised, hmmm?”

Dan grunted. “Maybe.”

Ollivander turned to Clare again, who, despite the dust in the air, had been watching with slightly widened eyes.

“My apologies, my dear, I don’t believe I know you.”

“I’m Clare Cooper. I’m going back to school and need to buy a wand.”

“Of course, a wand …” Ollivander looked her over and his gaze fell on the silver collar around her neck.

She shivered.

“There was a Clare Cooper on the books to go to Hogwarts some ten years ago …”

“That was me.”

“Ah.” Ollivander’s voice saddened. “Such a shame.” He then brightened. “Well, no time like the present, and education is the best investment we can make in ourselves … or something like that. Let’s get you fitted out, shall we?”

Ten minutes later, Clare held a thirteen and a half inch yew and phoenix feather wand in her hand and brought it down in a great flash of emerald green sparks.

Ollivander’s gaze slid from the wand to her and back again. “How surprising.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Early next Monday, with butterflies flitting all the way through her stomach and threatening to climb up her gullet, Clare flooed straight into the head office of Madam Goose’s Home for the Magically Gifted. An old witch sat behind a desk wearing a pointed white witches hat with stars on it.

“Miss Cooper, I presume?” the witch asked, peering over her glasses.

“Yes, Ma’am,” she answered, looking around. The office’s walls looked to be made of soft brown leather, while the floor was a massive patchwork quilt.

“Well then,” the witch continued, in the same level, even tone. “allow me to welcome you to The Shoe. I hope you have a productive time here.”

Clare nodded. “Thank you, Ma’am.

The witch stood up. “I am the current Madam Goose, the Headmistress, and you are a reforming criminal and a whore.”

Clare faulted. “I …”

“—You will act in such a manner as is befitting of a young lady of the wizarding world, and if you fail to do so, then not even Lord Slytherin’s influence will help you—do you understand?”

Clare straightened. “Yes, Ma’am.”

“That’s, ‘Yes Headmistress.’ ”

“Sorry, Headmistress. Yes, Headmistress”

Madam Goose stepped over to Clare, drew her wand, and tapped the silver collar around her neck. “You are now keyed into the wards. You will not try to leave until school-out time at three-thirty each day. You will make sure you have left the school by five o’clock. As one of the only students who lives off campus, you may not run errands for any of the other students. If a student asks you to buy something for them, you are to turn them down, understand?”

“Yes, Headmistress.”

“Good. Class starts in ten minutes.” The office door opened and an older teenager stepped through. “This is Rebecca—one of our seventh year students. She’ll help you find your way. I suggest you get yourself to where you need to be.”

Clare nodded again, took a last glance at the storybook style decor, and left by the office door.

So much for the warm welcome.

Rebecca turned to her and smiled. “You’ll be fine. Headmistress Madam Goose can be a bit scary, but most of the staff aren’t like that.”

Clare nodded, thanked her, and the two walked off down the equally storybook style hallway.

Clare stopped briefly at the first window they arrived at to look outside.

Rolling hills and lawn stretched out for at least a mile before hitting a sturdy looking wooden fence. Dozens of pre-teens and teenagers lounged around, dressed in typical muggle style school uniforms with flowing open robes. It looked like she was the only one dressed in the more traditional closed robes. One older teen showed off a broomstick in the middle of a large group of his friends. Another group was playing cards—another, hopscotch. It was unmistakably a school. Just like the one she’d left before she’d been dragged into hell.

“Clare?” Rebecca asked.

“Ah, coming.”

They carried on walking, eventually finding her classroom.

Clare claimed a desk at the back of the room after thanking Rebecca. She took her wand out of her bag and waited.

Eventually, her much younger class mates all filed into the room, many giving her strange looks. There looked to be around fifteen of them.

The teacher walked to the blackboard. The man didn’t acknowledge her. She supposed he just didn’t want to disrupt the class.

“Books out,” the teacher said. “Please read chapter three in quiet.” He couldn’t have sounded less enthusiastic.

Clare pulled out her book and stared going over the section that she’d already finished a few weeks back.

After thirty minutes, the teacher announced they would be going through the safety of magic, and from the many groans that sprang up all around, she supposed it wasn’t the first time.

Another thirty minutes went by, in which Clare learned such pearls of wisdom as, ‘never attempt a new spell without supervision,’ and, ‘only use ministry approved spells,’ and, ‘only qualified wizards are allowed to experiment with magic and even then only with ministry approval on a case-by-case basis, which none of you lot are ever going to get.’

She suppressed a yawn. It was like the man was deliberately trying to take all the excitement out of magic. How could you possibly make something like magic, dull?

The teacher then handed out a bunch of nails and told them to, ‘get on with it.’

Presumably, they were trying to turn the nail into a wooden spoon—the first exercise listed in the book. She pointed her brand new wand at the nail and got to work.

By the end of the class, some thirty more minutes later, she’d managed to make the nail a bit less blunt, and changed it brown. She was quite pleased with herself. She was doing magic! She even seemed to be ahead of some of her class mates. She frowned as a thought struck here. Sure, they were eleven year olds, but weren’t they supposed to have been at this for almost two months now? Surely they should be further ahead then this?

After another ‘practical’ class and lunch, she had wizarding culture and law class, and if she thought the practical classes was slow, it was nothing compared to this.

“… And the only circumstance in which you are permitted to use your wand in front of muggles is if your life is in immediate danger or you need to summon the obliviator squads …”

Maybe if she kept her wand under her table she could secretly keep trying to change her pencil into something else?

“… There are currently 114 active seats on the Wizengamot, each one held by a lord of one of the noble families …”

No, probably not a good idea. Getting caught would be horrific.

“… These ancient and noble houses hold a special place in our world and you will treat them with the respect and deference they deserve …”

Clare focused back on the teacher and tried not to snort. Respect? Bullshit. Fear, yes. People like the last lord who owned her debt—people like Mister Volf, who still haunted her nightmares—she could barely keep herself shaking in their presences.

Straight after class, Clare found herself flagged down by Rebecca from that morning, who invited her out onto the grounds to ‘hang out’ with her friends.

Rebecca’s friends were a pretty homogeneous lot. Four girls, one guy—four white, one obviously Hispanic—two muggleborns, three half-bloods. They all sat down around a large tree in the grounds and Clare got her first outside look at the school.

It was called The Shoe, but it more resembled a giant boot. Deep brown leather, tall, with huge laces that hung down to the ground. The double doors they’d exited from were in the heel.

“The dorms are up there,” Rebecca said, pointing to the tall bit where the world’s biggest giant would put his shins. She turned to her. “So, how come you’re only just now going to school?”

Clare shuffled on the ground. Looked like her story hadn’t come this far. “I … was a muggleborn whose parents refused to send me.”

The girls let out a collective sympathetic groan. “Oh, that sucks,” said Rebecca.

“I can not imagine what that must have been like,” chipped in one of Rebecca’s friends. “But you got in eventually. Good old Shoe.”

“I was actually accepted to Hogwarts.”

The groan that both the girls and the male friend gave now was quite a bit louder than the first one.

“You got into Hogwarts and your parents refused to send you?!” Rebecca threw her hands up in the air. “That’s like saying, ‘Oh, no Eton for me please, I’ll just go to the local comprehensive!’ ”

Clare smiled weakly. “Yeah.”

“So why are you here then?” asked the male friend.

“Hogwarts doesn’t take adult students, not those in my situation, anyway.”

The girls all nodded in understanding.

“So, how are you paying for this? I assume your parents still aren’t? Part time job?”

Clare shuffled some more. “Something like that.”

Rebecca grinned. “Shop assistant?”

“I work for Lord Slytherin.”

The group stilled and stared at her.

“No, you don’t,” said one of the girls.

“Err, yes, yes I do.”

“The Lord Slytherin?” asked Rebecca, eyes wide.

“Well, I don’t know if he’s worthy of having his article italicised, but yes, Lord Slytherin.”

“How did you score a sweet gig like that?!”

And so Clare spent the next twenty minutes answering or deflecting question after question. They ooed and ahhed over every little titbit that she felt safe or comfortable to hand them, and when they learned that she’d had dinner with him, twice, the giggling reached ridiculous levels. Rebecca even asked if she could set up a meeting for her with him, blushing cherry red all the while. Of course she couldn’t, but that didn’t stop the requests.

Really, what was so great about a guy in a damn mask?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

By the time Clare got back to the Grangers she felt thoroughly fed up. She marched up to her new bedroom, dumped her bag on the bed, and marched back downstairs, all the way to the ritual garage, heard a slap and a yelp, opened the door without thinking, and walked in on a sight that made her stop dead.

Lord Slytherin had Emma over his knee with her robes bunched up around her waist and had clearly just finished spanking her.

“Clare!” Slytherin(?) reached for his mask.

“I … I …” she stuttered.

The mask came off and the suddenly revealed Daniel Granger hastily pulled his wife’s robes back over her glowing red behind.

Emma got to her feet, blushing madly, and rushed over to her, “Please, Clare,” her eyes watered, “Please, please, please, don’t tell Slytherin about this.”

“Um, yeah, sure, don’t worry.” Clare got a hold of herself and smiled. “I mean, it’s not like I don’t understand, right? I’ve seen the whole range of interests, and this is pretty tame by comparison.”

Dan smiled sheepishly at her.

Emma collapsed thankfully into a nearby chair, although not without a gasp and a wince.

Clare took a moment to take in the room. The milling machine was now fully operational and she’d seen the results of their test runs, although nothing that screamed ‘magic!’ at her.

“So, when are you going to have something interesting to show from that massive monster of a machine?” She asked.

Emma beamed up from her chair, all embarrassment apparently forgotten. “Now! We’d just finished our first item.”

Clare gingerly picked up the mask that had fallen on the floor. While the front had been painted green and black, the back was still shiny aluminium. “Not the very first item, I see.”

Emma blushed again.

Soon, up in the secret fidelius room, Clare watched Dan set up an aluminium tile with a perfectly milled sphere of solid aluminium resting in the centre. Tiny, geometrically perfect runes covered both the tile and the sphere.

“Alright, Clare,” Dan said, “Just point your wand at this bit here, and make as though to cast a spell but without actually casting any specific spell.”

“Umm.. Okay.”

It turned out to be not quite as simple as that and it took her a good two hours before she finally managed it, but when she did, the aluminium sphere lifted up from the tile and hovered, unmoving, about three inches off the ground.

Dan and Emma whopped and clapped.

Clare let out a long shaky breath. “Very cool,” she conceded.

Dan grinned. “Isn’t it? I’m pretty sure no one in the wizarding world could replicate that little feat the way we just did it. They either use alchemy to mould metal, which requires inhuman levels of occlumency to get perfect visualisation, or else they work metal by charms, which has its own built in limitations. We’re pushing the edge here. Disillusionment’s next.”

“Disillusionment?”

“Imperfect invisibility.”

Clare’s eyes opened wide. “Now that would be amazing.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

A week went by and Clare was starting to get into the routine of school life again, although she was still waiting for the moment it all came crashing down. She never seemed to see Slytherin these days and the looks the headmistress and the teachers at the Shoe gave her weren’t exactly flattering.

Each day she came home and either got to work on homework, practised spells in the secret room, or helped Dan and Emma with some needed magic. Today, however, she came home to find a bright eyed Emma handing her a parchment.

Dear Mysterious Inventor Friends,

Tally ho! Allow us to introduce ourselves. We are the secret tinkerers of the wizarding world. We are they who hide around the corner, ready to pounce with fun and chaos. We are the people who happily take what the more wasteful carelessly leave behind them. We are the Hogwarts Buccaneers. And we have recently been enabled by our ‘mutual patron’ who suggested that we get into contact with you.

We’ve attached a few drawings of some of our more outlandish ideas with some of the more tricky sticking points. Any thoughts? Ideas? Howling criticisms? (No howlers, please).

Either way, it seemed like a good idea to open a discussion.

Signing out!

- The Hogwarts Buccaneers

Clare looked up at Emma who was looking at her eagerly. “So, what’s the problem?”

“Well, we’re going to owl them back, obviously, but we need a name.”

Clare eyed Emma with half lidded eyes. “A name.”

“Yes! They have the ‘The Hogwarts Buccaneers’—we need an equally cool name. You’re part of the team, so we’re asking you.”

She looked to Dan who stood nearby, smiling fondly at his wife.

“Any ideas?” he asked.

Clare shrugged. “I don’t know—Outcasts? Persona non gratus? Two muggles and a whore?”

Emma frowned. “Clare …” she said, softly.

Clare relented, feeling slightly ashamed. “Okay, okay, maybe that wasn’t called for. but you must admit we aren’t exactly welcome in this world. Remember what that snooty ministry rep asked? ‘How are you settling into life on the edge of the Wizarding World?’ ”

Emma continued to frown—then her frown morphed slowly into a wide grin. “That’s perfect.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dear Hogwarts Buccaneers,

Sounds good!

You might like to take a look at ‘Journey of an Alchemist’, chapter six—the author mentions a partial solution to the problem you’re having with deconstructing the omniocular, although it is an imperfect solution. If intellectual property spells were that easy to circumvent … well … no more need be said.

Also, your extendable ears idea has promise, although the range will be limited, even if you can make the runes that small (We do have a way to make that possible, although it’s currently a guarded process. We’d be happy to do part labour, though.)

Welcome to our mutual patron’s little club!

Yours,

- The Edge Settlers

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Autumn slid into winter and soon enough Christmas holidays came. After hearing what had happened to Clare’s muggle family and friends, Rebecca had invited her over for Christmas, but, obviously, she couldn’t just casually leave her prison like that.

Dan and Emma had left earlier that afternoon to pick up their daughter from the train station. They should be back soon.

Clare sat alone on the living room sofa, reading through the standard book of spells, grade two, and wishing they were going faster in class.

The door rattled, clicked, and opened to the sound of several voices laughing and talking.

A small figure with wavy-brow-hair appeared in the doorway.

“Clare,” came Dan’s voice from the hallway. He stepped through.

The wavy-brown-haired figure studied her.

“This is our daughter, Hermione. Hermione, this is Clare, she’ll be living with us until further notice.”

“Hello,” Clare said.

“Hello,” Hermione replied, sitting down opposite her. She lowered her head. “Thank you for keeping my parents safe for the past few months.”

Dan left the room.

Clare smiled. “That’s quite alright. I do my best.”

Hermione beamed. “Naturally. Our lord would not have chosen you otherwise.”

Whoa. Pretentious, much? Clare wetted her lips. “I’m not sure if he’s ‘my‘ lord. He just owns my debt.”

Hermione tilted her head. “Really? But you are in almost the same situation as me. A muggleborn witch in the wizarding world. True, you are of age, but you’re still a second class citizen. Even more so, considering …” She indicated her collar. “Isn’t it wise to claim protection? Especially if he’s someone as amazing as our … as my lord.”

Clare shifted in her seat. Having this conversation with a girl so much younger than her felt awkward. “How do you know what he’s like? You don’t know anything about him.”

Hermione waved vaguely. “That’s not quite true. My dorm mate is my lord’s betrothed and I’ve known him personally for years. Slytherin is amazing, and the longer you know him, the more obvious that becomes.”

Clare’s mind screeched to a halt. “Wait. Your dorm mate is betrothed to Lord Slytherin? And she’s your age?” incredulity permeated her voice.

“Yes,” Hermione said, unconcerned. “That’s quite normal in the wizarding world. It’s not like they’re getting married until they’re older.”

Clare tried to take this in, but couldn’t quite manage it. True, her impressions of the wizarding world up to this point hadn’t exactly been from the best perspective, and her clients had often asked for some pretty messed up things, but listening to a twelve-years-old, very clearly British girl calmly talking about arranged marriages with such large age differences like they were nothing unusual felt rather disconcerting.

Hermione tilted her head. “Would you care for some tea and biscuits?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The Christmas break came and went and Clare tried to reconcile the many rather extreme and unusual views Hermione seemed to hold with the obviously intelligent girl she was. She asked Dan and Emma what they thought about the betrothal thing in particular and they said they, ‘try not to think too hard about it.’

Clareon the other hand didn’t know what to think.

It was two weeks into the new school term when Slytherin next visited.

She and Emma sat upright on the large sofa in the living room while Dan and Lord Slytherin were sat in opposite arm chairs.

“So,” Emma started, “you’re trying to get at this thing that someone is protecting but is really using as bait to lure this other guy into a trap and you need an effective way to communicate to get past the defences in a high magical environment?”

“That’s about the size of it,” Slytherin said.

Clare couldn’t help herself. “But, why would anyone actually leave the thing in the trap if it’s so important? Why not just say it’s there?”

Slytherin nodded to her. “Trust me, anyone who knows anything about the guy in question would tell you he’s just the kind of arrogant to believe no one could get past his defences. He’d do it just to feel clever.”

Dan turned over the silver hand mirror in his hands.

“So,” Slytherin continued, “any possibilities?”

Dan rubbed his chin. “Getting at the runes on the inside without damaging the mirror itself … We were just talking with your buccaneers about that the other month. Yes, there might be a way from the non magical world.”

“Really?” Slytherin actually sounded surprised.

“Yes. We might be able to use a CAT scanner … there’s no iron in it … we don’t need to identify perfect detail, just what the symbols are and in what patterns …”

“How much would a CAT scanner cost?” Slytherin asked.

Dan snorted. “About one to three million pounds.”

“Ah.”

Dan shook his head. “No, we’d have to rent time on one.”

“And you could do that?”

Dan hesitated. “We might get away with saying it’s for archaeological research?” He looked towards Emma.

Emma inclined her head.

Dan turned back to Slytherin. “Okay, we’ll give it a shot. But what are you going to do about the family magic? Even if you know the rune patterns it’ll be useless without the enchantments.”

“I’ll just have to give them an offer they can’t refuse.” Slytherin relaxed back in his chair.

Dan, Emma, and Clare all looked at Slytherin with looks of amused concern, although in Clare’s case there was less amusement and more concern.

Lord Slytherin looked back and forth between the three of them, all staring at him. “What?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

January faded into February, and by now Clare had broadly came to terms with her place in Slytherin’s little world. She’d come a long way from the feeling of resigned despair at being forced to have sex every night with whoever was willing to pay.

Being able to go to magic school had been her dream for all her teenage years, and she now had it, even if it was rather slow going, but she was still waiting for the moment that Slytherin turned up to tell her it was all off and she was going to go back to being a prostitute again.

Still, Dan and Emma were much nicer jailers than the last lord who owned her, and, occasionally, she even got to go on field trips, although, if she’d known exactly where they were going for this one, she’d probably have asked to be left at home.

“Lot number 95,” the man at the front of the room called out. “Seven, large unopened boxes of Doctor Filibuster’s No-Heat, Wet-Start, Fireworks, one box slightly damaged. We’ll start the bidding at two galleons (£100).”

All around the large open room, wizards and witches raised wands and fired out numbers to show their bids and counter-bids.

Clare sat on her chair, uncomfortably aware that not seven buildings away from this one, stood the polyjuice brothel. A place she’d hoped never to get within a mile of, ever again, or, failing that, just Knockturn Alley.

“Lot number 106,” the man called out again. “A silver ring—good condition—dated at circa 1400’s Milan—showing the emblem of the Viradini family—we’ll start at forty galleons (£2,000).”

Clare couldn’t help notice, as the bids quickly picked up pace around the room, that Slytherin—sat a few chairs away from her, along with Dan, Emma, and a Lord and Lady Greengrass—hadn’t bid on anything yet.

She leaned over to Emma. “Is there anything in particular he’s looking for?”

Emma handed her the brochure. “Lot number 108—he’s just coming up.”

He? Clare flicked through the brochure and felt her stomach drop. ‘He’ was a house elf.

“A house elf?”

“Yes,” Emma whispered back. She sounded half apprehensive, half excited. “Our lord says that he needs at least two by this time next year, and they don’t come up on the block very often. But he can’t really make much use of him before then, so he’s going to lend him to us! Isn’t that wonderful?”

Oh, yes. Wonderful. Clare felt sick. House elves were magical beings. They had cores. They could power wards. Now that Slytherin was buying one, he’d have little more need for her. They could even channel magic just like wizards could—the one advantage she had over the magical plants in the garden. She swallowed and looked over at Slytherin’s ever blank and impersonate mask. If Slytherin got rid of her would she still be able to go to school? Would her new master force her to sleep with him? Would she even be allowed to keep her wand?

The bidding for lot 107 came and went and soon a small and spindly figure stood up on the auction platform. The figure was visibly vibrating with excitement.

The auctioneer cleared his throat. “Lot number 108—a male house elf—not yet named—five years old and just passed maturity—healthy and with full documentation from both the Ministry and St. Mungo’s—trained in domestic services and household management—we’ll start the bidding at six thousand galleons (£300,000).”

Clare just stopped her eyes from bugging out. Six thousand galleons!

Lord Slytherin immediately raised his wand.

Whispers filled the hall.

Another wizard raised his wand.

Six thousand galleons was like … she did the math in her head … a LOT more than she owed anyone.

Slytherin and the other wizard were shortly joined by a third.

The bidding quickly took on a frantic air. The bids kept creeping higher and higher. 6,100 galleons, 6,200 , 6,400, 6,800. Eventually Slytherin rose his wand and shot out a call for 7,600 galleons (£380,000).

“Any other bids? Gentlemen?” The auctioneer called to the last wizard still bidding. The man shook his head looking seriously miffed.

“No? Sure? Sold! To Lord Slytherin.”

A faint scattering of applause filled the hall.

Slytherin stood up and made his way to the back room, leaving Clare alone with the Grangers and the Greengrasses. A heavy weight settled in her stomach.

She barely paid any attention to the rest of the auction. Not even when Emma commented on how badly she’d want to get her hands on a pair of vanishing cabinets that eventually went for almost one thousand galleons (£50,000).

Eventually, Emma seemed to pick up on something being off. “What’s wrong?”

Clare shrugged her off. “Nothing. It’s nothing.”

Emma didn’t seem convinced but didn’t pry further.

Slytherin soon returned from the back room and started to bid for a few more items, so much so, that by the time the auction finished it was late at night. The crowd started to file out of the room.

Clare looked around. “Where did Slytherin go again?”

“I think he went out the back again,” Dan replied.

“Well,” said the witch who’d introduced herself as Lady Sunny Greengrass, stepping into their little circle. “How did you enjoy your first magical auction?”

“It was interesting,” Emma replied. “There were so many things I really wanted, but didn’t have a hope of affording. So many of the really good things were quite expensive.”

Lady Sunny nodded. “Many heirlooms are like that. They’re just not being made any more.”

Emma nodded.

Clare knew Emma knew all about the ways family magic gave the old houses a stranglehold on certain types of products.

Eventually they were the last one’s left in the room.

Slytherin appeared from the back room again. “My apologies,” he intoned, drawing closer to them “One of the sellers was being a little difficult about something.”

Lord Jacob Greengrass slapped him on the back. “You sorted it out?”

“Of course.”

“What about the elf?”

Slytherin patted his pocket.

Lord Greengrass laughed. “Sometimes, I wonder why you’re even bothering with a manor when you’re so attached to your trunk.”

Slytherin chuckled. “I think someone would complain quite a bit if I decided to live in my trunk.”

Greengrass snorted.

Clare watched the two lords back and forth, still not able to wrench that sickening feeling from her stomach. She didn’t say anything, even as everyone else started chatting and laughing. She held herself towards the back of the group, and walked a little bit slower.

The group of six made their way out of the auction house and into the now almost deserted nighttime of Knockturn Alley.

Somewhere nearby, a dog barked.

She breathed out.

Suddenly, a voice from just behind her caused her to swing around wildly, heart leaping into her throat.

“Well, well, look who we have here.”

It was Robert Volf, old, balding, bot bellied, but spry and still as unusually light on his feet as ever.

“Volf.” She tried to keep the tremble from her voice, backing away and towards the still receding group.

Volf leered. “Now where do you think you’re going? I’ve got an hour to kill—the joint is just up there.”

She quickly shook her head. “No, that’s not—I don’t work there anymore.”

He ignored her and made to grab her arm.

“HELP!” She jerked and tried to run away, but just as she turned she barrelled into the tall robed form of Lord Slytherin. She clutched his robes briefly before spinning and ducking behind him.

Volf straightened. “Lord Slytherin. You have something of mine behind you.”

Lord Slytherin shook his head. “No, you are mistaken. Her debt is now mine. Go find your entertainment elsewhere.”

Volf’s face reddened. “You’re not the only one the whore owes!”

Silence descended on the group, now backed up behind them.

“What?” Slytherin’s voice dropped dangerously.

“What!” Clare cried out, getting over her initial shock. “Yes, he is!”

The elder Volf produced a parchment with a flourish. “See?”

Slytherin took the proffered document and quickly scanned it.

Clare looked desperately between Slytherin and Volf. She didn’t owe anyone else anything. She knew she didn’t.

“Clare,” Slytherin started, “this document says you’ve sold Robert Volf exclusive rights to your un-polyjuiced ‘hospitality’ for five years in exchange for four hundred galleons (£20,000).”

Clare recoiled in horror. “I didn’t. I swear, my lord, I didn’t!”

“The parchment has your signature on it.” Slytherin produced his wand, waved it over the parchment and a tendril of magic arced between her, Volf, and the contract. “It is authentic.”

“I never received that much money for anything!”

Volf waved another parchment. “Receipt of deposit into the whore’s Gringotts account.”

Clare gasped. The already opened account. “But there wasn’t any money in it! It was empty when we went there!”

Volf shrugged and grinned. “Not my problem, my pretty little mudblood.”

Slytherin turned to her. “You don’t remember signing this?”

“No!”

He turned back to Volf. “You obliviated her.”

Volf grinned again. “ ‘I’? I don’t know just what you are accusing me of, Slytherin, but I assure you I did not. Of course, accidents can happen, but if you went through the trouble of healing whatever blocks may be in that worthless mind, I guarantee you will find nothing out of line. All my business with the whore is completely legal and above board.”

Slytherin grunted.

Clare looked on, horrified. They’d messed with her memories? She actually had signed that contract?

Volf spread his arms. “I had no problem with her staying at the whore house—made it easy for me—But now that she’s out—well … I just might want to make a claim of my own to be her prison guard, mmm?”

No. Clare started to shake. Volf as her prison guard? She couldn’t. “My lord, please—”

“—You’d never win that case.” Slytherin interrupted, ignoring her.

Volf smirked. “Oh, I know that. Your debt is bigger. Your political clout is bigger. I wouldn’t stand a chance—but that wouldn’t matter, because while I wouldn’t be able to win, I would be able to hold the case up in court for many months …” he trailed off, still smirking.

Behind them all, Lady Greengrass let out a small gasp.

Volf continued. “… And during that time, the law would insist that the debtor be held in a neutral third part location—Somewhere suitable for a criminal convicted of breaking the international statute of secrecy.”

Slytherin’s voice dropped to a deadly whisper. “Azkaban.”

Clare’s shaking got worse.

Volf smiled.

Slytherin handed the contract to Lord Greengrass. “What is it you want, Volf?”

“The rest of the whore’s debt. I’ll buy it. Such a pretty little thing isn’t she?”

Clare looked up at Slytherin, who gaze was still fixed on Volf. She reached out and desperately held onto his arm. “Please, my lord. Please don’t.”

Slytherin looked briefly at her and turned back to Volf. “Bugger off, Volf.”

Clare gasped and then let out a breath she didn’t know she’d been holding.

Another smile from Volf. “But of course you’d say that—very protective, aren’t you? One of the few things anyone knows about you. Oh well,” He gave a dramatic sigh. “There is one other option—You can duel me for it. Winner takes the other’s debt.”

Slytherin tilted his head. “You want to duel me for it?”

“Yes!” Volf’s voice suddenly became angry. “Just like you duelled my grandson!”

Clare looked between them, still on Slytherin’s arm. Grandson? Duel?

Slytherin said nothing.

“Well?!” shouted Volf. “What was it you said to the boy!? ‘You can accept the duel, or try your luck with the law?’ ”

Slytherin looked at her one more time. “Fine.”

Volf smirked.

Clare’s head swam.

Minutes later the alley was set up with temporary duelling wards.

Clare stood off to one side looking at the preparations as though watching a play. It all seemed too unreal.

Emma stepped up to her side. “It’s going to be okay,” she said in a soothing voice. “Lady Greengrass tells me Slytherin is the best duellist she’s ever seen.”

Clare looked over to the masked figure standing on one side of the impromptu duelling arena, tall and stoic. “I …” She swallowed. “I hope he wins. I don’t want to leave again.”

Emma hugged her shoulders. “Trust him, Clare. Trust in your lord.”

Clare briefly shut her eyes. Her lord. The words sounded oppressive and dangerous, but right then, she desperately wanted to believe in them. She opened them again. “In my lord.”

Emma squeezed her shoulders.

The two combatants squared off against each other. Someone had managed to find the auctioneer from the auction house who now stood off to one side holding a handkerchief.

The street was otherwise empty, other than for the Grangers, the Greengrasses, a few hags, some hooded men, and her.

“This is a formal duel between the Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin and the Ancient House of Volf over the rights to the debts owed to both houses by one Miss Clare Cooper. The combatants have agreed to extended class B rules. I am Andrew Richardson of the House of Richardson and will act as official witness. All combatants have agreed to limit their casts to non-immediately-lethal spells. When my conjured handkerchief lands on the floor, the duel shall begin.” He threw the small strip of cloth into the air with a flourish.

Clare watched the handkerchief fall to the floor, breath held, heart beating wildly in her chest.

It landed.

And chaos started.

Clare’s eyes widened trying desperately to understand what was happening. Spells flew everywhere, shields blocked some, others were dodged. Dan and Lord Greengrass shouted encouragement while Sunny and Emma just stared.

Clare gasped when a purple spell seemed to almost hit her lord but was battered away with so quickly that it had looked like he was playing squash.

The duel dragged on and her heart raced, faster and faster. Were they equal? Was her lord losing? She couldn’t tell. She didn’t know. What if Volf got a lucky shot? What if—

Then, suddenly, as though from no-where, half the street lunged up, turned into a giant snake, breathed a massive column of flame at a wide-eyed Volf, and crashed down on him with all the power of a landslide.

The ground shook.

The dust cleared.

Robert Volf lay unconscious on the ground, blood everywhere, arms and legs bent out at spine-shivering angles.

A few of the men in hoods darted out of the shadows and started to drag him away.

The contract in Lord Greengrass’s hands glowed white for a moment before disappearing in a flash of light and re-appearing in front of Lord Slytherin who snatched it out of the air as quickly as he’d swatted away that one spell.

Clare felt her knees go weak.

Emma grabbed her before she collapsed.

He’d done it.

The air slowly settled and Lord Slytherin walked over to them. “Miss Cooper.”

She looked up at him. “My lord?”

He held up contract from Volf.

She lowered her eyes. Of course. Now her lord owned the sex contract.”

She heard a ripping noise. She looked up, shocked, bits of parchment floating down around her like confetti.

Slytherin levelled his wand at the papery mess. “I hereby declare the contract originally signed between Miss Clare Cooper and Robert Volf of the Ancient House of Volf and now held by Me, Lord Slytherin, to be paid in full.”

The bits of parchment all glowed blue for a moment before vanishing out of existence.

Clare felt something she hadn’t known she’d been feeling before lift off of her. She gazed at Slytherin in wonder “You …”

“I am not that kind of man, Miss Cooper. I fully expect you to work hard to pay off your other debt, but I will not hold someone who means me no ill will to such a deplorable agreement.”

She nodded quickly, a wide smile forming on her face. “Yes, my lord. Thank you, my lord. I will work hard for you, my lord.”

Slytherin inclined his head. “I know you will, Clare.” He turned to the rest of the assembled group. “Let’s go home, shall we? I think we’ve had enough excitement for one day.”

And the group left for the floo, walking down the otherwise deserted Knockturn Alley. Knockturn Alley, where Clare hoped never to return to, but still often seemed to find herself in anyway.

“By the way, Dan, Emma …” Slytherin suddenly turned from where he’d been leading the group. He flicked his wand in a strange motion. “… I don’t suppose you could build a submarine could you?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Later that evening, in an all white room smelling of disinfectant and All Magical Mess Remover, a tall man with aristocratic features, long blonde hair, and a silver-snake topped cane, slowly walked along the rows of otherwise empty beds to the occupied bed at the very end of the ward.

The old figure in the bed, covered in bandages, splints, and straps, looked up as he approached. “Lord Malfoy,” the figure said, in a wheezy, half dead voice.

Lucius Malfoy inclined his head slightly to the bed-bound man. “Robert Volf. I see that, in the end, you did end up duelling him.”

Robert Volf nodded and then erupted in an uncontrollable fit of coughing.

Lucius Malfoy waited for the fit to die down before he continued. “So …” he ran his fingers along the metal bed-frame. “… You have it then?”

Robert Volf leered. “Have it? Have it? Of course I have it. And as you can see,” he smirked, “he was fighting properly this time.” He reached for his wand on the side table with a huge groan, brought the wand to the front of his balding head, and drew a long, silvery memory strand from it.

Malfoy brought out his own wand and conjured a small vial. The memory flowed into it and Malfoy reached out to take it, but Volf snatched it away first.

“Uh uh uh, Lord Malfoy.” Volf grinned. “Our deal.”

Malfoy sighed and produced a medium sized purse of gold from the pocket of his robes. He chucked it onto the bed with a flourish.

Volf picked it up with a victorious smile on his face.

Malfoy held out his hand for the vial.

Volf handed it over.

With a swish of his cloak, Malfoy turned and marched out of the room. Trust someone as tasteless as the Volf patriarch to make such a show of such a small amount of money. He flooed back to Malfoy Manor and immediately barricaded himself in his office.

He walked over to a cabinet on the far side of the room and carefully opened the doors. Hundreds upon hundreds of vials greeted him on the other side, all carefully labelled and sorted—only the most recent results of many centuries of memory collecting by his ancestors—duelling styles from Europe to Africa and Asia, from wars and bar room brawls to international standard duelling tournaments.

If anyone was anyone in the world of professional fighting, their name was here. It was an indispensable tool for the professional duellist as he had once been in his youth—to be able to freely study and practise a specific opponent’s subtle tells and tiny weaknesses. Everyone left traces, everyone left signs, unnoticeable though they might be to the eye of one who hadn’t spent all the time he had at the task of studying them. He clutched the conjured vial in his hands tighter. And tonight he was going to find those tells and rip off Slytherin’s mask once and for all.

He lifted the first batch of memories, poured them into his office’s pensieve, and got to work.

The clock ticked. Minutes became hours. Lady Narcissa came and asked after him. He shooed her away with a peck on the cheek and an assurance that this had to be done.

The hours continued and the vials started to be whittled down. He started pulling more and more outlandish names from the cabinet. His eyes drooped. He swayed as he walked. The darkness beyond the office curtain started to give way to the first light of dawn and still he carried on.

Then, finally, he emerged from the pensieve once more, but now all sleepiness had gone.

His heart was beating faster and faster.

His brow was sweating.

His hands were shaking, clutching two separate empty vials.

No. It wasn’t possible. How could it be possible? And yet … and yet Lucius knew he was not wrong.

The implications were too horrible to even consider, but consider them he had to.

He stumbled over to his writing desk, reached for the warded bottom draw and withdrew a nondescript black notebook. He opened the book to the first page, picked up a quill and wrote in an unsteady hand, ‘My lord, I have discovered the identity of Lord Slytherin.’

It should not be possible for the written word to convey impatience, but nevertheless, the single word written back managed it.

‘Well?‘ it said.

Lord Malfoy took another long, deep breath before writing the next three words.

‘He is you.’

—End of Chapter Twenty-seven—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: Well, that was the last of the non-Hogwarts chapters for this season. We’ve got five chapters left (probably) until the end of season two and it’s all Hogwarts, all the way from here, so all aboard for the final arc of book two!

A/N: A quick reminder of what Harry has (currently) told who.

Because sometimes, it just slips the mind, and I don’t always spell things out in big flashing letters.

The girls:

Daphne, Hermione, Ginny, and Luna, all know Harry is Lord Slytherin, is the boy who lived, and is from the future. These are the ‘three secrets’ that Harry spoke of when he first gave Ginny the silver lightning bolt ring.

Alexandra knows none of these three secrets, but she does know that Harry exists, and that he’s deeply connected to Lord Slytherin, far more so than anyone else who doesn’t know the secrets.

The parents:

The Potters know nothing (obviously).

The Greengrasses know that Harry is Lord Slytherin and the boy who lived, but they don’t know he’s from the future.

The Grangers know that Harry is deeply connected to Lord Slytherin, but that’s all they know.

The Lovegoods know that Harry is the boy who lived and Lord Slytherin.

Harry hasn’t told Sirius anything (literally, nothing, they’ve never spoken.).

The Weasleys know nothing (except the twins, see below).

The others:

Harry hasn’t told the Weasley twins much, but he has insinuated that his relationship with his parents isn’t very close.

A/N: No, Clare isn’t in the pairings.

Divination Dimwits Drugs and Detention

[The Day after Christmas Day 1991 (Boxing Day Morning)]

Curtis Lawless glared at the silent mobile phone on his desk as his number two filled him in on their current, rather low, drug stock levels. The pounding and throbbing of last night’s Christmas drunken revelry, which had echoed up through the Manchester nightclub’s walls and floors, had slowly given way to the simple pounding and throbbing of a mild hangover, and it was interfering with his ability to be properly annoyed.

“So you’re saying,” Curtis started in a grumble, continuing to try and will the mobile phone back to life with just the power of his toxin filled mind, “That because we mis … mis … er … got wrong the amount we needed to have—because of Christmas—that we’re now going to run out in just a few weeks?”

“Yes, boss,” his number two rumbled, standing like a mountain with his hands in front of him, fingering a large gold ring.

“And now we can do nothing but wait for Mister posh-boy Malfoy to call and hope he’s got something for us?”

“Yes, Boss.”

Curtis groaned. The drug runner who called himself Malfoy had said Curtis wouldn’t be able to get a hold of him using this phone—That he’d be the one to call Curtis, but it still pissed him off when he’d tried to call and got the ‘this number is unreachable’ response.

His number two made a small grunt. “He’s not let us down yet.”

“No, he hasn’t, but I’m not looking forward to when he does. I’ve no idea who we can get who’ll do us as low as he does.”

“Prices are coming down all over the place.”

“Not as fast as he is.” Curtis continued to glare at the inert mobile phone. Malfoy had said a while back that he’d call some time over Christmas or early in the new year. Hopefully the man would keep his word again. He didn’t like being so reliant on one person.

A glass of water thumped down on the table in front of him. He took it in his large fist and fumbled a half swallow.

Suddenly, a massive bang from downstairs caused the glass to shatter in his grip.

“POLICE! GET DOWN!”

Curtis slowly put his face in his hands and groaned.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

[January 6th, 1992]

John Potter confidently strode down the Hogwarts Express, shaking hands with boys and smiling at girls as was his duty as the Heir of the Ancient and Noble House of Potter, Leader of the children of the Light, and, if not the actual boy-who-lived, then the chosen of fate and death, at least.

The Winter Festival had gone well. He’d been the centre of attention at the Potter Christmas Party and he’d impressed all and sundry with his ‘advanced’ wand work and transfiguration skills. His Dad had pulled him aside not long after and given him the same ‘How to charm girls and influence people’ lessons that he’d received the first time around. This time, however, he’d been far more receptive, understanding exactly why charming girls mattered, beyond just the intellectual understanding of an eleven year old heir to a noble house, that is. Just why his Dad had thought giving him these lessons at age eleven was a good idea, though, was a mystery to him.

But, that didn’t matter now. There were quite a few girls he wanted by his side, and one in particular who he needed to, at the very least, negotiate with, if not win back. He patted the bag that hung at his shoulder. And he had just the thing to do it with.

John walked further down the carriage, shook a few more hands, winked at one particularly cute third year girl, getting a shy smile back, opened the door to the next carriage, saw a flash wavy brown hair, widened his eyes when he saw who Hermione was talking to, and ducked into the carriage’s first compartment, only to be met by the wide eyes of several second year girls. He gave them an apologetic smile and pressed his ear up against the door.

“—Don’t care about that, Heir Malfoy.”

“You should, Granger.” Malfoy’s voice dripped smugness. “You don’t always have Greengrass around to protect you.”

“You know what happened to the last person who attacked me.”

“Yes, Slytherin duelled them, but only because Volf didn’t want to go to court for assault.”

John tried to mould himself to the door to hear better.

“Do you want to go to court for assault?” Hermione asked.

“Not particularly.”

“Well, there you go then.”

Draco’s voice lowered and John had to shush the girls behind him who had started to giggle. “I bet you think you’re pretty hot stuff, Granger—joining the hunt and catching Lovegood, but you are not one of us. You will never be one of us. You are a jumped up mudblood with ideas above her station. Underneath all your training and manners and princess airs, you have nothing. No ancestry, no family magic, no legacy of contribution to the wizarding world. How many spells has the House of Granger discovered? How many artefacts has it invented? How many books has it published? None.”

“Not today, perhaps, but one day it will.”

John heard a loud laugh.

“Bwahahaha! Oh Granger, you are too much.”

The sounds of laughter travelled down the corridor and eventually faded away.

John carefully opened the door, waved at the girls, stepped though, and closed it behind him with an audible snap.

Granger whirled around causing him to raise his hands in surrender.

“Whoa there.”

“Oh, it’s you,” she said as though a cockroach had just scuttled in front of her.

John pushed away the hurt her voice caused and gave her a winning smile. “Malfoy being an arse?”

“Yes. Not that it’s any of your business, Heir Potter.”

“C’mon, Hermione. What have I ever done to you to get the ice princess treatment?”

“I could not imagine. Maybe you being a presumptuous arse, Heir Potter.”

John leaned on the door. “I just want to be friends. You like making friends, don’t you?”

“I like making friends with people who don’t strut around like the world owes them just for being born.”

Ouch. He didn’t think he strut around that much, and a certain amount of strutting was required of someone in his position. He smiled and shrugged. “Well, if not friends, why not acquaintances willing to make mutually beneficial trades?”

Hermione’s face shifted from icy glare to caution. “What kind of trades?”

John grinned and pulled out a book from his bag. He handed it to Hermione whose eyes widened in shock.

“This is …”

“That,” John said, “is a first edition copy of ‘Hogwarts a History’—one of only seven in existence.”

Hermione’s eyes remained fixed on the book and John was sure her pupils had dilated.

He inwardly smirked. Hermione had always had a near pathological book fetish. “Do you like it?”

Hermione looked up. She couldn’t have looked more guarded if she were wearing full plate armour. “What’s the trade?”

“Just that you accept this as a declaration of intention gift.”

“What!” Hermione squeaked.

“A declaration of intention gift. You do know what they are?”

“Of … Of course I know what they are!” Hermione’s voice raised in pitch. “But why are you giving me one!”

John smirked, still leaning against the door. “Why wouldn’t I? You’re cute, and powerful, and the best student in our year.”

“I …” she thrust the book back in his arms. “I’d need to talk to my lord.”

John frowned catching the book before it fell to the floor. “Hermione, do you need to ask your lord about everything? It’s your decision if you accept such a gift, no one else’s.”

“I need to … to ask his advice.” She turned to go.

“Hermione!” John’s voice rose. “Why do you defer to this guy so much? Are you afraid of him! Does he hurt you!”

Hermione stiffened and whirled around. “No! He does not hurt me! How could you even suggest such a thing!”

“Then why? What do you even know about him! Have you even seen his face?”

“I …” Hermione froze. Her very being seemed to shift. Tension drained out of her. Anger and embarrassed panic faded away. Slowly and surely, princess Hermione formed again, cool, calm, and collected.

John’s stomach dropped.

“I cannot give out my lord’s secrets. I’m sorry, Heir Potter.”

Damn. So close.

“I will consider your gift and let you know soon.” And with that, Hermione turned around again and left the carriage, heading back towards the middle of the train.

John watched her go before heading back to his own compartment, in which waited a girl who definitely hadn’t rejected his declaration of intent gift.

Susan smiled somewhat shyly as he entered and played with the citrine and onyx encrusted bracelet around her wrist. “Any luck?”

John shook his head. “She clammed up as soon as I asked.”

Susan frowned. “Well, Auntie could only haul her in for veritaserum if Slytherin had actually been convicted of a crime, anyway.”

John sat down heavily on the bench opposite the red-haired Bones heiress. “Still, you said she would only do that if Hermione had admitted she knew who Slytherin was.”

Susan nodded slowly.

John smiled. “I’m sure I’ll have more chances to get her to admit it.”

Susan looked down at a small notebook. “What about the polyjuice idea?”

John tapped his knee and looked out of the window. “If we can get a strand of Slytherin’s hair, or nail clipping, or something, then yes—pop polyjuice, and instantly find out Slytherin’s actual identity, but getting that hair …” he looked back at Susan. “… I don’t have a clue.”

The two sat in silence for a bit.

Susan was the first to break it. “So, Granger actually refused to say? She didn’t just say no?”

“Yeah, she refused to say one way or the other.”

“Doesn’t that mean that she probably has seen his face?”

John considered this for a moment. “It might,” he finally conceded. “Why?”

“I was just thinking that instead of polyjuicing to be Lord Slytherin, we could polyjuice as Hermione and talk to Slytherin while he’s around. You never know, he might let something slip.”

John chewed his cheek and thought. “Risky, but it might work. Certainly less risky than a love potion.”

Susan violently shook her head and half brandished her thirteen inch Hazel and unicorn hair wand. “No love potions, John, that’s just wrong.”

John grinned and raised his hands. “I know, I know, I’d never do that to Hermione.”

“Good.”

He lowered his hands and looked out of the window again. Still though, too much was going differently not to dig deeper. Not having Hermione this time round was killing him and she was looking to be doing even better this time around, too. He spotted Susan staring at him in the window’s reflection. Mmmmm. … He looked back at Susan again, who blushed under his intense gaze. Maybe. … He took a deep breath. “Say, Susie, how would you like some private duelling lessons?”

Susan’s eyes widened. “Private duelling lessons?”

John nodded.

“With you?”

He nodded again.

“Mister rumoured-to-have-taken-out-his-entire-duelling-team?”

“Yes.”

Susan broke out into an ear splitting grin. “Sign me up, Heir boy-who-lived.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daily Prophet Society Pages [6 th January, 1992]

LORD SLYTHERIN BUYS SCOTTISH ISLAND

Yesterday afternoon, a spokesman for the ministry confirmed that Gairsay Island, the ninety-ninth largest island in the Scottish Orkneys, is now the newest land in Magical Britain, and the largest such land transfer from muggle to magical in over one-hundred years.

The ever masked and mysterious Lord Slytherin has been making moves towards the building of a manor for his newly resurrected house for the last six months and, with this purchase, has sent a clear message to those few who still doubt his seriousness.

In a statement sent to the Prophet, Lord Slytherin said that he, “couldn’t be happier with his choice,” and that, “establishing the future seat of Slytherin House so close to the Scottish Highlands, and to Hogwarts, was deliberate.”

But Hogwarts to the South-West isn’t the only well known magical institution close to Slytherin’s new land. Azkaban Prison lies to the far North and East off the Shetland Islands, well into the North Sea, and Gairsay Island is now also the closest magical land to the formidable and forbidding fortress.

Floor plans for Slytherin Manor, filed with the ministry during the land transfer process, and marking the future Slytherin Manor as the largest magical manor in the country, include a two story circular ballroom and entertaining space. Whether 200 km between them and hell on earth will be far enough for future guests remains to be seen, but if there’s one thing we know about Lord Slytherin, it’s to expect the unexpected.

Just two weeks ago, Slytherin appeared for his first ever public social event, the Greengrass Winter Festival, in which he and his betrothed and vassal—Heiress Daphne Greengrass (12) and Miss Hermione Granger (12)—successfully caught Lord James Potter in his stag animagus form and Lady Pandora Lovegood in her flying squirrel animagus form, in a gruelling two hour hunt through the Greengrass Forest (more details on page 14).

Slytherin Manor is scheduled to begin construction in the next few weeks and to be finished in one year—just in time for the 1992 end of year winter festival and associated social highlights—and is slated to be costing 112,000 Galleons (£5.6 million).

BOY WHO LIVED TO FACE SQUIB TWIN IN DUELLING TOURNAMENT

John Potter, the boy who lived and defeater of He Who Must Not Be Named, is apparently taking his heroic past to heart and stepping up as Gryffindor’s first year duelling spot—and he’s not there just because of his name either, oh no. An informed source told the Prophet that, “John Potter is a duelling prodigy,” and that rumours said he’d “defeated several members of his team, even those older than him.” Even wilder rumours circulate about our favourite hero, including such unlikely tales as him defeating his entire duelling team, one after the other, all the way up to the seventh years. When asked about the likelihood of such a claim being true, long time duelling expert Mister Samuel Ratherberk (46), smiled and suggested that, “Some people may have been reading too many boy who lived adventure books.”

But perhaps what’s most interesting about the upcoming Hogwarts Duelling Tournament, is that John Potter will be facing off against his own twin brother, Harry, who recently returned to the wizarding world after growing up with Lady Lilly Potter’s muggle relatives. The little known Harry Potter (11) was long considered a squib, but was lucky enough to receive his Hogwarts letter last July and was subsequently sorted into Slytherin House. When asked about such a match up Mister Ratherberk said, “I’m surprised anyone mistaken for a squib could get onto the Slytherin duelling team, considering the usual fierce competition for the slot and the pride the House takes in its team.” What does that say about Harry’s chances against his more famous brother? This reporter, for one, will be watching with interest.

The Hogwarts Duelling Tournament takes place on Saturday, April 4 th in the Hogwarts Duelling Arena and is watched by many of the students, faculty, parents, interested members of the public, and scouts from the professional duelling circuit.

Dumbledore lowered and folded the paper and watched his many students file into the great hall for the welcome back feast from where he sat at in the middle of the head table.

So, Slytherin was starting to build his own stronghold only a few hundred kilometres from Hogwarts. That was a situation that would require careful observation. Luckily, he knew a few people who could be counted on for that task. His opinions on Slytherin kept yo-yoing back and forth and he just could not seem to pin down what he thought of the man. Sometimes Slytherin seemed to be just another politician, albeit one who refused to show his face, and other times he seemed to be … something else … something much, much worse—and not knowing which was maddening.

The man tortured those who crossed those he protected, as shown by his treatment of young Volf. He happily used those who were most vulnerable, as shown by his vassaling the Grangers and his buying and enforcing the horribly immoral debt of a muggleborn prostitute. And he was happy to ruthlessly manipulate events for his own benefit, as shown by his (and it was almost certainly his) strangling of the entire British market of a specific medicinal herb, fresh mandrake, just to keep Severus out of commission for whatever unknown machination he was playing. Albus had gone so far as to send an agent of his own out to track down an independent supplier of the herb and smuggle some into the country. Hopefully that would arrive soon.

However, the most troublesome thing Slytherin had done was ban the Hogwarts house elves from spying on students—a masterfully played move, making use of all three top families of the Dark, Gray, and Light, managing, however briefly, to unite them all against him.

Right now, Dumbledore needed information on a certain Harry Potter, and not having the elves available was annoying. The ghosts refused to spy for him, and the paintings were only of limited usefulness. It was ironic that Slytherin had unknowingly deprived him of his best tool to ensure that Harry Potter did not get any closer to the masked Lord in question.

Dumbledore frowned as the final students filed in and he saw the true boy who lived laughing and chatting right in the middle of the Gray faction at the far end of the Slytherin table. He couldn’t allow that to continue. It was far too dangerous. He picked up his goblet and swirled the liquid inside. Maybe it was time for him to take a more hands on approach and see what was going on for himself.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Later that night, after the welcome back feast had finished and the students herded back to their common rooms, Daphne Greengrass, the ice princess of the Gray, sat upright against her four poster bed’s headboard with her knees to her chest, hugging the massive fluffy snake Harry had given her at the Winter Festival. The rest of the dormitory had long ago turned in, but she was still fully dressed in her expensive school robes.

“Tempus,” she whispered, wand held in her off hand.

10:58

She squeezed the toy snake a little tighter.

“Tempus.”

10:58

“Tempus.”

10:59

After moving Angelystor with the help of the Black Heiress, Harry had gone back to those muggles of his. Daphne hadn’t seen him until the train ride back, and while they had talked on the train and during the feast, it had been the polite back and forth of two political agents, each playing carefully choreographed roles, rather than the relaxed peacefulness she liked to enjoy with her future lord and best male friend.

“Tempus.”

10:59

“Tempus.”

10:59

“Tempus.”

11:00

Daphne’s eyes lit up. She quietly untangled herself from her fluffy snake, slipped to the edge of the bed, and drew back the curtains.

Hermione’s head poked through the gap between her own curtains and the two exchanged an excited nod, although she thought she also detected a hint of anxiety from her friend.

They tiptoed down to a quiet and empty common room and Daphne gave a little squeak when a hand reached out of nowhere and tugged at her robes. A parting opened in the world and Harry quickly motioned her and Hermione under his invisibility cloak, which they both quickly scuttled under.

Harry held a finger to his lips and motioned them to the common room door, through the castle, across the ground, and up to the whomping willow. Harry cast a quick spell at the tree and it’s threatening trembling ceased. He then led them both down into a secret passageway.

Now freed from the cloak, Hermione tapped her on the shoulder, caught her eye, and motioned to ask her if she could move aside so that Hermione, now biting her bottom lip, could get in front of her.

Daphne nodded and moved to let her friend walk just behind Harry.

“Um, Harry?” Hermione sounded hesitant—worried even.

“Yes, Hermione?” Harry continued leading them down the dark corridor.

“This morning, on the train …” She trailed off.

“Yes?”

“… Your brother offered me a declaration of intent gift.”

Daphne couldn’t stop herself from letting out a small gasp.

“Turn it down.” Harry’s voice was flat and expressionless and as uncompromising as an iron bar.

Daphne saw Hermione’s shoulders visibly relax and her voice, when it next spoke, was more cheerful then she’d heard all day. “Yes, Harry.”

They walked in silence for a few more moments.

“Just out of curiosity,” Harry started, “what was the gift?”

“A first edition copy of Hogwarts a History.”

“Mmmm.” Daphne could hear the smile in Harry’s voice. “Then I will have make sure your gift is suitably better, won’t I?”

“My gift?” Hermione squeaked.

“For your birthday.”

“Oh, right.” Hermione’s voice calmed down again, but Daphne was sure she heard a hint of disappointment laced into the forced nonchalance and relief.

Daphne smirked and shook her head—and Hermione had the temerity to tease her about the fluffy snake.

After several more minutes, Harry stopped them. “We’re almost there. Hermione?”

“Yes, Harry?”

“Remember this—The Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin’s divination classroom is in the top floor of the shrieking shack.”

Hermione nodded.

Daphne grinned. She already knew the new fidelius secret from when Harry had set it up just a few weeks ago.

A minute later, they arrived at the shrieking shack’s top floor and were met by an incredibly bubbly pregnant ghost.

“Harry! You’re here! And you’ve brought another friend.”

Harry smiled and held Hermione’s hand as though they were at a formal ball, climbing up the rickety stairs. “Angelystor, may I present Miss Hermione Granger, Vassal of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin and my personal close, close friend.”

Hermione smiled and curtseyed, Angelystor clapped happily, and everyone exchanged greetings, happy to be finally getting to where they’d spent so much time and effort working towards.

Angelystor floated over to where Harry had set up some desks and chairs in mock imitation of a classroom. Dust tickled Daphne’s nose. By the window, the tiny tree cutting from the Llangernyw yew to which Alexandra Black had bound Angelystor sat in its plant pot.

Daphne took one of the seats and looked at the ghost expectantly. She might not quite have Hermione’s thirst for forgotten knowledge—her friend was now practically bouncing in her seat—but she couldn’t help feel excited anyway. It wasn’t every day you learned secret spells and the Greengrasses didn’t give their children access to the Greengrass magic until their thirteenth birthday.

Angelystor gave an exaggerated cough. “I thought I’d start by going over the different types of divination and what I can and can’t teach you.”

Harry nodded.

“Right then. First there’s seership—that’s the skill of using the inner eye to see thing far away from you, either in space or in time. That’s what most people think of when they think of divination, at least, they did in my time.”

“Our time too I think,” Daphne said.

Angelystor nodded. “Then there’s sensing—that’s using magic as a kind of echo location to detect various types of things.”

“Like homenum revelio?” Harry asked.

“Exactly like homenum revelio. That’s one of the spells I was going to teach you.”

Harry smiled. “Already know that one.”

Daphne frowned. “I don’t.”

“My neither,” Hermione added.

“Well, we’ll get to them soon enough.” Angelystor drifted back and forth as though she were pacing, hand under her chin, elbow resting on her other folded arm. “Thirdly, there’s warding, at least those wards used to gather information.”

“Detection wards?” Hermione asked.

“They’re a good example, yes. And finally, there are associated charms and enchantments which improve your senses directly. For example, ‘visus caligno’, or the true night vision charm.”

“True night vision …” Harry muttered, his eyes gleaming in the moon and ghost light. “… brilliant.”

Hermione straightened in her chair. “Umm … Professor?”

Angelystor giggled. “Just Angelystor, or Angel if you want.”

“Okay, ah … Angel. What are some of the seership spells you can teach us?”

Daphne saw Harry lean forward eagerly in his chair.

“Assuming you can successfully open your inner eye, I was trained in three spells. The first was the ‘Eye of Kilrogg—’

Daphne perked up. She remembered reading about that spell before in the library. It summoned an invisible eyeball that could float through walls and wards, and which the caster could see through.

“—The second was ‘mirror seership’, and the third was ‘threat seeing.’ ”

Harry tapped on his desk. “Is it possible to focus on those three first?”

“We can do that, although it’s more normal to focus on learning occlumency first.”

“We all know advanced occlumency.”

Angelystor made a surprised smile. “Really? That’s wonderful. Oh, that will make everything so much easier. Mmmmm …” She took a thinking pose. “let’s start with threat seeing—that’s the easiest to learn and it gives us a good idea of your ability to open your inner eye.”

Daphne and Hermione eagerly nodded and soon they and Harry each had a crystal ball in front of them.

“The wand incantation is ‘videt immino,’ the wand movement is three jabs diagonally upwards to the right, and a single small left spiral, along with the intention to know the severity of the threat you will face, all passed through your inner eye before being released from the tip of your wand and into the crystal ball at the exact end of the final spiral.”

Ten minutes later, Daphne focused again on her crystal ball, finished the final spiral of her wand movement, and released her spell into the sphere. Nothing changed. She frowned. It wasn’t the wand movements that were difficult—no, it was the whole ‘pass your magic through your inner eye’ business. Angelystor said it was a point just beyond where their magic flowed into their bodies from their cores, and that it should feel like trying to force their magic through a pinhole.

Daphne was sure she could feel something when she really focused on that point, but it was hard to get her magic to flow through it.

She glanced over at Harry and Hermione who each wore identical expressions of focused concentration and who both had similarly unremarkable results. That even Harry was having problems said a lot about how obscure what they were trying to do must be.

Daphne turned her attention back to her own crystal ball, closed her eyes and felt her magic flow into her body. It swirled through her. She knew she could mould it and direct it as needed, could even form intent strong enough for certain spells—like stupefy and protego—to materialise straight from her fingers without having to pass through her wand. Was that similar to what she had to do now?

She gently shepherded some of her magic back to the point magic flowed from her core and attempted to pool intent to … what? To solidify? To stay where it was? But this wasn’t a spell she was trying to create … it was more like an advanced form of manipulating the very magic itself. What she needed was pressure—like when she cast a wandless spell and could feel the pressure of the spell at the tips of her fingers.

She forced the magic down through her self and up again, down and up, trying to find some point for the magic to push against. Again and again. Wait. There! It was tiny and almost impossible to feel, but it was there—a tiny point of pressure, of resistance, and she thought she recognised it from when she focused hard before.

She gathered the smallest amount of magic that she possible could and tried to find that point in her again. There! Okay. Now, pool intent to know threat severity, and push it through that point.

The tiny amount of magic flowed through the point and slowly swirled around the other side.

Okay, now keep it up.

Slowly, ever so slowly, a respectable amount of channelled magic started swirling around her body. Daphne carefully nudged it towards her wand arm, allowed it to flow up through her arm, into her hand, and started the wand movements—three diagonal jabs to the right and a small left spiral. “Videt immino.” The spell easily flowed through her wand, seemingly almost pulled through by an enthusiastic hand, and bolted straight into the crystal ball, which shivered, and slowly started giving off a dim blue light.

Angelystor let out a gasp. “Daphne!”

Daphne let out a long breath and beamed.

Harry and Hermione looked up at her, the former with a smile, the latter with familiar competitive intensity.

“You did it! You actually did it!” The pregnant ghost floated over to her. “That’s amazing! I didn’t think any of you would get that for months, not even Harry! And it only took you a quarter hour!”

Daphne tried to not look too pleased with herself, but it was a loosing battle. Harry’s eyes were sparkling as he stood up and it was doing weird things to her insides. “Good instincts, I guess,” she said, trying to wave it off.

Harry had now made his way over to her desk. He picked up the crystal ball and inspected it up close. “Well, there’s nothing immediately hunting us down. Blue means no current threat, yes?”

Angelystor nodded. “Yes. And the brightness of the glow indicates how far into the future the threat is. We’d only have to be worried if the ball started glowing red.”

Hermione had already doubled back down and was focusing with patronus like intensity over her own ball.

“Any tips you can give, Daphne?” Harry asked.

Daphne’s smile grew even wider and that warm feeling from before grew stronger. She couldn’t ever remember a time in all the years she’d known him, when she was actually better at something than Harry, and now Harry was asking for her help. She explained what she’d done with her magic to a listening Harry and a suddenly fiercely listening Hermione, who’d been distracted from her ball the moment Daphne started her mini lecture.

Angelystor then put her back to work on, ‘opening her inner eye wider’ while Harry and Hermione continued to try to open theirs even a bit.

By the end of their session, though, neither Harry nor Hermione had made any progress, and Hermione was in a right huff.

“Not everyone has the ability to open their inner eye, Hermione,” Angelystor said, trying to console her friend. “And you’ve only been trying for a few hours. Maybe you’ll get it next time?”

But it was still a grumpy Hermione who climbed into the bed opposite her own in the Slytherin first years girl’s dormitory, and it wasn’t until next morning that the enthusiastic ‘learn all the spells’ witch returned.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Albus Dumbledore invisibly crept along the passageways of Hogwarts in search of his quarry. He hated that he’d been reduced to this, and indeed, if anyone on the board of directors learned that he’d taken to following an eleven year old boy around while invisible … well … awkward wouldn’t begin to describe it.

He soon found said eleven year old boy standing in a circle of his fellow Slytherins consisting of the Greengrass heiress, the Davis heiress, the muggleborn vassal, and Mister Zabini.

“But you still hang out with Malfoy and his ilk.” The Davis heiress looked ticked off.

Harry Potter smiled. “Sure.”

Davis growled. “You can’t be secretly on our side, Potter. That’s not how this works.”

“Why not?”

Davis huffed and opened her mouth again.

The Greengrass heiress put a calming hand on Davis’ shoulder. “Let it go, Tracey.”

“Buuutttt Dappphhhhh,” Davis whined.

Potter chuckled. “I’ll catch you later. I have some things to sort out.” And with that, he waved and left, heading back up the corridor.

Albus followed him and the last words he heard from the children of the Gray were, “I swear, Daph, if we lose him …”

The youngest Potter swung around a corner and marched down another passageway, Albus following closely behind. So, both the Dark and the Gray children were courting Harry, were they? That was troublesome, but at least Harry’s unwillingness to publicly pick a side would give him time to manoeuvre.

Harry stopped just outside a seemingly random tapestry and pulled out his wand.

Albus’s eyes lit up. If young Harry was in the habit of using his wand in the corridors, issuing him a detention so he could get a full evening with him would be easy.

This thought lasted only as long as it took the boy to jab the brother wand to Tom’s and muttered, “homenum revelio.”

Dumbledore froze and felt a familiar wave of magic sweep over him, singling him out, even while invisible, rending any form of concealment about as useful as a paper screen in a monsoon.

The boy glanced disinterestedly in his direction, turned, and walked off again, seemingly without a care in the world.

Albus stood there, rooted to the spot. “What the hell had that been?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

It was the second Monday after the students returned to the castle, and Hermione was tidying up after the first club meeting of the first year muggleborns, in which they’d briefly started occlumency lessons, although not the full on ‘Harry Potter Method’.

They didn’t have a name for their group yet. Sophie Roper had suggested, “The Newblood Club,” as she felt, ‘muggleborn,’ sounded like you had a mental birth defect. Justin, on the other hand, didn’t like the idea of giving the phrase, ‘pureblood,’ legitimacy by defining themselves in relation to them. He preferred, “The Founder’s Club,” because, as he said, “we are all the founders of our own houses.”

Hermione couldn’t help liking that one—‘Hermione Granger, Founder of the House of Granger’—It had quite a nice ring to it.

Kevin Entwhistle had shrugged his large shoulders and said it was, “six of one and half a dozen of the other, you know?” to which Hermione had pointed out that if you took six of one and half a dozen of another, then you would still have two identically numbered sets of different things.

Dean Thomas had then jokingly bopped her on the head, resulting in an impromptu duel that she had easily won, hands down.

Hermione now stood in the empty classroom, shrinking and pocketing the trunk that contained the portrait of Daphne’s grandmother. She heard the door creak open and idly turned her head, expecting to see Sophie, or maybe one of the others back again. What she wasn’t expecting to see was Draco Malfoy, leaning against the door frame and wearing that same smirk he’d worn on the train.

“Heir Malfoy.” A heavy feeling slowly formed in her stomach. Her wand softly slid into her hand from her holster.

Malfoy kicked off from the door. “Hello there, Granger. Fancy meeting you here.” The door closed behind him with a soft little click. “You know, amazing thing … I was just minding my own business when suddenly, a muddle of mudbloods from all the houses strolls right past me, and I thought, ‘well, that’s something you don’t see everyday—I wonder if I follow the stink they left behind them, if I’ll find the mudblood princess,’ and here you are.”

Hermione stuck her nose up slightly and sniffed. “Can I help you, or are just here to bark?” She couldn’t help but noticing Malfoy’s own wand sliding into his hand.

Malfoy’s smirk grew larger. “Whose to say I’m not here to bite?”

“Oh, please. We already had this conversation on the train.”

“No, Granger,” he drawled, “we had half a conversation on the train. We never finished it.”

“You walked away.”

“I saw no reason in having the second half of our conversation were other’s would see.”

Hermione was getting an uneasy feeling. “Well then?” She eyed the classroom’s only exit, depressingly far away with Malfoy still standing between her and it.

“As I said on the train, I have no wish to be charged with assault, even as a minor—such a thing would be unseemly of someone in my position.”

Hermione snorted.

“But that’s okay, because after consulting with my lawyer“—and he said the word lawyer the way other people might say, ‘mansion,’ or ‘diamonds,’ or ‘five-star luxury cruise’—“I have found a solution.”

Hermione gripped her wand tighter. She really didn’t like this.

Draco cleared his throat. “Just one moment, let me get my occlumency up …” His eyes went in and out of focus. “Ah, there we are. Article 67, clause 4A of the magical crimes and violence act, 1778. The ministry shall maintain and make available a list of spells, the offensive use of which is not considered assault, unless leading to grievous bodily harm as defined in Article 48, clause 1A of the act.” Malfoy’s smirk turned to a full on grin. “The prank clause.”

Hermione’s mind blanked out. “Prank?” she blinked. “You, Heir Draco Malfoy, of the Noble House of Malfoy, the leading family of the Dark, and the most self important and pretentious person on the planet, are planning to use prank spells?” The last bit was said in utter disbelief.

“The list was quite an eye opener, I must say—Spent a good chunk of the Winter Break reading it through.”

Hermione ground her teeth together. “I’m honoured.”

Malfoy smirked and produced a slip of paper from the inside of his robe. “Listen to this one—‘foot dangling jinx’—hoists the target up into the air and dangles them helplessly from one foot. Or this one—‘the terrets jinx’—forces the target to intermittently shout out loud expletives for the duration of the jinx.” He looked up at her. “Must be quite embarrassing, that one.”

Hermione narrowed her eyes.

“And the best bit about all these is that you can only fight back with prank spells of you own, or you’re in big trouble, little vassal. How many prank spells does the prim and proper mudblood princess know, I wonder?”

Hermione scowled again. The answer was none and they both knew it.

“Oh, here’s a good one,” he continued. “Proper place jinx—forces the target to walk on their hands and knees for the duration of the spell. Hah! And this one is my favourite—Maiden’s shame jinx, changes the target’s hair colour to match their knickers.”

Hermione froze, horrified.

Malfoy looked up, and smirked. “Only works on witches, naturally.”

And suddenly, a bolt of yellow shot towards her and she only just raised a frantic shield in time. Another bolt of yellow splashed into her shield and she desperately pushed more magic into it. Bolt after bolt slammed into it and Hermione knew that if she didn’t get out of there soon, her shields would fail and in the cramped and crowded space of the classroom, she’d be unable to dodge and would be quickly backed into a helpless corner.

Heart hammering in panic, she ran straight at and past Malfoy, lunging for the door and fiddling with the door knob, all while Malfoy laughed and laughed and poured spell after spell into her rapidly weakening shields. She yanked the door open and fled down the corridor, closely followed by a howling with laughter Malfoy, still raining spells on her all the way to empty Slytherin common room, filled with smirking students, before she finally barged it to the sanctuary of the girls dormitory and slammed the door behind her, where she collapsed onto her bed and angrily pummelled her pillow with her fists, eyes watering with humiliation, Malfoy’s laughter still ringing in her burning red ears.

Minutes passed and she slowly stopped beating up the pillow and instead hugged it to her chest.

“Hermione?”

Slowly her tear stained face rose up off the sheets and turned to the familiar voice.

Daphne stood in the dormitory doorway looking at her in shock.

Hermione sniffed and soon found herself in a comforting, but rather hesitant hug with the other girl.

“What happened?” Daphne asked, shifting up behind her on the bed.

Hermione told her.

Daphne looked furious. “That bastard! What do you want to do about it?”

Hermione looked down at the floor. “I … I don’t know. Maybe we should ask our lord.”

Daphne paused then giggled. “No need to do that. We both know exactly what he would do.”

Hermione looked up thought about it for a moment. Then her face hardened and she nodded. “Get help, get stronger, get revenge?”

Daphne nodded and smirked. “Close enough.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

For the next few days, the Slytherin common room became a tense borderland, complete with buffer zones and trading ports, while Malfoy passed out wizarding photos showing a panicky Hermione fleeing from a gleeful Malfoy. Harry, as someone who flittered from the Gray to the Dark and back again, had discreetly summoned and burned the photos as quickly as they appeared, and then given Hermione a thick large tome titled The Pranker’s Compendium.

For days afterwards, Daphne wouldn’t let Hermione out of her sight, for which Hermione was grateful, and which was just as well, because Daphne had pushed out far ahead of him and Hermione in Divination, much to Hermione’s chagrin. Neither he nor Hermione had managed to ‘open their inner eye’, and Harry was starting to suspect it wasn’t worth it, considering they had Daphne who had succeeded, and who was already starting to learn the Eye of Kilrogg spell.

But while Hermione might be annoyed about having to watch her back ²⁴⁄₇, which only stressed her out more, considering she already had homework, healer training, muggleborn teaching, and divination, it was nothing to how Harry was feeling right now, as he moved through the school at a casual saunter, occasionally snapping off a homenum revelio, and noticing that his invisible pursuer, who had started occasionally following him a few days ago, and who was almost certainly Dumbledore, was still there.

Losing the man was difficult and time consuming and really starting to cramp his style. Not knowing what the man hoped to accomplish with this benny hill style rigmarole was really getting to him as well.

“It’s not anything, John!”

Harry stopped dead just before he reached the next corner and flattened himself to the stone work.

“Don’t give me that, Dean.” His brother’s voice filtered around the corner, sounding angry. “All our friends say they’ve seen you talking with her, a lot. What’s up?”

Dean sounded exasperated. “Nothing’s up. And if anything was up it would be none of your business.”

Harry snapped off another homenum revelio and revealed the presence of the headmaster behind him and the two boys, Dean and John, around the corner.

“The Slytherins are my business—and Hermione is my business even more so.” The voices started to get fainter and it was clear they were moving away.

“Well, why don’t you talk to her yourself then? Then you can hear it from her that there’s nothing up.”

The voices faded away and Harry carried on walking ahead, deciding not to follow the boys, pointedly ignoring the Headmaster behind him, and giving no hint that he cared for anything about that conversation apart from not becoming a part of it. He shrugged. Maybe he’d go to the library and finish his homework for charms. He was sure that standing still in a library watching an eleven year old write essays was exactly what Dumbledore wanted to do with his time.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lord Chief Auror Sirius Black leaned back in his office chair and shoved another parchment into the out tray. He reached for his in tray and grabbed the next parchment from the pile. Next to it stood a wizarding photograph of himself holding a happy four-year-old Alexandra in his arms, both waving up at him. In the corner of the room, a massive magical cactus plant was starting to yellow.

The door burst open.

“Hey, Bolt.” Sirius greeted his auror partner without looking up.

“Hey Sirius,” Shacklebolt rumbled in his deep baritone. “Thought you should take a look at this—might become hot soon.” He threw a document at him.

Sirius now looked up, caught the roll, unfurled it, and started reading. “Muggle smugglers?”

Shacklebolt nodded. “The boys down in the DoM tripped the keyword ‘magic’ three times in the official police interrogation transcripts. Things like ‘he would appear like magic from behind trees,’ and ‘I don’t know how he did it, it was like magic.’

Sirius frowned. “Doesn’t seem like the kind of thing we would usually follow up on.”

Shacklebolt grinned. “It isn’t. But check who the perp fingered as his main supplier of smuggled goods.”

Sirius’s eyes scanned down the document. His eyes widened and he choked. “Malfoy!”

Shacklebolt laughed, a deep low rumble. “Indeed.”

Sirius tapped the office desk and frowned. “As much as I wish it were true, that’s just not something I see Lucius Malfoy getting involved in.”

Shacklebolt continued to chuckle and shook his head. “No, I agree. But it massively raises the chance that there’s a wizard at play, and that, along with the muggle authorities involvement, puts this firmly in our hands as a possible endangerment of the international statute of secrecy.”

“Any leads?”

Shacklebolt shrugged. “Not at the moment—it’s just a waiting game for us. Nothing might come of us it, but I thought I’d give you the up.” He stepped back towards the door. “You need to get out of the office more, anyway. Take little Alex out to a quidditch match, or something.”

Sirius looked around distractedly. “Ah, yeah, I should really do that, shouldn’t I?” He moved a stack of parchments. “You don’t know what happened to the file with the department’s new shield maintenance contract do you?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore invisibly jogged down the first floor corridor, quickly turned the next corner, and arrived in the empty castle entrance hall—the operative word being ‘empty’. Damn. He’d lost the little snake … again!

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The moon shone in through the shrieking shack window. Daphne Greengrass focused intensely and tried to push more magic through her inner eye than she had ever pushed before.

She raised her wand and pointed it at the floor, just a few feet in front of her. “Profero oculus Kilrogg!”

Suddenly something really weird happened to her world. She looked both up and down, and saw herself, looking at herself, and at a horribly ugly floating green eyeball the size of a bludger, all at the same time.

“Daphne! Well done!” Angelystor clapped and whooped.

Hermione let out a resigned sigh and gave her a wistful smile of congratulations. “Yes, well done. I guess we now know who the seer of the team is.”

Daphne smiled back at her. “I promise to lend you my new super powers if you ever need them.”

Hermione’s wistful smile widened a bit.

Harry was hungrily circling the Eye of Kilrogg and Daphne couldn’t help feel a little dizzy from following him in two places at once. “Yes,” he muttered, “this is going to be just what we need. The range is extremely limited, but that’s not a problem. We can work from the pipe network right next to the third floor. It can already pass through most wards. … Can you move it?”

Daphne looked towards Angelystor.

Angelystor coughed. “It’s all will and intent. No fancy wand movements or incantations.”

Daphne nodded, sat down in her chair and started learning to direct and control her new floating eyeball.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

While Daphne was settling down to practise with the floating eyeball, Harry stepped outside for a breath of fresh air and to get some business sorted. The winter festival had been productive in many ways, and one of those, was getting some fresh goods from Afghanistan. After all, mansions didn’t pay for themselves.

Safe in the knowledge that the girls were protected by the fidelius, he wrapped himself in the invisibility cloak, and soared out across the Hogwarts grounds, all the way to his other fidelius property in Hogsmeade.

As he landed, he couldn’t help but chuckle. He now had four fidelius charmed locations and he was already planning a fifth—the Black Library. The sheer overpowered nature of that spell boggled his mind. Luckily there were only three people in Magical Britain who could cast it, him being one of them.

He quickly grabbed his mobile phone, gave his loyal sooty owl some owl treats, and made his way back outside, before shooting of again into the mountains where the reception would be horrible, but the magic would be low.

He punched in the phone number and waited.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The phone rang.

PC Woodman, currently serving the graveyard duty for ogling the Inspector’s wife longer than was polite, stared at the mobile phone in the evidence rack behind his desk in shock and disbelief.

He quickly picked up his own phone and punched a number in.

“Hey, Robert?”

“Charles! Curtis’ phone—the one to Malfoy—it’s ringing!”

There was a sharp intake of breath. “Don’t pick it up! Just leave it for the moment. I’ll be there in two.”

His connection clicked dead, and all the while the phone continued to ring.

PC Woodman stared at the ringing phone in bewilderment. The arrest of Curtis’ and a good chuck on Britain’s drug dealing elite had been all over the national news and in all the papers. What kind of hole would someone have to live in to not know that?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry stared at the phone in mild annoyance. Curtis usually picked up pretty sharpish. Hopefully someone hadn’t muscled in on his business while he’d been out of it. That would be awkward, but at least he’d have the philosopher’s stone project in backup. Despite the great relationship he had with the Boneslicer Clan, he still didn’t fancy testing how friendly they’d stay if he stopped paying his debts.

He punched the number into the device and tried again.

Click.

Finally.

“Hey, Malfoy,” said the gruff voice Harry easily identified as Curtis Lawless from the other side, “that you?”

“Yes, Mister Lawless, it is me.”

“Christ mate, thank god you called. I’ve had it up to ‘ear with this lot. Listen, we need a whole lot of ships from you, understand? You can do it right?”

“Yes, I can do it. I have seventy kilos in my safe house, but I’m going to guess you need, what? Thirty-five?”

“Thirty-five is good—same rates as before.”

Harry raised a single, slightly surprised eyebrow. “Sounds good on this end. Same meeting place as usual? 2:00am next Wednesday?”

“Yeah, alright. My boys will see you there.”

“Right.”

The phone clicked dead. Harry smiled, pocketed the phone, flew back to Hogsmeade, deposited the phone back on his desk, and flew back to the shrieking shack, to be met by a happy and bubbly Daphne who’d just managed to get the floating eyeball to zoom around the room and turn invisible on command.

As he happily waved good night to the girls at the entrance to the Slytherin dormitories, and climbed into his comfortable four poster bed, he couldn’t help think that things were going really quite acceptably.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Granger.”

Draco Malfoy had wondered if the mudblood meeting was a regular event and it turned out he’d been right. He had the mudblood princess boxed into the room again, and this time, he’d made sure to have Crabbe and Goyle on the other side of the door, holding it shut against all attempts to leave. Victory last time had tasted sweet. Victory this time, would be a full course banquet.

“Heir Malfoy,” Granger said, looking at him nervously, fiddling with her beautifully crafted trunk before shrinking and pocketing it, and causing a slight tinge of jealousy to pass through him. No. He shook his head. Not jealousy—anger—yes, that’s right—anger that someone so unworthy was allowed to possess such valuable artefacts.

He smirked. She looked like a trapped animal, the way her eyes flittered to the exit, the way she stood, the way she breathed. How good would she look in a cage? He chuckled and shook his head.

“Might I ask what’s so funny?”

“Oh, nothing,” he drawled, raising his wand. “just wondering what colour your hair’s going to change.” And with that, he let loose the first of his spells.

Granger brought up a shield like expected, and it splashed off it. He fired a second spell and again the spell hit the shield and did nothing. But unlike last time, Granger seemed to be making no frantic bolt to the door. Heh. He casually threw a tourettes jinx. All the easier for him.

Then, suddenly, with a flick of her wrist, Granger sent a bright blue spell directly at him.

Shocked, Draco raised a shield of his own and the spell splashed off of it. “Granger!”

“What?” Granger took a step forward and suddenly Draco noticed that her whole stance had changed. Gone was the nervousness, the darting eyes, the bent stance—instead she stood like a jungle cat getting ready to pounce.

“Y-you can’t! You’ll get into trouble!”

“Oh, Malfoy.” Granger tilted her head to the side. “That was last week.”

An orange spell splashed off his shield.

“That was a soprano jinx,” Granger said, as though she were answering a question in class. “It raises the tone of your voice to almost a squeak.”

A fluorescent pink spell was next. Draco cringed.

“That was a rapunzel jinx—causes your hair to grow a foot a minute until it wears off.”

Draco felt his shield weaken as a bright orange spell hit it. Damn how powerful was Granger?

“And that one,” Granger said with an almost demented grin, “was the oedipus jinx …

Draco gave her a look of horror.

“Oh, I see you know what that one does,” she said sweetly. “I’m sure the world will love to know how much you think about your Mummy, Heir Malfoy.”

And suddenly Draco didn’t have time to do anything but shield and try to cast offensive spells wherever he could, which wasn’t often.

A soprano spell clipped him through his shield and he gave a little squeaky yelp while barely managing to side step an unknown rainbow beam of magic. He sweated. This was a mistake. A bad mistake.

Granger smirked and his nerve broke. He shielded one more time and dove for the door, grabbing for the handle and twisting madly, only for it to not move a Merlin damned inch. He rattled the doorknob. “Let me out!” he squeaked.

“No way, Granger!” came a muffled shout from the other side.

A spell shattered his shield behind him.

“It’s me, you idiots! Draco!”

“It doesn’t sound like you.”

He rattled the door again, and turned around to shield again.

“It’s a spell!”

Granger was now only a dozen feet away, smiling like a demon from the nether world.

“Sure, it is.”

He had just enough time to say, “Granger, how about it we—” before sparkly lights flashed towards him and a half dozen hexes hit him, one after the other, and his world become one whirling ball of weirdness.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Later that night, the Slytherin common room was almost perfectly divided. A third were howling with laughter, a third were quietly sniggering, and the final third were doing their best to look outraged while occasionally hiding a snort into a pillow or a giggle behind a raised book.

The wizarding photos this time showed a Draco Malfoy with gorgeous pink tresses so long they dragged on the floor, wearing his fine robes as normal, but lined with lace and frills, with deer antlers on his head, walking on his hands and knees, vomiting up slugs, with pink polka dotted skin, and occasionally shouting something that the lip readers of the room could identify as, “I love my Mummy!”

“You see,” Tracey giggled, sitting with the rest of the Gray students to the right of the large empty Slytherin throne in the middle of the common room, “this is why you should declare yourself for us, Potter. Because we’re awesome.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

It was the next afternoon, just after lunch, and Harry had to agree with Tracey pronouncement the previous night. … They were awesome.

Harry casually ducked behind a tapestry secret passageway, ran at full tilt up the corridor, turned the next corner, arrived into a tall hallway, disillusioned and silenced himself, wiped his cloak around him, and flew up into the rafters, sitting himself on the huge wood beam and dangling his cloaked feet over the edge.

Seconds later, Dumbledore barged into the hallway, looking around in obvious frustration.

Harry stayed quiet and watched as the man slid his own wand from its holster.

“Homenum Revelo.”

Harry smirked.

After a few more moments, a rather confused looking Dumbledore left, and Harry descended back down to the ground.

He made his way towards the library, hoping to squeeze in some restricted section reading before dinner—but as he arrived, he spotted just who was facing off against each other just outside the library door.

“C’mon, Hermione!” His brother’s voice wheedled.

“I said no—I’m not interested.”

Wow, Hermione was attracting all the trouble these days, wasn’t she? First Draco, now John.

John Potter ran his hand through his hair. “But why? Is that what Slytherin told you?”

“That,” Hermione said in a frosty tone, “is none of your business.”

Harry surreptitiously drew closer, keeping his wand in hand, just in case.

“I just don’t understand how you could allow someone so much power over you. It’s not like you.”

“Again, none of your business.”

John Potter looked away, obviously frustrated. “Shouldn’t Slytherin want his vassal to pair up with someone like me? I’m the heir to an Ancient and Noble House, one of the wealthiest houses in Britain, with family magic going back over a thousand years. You couldn’t ask for a better suitor.”

Harry’s lip curled. Oh, that whiny look on his brother’s face when he wasn’t getting his way.

“Have you considered the idea that maybe my lord simply wishes me to wait until I’m older before accepting such gifts? No one else is giving them out yet.”

John scoffed. “Puuurleeze. Slytherin signed contracts with two witches when they were eight. I don’t think he much cares about that.”

“Well, if you weren’t going to accept my reasoning then you shouldn’t have asked for it,” Hermione snapped, before turning and starting to walk away.

“You won’t be able to run away forever, Hermione!” John called from behind her. “This is part of our culture!”

Harry followed the furious Hermione around the castle until he managed to get her alone.

“Harry,” Hermione whispered softly when he finally whipped the cloak off himself and dragged her into an empty classroom. “Did you hear all that?”

“Yeah,” Harry smiled. “He didn’t look too happy did he?”

Hermione huffed and folded her arms. “Can you believe him! I wanted to hex him to hell and back for that last comment. As though the only reason I couldn’t possibly want his stupid gift is because I’m a stupid muggleborn who doesn’t understand the culture. GrraAAhhhh!” She threw her hands in the air. “It makes me so mad!”

Harry chuckled. “Well, at least he won’t be able to force anything. Even if he somehow managed to trap your parents. We made sure of that.”

Hermione stopped silently ranting and shivered. “Oh Merlin, you don’t think he’d try something like that, do you?”

“I wouldn’t put it past him, but probably not.” Harry frowned. “I’d advise checking your food and drink for love potions from now on anyway, just in case.”

Hermione nodded. “Are you sure I can’t just Hex him to hell like I did Malfoy?”

Harry grinned. “As tempting as that is, we still want stay under his radar as much as possible, at least for the moment. And besides, it may not be illegal, but you might still get detention or whatnot. Best not to give Dumbledore any good reason to get you in trouble.

Hermione pouted.

Harry smiled “One day, Hermione, I promise. John’s time will come.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

A few minutes previously, John Potter marched away from the Library in a bad mood. Getting back with Hermione was his best plan for sniffing out information on Slytherin. If she wasn’t willing to let him near her, as much as that hurt, then he’d have to try other tactics.

He walked up a flight of stairs and down a corridor. Maybe he’d go talk with Susan during History of Magic. She’d have some ideas. It was just annoying they were in different houses so he couldn’t have her around all the time.

He was just walking by the hospital wing, lost in thought, when the main door to the wing opened and who should walk out, but junior death eater number one.

John smirked and slowed down as Malfoy turned and spotted him. “Well, hello there.”

“Potter,” Malfoy spat. “What do you want?”

“Not much.” John looked Malfoy over. “What were you doing in there? You don’t look ill.”

“None of your business.”

Did Malfoy just blush?

John grinned. “Heh, bet someone just hexed your annoying arse.”

“T-that’s …”

“Oh Merlin, they did! HAH! Who was it? I need to thank them.”

“They were just lucky!”

“Sure, they were.” John smirked. “If they were so lucky, how about you duel me? I could really do with letting out some frustration.”

Malfoy gave him a deadpanned look. “I’m not duelling you, Potter. I’ve heard the rumours of how powerful you are.”

John raised an eyebrow. There was the good old Hogwarts rumour mill hard at work again. “And you … believe them?”

Malfoy folded his arms. “Yes, I do.”

Wow. That was surprising. He smirked. “So, Slytherin is ready submit before the might of Gryffindor?”

Malfoy smirked back. “Hardly.”

“Hardly?”

“Yes.” Malfoy turned his back on him and started to walk off. “After all,” he glanced back once more before walking off again, “we have our own Potter.”

John stared after him with his mouth hanging open. Then he started to laugh—huge belly laughs that erupted from deep within him and echoed away down the large stone hallway. As if his pathetic little Slytherin twin brother could ever win in a duel, against him.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne stood in front of the massive mirror that Harry had hung on the wall of the shrieking shack. Behind her, Harry and Hermione sat at the small divination classroom desks, the former working on paperwork, the latter switching between two different books, the first, ‘The healer’s Art—Twenty-sixth Edition,’ and the second, ‘If You Cant Beat Them, Prank Them.’

By Daphne’s side, Angelystor gave her an encouraging smile.

Daphne shut her eyes, passed her magic through her inner eye, formed the intent of the spell, made a delicate wand motion towards the mirror, and focused on the three Ds of apparition—destination, determination, and deliberation.

The mirror’s surface blurred, and the next moment, was showing her not her own head and body, but Harry’s, still bent over his desk.

She grinned.

“Well done, Daphne!” Angelystor clapped.

Daphne let out a deep breath.

“You got it?” Harry had set his quill down and looked up.

Daphne preened. “Yes, I did.”

“Excellent. It’s all range and control from here on then?”

Angelystor nodded. “Yes, although, because the mirror spell can’t pass through wards, even weak ones, we’ll have to practise range from outside of the fidelius charm.”

Harry frowned. “That’s … I’m not sure I’m comfortable with that.”

“Oh, Harry.” Daphne made doe eyes at him. “I’m sure it will be safe if we do it just outside the shack. Then, if danger comes we can just duck back inside the charm. I can even keep casting the threat seeing spell on my crystal ball, just to make sure nothing dangerous is going to happen.”

“Well, I’m not too comfortable about relying on that threat seeing spell like that. Exactly what it sees as a threat might be suspect … buuuttttt. …”

Daphne continued to make doe eyes at him.

“Oh, alright. As soon as we get the mirror set up.”

Daphne smiled brilliantly at him. “Thanks, Harry!”

“But not tonight. I’ve got an appointment soon.”

Daphne smiled and turned back to the mirror. That was fine with her. She would get this whole divination thing working perfectly and then she’d finally stop being the team member whose only use was as a Daughter of the Ancient and Noble House of Greengrass.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry left the Shrieking Shack in high spirits. Daphne’s divination studies were coming on amazingly well. At this rate, they’d be ready to start exploring all the bits of the third floor corridor in just weeks. Once they knew exactly what they were up against, they could hatch a plan to crack it wide open and swipe the ultimate prize, right under Dumbledore and Voldie’s big-fat and non-existent noses.

He chain apparated all the way to his secret cave safe in the Hebrides, grabbed seven-thousand galleons (£350,000) of Afghan white, popped an ageing potion, transfigured his face to his Malfoy-esque smuggler persona, and then chain apparated to a spot not far away from his trade spot.

The night was perfectly still. Clouds moved across the sky, alternatively bathing the land in moonlight, or cloaking it in darkness. The chill air tried to bite though his warming charms, and made visible his long slow breaths.

Slowly letting his body wash away the accumulated toxins from chain apparating up and down the country, Harry walked down the country lane, with its hedgerows on either side, and into the forest, on the other side of which, was his meeting point with Curtis’ men.

“Homenum revelio.”

Nothing. Not that he was expecting anything, but it always paid to make sure. The last thing he wanted was a gunshot wound to deal with. He always kept his wand in hand over a long sleeve during these exchanges. If they ever did try anything funny, they’d be quite surprised when they found their bullets stopping in mid air between them.

He trudged on a bit further.

“Tempus.”

1:57am

Okay, that should be long enough.

He silenced himself, and apparated some five hundred metres south, right behind a random tree around the clearing in the woods.

“Homenum revelio.”

The hairs on the back of his neck stood on edge. There were two people standing in the middle of the clearing, like usual, but there was also one person standing behind him, almost outside the range of his detection spell. Almost, but not quite.

What was he doing there? A scout maybe? A watcher? Someone Curtis assigned to make sure the men he sent were doing their jobs? He was too far away to interfere directly with him, and wouldn’t be able to see him through all this underbrush, so that didn’t make much sense either.

He hefted the heavy bag from his shoulder. Whatever. He’d deal with it.

Harry stepped out from behind the tree and walked towards the two men, making sure to keep his physical shield cast in front of him.

“Malfoy,” Goon A greeted him with a grunt.

“You have the money?”

Goon B nodded. “You have the goods?”

He nodded, and flashed the inside of the rucksack.

Suddenly, magic flowed over him, very familiar magic. His eyes widened slightly. An anti apparition ward.

“Malfoy? You okay?”

He looked the man straight in the eyes, watched memories flash across his consciousness, saw the trap, and moved.

Goon A clutched his head, cried out, and stumbled back.

Goon B shouted.

Harry wandlessly banished both of them backwards with a swing of his rucksack holding arm.

And then, seemingly from nowhere, a huge dog leapt from the underbrush straight at him.

Startled, Harry stepped backwards and went for a disillusionment.

The dog transformed into Lord Black complete with Auror shield.

Fuck.

Harry’s disillusionment activated.

Lord Black started a stunner chain.

Harry flicked the first stunner away, dodged the second, and swung his cloak around him on the third, watching with wide eyes as the stunner hit the cloak, travelled along the inside of the water-like cloth, and out the other side, barely missing his shoulder, but giving him just enough time to point his wand at the ground, cast the most powerful smell obliterating tergeo spell he could, and fly up into the air, tracing his path back to the tree and casting lessor, silent tergeo spells as he went.

Shouts and cries went up all over the clearing.

Just as he reached the tree, a second wave of magic flowed over him. A containment ward. His heart pounded. Trapped. Trapped! TRAPPED! He shook himself. NO! Not trapped.

Sweating, fighting down the urge to panic. Harry flew at top speed to a random point in the forest, landed, unshrunk his trunk, climbed inside, flinging his cloak over the trunk as he descended, grabbed his miniature ward stones, climbed back out, set up the stones in a one metre square around him, sat crosslegged on the ground under the cloak and started to meditate.

For twenty minutes, the shouts of men and the casting of dozens of different types of detection spells rang out across the clearing and through the woods. Everything from homenum revelio, to water spells, and chalk, Animagus Revelio, and elemental wind, rain, and fog spells.

Harry sat, his heart beating like mad, as one auror, tall, bald, and black, walked past him, not twenty metres away before continuing on.

Eventually, he took a long breath, pointed his wand at the wardstone standing right between his crossed legs in the middle of the square metre space, summoned all his magical powers, and hissed, “Fidelius Occultum.”

The fidelius charm activated.

Harry let out a sigh of relief.

Safe.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

It had taken the auror team three whole hours to finally give up—often with Alex’s father sniffing around the fidelius charm, making puzzled, doggy whining noises. Needless to say, Daphne, Hermione, and Angelystor were out of their minds with worry when he Morse coded them his situation on his lightning bolt ring, but the desperate hug he’d gotten when he finally stumbled back into the shrieking shack had left him feeling strangely okay about the situation.

“You mean, the money to build the manor, came from drug smuggling?” Hermione sat crossed legged on her chair, nibbling her lip, and looking worried.

Harry nodded. “Safest way I had. It’s not like I personally go around doing the stuff that drug dealers do. I just moved things from point A to point B.”

“You were nearly caught, Harry.”

Harry cringed. “Well, it hardly makes any difference, Curtis seems to be out of the game now. He was fifty percent of the business, and I never could find other buyers with the time I had.”

Daphne had sat herself on one of the desks and was idly swinging her legs back and forth. “So, what’s our position then?”

“We’ve got fourteen thousand galleons (£700,000) in stock. Assuming nothing happens to my other buyers, that’ll be liquidated in the next twelve months.”

“And how long will that last us?”

Harry wrinkled his nose. “Depends on how much we spend—mostly on how much our house elves end up costing us. But assuming we can’t get the philosopher’s stone … we’d be in deep trouble by this time next year.”

The three pre-teens stood and sat in thoughtful silence for a moment while their pregnant ghost seer hovered nearby.

“What about you, Angel?” Harry asked. “Can you offer any insights for the future?”

Angelystor slowly shook her head. “It doesn’t work like that. I’m sorry, Harry.”

Harry shrugged. “Oh well.” He turned to Daphne and grinned. “So, it’s all on you now. No pressure.”

Daphne scowled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

It was all on her.

Daphne sat in defence against the dark arts and stared at Lord Voldemort who was currently demonstrating the correct way to use a tripping jinx to interrupt an enemy incantation.

Hermione sat next to her and she couldn’t help notice that her friend was attracting several stares from persons of interest, most notably, Draco Malfoy and John Potter. Both seemed to be trying to bore into Hermione’s head with the intensity of their gazes.

Both boys, however, would occasionally switch their gazes to Harry—Malfoy with a look of cold calculation and John Potter with one of scorn and derision.

Harry, sitting in front of her and Hermione as usual, ignored them both and kept his attention on Voldemort, who had just banished away yet another hanging garlic bulb, with a flick of his hand, and a disgusted look on his face.

Daphne couldn’t help wondering just how much of quirrell was left, and how much was nothing more than rotting possessed corpse.

She shivered.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

After defence, Harry stepped outside the classroom, nodded to Daphne and Draco in turn, and headed off down the corridor. As soon as he was out of eyesight, he whipped out his wand, as he’d made a constant habit of over the past few weeks.

“Homenum revelio.”

An invisible presence faded into his consciousness.

Damn. He casually started making his way towards one of the many maze like sections of the castle, determined to quickly lose his annoying pursuer. Really … didn’t Dumbledore have more important things to do?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione had barely parted ways from Daphne after defence before she turned a corner into a zigzag corridor and the annoying person stepped out from behind the other corner.

“Hello, Granger.” John Potter leaned on a stone pillar by his corner with his legs crossed and his arms folded in the universal, ‘I’m a dick’ position.

She sighed. “What is it this time?”

“I thought I’d give it another go to have you accept my gift.”

Hermione folded her own arms. “I thought I told you I’m not interested.”

“Are you sure?” John Potter took out the book from his shoulder bag and wiggled it in front of him. “Nice juicy, juicy book.”

Hermione narrowed her eyes.

John Potter opened it. “Listen to this! Handwritten annotations by the original author themselves. Hidden secrets purged from later editions.” His voice dipped to a mysterious drawl. “Think of the knowledge, Hermione. Wouldn’t you like to read it?”

“Yes,” Hermione said through clenched teeth, “I would. It’s very nice. But I’m still not accepting it. All you’re doing is pissing me off …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry ducked into a secret, parseltongue only secret passageway, ascended a steep spiral staircase, walked along a dusty corridor, descended another spiral staircase, came out the other side, and removed his disillusionment, silencing charms, and cloak. Heh. That one had been easy. Dumbles was getting sloppy. He walked up the passageway whistling as he went, until a familiar and most unwelcome voice caught his attention.

“Think of the knowledge, Hermione. Wouldn’t you like to read it?”

Carefully, he crept up the passageway until he reached the corner, leant around it, and saw his brother’s back, squaring off against Hermione and waving a book around.

“Potter?” A faint voice called from where he’d just come.

He whirled around. It was Tracey. He put a finger to his lips and motioned her over.

“Yes,” Hermione said through clenched teeth, “I would. It’s very nice. But I’m still not accepting it. All you’re doing is pissing me off …”

Tracey sidled up to him, glanced around the corner, ducked back, and gave him a look of confused suspicion.

“Maybe you just need a little bit more … incentive” John Potter flourished another book so he now held one in each hand. “This is a list of all the books in the Potter Library. You could go through it and choose one for yourself.”

Harry narrowed his eyes. He wouldn’t mind a look through that himself.

Hermione stuck her nose up in the air. “I’m not accepting any gift from you no matter what it is.”

“Oh, come on! John waved the new book around in obvious frustration. What’s so bad about me that you, you, Hermione—Jean—Granger, would refuse a pick-any-book-you-want from one of the best magical libraries in Britain. It’s not as if you’re actually agreeing to a contract or anything!”

Hidden behind John, Harry smirked. Beside him, Tracey shot him another suspicious look.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Draco couldn’t believe he’d forgotten his book in the defence classroom. It was exactly that kind of sloppy mistake that he didn’t need. His standing had taken enough of a beating after what Granger had done to him the other week, thank you very much.

He marched up the corridor and was nearing a zigzag corner when a hated voice stopped him dead.

“It’s not as if you’re actually agreeing to a contract or anything!”

He pressed himself up against the wall, edged forward and tilted his head around the corner.

Granger was right there. Standing with her back fully exposed to him while John light-shines-out-of-my-arse Potter, ranted and raved while waving around some old looking books.

“My answer is still no.”

“Not even if I do this?” John Potter dropped one of the books, held his wand up to the other and produced a small flame on it’s tip.”

Granger freaked out. “WHAT ARE YOU DOING!”

John Potter smirked. “Accept the gift.”

Granger took a step forward. “STOP IT!”

“Take it, or the book burns.” He playfully jabbed the wand closer and closer to the book while grinning smugly.

Draco smirked. Oh, this was just too good to pass up.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Take it, or the book burns.” John Potter playfully jabbed the wand closer and closer to the book while grinning smugly.

Harry stared, wide-eyed, as John tried to blackmail Hermione into accepting the declaration of intent gift.

Tracey was slack jawed. “This is so, so dumb,” she whispered.

He nodded.

And just then, Harry spotted something out of the corner of his eye. So focused was he on the show down in front of him that he hadn’t noticed another figure, standing behind Hermione, almost completely hidden around the corner on the far side of the corridor.

Draco Malfoy.

His eyes narrowed.

Draco Malfoy preparing to take a pot shot at Hermione’s back.

“STOP IT!” Hermione yelled almost in hysterics. “OR I”LL STOP YOU!”

“TRY IT!” John happily yelled.

And all hell broke loose.

Hermione cast a bright blue spell straight towards John.

John shielded and cast one of his own back at her.

Malfoy chose that moment to cast a yellow spell that Harry now recognised as ‘Maiden’s shame’ right at Hermione’s back, which Harry managed to shield against by lifting a whole floor-stone right out of the floor behind Hermione and straight into the path of the spell, where it cracked and dropped back to the ground with an almighty smash, much to Malfoy’s obvious surprise.

“MISTER POTTER!”

Harry froze.

John Potter froze.

Hermione froze.

Malfoy froze.

They all instantly stopped moving, their wands all pointed which way, the ziz-zag corridor already a war zone of broken stone and scorched masonry.

Tracey was standing to the side, trying to look as innocent as possible.

Harry turned his head, and there, halfway down the corridor he and Tracey had just walked up, stood his long time pursuer, Albus Dumbledore. Damn.

“Detention, Mister Potter!”

He lowered his wand. “For John too?”

John scowled, apparently rather shocked by his twin standing right behind him.

“I only saw you, Mister Harry Potter. You will serve detention with me next week on Wednesday.”

Harry gave a low bow, “Of course, Headmaster.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“I still can’t believe that man!” A week had passed and Hermione was pacing in the shrieking shack while Daphne watched and Harry levitated the large wall mirror. “You were only protecting me. You were the only one out of us four who wasn’t attacking anyone, and he still singled you out! Gah!”

Daphne smirked. It was amazing just how much righteous indignation Hermione could hold onto about anything relating to Harry.

“Don’t worry about it, Hermione.” Harry walked with the mirror out of the shack, followed by the two girls, and hung it on the wall facing towards the forbidden forest and away from Hogsmeade. “I’ll be fine. Focus more on the next task.”

Hermione took a deep breath and nodded.

Daphne sat down on a chair she’d carried from the shack, and placed her crystal ball on the ground. She’d spent almost all of last week since Dumbledore had given Harry detention on the Eye of Kilrogg spell, and she was now starting to practise with the mirror seeing spell. But while the Eye of Kilrogg could pass through most wards, the mirror spell could be blocked by even the smallest and weakest magical barriers. The benefit was that while the Eye of Kilrogg had a very short range, the mirror seeing spell could extend as far as the seer’s magic let it, rather like apparition.

The problem with this was that she could only practise the spell outside of the fidelius charm—something Harry had only reluctantly agreed to, especially when he wasn’t there, like now when he had his detention with Dumbledore.

Harry stepped back from the mirror and turned to her and Hermione. “Right. Now, what are the rules?”

Hermione raised her hand, which made Daphne stifle a giggle.

“Yes, Hermione?”

“Always keep the cloak nearby, duck into the shack at the first sign of danger, and message you with our lightning bolt rings if we get in trouble.”

“Right.” Harry handed the invisibility cloak to Hermione. “I’ll see you back in the common room. He then turned around, hit himself on the head with his wand, and became an outline against the background.

Hermione settled herself down cross-legged on the ground to read.

Daphne turned back to the mirror, raised her wand, and began to practise.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore waited in the empty classroom. He’d chosen it specifically for tonight. It was large and gave the feeling of isolation to a student on their own. Also, the dais was raised and allowed the lecturer to look down on the students in the first few rows. It was the classroom he’d once held transfiguration in when he’d been a full time teacher.

There were many questions he hoped he’d get answered tonight.

The door opened and a lone figure walked in.

He waited until his current focus of interest was a good two-thirds of the way down the seating steps before raising his head. “Good evening, Mister Potter.”

“Headmaster.” The boy’s tone was neutral and respectful. His gaze giving neither challenge nor submission.

Dumbledore smiled—a smile he’d spent a lot of time over the years getting just right. He knew it was welcoming and warm, while at the same time firm, with a hint of steel. “I suppose you might be wondering why I decided to oversee your detention personally rather than give it to your head of house?”

The boy finished sitting himself down, and Albus couldn’t help notice that the spot he choose was exactly the same one that Riddle had sat in for his seven years of Hogwarts. “I assumed it was because he’s a ghost?”

“Not at all, my boy. The Baron is just as much a head of house as Professors McGonagall, Sprout, or Flitwick. No, the reason is that I wished to talk to you personally, and felt that this would be a good opportunity to do so. I had been planning to speak with you soon anyway, but your, ahem, actions“—and here he looked over his moon shaped glasses down at the boy—“caused me to alter my plans somewhat.”

Harry Potter tilted his head.

“You’ll be working on your transfiguration. I’ve heard rumours of your abilities, and I’d like to see what you’re capable of. I was something of a prodigy myself in my younger years, you know.” He floated over a brick to Harry Potter’s table. “Now, why don’t you show me what you can do?”

Harry Potter shrugged, picked up his wand, and started to shape the brick into many wondrous things, many far more advanced then any first year should possibly be able to do, but none quite as good as conjuring an armchair right in the middle of the Slytherin common room.

Mmmm …

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne smirked. She didn’t know the forbidden forest, and, like with apparition, you couldn’t use a mirror to see a place you had never seen yourself. But that didn’t stop her. Just like a chain apparating wizard could hop from one visible location to another across the land or sea, so she could jump from spot to spot using the mirror, so long as the mirror could see the next spot she wanted to jump to.

She was currently viewing a beautiful little creek, in which water ran over a tiny waterfall. It was just a shame that the mirror couldn’t pick up sound, or this would be quite relaxing.

A small beeping noise distracted her.

Hermione looked up from her book and shook her beeping wand. “Time for the threat assessment.”

Daphne nodded, focused her magic through her inner eye, and tapped the crystal ball in front of her. It lit up a dim pink.

The two girls stared at it.

Hermione bit her lip. “Maybe we should head back inside?”

Daphne shook her head. “It’s still fine. What ever it is isn’t going to happen for a while. We’ve got time.”

Hermione nodded uncertainly, but did return to her book.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And are you making many friends?”

“Oh, yes, Headmaster. Draco, and Daphne, and Hermione, and Theo, and Pansy.” Potter thought for a moment. “And Tracey.”

Albus frowned. “You might want to be careful, Harry. Young Draco’s family in particular are not known for their fondness of people in your situation.”

Harry Potter frowned. “But, they all seem so friendly—especially when I showed them some of my better tricks.”

Albus mentally winced. While Harry going to Slytherin had been expected, Harry being powerful enough to overcome the natural leeriness his peers would have to a muggle raised, squib-mistaken, half-blood, Potter, twin brother of the boy-who-lived, had not.

“Harry,” he took off his glasses and rubbed his face. “It gives me no pleasure in saying this, but there are many who will try to be friendly with you, just to use you. And the moment you are no longer useful, they will abandon you.”

Harry’s expression darkened. “Like my parents, Sir?”

And there it was. Albus suspected it would be there, but he hoped it wouldn’t. Resentment. He sighed. “Harry, your parents did what they did for a very good reason.”

Harry Potter leaned forward. “What reason?”

“Alas, I cannot say. Not now—wait,” he said, seeing Harry was about to interrupt, “when you are older, no, when you are ready, you will know.”

Albus settled back and regarded the boy in front of him, still watching him with those darkened eyes. Had he made a mistake by asking Lily to have Petunia to treat Harry as her own? He figured a well brought up child would be less risky than one who followed Tom’s path too closely, but now … he wasn’t so sure.

Whatever the case, it was clear the youngest Potter was still holding secrets. He could smell them all over him. So did John, for that matter—and that, was perhaps more worrying than anything else.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne gasped. There, in the mirror, she could clearly see the beautiful and majestic form of a unicorn limping through the forest. The almost glowing white of its hair flowed across its back and sides until it hit a horrible gash in the animal’s back leg, from where silvery blood dribbled out and fell on the floor as the purest thing Daphne had ever seen whinnied and tossed its head in pain. Even without sound, it tore at her heart.

“Hermione,” she whispered.

Hermione didn’t move.

“Hermione,” she said a little louder.

“Huh?” Hermione looked up and gasped. “Oh no. Poor thing.”

Daphne stood up, heart hammering in her chest. “It’s not far. You can help it right?”

Hermione’s eyes widened. “But, we can’t! Harry said we mustn’t leave.”

“No, he said ring him if there was trouble.”

“And! … Go back inside!”

“Only if it was dangerous,” she wheedled.

Hermione pointed wildly at the mirror, eyes panicked. “Have you forgotten what’s hunting it!”

Daphne bit her lip. “But … but …”

“Do the threat check spell!”

Daphne cast the spell on the crystal ball, all the while looking back at the mirror. The crystal ball glowed an angry bright red.

“You see!”

Daphne couldn’t help it. Tears started to form around her eyes. “But, if we don’t do anything, the unicorn is going to DIE!”

Hermione’s lip trembled. Her shoulders slumped.

Daphne plunged on. “Look, we’ll have the cloak. We can message Harry. It’s not far. We can go out, heal it, and get back to the fidelius charm if we run into him. Nothing can see through the cloak—not even him.”

Hermione’s started pacing frantically.

In the mirror, the unicorn gave a silent cry of pain and collapsed in a lush green clearing, in a slowly expanding pool of silver blood.

Hermione stopped pacing, took a deep breath, and clutched her fists together. She closed her eyes. “How far is it?”

“Five minutes, maybe.”

Hermione groaned, her eyes snapping open. “Okay, fine! Get under this thing and let’s go. And be sure to message, Harry.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Albus Dumbledore was getting more and more agitated the more he considered the boy in front of him. It wasn’t any one thing, it was all the little things that added together to create a disturbing whole. Like the way he flicked his wand his at the end of a transfiguration and then gave it a little jab downwards. The jab down wasn’t necessary, it was a mannerism. One he’d seen before. That and a few other tells had alarm bells ringing in his head.

If only he could get Harry and John performing together in an equal test of magic … that would give him the needed results to know just how much of what was going on was a result of Harry being a Potter twin, and how much of it was that fragment of soul in his forehead.

Of course, there was the duelling tournament.

Harry Potter was currently working on the transfiguration essay that Minerva had assigned earlier that week.

Albus stroked his beard. Maybe …

Suddenly Albus twitched in his seat. Something was happening. Almost impossible to feel for someone not as sensitive to magic as himself, but something was happening. A tiny amount of magic was flowing into and out of young Harry.

Albus stared.

Harry’s expression slowly changed—almost beyond his ability to detect, but the change was there. A tiny hint of concern, of worry. And a tiny leak in the boy’s mind.

Albus continued to watch and the magic continued to flow into the boy. Then, the magic started flowing out of the boy, in the same minute amounts.

What was going on?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne and Hermione crept through the undergrowth of the forbidden forest, careful to always stay under the cloak as they made their way to their target.

They rounded the next tree trunk and Daphne’s heart broke.

The unicorn lay there on its side, silver blood everywhere, its chest rising and falling in time with its sad little whines.

“Gogogo,” Hermione whispered.

They quickly made their way over to the animal, wading their way through the long greenery of the clearing, still hidden under the cloak.

When they arrived, Hermione groaned. “It’s so deep—and unicorns are highly magical creatures already. I don’t know if I have enough magic to make this work.”

“Please, just try.”

Hermione pointed her ash and dragon heartstring wand at the animal from under the cloak. “Concrescat sanguinem!”

Slowly, the silvery blood started to dry around the wound, but the longer Hermione held the spell on the animal, the quicker the blood flowed out. Suddenly, the clot gave way, and the wound opened up again. Hermione eyes watered. “It’s too much. I can’t do it.”

The unicorn gave a loud whinny.

Daphne looked around frantically for anything that might help them, and then stopped and saw what they were sitting knee deep in. She shook Hermione’s arm. “Hermione. Look around you!”

Hermione tore her tear-filled eyes from the dying unicorn and gasped. Daphne grabbed one of the nearest plants and started to shred it with her wand. They were sitting in a Merlin damned field of huntsman’s sorrow the size of one of the Hogwart’s greenhouses.

Hermione quickly joined her and moments later they were packing the shredded herb into the wound on the animal’s side. Hermione pointed her wand at the wound again. “Sano caro!”

Slowly, painfully slowly, the wound started to knit itself together, the wound closed, and the blood flow slowed, slowed, and stopped.

Hermione let out a deep breath, and flicked a diagnostic charm over the animal.

“All good?” Daphne asked.

Hermione turned to her, tears leaking out the sides of her eyes. “No, Daphne. It wasn’t enough. She’s still dying. She lost too much blood and I don’t know what else to do. We don’t have any blood replenishers.”

“I …” Daphne felt a lump form in her throat. “There must be something we can do!”

Hermione let out a small sob. “I don’t know!”

Daphne frantically looked around again. There had to be something, but there was only the huntsman’s sorrow, the unicorn, them, the cloak, and the pools of silvery blood still soaking the ground, and trailing away into the forest.

She looked down where the unicorn blood had already started to soak in the silk of her robes where she had knelt down on the ground.

That … that couldn’t work … could it?

“Hermione!”

Hermione looked up at her.

“The unicorn blood! Give it to her!”

Hermione looked confused for a moment before her eyes widened. “Will that work?”

“I don’t know, but what else is there to lose?”

Hermione wiped her nose on her sleeve, and nodded.

Daphne transfigured a small trough from surrounding dirt and soil.

“Accio unicorn blood!”

Unicorn blood soared through the air at them, and they managed to catch, at least some of it in the trough, while being very careful not to accidentally drink any themselves.

Daphne put the trough down in front of the unicorn, which looked up at her with pain filled eyes. “C’mon,” she said, stroking the animal’s nose, “I know you wouldn’t normally do this, but this is your only chance. Please. Don’t die.”

The unicorn looked up at her again, and with Daphne and Hermione’s help, managed to raise its head and, lowing it back into the trough, started to drink. And as it drank, the animal started to glow silver white.

Hermione flicked another diagnostic charm over the glowing animal, let out a massive smile, and gave Daphne the thumbs up.

Daphne’s heart soared. They’d done it.

And it was at exactly that moment when a darkened figure, face hidden by a long black hooded cloak, descended from the sky not a dozen metres from where they sat, slowly clapping.

Terror gripped Daphne’s soul. She didn’t wait to see what the corpse possessing Dark Lord was going to do. She shielded, leapt for Hermione, grabbed the cloak from her, covered them both in it, grabbed her friend, and stumbled to where she’d just been, moments before a dozen spells splashed at and around where they’d just been standing, only seconds earlier.

Hermione shrieked.

Obviously alerted by her friend’s cry, Quirrellmort threw more spells in their direction.

Daphne shielded, managing to stop one whole spell before the shield shattered and three different spells hit the cloak, flowing around them and out the other side, but not before one hit Hermione, opening up a huge cut in her shoulder, and causing her to cry out again.

Suddenly, the still glowing unicorn was on its feet and charging.

Voldemort shot up into the air to evade and the unicorn pivoted around, stopping right in front of them.

Without needing to think, Daphne hoisted herself up onto its back, grabbing a still whimpering Hermione with the help of one almighty Accio.

The unicorn bolted away, the girls desperately clinging on as hard as they could, curses and spells raining down around it them.

She sent a series of frantic pulses of magic into her lightning bolt ring. ‘LV’.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore was still trying to work out was what going on when suddenly a small eruption of magic came from the boy. Not the subtle mystery from before, but a simple flare of determination.

Harry Potter stood up quickly. “My apologies, Headmaster, I need to use the bathroom, if I may be excused.” He turned to go.

Albus twitched. “No, I think not, Mister Potter. Please sit back down and continue.”

Potter ignored him.

Albus sighed and flicked his wrist, causing the large double doors to the classroom to slam shut and bolt themselves.

Harry Potter froze.

Albus got to his feet and walked up the other passageway to the main doors. Reaching them, he turned back to look at the boy, whose facial expression was now so blank that Albus couldn’t detect a single emotion on it. It was as though Harry had completely closed himself off from anything and everything in the world.

“Please go back to your seat, Mister Potter.”

Harry Potter didn’t move. “I need to leave.”

Albus frowned, still standing between Harry and the room’s only exit. “Perhaps I didn’t make myself clear, Mister Potter. You. May. Not. Leave.”

The blank facial expression lasted all of a few more moments before being replaced by a flash-flood of raw, uncontrolled magic, and one simple overriding emotion. Terror.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ploughing through the forbidden forest on the back of a glowing unicorn, Daphne risked a glance behind her and gave a whimper of her own. The Dark Lord flew around them just like Harry could, just as agile as any broomstick, managing to keep pace despite the many forest obstacles.

The unicorn flowed through the woods like water.

Daphne couldn’t help thinking that riding bareback at this speed should be far more uncomfortable than it actually was. Time seemed to slow down and moments stretched to eternity. She wasn’t sure how long the chase lasted, but it felt like forever. In the darkness of the deep woods, every spell flash felt like a supernova in the back of her eyeballs.

Then, after what seemed an age, they danced around another bush, into a clearing and what Daphne saw ahead made her heart stop. Six centaurs, tall and powerful, stood in a semi-circle, their bows drawn and pointing right at them.

Not seeming to care, their pure-light mount continued straight on, dashed past the taut row of bristling death, and screeched to a stop behind the line.

Voldemort zoomed into the clearing, and, without even seeming to hesitate, made a large upwards curve, straight up into the sky, as six arrow heads zipped straight through where his borrowed body had been, only moments earlier.

And then the clearing was silent.

From behind her, Hermione mumbled, “concrescat sanguinem.”

The centaurs all turned to them.

“Umm … hi?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Mister Potter, control yourself!” Albus roared through the whirlwind of wild magic pouring off the young sorcerer. Chairs and tables lay smashed all around him. He flicked his wand again, shielding against yet another flying desk.

Harry Potter stood in the middle of an almost completely destroyed classroom. His posture was like a caged animal, eyes white with mindless terror, magic totally out of control, and Albus knew the boy was going into full scale magical meltdown—the pathway to his core had snapped open and his body was desperately trying—and failing—to contain the totality of his magic, every single Merlin being unloaded from his core, all at once.

Albus cursed and tried to shoot a stunner at the boy, which had about as much effect as hitting a steel door with a feather. He transfigured the stone in the floor to form a solid egg around the boy, only for it to be torn through like paper.

The magical build-up was ridiculous.

“Albus!” Minerva’s voice shouted from the other side of the bolted door. “What’s going on!”

“Minerva!” he shouted. “Clear the area! Get all students away! Now!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Thank you for saving us.” Daphne said.

The centaurs all looked between each other before what seemed to be leader stepped forward. “It is not we who saved you, young seer, but the stars.”

Daphne’s eyes widened. They knew she was practising divination. That was supposed to be, like, super top secret knowledge. “Umm …”

The centaurs all looked to the sky, but didn’t say anything more.

Under her, the unicorn let out a little snuffling noise.

Hermione was still tending to her shoulder.

“Jupiter shines brightly tonight.”

Daphne frowned. Angelystor hadn’t taught her anything about astrology and their astronomy classes were of questionable helpfulness. “Is that good?”

The leader, large and chestnut coloured, looked down at her.

“The last time around, it was Pluto, and the time before that, was Mars.”

“The last time?”

“The stars carry messages of their changes, young seer—changes in space—changes in time.”

The words crashed into Daphne like a hammer. “Y-y-you know?” she squeaked.

“Around and around you go, will you ever get it right? I hope for our sakes, that you will.”

“W-we intend to.”

“I’m sure you do.” The leader looked around at his fellows again before turning back. He sighed. “Well, I understand that your kind set great store by trades. This thing for that thing. I would trade with you, Lady Slytherin.”

Daphne was suddenly on guard. “Trade?”

“For saving your lives, young fillies, we simple ask that you remember that, for us, the forest is our home, and always will be.”

“You want me to remember that?”

“Yes.”

Daphne thought for a moment. “Very well. I, as Lady Slytherin, will remember that the forest is your home and always will be.”

The centaur bowed. “That is all we ask.”

Suddenly, from far in the distance, there was an almighty BOOM that shook the ground under them, and caused leaves to fall from trees.

“What was that?” Daphne asked, alarmed.

“That, was your lord.”

Daphne and Hermione stilled, wide eyed. Harry!

“I daresay, he is in need of your help, young ones.”

And with an adrenaline fuelled jolt, the unicorn surged into motion again, Daphne and Hermione no longer thinking of anything, but getting to their friend and leader.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore stood up from where he’d been crouching in a protective bubble of almost pure magic, reinforced by transfigured stonework, and conjured titanium. The room was a mess. Another large beam crashed down to the ground in a heap of flaming wreckage.

He quickly made his way over to the boy, now laying unconscious in a crumpled heap. That reaction had been the most extreme thing he’d ever seen, and he’d seen a lot. Magical meltdowns weren’t unknown, but they rarely happened to people who had such apparently large cores.

He pointed his wand at the young boy’s head. “Legilimens.” His probe hit something as solid as steel and bounced straight off. He stumbled back, shocked. What in Merlin’s name?

“Albus!” Minerva appeared by his side, stepping over rubble to do so. “What happened?” She caught sight of Harry. “Oh, my goodness!”

“He needs medical help, Minerva. Can you take him up to the hospital wing?”

Minerva McGonagall nodded, “Certainly.”

Albus Dumbledore watched his number two levitate the unconscious boy and leave the room.

Mmmm … now what to do?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione and Daphne charged up to the school, pausing only for cleaning charms to get rid of as much unicorn blood as possible and turning their robes inside out to hide the rest. They ran past an incensed Filch, was screamed at them about at it being almost curfew, and ran down to the Slytherin common room, only to find Harry wasn’t there. They then ran to the one other place they though he might be … the hospital wing.

“Harry!” Hermione and Daphne cried in unison upon entering the wing.

“Miss Granger! Miss Greengrass!” The matron stormed over to them. “Keep your voices down. You, Miss Granger, I expect you to know better.”

Hermione wasn’t listening though. “What happened to Harry?”

“Some kind of magical overloading.” Madam Pomfrey made an unamused cluck sound with her tongue. “Blew up one of the classrooms on the fourth floor.”

Daphne took up position on Harry’s right side. “Is he going to be okay?”

“Yes, with time and rest. It’s very difficult to tell, of course, but he’ll probably be up and about by as soon as tomorrow morning, as insane as that may be.”

Daphne sagged with relief. She saw Hermione do the same. She could remember the last time something like this had happened—when Harry had been trapped at the Weasley’s—but it hadn’t been this bad then.

They both took one of his hands in theirs and sat down to wait for as long as they could, before Madam Pomfrey eventually kicked them out.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

In a corner of the hospital wing, disillusioned and silenced, Albus Dumbledore watched the two young ladies eventually leave with mixed feelings. Such shows of loyalty and friendship were admirable, and in any other circumstance, he’d be beside himself with joy. But right now, it could not be happening at a worse time.

He’d spent the last few hours thinking about what had happened and had come to the conclusion that Harry had not only shown himself to be powerful, charismatic, and likeable, but he was also keeping secrets, and had occlumency barriers far stronger than anything he’d ever seen before. Not only that, but all those normal memories and feelings that Albus had been plucking from the boy’s mind up to now were obviously fake. An extra layer of shielding against legilimency attacks that only the very, very best occlumens could pull off.

That combined with the boy’s apparent instability, as made clear by tonight’s events, lead him to one painful conclusion. The lad was dangerous. Far too dangerous for the status quo to be allowed to stand. But what was he to do? Lily and James would never allow him to be pulled from Hogwarts, not without an obvious event that showed something had gone wrong. That would go counter to everything he’d told them.

But he needed Harry to be somewhere safer. Somewhere he could keep an eye on him, where Harry couldn’t just run away, where he couldn’t build up influence the way Tom had. And where Dumbledore could grab the boy when he was needed to square up against Tom again, after the experiment with the stone had run its course.

He stared at the blank wall of the hospital wing.

And then it came to him.

He let out a long, depressed sigh. Of course, that was were he could maneuver for young Harry to be placed, as horrific as it would be … Azkaban.

—End of Chapter Twenty-eight—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: I’m back! This chapter damn well nearly did me in. I swear. I’m going to try and make future chapters a bit tighter, as well as not jump PoVs so much, but damn. They just grow and grow and growwwwwwwwwwwwww :O

A/N: Some points to discuss about last chapter.

Quite a few people want to know what happened with the four hundred galleons Volf was supposed to deposit into Clare’s Gringotts account. I’m in two minds about whether to just tell you in the author comments or wait for a good opportunity to explore it in story. Obviously, I know what happened, but it might be quite a while before the gang find out, and isn’t really all that mind blowing. I’ll probably wait until I’m sure it doesn’t become story critical and tell you all sometime in the future. I will say this though—When Harry declared the contract paid in full, magic accepted the declaration. It wouldn’t have done that if Harry hadn’t fulfilled his side of the agreement (originally Volf’s side).

A/N: “But LeadVonE! The centaurs wouldn’t be able to see Pluto, and it was only discovered in 1930, anyway, AND it’s not really a planet!”

Oh, go away ^^. It’s magic, okay?

A/N: Happy one year birthday of Dodging Prison and Stealing Witches! Can’t believe it’s been a year already. And the popularity of this story continues to blow my mind.

Cleithrophobia and Planning a Heist

Goblins. Why did it always have to be goblins?

Stan Shunpike, currently on secondment from the bus division of Knight Logistics, drove his knight wagon along the Scottish coastline, occasionally shooting glances at his much shorter driving companion. The huge purple lorry zoomed up the mostly deserted road, occasionally bending past a car or motorcycle, or even jumping straight over, if two blocked the road at once.

The goblin sitting next to him hadn’t said much, despite Stan’s best cheerful efforts to make conversation.

“So, you reckon his lordship gonna be puttin’ on all kinds of fancy parties and whatnot, when you lot are all done with it all?”

The goblin grunted and continued to stare out the lorry’s side window.

“I just reckon I could fit in well at one o’ those dos, don’tcha think?” He fiddled with his bowtie and swerved to avoid a man riding on horse back, causing his green companion to clutch at the side door and curse in his harsh tongue. “My ma always said I had a touch of the nobby in me, she did.”

The goblin glared at him. “Just keep your eyes on the road, human.”

Stan shrugged and turned forward again. Could never get a good word out of a goblin. Wouldn’t it do the vicious little buggers just to lighten up a bit?

They continued to zip across the country, keeping up with the knight wagon in front and making sure not to get too far ahead of the knight wagon behind them. The whole convoy eventually made it to a small strip of land jutting out onto the water in the middle of a sleepy village. The deep purple lorries clashed against everything around them, from the white washed stone walls of the houses, to the brown woods of the jetty, and the faint blue of the water and sky—and yet, not one of the hundred or so residents of the village looked askance at the colour mad insanity that had just invaded their home, or even noticed it.

Stan tapped the side of his wagon, waiting for the boat they were to unload the cargo onto, and trying to ignore the goblin, who had taken what looked to be a cooked rat out of a paper bag and was now messily devouring it.

The wait continued. Stan frowned. Shouldn’t be taking this long, should it? He turned off the engine, opened the door, and stepped down onto the worn tarmac road. Some posh bloke was talking to his mate, Richie, over at the leading Knight Wagon. An argument looked in the offing. He wandered over. “Oi, Richie, what’s going on?”

Richie scowled and nodded towards the other man who, in Stan’s mind, screamed, ‘Ministry’.

“Mister Shunpike?” The man said in a snooty voice. “I am Geoffrey Perkins, an inspector with the department of magical trade—and I’ve been assigned the task of overseeing all materials and artefacts used in the construction of Slytherin Manor.”

“Oi. You can’t do that, can he, Rich?”

“I assure you, Mister Shunpike, that the ministry has authorised it.”

“This is Goblin business, human.” Stan’s goblin companion appeared from nowhere to stand beside him. “The cargo is our responsibility and you have no right to inspect a goblin cargo under treaty.”

The ministry inspector’s lip curled up. “Thankfully, that will not be an issue, as I will not be inspecting any goblin cargos.”

“What?”

Suddenly, another goblin appeared, standing next to Perkins and grinning evilly.

“YOU!” Stan’s goblin shouted.

“Me.” Perkins’ goblin replied.

“What business does the Goldtooth Clan have with the House of Slytherin?”

“None what so ever, merely a profitable contract with the ministry to assist in the overseeing of wizarding business.”

“YOU TRAITOR!” Stan’s goblin produced a battle axe from no where.

“You call us traitors?” Perkins’ goblin spat, producing a two handed sword. “You, the Boneslicer clan, call us traitors! YOU POWER GRABBING DESPOTS!”

They charged.

Stan, Richie, and Perkins all ran for it, determined to avoid losing any limbs as the two goblins settled what all three humans quickly agreed was an internal goblin matter, and absolutely nothing to do with any of them.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione landed, looked around her, and shuddered. The room she found herself in was dark—so dark that she couldn’t see anything. Moments later, Daphne joined her, dropping out of the air as though from a cloud.

The two shared an apprehensive look, themselves being the only things visible.

Hermione’s lip quivered.

Harry was disappointed with her.

A heavy door opened, light flooded in, and both Hermione and Daphne gasped.

In the doorway, stood Dark Lord Voldemort, tall, bald, white skinned, red-eyed, noseless, terrible—a visage to frighten not only little children, but also parents, teachers, soldiers, and heroes.

Now visible on the wall opposite, hung an older Hermione, chained to the ceiling by her wrists, feet not touching the floor, robes torn, hair messy, face bloody, skin dirty, figure so skinny they could see her bones.

Older Hermione raised her head and the look of despair and hopelessness on her face made younger Hermione flinch.

The Dark Lord didn’t say anything—just stepped forward and raised his wand.

“P-please,” older Hermione managed to choke out before a purple spell shot from Voldemort’s wand, hitting older Hermione right in the chest, and ripping a scream from the helpless witch, writhing and jerking in mid air, hands fisting and grasping thin air from where the manacles cut into her wrists.

Younger Hermione tightly clung to Daphne, Daphne doing the same back to her, both desperately wanting—but not daring—to look away as older Hermione screamed and kicked and occasionally begged in between great heaving spasms.

Finally Voldemort seemed to have had enough. He lowered his wand, opened his mouth as though to say something, seemed to change his mind, and, with an almost bored wave of his wand, fired a red spell at Older Hermione.

Younger Hermione and Daphne screamed.

Older Hermione’s head exploded, painting the blank stone walls red. The chains holding the now headless corpse gave way and the dead older Hermione fell to the ground.

Voldemort left the room and a massive snake slithered in. The last thing Hermione and Daphne saw was the beast working its jaws over the corpse’s feet, massive teeth puncturing skin, powerful muscles slowing dragging the body across the floor.

Hermione felt sick.

The scene shifted and now Hermione was following the Dark Lord into a small cottage whose door had been blown off. Screams came from inside.

“No!” A man was kneeling on the floor begging as a screaming and flailing young woman was being dragged away by masked figures. “Please! Don’t!” the man begged. “Please! She’s done nothing wrong!”

Voldemort stepped in front of the man, who looked up at him in terror. “She is a mudblood—and you have disgraced yourself by marrying such filth. Crucio.”

The man screamed, filling Hermione’s head with its intensity. She clutched Daphne ever tighter, tears starting to cloud her vision.

The scene shifted again. This time they were in a huge, closed room, packed with hundreds of witches and wizards of all ages. Every face looked tired, dirty, and scared.

A door opened and Voldemort walked in, along with several dozen death eaters. “Witches and Wizards,” Voldemort said in a soft voice that still carried all the way across the suddenly quiet room. “You have all resisted when you were told to surrender. The punishment for resisting Lord Voldemort is death.”

The death eaters then started systematically murdering every person in the room—men, women, children, the old, even babies still clutched in their mother’s arms, paying no heed to the screams, the begging, and the always brief howls of anguish.

Voldemort stood, watched, and smiled.

Scene after scene, on and on it went. Hermione’s face ran with tears. Her body trembled and shook. Daphne clung to her so tightly that ice started to form on Hermione’s skin.

Eventually, it was done. Hermione felt herself pulled up and up, and she exited the pensieve, landing in an inelegant heap of sniffling witch.

In front of them, next to one of the trunk walls, Harry sat on a simple wooden chair, watching them impassively.

Hermione and Daphne got to their feet, eyes downcast.

“And what lesson have we learned?” Harry asked.

Hermione sniffled. “D-Don’t go against your orders, Harry.”

Next to her, she felt Daphne tense.

“No, Hermione.” Harry’s voice was firm. “That is not the lesson. You know I’ve always told you that orders can sometimes be disobeyed, under the right circumstances.”

Daphne raised a shaky hand.

“Yes, Daphne.”

“Don’t put our lives at risk for …” she looked down again, “for things that aren’t that important.”

Harry took a deep breath. “You got half of it right. Yes, you take into account how important the thing is, but you also take into account how much you’re risking your lives. You’ll notice I didn’t say anything when you two went after the troll on Halloween, despite my orders then not to. Why not? Hermione?”

Hermione’s lower lip trembled. “Because the risk was lower and the thing we were fighting for was more important?”

“Exactly!”

The sudden shout caused both her and Daphne to jump.

“Okay, Sophie Roper wasn’t on our side at the time, but there’s a better than good chance she might be one day, and she’s human. Two good reasons. Unicorns, on the other hand, while being light creatures, pure and good, and all that, arenot people—they are animals—intelligent animals, no doubt, but still animals. Daphne, I know you have a thing for unicorns, but you are more precious than any unicorn.”

Daphne shook.

Harry took another long breath. “And to compare threats—one the one side you have a mountain troll, which, while dangerous, you were able to handle, proving you’d made a good risk judgement, and on the other hand, you have Voldemort—a weakened Voldemort, yes, but still Voldemort—the freak’n Dark Lord! Has five months being taught by him in a classroom perhaps reduced your respect for him?”

Hermione stood with her head down, not saying anything, fighting back tears of shame, images of Voldemort’s murderous rampage still fresh and sharp in her mind. She’d never felt like she’d let Harry down so badly before.

Harry stood up. “Was this enough of a reminder of what we’re fighting for and the type of person we’re fighting against?”

Hermione and Daphne both nodded.

“Do you need another spin in the pensieve?”

Hermione and Daphne both shook their heads.

“Hermione, what is our overall mission?”

She looked up. “The defeat of Voldemort and the control of Magical Britain.”

“Daphne, how do I expect you to behave differently in the future?”

“Don’t do dangerous things that don’t help with our overall mission, and even then, only if the danger is less than our ability to cope with it.”

Harry let out a deep breath. “Alright.” His face softened and he spread his arms. “Come here then.”

Hermione collapsed into him, sobbing freely, letting the tension drain out of her, joined moments later by Daphne.

Harry wrapped his arms around them and held them.

They stood like that for an age before finally disengaging.

Hermione drew back and blowed her nose with a Harry-conjured handkerchief.

“Right.” Harry conjured two extra chairs for the two of them and they all sat down. “Now, as much as we might like to move on to other things, we do need to discuss consequences. Let’s start with the most obvious thing. Dumbledore.”

Hermione stiffened.

Harry continued. “Dumbledore now knows that something is up.” Harry shifted uncomfortably. “My … reaction … last night will likely bring up some red flags for him—yes, Hermione?”

Hermione had raised a hesitant hand. “I actually did some research on that this morning.” She meekly reached into her bag and brought out a book.

Harry nodded. “In a moment, sure.” He tapped on his chair. “I heard Madam Pomfrey talking to Dumbledore. He now also knows that I’m much closer with you two then just casual acquaintances. He may well do something to try and split us apart and we need to be ready for that. You, Hermione, need to be even more careful, since you don’t wear a noble house ring, and while with your level of occlumency, an obliviate wouldn’t be horrific, just annoying, some potions on the other hand, would be quite bad.”

Hermione nodded. She was already checking everything she ate and drank because of John Potter.

“Dumbledore may well also try to do something to remove me from the school or even put me in Azkaban. He did it last time, although then he had an actual student death on his hands. I don’t know whether he’d go so far as to manufacture a whole crime, just to get me put away, but we can’t rule it out.”

Beside her, Daphne nodded firmly.

“And finally, we have Quirrellmort.” Harry frowned. “He now believes you have an invisibility cloak, even if he doesn’t know it’s the invisibility cloak. We’ll need to check the remaining defences in the third floor corridor and make sure there aren’t any that could be defeated with such an artefact, or you’ve suddenly got a large target on your backs.”

Hermione shivered.

“We’ll also need to guard against him in general, so I don’t want you splitting up from each other if you can help it, unless its for one of our projects that requires it.”

Hermione and Daphne nodded.

“And until Voldemort is out of the castle, no more mirror training.”

Daphne’s face fell, before she reluctantly nodded.

“Right.” Harry slapped his hands on his knees. “Hermione, you said you did some research?”

Hermione nodded quickly and held up the book again. The moment she and Daphne had left the hospital wing the night before, they’d had a long talk about the last time Harry had had such a strong reaction—Daphne filling her in on the Weasley incident when Harry had almost blown up the Burrow. They’d bounced ideas back and forth, but it was Hermione’s muggle background and mountain of healing books, both magical and muggle, that had eventually produced their current theory. She handed Harry the book, titled American Directory of Psychological Disorders. “We think you may have cleithrophobia, Harry.”

Harry frowned. “What’s that?” He started scanning the page she’d opened for him.

“It’s the irrational fear of being trapped. Probably from your time in Azkaban. At first we thought you might have claustrophobia, but then we realised that wouldn’t make any sense because …”

“… Because I’m fine with being in confined spaces.” Harry nodded while he read. “Yes, this sounds … eerily accurate … ‘patients report experiencing panic attacks when in rooms locked from the outside, when in cars trapped in traffic jams, even sometimes by merely being in a room with someone blocking an open door.’ Wow. Okay, I’m not that bad. It only happens to me when …” He looked to be thinking for a moment. “When I believe that I can’t get out. Even with all my magic and powers, when I feel I’ve been backed into a corner.” He took a deep, long breath. “And obviously, because we’re magical, a high level panic attack for some reason, in my case, materialises as going boom.”

Hermione wordlessly passed him another open book, this time magical, and open to a page describing the phenomenon of magical meltdown.

Harry smiled. “Yeah, I checked that out at least after the last episode. I see now that I should have put you on this case ages ago, Hermione.”

Hermione blushed. At least Harry had stopped giving her the disappointed look.

Harry sighed and leaned back in his chair. “Okay, so I have cleithrophobia. What can I do about it? I don’t need to say that freaking out like that just because Dumbledore stands in front of a door and tells me I can’t leave, isn’t great from a strategic point of view.”

Daphne nodded.

Hermione handed Harry a third book. “There was only one reference that I could find to fighting phobias in the magical healing books. The muggle books have lots of treatments, but they are. …” She hesitated. “Problematic, if you’re going to, ‘go boom,’ every time it happens.”

Harry took the open book and read down the page. He looked up from the book. “Special occlumency?”

Hermione nodded. “The book says it can take decades to eliminate a phobia entirely though.”

Harry smiled. “Maybe—but occlumency does happen to be something I’m very, very good at.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne sat cross-legged on the magically expanded water pipe’s cool, rounded, metallic floor, just outside the third-floor corridor room containing the muggle pensieve thing, and slowed her breathing.

Occlumency was amazing magic. Under occlumency your thoughts were clearer, your memory better, and your skills developed with the ease of the mythical naturally gifted—but that didn’t mean it was without its drawbacks.

Opposite her, sat Harry, also cross-legged, studying her carefully. Hermione stood to one side, alert, watchful, wand in hand, snake in pocket.

Daphne reached inside and sunk into her own mind.

Occlumency allowed her great control over her day to day emotions—anger, jealousy, resentment, fear—all the things she didn’t like feeling—but the problem with that was that it did allow her to somewhat control them. Sometimes, paralysing fear was a good thing. Occlumency also brought an understanding of the world far beyond her years, but that understanding could be both a blessing and a curse, for while she was able to make decisions with the clarity of an adult, it also made her mistakes all the more painfully obvious, once she’d made them.

In short, she’d never felt more of a little twelve-year-old girl, as she had when Harry had been telling her off, not half an hour ago. The shame and guilt still stung. Harry had never told her off before. Harry had never needed to tell her off.

“Profero oculus Kilrogg,” Daphne whispered, pointing her wand at the space in between her and Harry. Her world split in two and a large floating eyeball appeared, visible only to herself in sight, and to Harry in magic. She’d sworn to never let him down again.

Harry nodded and raised his wand to point at her head. “Legilimens.”

Daphne opened her mental defences and surrendered to him, letting him sink deep into her now vulnerable mind, to feel her feelings, explore her senses.

Harry pushed himself to her sense of sight, and there he settled, sitting snug behind all three of her eyes.

“Ready when you are, Daphne. I suggest we start with the first room.”

“Okay.” Daphne moved the eyeball into the room beyond, feeling Harry’s own mind watching through her’s as the eye passed easily through metal and wards alike. She quickly moved it through the various rooms, spotting statues and glasswork and what looked like a small forest, before finding her disembodied self in a completely empty room.

“This was the chimaera room.” Harry commented.

“There’s nothing here.” She angled the eyeball to take in the whole room.

“It looks like that, doesn’t it?”

“I for one am glad we don’t have to face another chimaera.” Hermione’s voice said.

“Next room, Daph.”

Daphne nodded, turned the eye around, and moved through the solid door into the next room, to be met again, with what looked like tropical rain forest.

“This room didn’t present much of a threat when I last walked through it, although I was under the cloak. I’m guessing the plants are here to power all of this.”

“Why?” Hermione’s voice asked, “Why not just use the magic of Hogwarts?”

“Probably because the Hogwarts magic is channelled through the wards.”

A lumos went off in Daphne’s head. “Wards that you in part control.”

“Exactly—and Dumbledore knows that. Clearly he doesn’t want Lord Slytherin to casually saunter down here.”

“What is that?” Daphne asked, spotting a large vine like thing wrapped around a tree with spikes on it the size of daggers. Many of the spines were embedded in the tree, occasionally pulsating.

“That is a Brazilian strangle vine. It attacks and feeds off the magic of other plants. It moves kind of like devil’s snare that we did in herbology.”

“It’s a parasite?”

“Yep.”

“What’s it doing here then? Wouldn’t Dumbledore want the most magic available?”

“He should. I don’t know why it’s here—it’s a dark plant. Voldemort even used it as a symbol of hatred.”

“Why?” Hermione’s voice asked.

“One of the more extreme pureblood propaganda pieces is that muggleborns steal magic from other witches and wizards.”

“And this plant steals magic from other plants.” Hermione’s voice said, laced with understanding.

“Indeed. Maybe Quirrellmort found his way into here and scattered some strangle vine seeds … actually that would make a lot of sense. If he could drain away some of the magic, breaking through the wards could be a bit simpler.”

With little else to see in the room, apart from some venomous tentacular, and a young whomping willow, Daphne moved the floating eyeball into the next room.

A small army of statues lined the two side walls of the room, all armed with battle axes, swords, and crossbows. There had to be at least a hundred of them on each side, forming a wide corridor to the door on the far side of the room.

Daphne swallowed. “I guess if you enter this room, they attack?”

“Or pass a certain point,” Harry agreed. “The basilisk made short work of them last time.”

“Why put a defence back in place, if Voldemort has already shown he has a way to get past it?” Hermione’s voice asked.

Harry shrugged. “Probably because Dumbledore doesn’t actually consider this to be the true defence, just a bunch of ways to slow Voldie down, or somehow make a confrontation between me and him more likely.”

“Could you handle them, Harry?” Hermione’s voice asked.

Daphne looked critically around at the hundreds of armed stone warriors.

“Yes, but it would take quite a bit out of me. Don’t think there’s much more to inspect here. Daphne?”

Daphne moved the eyeball into the next room.

Complex glasswork lined one side of the room. Hundreds of twisty and curved pipes and tubes joined dozens of glass beakers and spheres. The large sphere nearest them, contained what looked to be a large sphere of dull metal.

“Parchment on the desk in the centre, Daphne.”

Daphne spotted what Harry pointed out and moved the eyeball over to inspect it.

Dear visitors,

To open the door, please move the sphere of iron from one side of the glass maze to the other without breaking any of the glass. If any glass is broken, chipped, melted, or in any way damaged, moved from the bench, or transfigured, the locks on both doors will activate and an alarm will sound.

Good luck.

“Magical Merlin,” Harry breathed. “This one is actually damn tough. Could you take us to the start of the maze, Daph?”

Daphne did so.

“A maze?” Hermione’s voice asked.

“A maze made of glass tubes and spheres,” Harry said, presumably inspecting the sphere of iron held in the large glass sphere. “Like they use in our classes to demonstrate magical theory. You have to get a ball of iron from one side of the maze to the other without breaking or interfering in any way with the glass. Problem is, the iron ball is much larger than most of the tubes and even some of the glass spheres on the way.”

“Transfiguration?” Hermione’s voice asked.

Harry shook his head. “Can’t get the transfiguration spell to the ball with the glass in the way—no—there’s only one thing I can think of that could do this job … alchemy, but even with my skill, it would be damn difficult. You’d have to melt the ball and move molten iron through the maze in a tiny stream, quickly enough not to melt any of the nearby glass and making sure not to touch any of the glass walls. There’s no way any first year could manage it, that’s for certain. In fact, I doubt there’s a single normal student in the whole school that could.”

Daphne slowly nodded. “I guess it’s a good thing we don’t actually have to do it then?”

Harry grinned. “Quite.”

The next room would have been pitch dark, if it weren’t for the thousands of stars that lighted up the roof, just like midnight great hall on a clear night. Daphne looked around. “I can’t see anything.”

“Keep looking.”

Daphne kept looking, but it wasn’t until she’d lapped the room several times that she finally found a parchment on a desk. “Wish Angelystor had already taught us the night vision charm,” she muttered as she leaned into the parchment, just making out the writing in the almost total darkness.

To continue, move the stars and planets to the positions they held on your birthday.

“That’s it?” Daphne asked. “How do you do that?”

“Is there a control panel? Maybe something like Professor Sinistra’s astrolabe?”

Daphne spent another few minutes searching around the room before finally finding it. “Here!”

“Mmmm …” Harry said.

“What is it?” Hermione’s voice asked.

“Birthday ID check combined with astronomy knowledge. I don’t know how it’s supposed to know what your birthday is to make sure you’re telling the truth, so, unless this whole thing is completely pointless, there must be a list of acceptable birthdays.”

“So, you could enter the position of the stars and planets on Dumbledore’s birthday and it would let you through?”

“Maybe—or maybe just professor Sinistra’s? Either way, let’s move on.”

Daphne moved the eyeball through the far doorway, and into the room with the muggle pensieve in it.

“Careful now.” Harry said as she neared the next doorway to the next room. “We should be fine here, but there’s always a risk that the tripwire will still trip, even for the eyeball.”

She nodded and pressed ahead. The eyeball slipped through the door, into the next room, and into its middle … and she still knew why they were here. She smiled.

“Excellent.” Harry sounded delighted. “Well, that’s one problem cracked.”

Daphne now took the time to look around the room, mostly dominated by a huge stone statue of their currently, and rather ironically, petrified potions professor and former head of house, Severus Snape. A small table sat in front of the statue, on which stood a single tiny glass of perfectly clear liquid … and a parchment.

Daphne moved the eyeball over to it and read.

Danger lies before you, while safety lies behind,

So drink the potion and answer my questions truthfully, because I’m not in the mood to write another damn poem!

“Veritaserum.” Harry said, “And neither Voldemort nor Quirrell are noble, so they have no defence against it” He snorted. “How very cunning. So this one is probably a straight up lie detector test with certain preprogrammed answers granting access to the next room.” He paused for a moment. “Or just poison, of course.”

“Two of us are noble.” Daphne supplied.

“Yeah, I’m going to have to think about that. Obviously whichever of us goes in front of this thing will be under the cloak with a modified voice. It would be rather embarrassing if the statue could tell Dumbledore that one of us was granted access to the next room.”

“That would be bad.” Hermione’s voice said.

Harry nodded. “Next room, I think, Daphne.”

Daphne moved the eyeball through the door next to the massive statue, into the next room, and a dozen doors suddenly appeared before her, but something wasn’t quite right. It took a confusing moment to understand what it was she was seeing. “Mirrors?”

“Mirrors.” Harry said.

The room was filled with hundreds of mirrors, all ornate, old looking, and angled just so to reflect a billion reflections from all the other mirrors, creating a confusing maze of images that stretched her large green eyeball out and into infinity. Every mirror had the same plaque at the bottom. “Erised stra ehru oyt ube cafru oyt on wohsi.”

“Oh Merlin,” Harry whispered. “This must have taken Dumbledore ages to set up. Does the man not have anything better to do with his time?”

“Harry?” Daphne asked. “What are they?”

“I think they’re supposed to be copies of the Mirror of Erised, although exactly how closely they resemble the original, we’ll only be able to tell once we’re actually in here. But there was only one last time.”

“This is the last room,” Daphne said, looking around. “Is the stone in here?”

“The stone’s hidden in the real mirror … probably. Last time around, John was able to somehow extract the stone from it. Voldemort later theorised that the mirror screens for intent, so only someone who wanted to find the stone, but not use it, would be able to retrieve it.”

“Won’t that be a problem?” Hermione’s voice asked.

“Hopefully not,” Harry said, smiling, “I have a plan. Daphne? Can you check the room’s edges?”

Daphne moved the eyeball where Harry asked and immediately saw something she recognised.

Harry started laughing.

Daphne stared. Rune stones. The exact same miniature rune stones Harry always used for his makeshift fidelius charms.

Harry grinned. “Mmmm … that should give us some possibilities.”

“What?” Hermione’s voice asked eagerly. “What are we going to do?”

Harry shook his head. “Just … just give me some time to think first, okay?”

Daphne could hear Hermione pout. “Yes, Harry.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The next few days had Hermione on high alert. Dumbledore didn’t seem to make any moves, although Harry had caught the man studying him during dinner more than once. Unsurprisingly with the amount of damage caused, news of the incident had spread around the castle, no one quite knowing what to believe, but the general understanding being that Harry Potter had done a particularly destructive piece of accidental magic and had spent the night in the hospital wing to recover.

Many Hufflepuffs and Gryffindors were treating Harry like a bomb that might go off at any moment. Most Ravenclaws were more interested in understanding what had happened to trigger the event. Slytherins, by contrast, tended to thump her friend on the back and congratulate him, usually while making comments like, ‘Give em’ hell at the duelling tournament, Potter.’

It was in this context that Hermione found herself in the tail end of an interesting discussion about the culture surrounding accidental magic with the members of the newly named, ‘Founders Club’, just before the start of their next meeting, and for which she had a special surprise for the members.

Sophie idly swung her legs back and forth while sitting on a desk. “But why is it so important? If they can test for magic just by having the child open a chocolate frog package …”

Hermione shrugged. “It’s not so much a, ‘does our child have magic,’ thing as it is a, ‘how powerful might our child be,’ thing. The old families especially are always watching out for powerful bouts of magic or unique talents emerging, like metamorphism, or seership.”

“I guess that makes sense.”

Kevin Entwhistle and Justin Finch-Fletchley nodded.

The door opened and Dean Thomas walked in. “Am I late?”

“No.” Hermione stood up and pulled her shrunk trunk out of her pocket. “You are right on time.” She put the trunk on the floor and un-shrunk it. “But before we start today, there’s something I need to bring up.”

Dean Thomas crossed the room and sat down.

Hermione took a deep breath. “You know we’ve been starting to study occlumency?”

The four members of the Founder’s Club nodded.

“Well, my lord would like to have a word with you about that.”

The four all looked startled.

“You mean, Lord Slytherin?” Justin asked.

“Yes.”

“He’s coming here?” Dean asked incredulously.

Sophie gulped.

“He is here.”

The assembled muggleborns exchanged nervous glances. Justin was already staring at the trunk.

Hermione knocked five times on the trunk lid, the trunk opened and Harry slowly climbed out. He towered over the nervous first years, none of whom took their eyes off him as he turned, conjured a plush armchair in the middle of the room, and sat down. “Good afternoon, children.”

Driven by several months of wizarding culture training, the four hastily got to their feet, scraping chairs and desks as they went, and executed bows and curtsies with varying degrees of success. Even Kevin didn’t do too badly.

Hermione couldn’t help but smile.

“Good afternoon, Lord Slytherin.” They said in almost unison.

Harry’s mask nodded once and turned to her. “Very well behaved group you have here, Hermione.”

Hermione’s smile widened.

Sophie blushed.

Harry turned back. “Please, sit.”

They did.

“So,” Harry began, talking into the silence of five first years dutifully watching an adult. “I’ve been hearing quite a bit about what’s been going on here. To say our world isn’t the best when it comes to transitioning new peoples to our society would be a massive understatement. That is something that I intend to help change—and it’s projects like this,” he made a sweeping hand gesture, “that will help to make that change. I understand you’ve recently begun to work on equalising one of the many advantages that old families have on new ones.”

They looked at him blankly.

“Occlumency,” Harry clarified.

They all made ‘oh’ noises and nodded quickly.

“Normally, learning occlumency takes years, and that’s primarily why children start learning at an early age, often as young as six, however, I have a Slytherin family method to rapidly speed up that teaching time.”

Four pairs of eyes widened. Kevin and Justin glanced at each other with raised eyebrows.

“Normally, this method is restricted to those of Slytherin House, however, I’m experimenting with a slightly altered method, which, while not quite as effective as the original, should still be a lot faster than the traditional method, and, if you’re up for it, I’d like to try out that method with you four. Thoughts?”

Sophie raised a nervous hand.

“Yes, Miss Roper?”

“We’re currently doing meditation exercises, how is this new method different?”

“Questioned like a true Ravenclaw.”

Sophie made a nervous smile.

Harry reached into the pocket of his robe and produced a small stack of parchments. “Do you know what these are?”

All four nodded.

“Those are Gringotts contract parchments.” Justin said.

“Yes,” Harry said, “and on them are confidentiality contracts. If you wish to go ahead and join this program, you’ll have to sign one of these first.”

All four looked at the parchments warily.

Hermione grinned.

“Good.” Harry said. “You are cautious. That’s a trait that should keep you out of a lot of trouble in the future. The contracts are quite simple. Please feel free to read them over.” He handed the stack to Sophie who took one for herself before passing it on. “They say, in short, that you will not speak of or in any way communicate the new occlumency method to anyone, without my written permission, for the next ten years, after which you will be free to do so as you wish.”

“And if we do?” asked Dean.

Harry’s tone remained casual. “Then your name will turn up on my original contract and I will take you to court for theft of noble family secrets.”

Dean grimaced.

“What if we slip up by accident?” Sophie asked meekly.

“The contract contains a compulsion clause. It is possible to break if you really try, but it will stop you from accidentally blurting out the secrets.”

Justin raised his hand again. “How much quicker do you expect this new method to be?”

“I expect you to reach the level of someone like Draco Malfoy in three months … rather than three years.”

Justin’s eyes widened.

Kevin looked between the contract and Harry. “What about Hermione?”

Lord Slytherin’s voice grinned. “Hermione is a demon who has been using the original Slytherin method, continuously, for three years. You will never catch her.”

Hermione felt herself blushing.

Silence settled on the group for a moment.

Justin held up a clenched fist. “Well, I for one, have no desire to be left behind. I’ll join.”

“Me too,” Kevin said.

Sophie hesitated for just a moment before adding. “I’m in too.”

The group turned to look at Dean, who was still looking at the contract with wary eyes. “You know, I’ll probably be skinned alive if my house mates ever find out about this.”

Kevin grinned and thumped him on the back. “Then you’re lucky the contract stops you telling, yeah?”

“The method really works best with equal numbers, Mister Thomas,” Lord Slytherin broke in. “You’d be doing your friends a service, if nothing else.”

Dean looked down at the contract in his hands again. He looked back up. “Oh, alright, I’m in.”

Sophie, Justin, and Kevin cheered and clapped.

Lord Slytherin sat in his chair, only a slight nod showing his feelings.

Hermione just beamed. Phase two, complete.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

A week later, Harry, dressed as Lord Slytherin, appeared outside a beautiful Tudor house in the Suffolk countryside, white walled, wood beamed, clay roofed. It certainly didn’t look like the house of an old dark, pureblood family—if anything, it suggested a more light attitude with the dozens of flowerbeds of every colour leading from the front gate to the door.

Harry pushed his wand into the wards around the building, and magically knocked. It was time to get the first of two charms needed for the Granger’s new toy.

The wards granted him entrance. He walked up to the front door, idly fingering the pair of devices in his pocket. His vassals had really done a wonderful job. He’d tried on one of the ear pieces before leaving and it fitted like a glove. Its range would be short, what with the tiny mirror and similarly tiny runes, but to get around the patent laws and to persuade the two families to grant him their magic … it was worth it. Certainly until Alex arrived next year with the other half of the original.

The door opened and he was greeted by a curtsying dark-skinned lady wearing what were obviously her very best robes. “Lord Slytherin, we welcome you to our humble home.”

“Mrs. Harper,” Harry offered his hand, took hers in his, and knelt down slightly to it, “A pleasure.”

Mrs. Harper smiled brightly. “Please come this way. My husband is in the drawing room.”

Upon arriving at their destination, Harry was pretty sure that the ‘drawing room’ was actually a small dining room. Four indents in the carpet suggested a large table, hastily removed.

“Lord Slytherin.” Mister Peregrine Harper rose from the small sofa and the two men shook hands. “I understand you’re interested in a certain spell of ours?”

They sat, Mrs. Harper settling herself beside her husband.

“Yes,” Harry said. “The mirror hearing spell, and, if possible, I’d like to set up a contract for it.”

Peregrine Harper smiled. “We do have a few contracts open on that spell. Talking mirrors are still quite popular, Merlin himself only knows why though.”

“I’m sure I could make it worth your while.”

“I’m sure you could. Might I ask why you’re interested in the spell though?”

“Something one of my people is working on for an internal project.”

Peregrine flashed a grin. “No, then. No worries. It’s not as though you’d be able to make communication mirrors or anything—what with Lestrange holding the patent rights and rune clusters.”

“Well, quite.”

“And Bell would rather go bankrupt than help a chap out.”

Harry titled his head slightly. “They’re still angry about the whole house thing then?”

Peregrine smirked. “I swear, you repossess one little house and you don’t hear the end of it for the next three hundred years.”

Harry looked around. “It’s a nice house.”

Mrs. Harper beamed.

“So,” Harry continued, “what are your other spell contracts paying for an application?”

“Ah,” Peregrine leaned back slightly, “Straight to price hmm? You know, sometimes I wonder if gold is really the answer to all our world’s problems.”

Behind his mask, Harry raised a single eyebrow. “Oh?”

“Yes, man of my age, getting on in life and all that, young Hobby will be off to Hogwarts next year. Have you seen a picture of our son?”

Harry shook his head and Mrs. Harper handed him a wizarding photo of a vaguely familiar dark-skinned boy with hair so short he was almost bald, trying to look as stoic and dignified as he could while holding a nimbus 2000 broomstick.

Harry had a suspicion he knew where this was going. Everything about the Harpers screamed, ‘social climbers,’ even for a Dark non-noble family. “I’m going to guess the most important thing in life is the future of your family?”

“Exactly, Lord Slytherin. Exactly.” Peregrine made a pointed jabbing motion with his fingers.

“And how can I help with that?”

“You are betrothed to Lord Greengrass’ girl—the troll slaying princess.” Peregrine smiled. “A word from you to Lord Greengrass on behalf of our Hobby …” the man trailed off.

Ah. So this was about Astoria. “The most I can do, in regards to that, is to write you a letter of introduction when Lord Greengrass starts accepting proposals, which I gather won’t be for quite a long time. Until then, it would be up to your boy to not incite my future sister in law’s dislike, because I can guarantee you, the surest way to kill any possibility on that front would be for Astoria to not want it.”

“A letter of introduction would be welcome.”

“And of course, Lord Greengrass would be more likely to entertain proposals from houses who are more closely aligned with him, politically.”

Harry let that hang in the air for a moment.

Peregrine Harper eyed Harry thoughtfully. “Why did you decide to vassal a muggleborn?”

Behind the privacy of his mask, Harry flashed a grin.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Unlike the Harpers, the Bells lived in a tumbledown stone house with a slate roof in the former industrial town of Cokeworth and were famed for resenting their former business partners for it.

Unlike the Harpers, the Bell’s wards were applied directly to the walls of the house, allowing Harry, with two shiny new enchanted earpieces in pocket, to walk right up to the door to knock. He’d sent an owl ahead of him, so they knew he was coming, although, unlike the Harpers, he hadn’t received a reply back.

A suspicious eye poked around the door. “Yes?”

“Mrs. Bell? Lord Slytherin. I—”

The door slammed in his face. The wards bristled with ill intent.

Harry stared at the blank door blankly for a full thirty seconds.

Friendly. He frowned. Maybe more extreme persuasion methods, then? Mister Bell worked as a production line manager for Honeydukes and Mrs. Bell worked part time at Witch Co. A word to Jacob to lean on his buyers to lean on the Bells … ?

He smirked.

Or … maybe …

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Katie Bell left the great hall after dinner, determined to get some practise in before curfew. It sucked that she couldn’t afford a better broom, so she just had to make every practise hour count.

“Miss Bell,” a voice called.

Katie Bell started. She was being addressed by none other than the ice-princess of the Gray, Daphne Greengrass. She composed herself. “Heiress Greengrass—can I help you?”

Daphne Greengrass smiled. “Yes, actually. How would you like to earn some extra pocket money?”

Katie’s ears pricked up, thoughts of replacing her old comet flashing through her mind. “I’m listening.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry climbed into his trunk happily inspecting his two, brand new, miniaturised communication mirrors in earpiece form. Between the miniature Granger milled runes, the charms, the enchantments, and the alchemy, they’d managed to put together a device that allowed two people to talk to each other over distances of up to five-hundred metres. They hadn’t tripped any intellectual property spells and, so long as they kept Katie sweet, they had all the contacts needed to manufacture en masse if needed. Thank Merlin for cash strapped teenage girls.

He landed in his large comfy armchair opposite Hermione and Daphne with a satisfied smile. “We have everything we need.”

The two girls exchanged a glance.

“So,” Daphne started, “how are we going to get past the fidelius around the stone?”

Harry started drawing a diagram in the air between them with his wand. “Here’s a diagram of the location. We have the pipe, which we use to enter the corridor next to the muggle studies defence, leading straight into the potions defence and the fidelius trip wire. Straight after that, we have the final mirror room, which also contains the fidelius charm and the rune stones that maintain it.”

The girls nodded.

“What we need to do is disable those rune stones and plant a set of rune stones of our own, which I will then use to cast my own fidelius charm, thus locking Dumbledore and Voldemort out from the room, and giving us as long as we like to work on cracking the final defence.”

Hermione looked puzzled. “But wouldn’t we forget everything to do with the stone and the room the moment we enter the ward in the potions room ?”

“Yes.” Harry nodded. “And getting around that little problem won’t be easy. But because of the way Dumbledore set this up, not impossible. Because this isn’t an ‘always active’ fidelius charm, we can study the layout of the room before hand using Daphne’s Eye of Kilrogg, and then create written instructions that we follow exactly to disable the stones once the fidelius is tripped.”

Daphne frowned. “But, we wouldn’t have any reason to follow the orders.”

“The fidelius only works to cause you to forget things directly relating to the thing it protects. We should be able to train ourselves to follow written instructions from ourselves or me that we don’t remember writing or being told about and not have that skill overwritten by the charm.”

Hermione sucked in her breath. “That sounds really dangerous. wouldn’t that leave us vulnerable to someone impersonating us and ordering us to do things by simply leaving us a message in our writing?”

“Yes. Which is why we secure each message with a fidelius ID check. You know how we use the fidelius to scan the local area for listeners, by having a non-secret keeper attempt to speak the secret out loud?”

The girls nodded.

“Well, only a secret keeper can write down the secret they hold, so if each of us is made the secret keeper for a separate fidelius charm, we can use it to authenticate any written message from any of us by writing down the secret at the end of the message.”

Hermione nodded slowly. “So, we train ourselves to unquestionably obey messages with a certain code like, ‘step-by-step order,’ or something, along with an authenticated ID.

Daphne tapped on her chair. “Isn’t there a chance the stone fidelius would block knowledge of the code from us?”

Harry nodded. “Yes, there is a chance—that’s why we experiment with it first, and if it is the case, then instead of using a normal code, we use a separate additional fidelius code, instead.”

Daphne’s eyes started to glaze over.

“I suspect the fidelius can’t remove knowledge secured by other fidelius charms. I could be wrong, we’d need to check, but I don’t think it will be necessary.”

“What about that confused feeling you get when you’re inside a fidelius area? It’s like your eyes can’t make sense of what you’re seeing.”

“I blindfold myself so I’m receiving no information about what I’m doing, and, to make sure there is as little fidelius interference as possible, Hermione will obliviate me first.”

“What!” Hermione yelped.

Daphne’s eyes widened.

“One of the theorised weaknesses of the fidelius charm is that the more you know about the area under fidelius, the stronger its power is. Thus, if I want to stand any chance of being able to function while in the area protected by the charm, I need to have as few memories as possible of where I am, and what I’m there for.”

“B-b-but I’ve never done obliviation before!”

“You’ll need to learn. Don’t worry, I can push the needed memories to the front of my mind to make it as easy as possible for a beginner, and with your level of occlumency you should be able to get the basic skill in a few weeks.”

“Harry,” Daphne started, “what about your noble house ring?”

“I’ll need to take it off for the duration of the mission.”

“Ugh, I don’t like that.”

“Me neither, but it’s not for long.”

“How do you follow written instructions if you’ve blindfolded yourself?” Hermione asked.

“That’s what these are for.” Harry brought out the ear pieces. “Daphne will relay written instructions to me from outside the room.”

Hermione still looked worried. “Doesn’t it take you like, twenty minutes to cast the fidelius charm for a very basic space? Dumbledore was there in less than a few minutes last time we tripped the charm.”

Harry nodded. “Before we initiate the fidelius cracking part of the mission, we’ll set up a temporary fidelius of our own in the muggle studies defence room.”

Daphne smirked. “That way Dumbledore can remember where the stone room is, but he can’t remember where the room en route to the stone room is. I like that.” She looked thoughtful for a moment. “We could also do it on a day when Dumbledore has a Wizengamot session to slow him down even more?”

Harry grimaced. “Best not. We’ve done that once already and he thinks he knows that was Lord Slytherin.”

Hermione slumped back in her chair. “This plan is insane.”

Harry half nodded. “Well, the fidelius charm is an insane defence. The only reason we stand even a chance is all down to Dumbledore being just a bit too clever for his own good.”

“Can we get an overview of this plan then?” Daphne asked.

Harry nodded and started waving his wand over the floating glowing diagram between them. “Step one will be to cast a fidelius in the pipe outside the muggle studies defence room. This will be our HQ for the mission and will contain the papers and things we need for the plan.” A little number one appeared in the pipe.

“Step two will be Hermione cracking the muggle studies defence room—that muggle VCR challenge—and opening the door to the next room.” A little number two appeared in the muggle studies room.

“Step three is to fidelius the muggle studies room. Step four is Hermione obliviating me of all knowledge of what we’re doing, and blindfolding me. In step five me and Daphne will enter the potions room under polyjuice, trip the fidelius charm, and Daphne, who will still have on her noble house ring, and who will be guiding me by hand and receiving instructions by Hermione with the ear piece, will answer Statue Snape’s questions under veritaserum, which obviously won’t work on her, but not before she’s checked the liquid for authenticity.” Harry took a breath and glanced at Daphne. “I’ll be sure to teach you that spell.” He continued waving his wand and the diagram continued to update itself. “In step five, Daphne will fit me with the ear piece and return to the pipe to meet up with Hermione, who together will use their written instructions to guide me into the area actually protected by the fidelius charm, through the mirror room, and to each of the rune stones in turn, where I will set up my own rune stones from a bag I’ll be carrying. Then I will redirect the rune stone’s magic to my own rune stones, and, when it is safe, deactivate the fidelius charm. Then Hermione will run to me and help me restore my memories. We’ll use liquid memories siphoned off before hand to help speed up the process. Then I’ll spend the next thirty-ish minutes casting my own fidelius charm—and boom—one secured mirror room. We then get out of there and be back to our dormitories right in time for dinner, or whatever.”

Silence descended on the trio.

Daphne took a deep breath. “We’d better have some really good safeguards in place for if this all goes badly wrong, which it sound like it might, even with practise and training before hand.”

Harry nodded. “I agree. The chance of this actually working, aren’t great. A lot of things could go wrong. We’ll make sure we have emergency outs, but this is our best, and possibly only, chance of grabbing the single most powerful artefact our world knows of.”

Daphne and Hermione’s faces firmed in twin expressions of determination.

Harry clapped his hands. “Right. Let’s get down to some practise and testing.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

- Gringotts Official Communication -

- 20 th February, 1992 -

Lord Slytherin,

You will be pleased to hear that construction of Slytherin Manor is progressing smoothly and is on schedule. The construction jetty has been completed, our contractors are currently unloading the phase one stone, and the top of Gairsay island has been levelled and the earth redistributed.

Our agents are currently sourcing ideal magical plants and are on schedule to be ready to start planting and transplanting with the first leaf of spring.

However, a situation has arisen which I believe you would appreciate being made aware of. The department of magical trade, possibly influenced by external parties, has authorised a ²⁴⁄₇ manned goods inspection post for all goods bound for Gairsay island. Much to my shame, this inspection post is manned not only by humans, but also by Goblins. We have attempted to make inquiries as to where this post is, so as to better foster communication between the ministry representatives and our project managers, but we have been unsuccessful in doing so. I believe the inspection post has been concealed with a fidelius charm, hence my suspicions about external influence.

Because of this development, I am required to remind you that any goods bound for Gairsay island that would not pass ministry inspection should not be included in any shipments. This includes: Cursed items, illegal rune stones, inappropriately charmed muggle items, muggle items not on the cleared list for magical possession, regulated magical creatures, restricted items for which you do not hold the appropriate licences, banned books, sufficiently large quantities of do-not-stockpile items, items for which another house has been granted a use monopoly or, indeed, anything that you would not be happy to become part of official ministry documentation.

May your gold flow and your enemies suffer,

Ragnok Boneslicer, Account Manager, Chief of the Boneslicer Clan.

It was night. Harry was sitting crosslegged on the floor of his Hogsmeade apartment. He put down the letter and frowned.

So, Dumbledore had decided to spy on his manor construction, mmm? That was annoying. The Headmaster hadn’t yet made a move on Harry Potter, but Lord Slytherin, apparently, was fair game. It didn’t feel good having the fidelius charm used against him so much.

He didn’t have anything at the momentthat would cause the inspectors issue, apart from personal items like his cloak, but … when the Grangers were to move over to the island, which he wanted them to do as soon as the wards were up. … Well, the Grangers had enough muggle equipment and runed trinkets to keep the departments of trade and muggle affairs busy for months—not to mention that so much of it was explicitly being used to circumvent intellectual property spells—and a lot of the Granger’s stuff wouldn’t react well to having magic used on it directly. He’d have to have a chat with them about it—come up with some way to smuggle their stuff onto the island when the time came.

Harry turned the letter over on the floor and focused back on the occlumency exercises from the book Hermione had tracked down for him. Never again, he’d vowed. He never again wanted to be that helpless in the face of being trapped. Once was already one time too many. He’d figured his first freak out was because he’d almost been caught. Simple solution to that—don’t get put in those positions. But that had turned out not to be the case. That overwhelming feeling of panic could be triggered by other, far more innocuous things, and that was not acceptable.

He turned in on himself and started to split his consciousness in two, the first step of the treatment.

Hermione was busy learning the basics of obliviation.

Daphne was busy learning to work from instructions under the influence of fidelius magic.

They were on schedule to make an attempt on the mirror room on March 28, exactly one week before the duelling tournament.

The main question still rattling around in Harry’s mind, even as it sunk deeper and deeper into his occlumency induced trance, was, ‘would Dumbledore try anything before then?’

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore watched the Slytherin breakfast table from his large throne at the front of the great hall. Specifically, he watched the fourth goblet from the end, currently in front of one Harry James Potter. As necessary a solution as Azkaban was, it was far less likely to work if one of his rival factions swooped in to support the boy. Framing someone for a crime they didn’t commit was tricky business. After all, the whole point of the law courts was to find out the truth.

For his plan to work, he first had to isolate Harry Potter from the Gray and the Dark—and watching the way Heiress Greengrass had fawned over the boy in the hospital wing, had hopefully given him the key.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The great hall started to fill for breakfast. Harry ate next to Hermione, enjoying the mindless chatter of his sort-of innocent peers, interspersed with the occasional political barb or well veiled insult. This was the Slytherin table, after all. The current topic of conversation was the Slytherin-Hufflepuff quidditch match, which Slytherin had won, but which still put them eighty points behind Gryffindor for the Quidditch Cup.

Despite John’s loss at the Gryffindor-Slytherin match, his twin brother’s performance against the Ravenclaws had more than made up for it, and it was looking less and less likely that Slytherin would win when all was said and done. That would all change next year of course, when Harry’s red headed spitfire took to the skies around Hogwarts. He’d make sure of that, even if he had to beat Flint into the ground and set Alex on the Bloody Baron.

Harry took a sip of his pumpkin juice and froze with the goblet still to his lips. The scent of fresh grass and snow filled his nostrils. Mmmm … so nice. His invisible Head of Slytherin House ring heated up on his finger, ancient magics doing battle with a far inferior foe. He put the goblet down and adopted a good natured look of mild concussion. The trick, of course, was not to act in any way like he knew what he’d just drunk.

Harry’s mind raced. Payoffs and prices. Causes and consequences. Pull, and then, when they’re least expecting it, push.

He pulsed a series of magical signals into his lightning bolt ring and watched momentary looks of concern and worry flash across both Hermione and Daphne’s faces before they returned back to their normal and icy public personas.

Harry put his chin in his hands. And didn’t Daphne look utterly enchanting this morning? The way her silky blonde hair flowed down her shoulders, the way her cute nose twitched slightly when she gave a disapproving sniff, the way her ice-blue eyes sharpened, lance-like, when casually dismissing some sycophantic comment. He let out an exaggerated and very visible sigh. That was young love, after all.

It was such a shame he couldn’t kiss her. Lord Slytherin would get ever so pissed if he did that, wouldn’t he? Oh, yes. Heh. Yes, he certainly would.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Harry?” The twins looked up from their workbench in surprise.

“Hi there,” Harry half descended the stairs of the Twin’s work trunk. “I’m going to need to exercise the map clause of our agreement for the next few hours.”

The twin’s looked at each other. Twin A grabbed the marauder’s map and tossed it to Harry.

Harry elegantly snatched it out of the air. “Thanks. You’ll have it back soon.”

“Sure thing.” The Twin’s bent back over their work bench.

Harry paused at the trunk’s lid. “Oh, and thanks for helping the settlers out with that bit of alchemy. It was really helpful.”

“So long as they can continue doing rune jobs for us.” Without looking around, Twin B idly waved a small sphere of aluminium on which hundreds of tiny runes were engraved. “These things are INSANE!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

From inside Harry’s trunk, safe in the fidelius in the Hogwarts library, Hermione gazed at the marauder’s map. Some two hundred metres away, Harry and Daphne were walking in a loop around the second floor—well within their ear mirror’s range.

“Status?” came Daphne’s voice through the tiny mirror in her ear.

“DD is still circling the third floor on the left hand side. I think … yes—DD has started moving towards the second floor,”

Hermione saw Harry and Daphne stop where they were, half way down their current corridor.

“DD is coming down the stairs. He will turn the corner behind you in ten—good luck—seven, six, five, four—”

“Cutting magic.”

“—three, two, one.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry glanced up the corridor just as Daphne quickly shoved the miniature ear communication mirror into the pocket of her robes.

There was no one there.

“H-Harry,” Daphne bit her lip, standing far too close to him for what would be considered appropriate. “We shouldn’t be doing this.”

“Why not?” Harry gave her an adoring look and pulled her unresisting arm into a nearby empty classroom. “You are just so, so perfect.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore couldn’t believe his luck. Invisible, he carefully walked up to the open classroom door.

“H-Harry.” A breathy voice sounded from inside.

He moved into the classroom and the scene that greeted his eyes could not have been better if he’d planned it, which, in a way, he had.

The Greengrass heiress was sitting on a table, allowing an obviously aggressive Harry Potter to kiss her on the lips. The kisses were hardly more than pecks, sweet and innocent, but the closeness of the two, and the way they had their hands intertwined, made it clear that this was the pre-teen equivalent of what, at an older age, would certainly require certain cautionary potions and charms.

He faded into sight. “Mister Potter! Miss Greengrass!”

The Greengrass Heiress jerked backwards and stared at him in horror. “Headmaster!” She ducked away from the boy, jumped off the table, and straightened her robes.

Harry Potter glared at him.

“What are you doing, Miss Greengrass?”

The look of horror quickly faded to be replaced by that familiar indifferent countenance of the trained occlumens. She cleared her throat. “Ah, Headmaster Dumbledore, I trust I can count on your discretion on what you’ve seen here?”

Harry Potter had sidled back to the Greengrass heiress, trying to put his hand in hers, which she was subtly trying to swat away.

Dumbledore shook a disappointed head. “Miss Greengrass? Surely you must understand the seriousness of what you were doing? You are under contract. As a responsibly adult, I have no choice but to bring this to your father and betrothed.”

The icy look of indifference cracked and a look of fear seeped through. The girl started to breathe harder again. “Please, sir. Please don’t. It was just kissing! My contract doesn’t say anything about that! There isn’t anything—”

Dumbledore continued to shake his head.

“—wrong with it!”

“I’m sorry, Miss Greengrass. If there truly isn’t anything wrong then you won’t be in trouble, but it is expected of me.” He turned to leave. “And you, Mister Potter, I suggest you distance yourself from Miss Greengrass for the foreseeable future.”

Harry glared at him. “I love Daphne!”

Greengrass winced.

“I won’t let anyone have her! No matter what any stupid contract says!”

The Greengrass heiress now looked mortified.

Perfect.

He frowned in disapproval one last time before leading the two out of the room and escorting them back to their common room, after which he immediately locked himself in his office, pulled a silvery strand of memory from his temple, corked it into a vial, and began to write.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Later that day, Hermione, now under the effects of half a dozen potions and transfigurations, marched through Hogwarts like she owned the place, trying to give off just the right amount of righteous anger and rage, occasionally adjusting the mask on her face, and fighting not to blush to high heaven at the thought of what was now weirdly situated between her legs.

She approached the great hall’s huge double doors, almost completely closed except for the small door at the bottom that allowed students in and out for mealtimes, which it now was. Dinner, in fact.

Hermione pulsed a pre-arranged message into her lightning bolt ring and continued to stride forward as though there wasn’t several tonnes of solid oak in her way. Now, boy thoughts. No, male thoughts. Man thoughts! Rage. Rage and fury. Someone was kissing my girl! Rawr!

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry, sitting two chairs down from Daphne at the Slytherin table, felt a pulse on his lightning bolt ring. He reached into the wards and carefully manipulated the magics on the great hall doors.

The huge doors swung open with a loud whoosh of colder castle air, every head turned, and ‘Lord Slytherin’ strode into the hall like an angry god.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John startled the moment Lord Slytherin walked into the great hall. He was here. He was here right now. This was his chance. He stood up, making some excuse to his year mates.

“Daphne! Come with me.” Slytherin’s voice boomed around the hall.

John caught Susan’s eye as he left by the side exit, giving her what he hoped was a meaningful look.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore tried not to smile from the head table.

“My lord?” The Greengrass Heiress said meekly.

“Now!”

Daphne Greengrass rose from her seat.

Lord Slytherin shoved his wand under a trembling Harry Potter’s chin and snarled, “You better not be sitting here when I get back, you little shit,” before sweeping out of the hall with Daphne in tow.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Tracey Davis looked on in horror as Daphne walked out of the hall with as much dignity as she could muster and Harry Potter got up and moved back to the middle of the table. Everyone started whispering to each other. What the hell just happened?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Are you sure about this?” Susan looked worried. The muffled dressing down Greengrass was receiving for whatever it was she’d done could just about be heard through the classroom wall.

John Potter smiled. “Susie, don’t worry about it. I got this.”

“You do know how bad it will be if you’re caught?”

“We need to know!”

Susan bit her lip. “Well then, I hope you really are as good at this as you say you are.”

John flashed her a bright smile. He wouldn’t mess up. He had fate on his side.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione stalked out of the classroom, leaving a visibly distraught Daphne behind her. She felt really bad about all that shouting. She’d been practically cringing herself at the sound her lord’s angry voice and it had been her doing the shouting. She’d have to do something to make it up to her friend later, but not before she extracted every tiny detail from her on what those kisses with Harry had been like. For purely academic reasons of course. For research.

She turned a corner and a much smaller body crashed into hers. Anger flared through her. “You!”

John Potter looked up at her. “Lord Slytherin?”

“Ah.” Damn. Had Harry ever met John as Lord Slytherin? “John Potter.” Her voice immediately took on that cool, calm vibration she’d so often heard her lord use. “For a moment, I thought you were someone else.” Nice save.

John Potter nodded, bowed, and walked off.

Hermione watched him go, frowning. Why did she get the feeling she’d just missed something?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John ducked back into his own empty classroom, a massive grin plastered on his face.

“It worked?” Susan asked with obvious excitement.

John held up several hairs. “Wordless, ‘accio loose hairs,’ with wand up my sleeve. He never felt a thing.”

Susan’s eyed the hairs in awe. “I can’t believe it worked!”

He smirked. “Ready?”

“Wait.” Susan held up her hand. “You’re going to be stuck like that for an hour. We should do it somewhere safe.

Yeah, that was a good point, wasn’t it? See, this is why he had Susan with him. “Down by the lake then? Where we can hide in the trees?”

Susan nodded.

Twenty minutes later, they were in the rapidly failing sunlight hiding behind a thick clump of bushes.

“Well,” John flourished the now colour changed potion containing a single black hair. “Bottoms up.” He drank.

Suddenly everything started to change, but the changes were not what he expected. His hair lengthened, his arms and legs thinned, a faint feeling of something pressed against the inside of his shirt, he even shrank slightly, and, most worryingly of all, everything down there, re-arranged itself, leaving him feeling strangely … missing. Missing and empty.

Susan had her hand over her mouth.

“What happened?” he said and his voice had changed too. It sounded like …

“You turned into Granger, John.”

“What!” He ran out of the tree line to the lake’s edge to gaze into its reflective surface. A brown wavy haired head of hair crowning an angelic face stared back at him. “I am Hermione!” He clutched at his new features. Oh Merlin, this was so weird, but …” His mind caught up with what had happened. “Hermione is Lord Slytherin!”

A sharp sting hit him on the back of the head. “Ow.” He turned to see Susan looking at him with an unamused expression, her wand clutched in her hand. “Stop pissing about, John, and be serious.”

He rubbed the back of his head where the stinging hex had hit and grumbled.

Susan tapped her foot on the slightly damp ground. “Obviously you just picked up Granger’s hair.”

John frowned. “But Hermione has brown hair, the hairs I picked up were black.”

Susan held out her hand and he passed over the small glass bottle in which he’d stored the precious hairs. “They look brown to me.”

“What?” He snatched the jar back and looked again. The hairs did indeed look brown. “That’s weird, I could’ve sworn …”

“Slytherin obviously has a defence against people accioing his hair from his clothes, and the only hairs your spell picked up were Granger’s.”

“But why would Slytherin have Hermione’s hair on his clothes?”

Susan blushed.

“What?”

She looked away. “Nothing.”

John shrugged. “So, that didn’t work out so well then.”

Susan nodded, still not meeting his gaze.

A thought struck him. “But we do now have some of Hermione’s hair. We could always go with plan B if we get the chance.”

Susan finally looked back. “Yes,” she said, slowly, “we could.” She grinned. “Are you going to do that too? You seem to make a good witch—although first, I think I’d need to teach you to curtsey, and how to sit like a lady, and …”

John violently shook his head, causing his long hair to whip him in the face.

Susan giggled.

John grimaced. This was going to be a long hour.

—End of Chapter Twenty-nine—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: Early chapter! Catching up from my previous late ones.

A/N: Harry’s Potter-noble-house-ring. Harry has yet to summon/claim his House Potter noble ring. Obviously, being muggle raised, he should have never learned how to, which is the only reason why Dumbles even tries the trick with amortentia.

A/N: Next chapter: Attempt on the Mirror Room and the Tournament. Only three chapters left till the end of season two! After that we’ll be taking a six month break while I work on other things. The upload schedule for the final three chapters is up in the air. I want to post the next two chapters on the next back-to-back Sundays with the final chapter having the usual two week period, but we’ll see.

Securing the Area …

Hogwarts castle holds many secrets. Some secrets are open to all who care to listen, told to first year students the moment they walk through the doors. Other secrets are hidden by layer upon layer of enchantment, illusion, and age old runes, buried so deep in the very stone work that none but the most learned or lucky ever find them. But by far the largest number of secrets are protected only by the will of the minds that hold them—secrets of forbidden trysts in broom cupboards, of broken promises and unspoken favour swapping—a web of lies and deceit expertly woven in the playpen of future magical leaders, cunning, byzantine, and alwaystotally innocent of all charges, no really, it wasn’t me professor, it was him.

Compared to the actual leaders of the magical world though …

Albus Dumbledore crept through a row of books, soundless and invisible. His target sat alone and soon he would have what he needed. Framing someone for a crime they didn’t commit wasn’t easy, unless, of course, you controlled the defence—then it was no more difficult than a hair, a polyjuice, and a well placed illegal dark curse.

Harry Potter was reading in a library chair, taking about as much notice of the world around him as a nail in a block of wood.

Dumbledore raised his wand and thought, ‘accio loose hairs.’ Nothing happened. No loose hairs zoomed towards him. He frowned.

Harry Potter carelessly scratched his nose and shifted so his legs hung over the chair’s armrest, the book now held high over his face.

Dumbledore turned and headed back the way he came. Well, okay then, maybe not quite as easy as that.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Dumbles just tried to sweep me for hairs.” Harry climbed into his trunk and shut the lid behind him.

Daphne and Hermione looked up from their own books on their couch and frowned.

“He didn’t get any did he?” Daphne asked.

“No, of course not.”

“Good.” Hermione carefully put a bookmark in where she’d been reading and placed the book on the table in front of her. “I hate to think what he’d try if he had.”

Harry landed in the armchair opposite the girls. “I have thought about it.”

“And?” Daphne asked, copying Hermione and giving Harry her full attention.

“Could be for a love potion, possibly on one of the non-noble Dark witches keyed to me—you know—try the same trick that he thinks worked with you, Daph, to make sure the Dark also distance themselves from me like he thinks the Gray have.”

Daphne nodded.

“Could also be a straight up frame attempt with polyjuice.”

Daphne frowned. “But framing someone with polyjuice is almost impossible. That’s what the polyjuice defence is for.”

“Yes, but it’s easy if you control the defence.”

“I’m sorry.” Hermione raised her hand. “What is the polyjuice defence?”

“Oh.” Harry turned to her. “It’s a legal defence. Because polyjuice isn’t illegal and is readily accessible for the right price, it’s impossible to convict someone of a crime with eye-witness testimony alone, unless you can catch the person red handed and then hold them under surveillance for an hour to make sure they’re not under polyjuice.”

“Because otherwise the person who committed the crime could just have been pretending to be the defendant using polyjuice.” Hermione nodded in understanding.

“Exactly.”

“But what was that about Dumbledore controlling the defence?”

“Last time around, when they convicted me of Ginny’s murder, guess who was my defence lawyer?”

Hermione’s jaw dropped. “No way! Dumbledore?”

“Yep.”

“That’s hardly fair.”

Daphne shrugged. “The defence of a minor would have been appointed by the minor’s lord if he was noble. We don’t know Lord Potter’s motivation, but apparently he saw no problem with it.”

Hermione folded her arms. “Well, Dumbledore didn’t get any of your hairs, so it shouldn’t matter, right?”

Harry chuckled. “Oh, if only. This shows that there’s a good chance he maybe plotting something similar to the end of the second year in the second timeline.”

Hermione’s frown turned worried. “So what do we do?”

“We let him overextend himself. He thinks the Gray has distanced itself from Harry Potter when it hasn’t. This could be a perfect opportunity to strike a powerful blow. After all, we’ll have no more use for him here once we have the stone.”

“You mean let him frame you?” Hermione worried her lip. “But Harry, what about … you know …” she looked towards the book on mind healing open on Harry’s desk.

Harry let out a long sigh. “I’ll just have to focus all my free effort on getting that under control as quickly as possible. I can’t let that continue to be an issue.”

Daphne drummed her fingers on the chair rest. “Even then, it’s not like we should be happily running around clueless. It will massively help our cause if we know what he’s planning to frame you for, if he even is.”

“Yes, it’s a shame we can’t use Eye of Kilrogg on him, or anyone with magic sensing for that matter. We’ll just have to keep our normal eyes and ears open.”

The girls nodded.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Malfoy Manor, currently the largest and newest manor of the three powers of Magical Britain, could never be said to be understated. White and pillared, it looked more like Versailles than Kensington Palace. Once a year, it played host to the Malfoy Yule Ball, the premier event of the social calendar, even for those who didn’t buy into the Malfoy’s more divisive political views. Light, Gray, or Dark, they would all be greeted graciously by Lord and Lady Malfoy, although sometimes the smiles guests received were rather fixed. It was, after all, rather embarrassing to be hosting as guests, people who you’d been doing your level best to murder when you were younger.

Fixed didn’t even begin to describe the rictuses now on Lord and Lady Malfoy’s faces as Lord Slytherin glided up the steps to the front door, which was interesting. Harry had brief dealings with Malfoy in the past three years, but never before had, ‘barely contained dread,’ ever entered his mind to describe a Malfoy smile.

The Lord and Lady greeted him and led him to the drawing room, all the while throwing him occasional hasty glances and reassuring smiles, although who they thought they were reassuring was anyone’s guess.

“Drink, Lord Slytherin?” Lord Malfoy asked when they arrived.

“Ogden’s 59, if you have it.”

“O-Of course.” Lord Malfoy picked up the bottle and Harry couldn’t help noticing the man’s knuckles whitening around the bottle. “So,” he started once he’d poured Harry a glass and sat down beside his wife, “what can this humble wizard do for you?”

“I’m planning on taking my place on the Hogwarts board soon and I wanted to discuss some key issues I intend to bring up.”

“And you would talk with me? Rather than your Lord Greengrass?”

“One of those issues requires a … shall we say, more united front, than the usual trivialities of whether to upgrade the school brooms.”

Malfoy hesitated with his glass halfway to his lips. “Oh?”

“Dumbledore.”

Narcissa breathed in sharply. “Y-You intend to go after Dumbledore?”

“I feel that the time may be coming where he could better utilise his many talents somewhere else.”

Lucius and Narcissa shared a meaningful look.

“And how do you plan to accomplish this?” Lord Malfoy asked. “Dumbledore’s supporters hold the power on the board—not even the Dark and your Gray together would be able to remove him.”

Harry made a nonchalant hand gesture. “Dumbledore might soon be having some problems.”

“Really?” Interest pierced through Malfoy’s otherwise cautious eyes. “I haven’t heard any issues coming up.”

“That’s because they don’t exist yet.” Harry took a sip from his glass. “Mm, on that note, there is one thing I’d appreciate your assistance with.”

Malfoy slightly inclined his head.

“Harry Potter.”

Narcissa sucked in her breath through her teeth. “The little boy who couldn’t keep his hands to himself?”

“The very same. I’d like him isolated for the next month.”

“Just isolated? Just the next month? Seems rather lenient.”

“Ah, well, I believe Dumbledore,“—he spat the name—“would say that the greatest power in the world is love.”

Silence.

Then Narcissa gasped. “Love potion? But, he is noble.”

“And was never taught how to call his ring.”

“Then why the isolation?”

Malfoy’s eyes sharpened. “This has something to do with Dumbledore’s problems.”

Harry idly swirled his drink in his glass and smiled behind his mask. “Perhaps. Either way, I hope I can count on your support on this?”

Lucius and Narcissa exchanged another look. Then they both turned back and nodded.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ten minutes later, Harry walked to the edge of the Malfoy wards, crossed over, and chain apparated back to his Hogsmeade apartment. The meeting with Lord Malfoy had gone well—amazingly well, in fact. Harry had been expecting to fight with the man on an upcoming Dark focused Wizengamot bill or two, maybe make some well chosen concessions in return for Harry’s requests, but no, Malfoy had practically rolled over like a dog before his master. The way Malfoy reacted when Harry had asked for that particular Ogden’s vintage was telling. It had been Tommy boy’s favourite, after all. If Malfoy had gotten it into his head that Lord Slytherin was Voldemort … well, it would certainly make his life easier in the next few weeks.

He conjured his favourite armchair and sat down. Right now however, he had an empty time slot available to deal with something that had been demanding his attention for the last few days.

“Elf!”

A young naked house elf popped into the space in front of Harry, vibrating with enthusiasm, bowing so low his long nose touched the floor. “Master, your elf is at your service.”

“Good. I’ve thought long about what you will be called and have decided. From now on, your name shall be Plato.”

The elf looked up from the floor with eyes as large as bright as lightbulbs. “Oh, thank you, Master. Plato will do his best to serve his Master, Master.”

Harry nodded. “Let’s set down some rules, okay?”

The newly named Plato nodded his head up and down, still bowed to the floor.

“Rule one—you need only bow to me once upon being called, then you will stand at rest.”

Plato instantly straightened.

“Rule two—when I am wearing this mask, you must call me either, ‘Master,’ or, ‘Lord Slytherin,’ never anything else, understand?”

Plato nodded. “Understood, Master Lord Slytherin.”

“Rule three,” Harry took off his mask, drank an ageing potion antidote, and un-transfigured his face. “When I am like this you must call me either, ‘Harry Potter,’ or, ‘Mister Potter,’ never anything else, understood?”

Plato regarded him with wide-eyes. “Master is young Master.”

“Do you understand, Plato?” Harry demanded, his voice turning firmer.

Plato quickly nodded. “Plato understands, Mister Potter”

“Good.” Harry put the mask back on. “Shall we move on?”

“As Master Lord Slytherin wishes, Master Lord Slytherin.”

“Rule four—as a member of the Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin, you must always comport yourself with the dignity and bearing of the house. Do you understand?”

Plato stood a bit taller, completely unashamed by his nakedness. “Plato understands, Master.”

“Rule five—you are never to speak the secrets of the Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin to anyone who is not of the House, under threat of clothes, understood?”

A twinge of fear entered Plato’s eyes. “Plato understands, Master.”

“Rule six builds on rule four—you will attire yourself as I expect—and what I expect is plain emerald green robes with the crest of Slytherin House on the arms, do you understand?”

Plato’s eyes widened. “Master, house elves is not to be wearing—”

“—You are not just any house elf, Plato, you are my house elf. When people see you, they will be seeing me—my house—my family, do you wish to shame me by showing people a member of Slytherin House wearing rags?”

Plato’s lip trembled.

Harry shook his head. “The robes you wear will remain the property of Slytherin House. You will not own them, merely take care of them, keep them clean and well maintained, is that a fair compromise?”

Plato’s lip stopped trembling. He seemed to think for a moment. Then he nodded. “Plato understands, Master. Plato will wear Master’s clothes and keep them in perfect condition.”

“Excellent. Raise your right hand.”

Plato raised his right hand, and Harry waved his wand over it. A ring appeared on Plato’s finger. Plato stared at it in awe.

“This is a servant ring. It grants you limited access to the Slytherin Gringotts vault and acts as identification when doing business on my behalf. I will be spending most of my time in Hogwarts, where, unfortunately, you will not be able to directly serve me, at least not for the moment.”

Plato’s awe quickly vanished. His head drooped and his ears sank down flat against his face.

“It’s something I’m working on it. While I’m there, you will stay with my vassals, the House of Granger, but let’s go over what else we need to do.”

Plato shook away his disappointment and stood back to attention. “Yes, Master Lord Slytherin. Plato will always serve you, Master. Even when Master is away.”

Harry smiled. Merlin, house elves were awesome.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Draco sat at breakfast and read his owl from home.

Dear Draco,

We hope this owl finds you well and that you are proceeding satisfactorily with your studies. I look forward to seeing your outstanding results at the end of the school year.

Draco looked uneasily over at where Greengrass and Granger sat at the opposite end of the table. He’d be feeling a lot more comfortable if Anthony Goldstein from Ravenclaw, a friend of the family, hadn’t told him that he currently sat in twelfth place overall in the year, according to the Ravenclaw academic tables in the Ravenclaw common room. He cast his eyes back down to the owl.

A matter has come up which requires your action. For the good of the Dark and the Noble House of Malfoy, Harry Potter must be isolated from us and all our allies for the next four weeks. I trust you will be able to accomplish this. It is very important.

Love,

Father and Mother

Draco’s eyes widened. Really? But it was almost the duelling tournament. This was the moment when being seen to have Potter on their side would be most beneficial. He’d actually quite enjoyed having the super powerful boy in his circle for the last week, but. … He traced the signature at the end of the owl with his finger. … If father demanded it, then it had to be done.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Good help is hard to find. Sometimes though, good help isn’t what a wizard is looking for.

Dumbledore sat in the small throne behind his desk in the Headmaster’s office. His many trinkets biped and bobbed and occasionally one would let out a little hiss of steam or plop of dripping water.

The door opened and a seventh-year Hufflepuff witch stepped through. She looked nervous. Her hair was short and bubblegum pink.

“Ah, Miss Tonks,” Dumbledore smiled a grandfatherly smile. “Please sit down and don’t mind the mess.”

“Ah, thank you, Headmaster.” Tonks sat down in the chair offered. Her eyes quickly darted around the room before focusing on the Headmaster again. “I’m not in trouble, am I? This isn’t about the duelling club, is it? Because I swear I didn’t mean to hex Catherine quite that badly during practise.”

Dumbledore waved his hand jovially. “No, not at all Miss Tonks. Not at all. I actually wanted to talk about your immediate plans after your NEWTS. I understand you plan to join the auror training program after graduation.”

Tonks nodded.

“Are you aware that in the last war, I led a … shall we say, resistance force, against Voldemort?”

Tonks flinched before answering. “It was always rumoured, sir, but no one knew for sure.”

“You know why I formed that organisation?”

“To fight you-know-who.”

“Yes, but why did I need to? Why weren’t the aurors able to?”

“Uh.” Tonks hesitated. “Because of the Dark in the Wizengamot?”

Dumbledore slightly inclined his head. “I need to ask you a question, Miss Tonks. If another war happened like the last one, terrible though that would be, would you stay to your command in the aurors, doing nothing to protect the people who cannot defend themselves, or would you do the hard and dangerous thing, and work behind the backs of your superiors and colleagues, knowing that if you’re caught it could mean your job at best and your life at worst?”

Tonks swallowed. “I … I like to think I would, yes.”

“Even if it meant breaking the law?”

Tonks hesitated again, before straightening. Her eyes firmed. “If the law no longer protects the innocent then it is no law at all.”

Dumbledore leaned in closer and looked at Tonks’ over his moon shaped glasses. “What if you had to do things that were not only illegal, but were also immoral? What if the only way to save many innocents was to cause the death of one innocent?”

Tonks’ hair shifted from pink to white. “I don’t know. Surely there would be some way to save them all.”

Dumbledore slowly shook his head. “War does not always allow us that luxury, I’m afraid. That is the terrible responsibility that is placed on those who fight the darkness.”

Tonks sat in her chair. She stared at the window in thought for a long while. Her hair shifted from white, to yellow, to red, and back to pink again. “No, sir.”

Dumbledore raised a single bushy eyebrow.

“Miss Tonks?”

“I don’t accept that, sir. I suppose there might be situations where things go wrong, but I believe you should always fight to do the right thing for everyone equally.”

Dumbledore regarded the stone faced young metamorph in front of him for a few long seconds before smiling widely and letting out a laugh belly laugh. “Well spoken, Miss Tonks.”

Tonks’ stern face became confused. “Sir?”

“That is exactly the attitude of a fine auror—one that Magical Britain can be proud to have defending its citizens.” He leaned over the table. “Remember that attitude, Miss Tonks. And never forget it. “

Tonks’ confused look broke into a wide smile. “Ah, yes, Headmaster.”

Dumbledore settled himself back in his chair. “Mmm … as it happens, a friend of mine is looking to get into auror prep after retiring from the department. If you feel ready, I could forward your name to him to work with you over the summer break to help prepare you. Auror training is not for the faint of heart and you will need every advantage you can get.”

Tonks’ eye’s lit up. “Yes, I’d very much like that, thank you.”

“Now, I’ll let you get back to what you were doing. I’m sure you’ll help bring Hufflepuff the duelling cup this year.”

Tonks grinned. “I plan to!” She stood up, turned around, and exited, leaving the Headmaster alone in the room.

Dumbledore stared at the now closed door.

… Damn.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

It was during one of the mission preparation sessions that Harry and the girls now spent every free moment of their time in, that it happened.

Every single foot placement, every hand movement, every spell—Harry, Hermione, and Daphne had mapped out and written down every step needed to deactivate the fidelius once they’d tripped it.

On the outskirts of the forbidden forest, they’d set up fidelius charm after fidelius charm, always with Daphne as the secret keeper, continually experimenting with how Harry and Hermione reacted to different instructions, both inside and outside the charms.

Harry had spent days learning how to measure his footsteps and hand movements, all to a set of standard measurements, even while blindfolded.

Hermione had learned both how to overcome the weirdness of suddenly being faced by a list of instructions with no memory of how it came to be, and to quickly persuade a similarly confused Harry to follow her instructions.

But despite their best efforts, they still found guiding Harry, footstep by footstep, through a test maze they couldn’t remember, and which Harry couldn’t see, to be hard going.

That was when Daphne had the idea that since Harry could sense magic, he could follow a trail left behind by her invisible Eye of Kilrogg. That way Daphne could be the one to follow the pre-written instructions, and since moving the eye only required magical intent, rather than physical limb placement, it would be much easier to control to exact location of the eye.

Of course, this now meant that Daphne too had to learn to follow pre-written instruction under the influence of fidelius. So, she’d summoned her eye of Kilrogg, placed it in the middle of the area to be placed under fidelius, and waited for Harry to finish the charm and place the role of secret keeper with Hermione.

Harry did so.

And Daphne could still remember.

Hermione frowned as she turned to her.

“Hermione.”

Hermione didn’t say anything, just continued to observe her behaviour.

“I remember.”

“What?”

“I remember. The fidelius didn’t work on me.”

Hermione’s eyes widened in shock.

Harry was still busy reading his parchment, looking confused and weary, just as he always did when the fidelius had just wiped his memory of where he was standing.

Hermione looked around frantically. Her voice dropped to a fierce whisper. “That’s impossible!”

“It happened. I think it was my Eye of Kilrogg. It was in the area before the fidelius activated.”

Hermione quickly told Harry the fidelius secret and together she and Daphne told Harry what had happened.

Daphne thought Harry couldn’t decide whether to be excited or alarmed. Eventually he drew his wand and pointed it at the sky. “This doesn’t leave us,” he firmly stated. “We have accidentally discovered a weakness in the fidelius charm. We use that charm for so many things. If anyone found out that it was possible to negate the charm if you can somehow get an Eye of Kilrogg into the charm space, we’d lose so much of our tactical advantage it isn’t even funny. From this moment on, I declare this to be a Slytherin family secret.”

Hermione and Daphne nodded, slightly wide eyed, feeling the compulsion magic slowly settle on them like a flurry of light snow.

Harry lowered his wand. “Having said that, if Daphne can get into the charm space while the fidelius is active, and still keep her head, then the chances of this ridiculous plan actually working just shot up massively.” Harry grinned.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore sat, once more, behind his office desk. Getting the metamorph on his side would have been perfect for his plans, but it seemed it wasn’t to be. No matter. He had a feeling his backup plan would be far more willing.

The door opened.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John walked into the Headmaster’s office and sat down in the chair opposite the wise old man. “You asked for me, Headmaster?”

“Yes, John.” Dumbledore sighed. “I feel I owe you an apology.”

An apology? John’s eyebrows rose and clearly his surprise showed on his face.

“Yes, an apology—for not listening to your counsel at the start of the year. It would seem that in my old age, I’ve become far too sure of myself.”

“Counsel?” John racked his brains but the only time he could think of talking with the old man had been. …

“When you advised me about your brother’s behaviour. Recent events have forced me to reconsider my original stance. You no doubt heard about the explosion on the second floor? It was caused by your brother. He is, in fact, far more dangerous than I had originally feared, and his raw power unquestionably matches your own unusually high levels. He is just like you—twins in every way, it would seem.”

John’s eyes widened. How was that possible? Yes, he’d heard rumours of his brother doing powerful magic, and there had been that bragging from Malfoy, but Malfoy was always bragging, wasn’t he? But if Harry really did match him in power. … He was only that powerful because he’d come from the future … which meant … John’s heart started to race.

“Although we’ve no way to prove it, I also believe that the explosion at the Burrow last year was indeed Harry. The similarity to the incident on the second floor are just too many.”

He knew it! Ginny. His Ginny. John clenched his fists together.

“I’m sorry, John.”

“Headmaster.” John steeled himself and stared straight into Dumbledore’s eyes. “We have to do something!”

“Mmmmm. …” Dumbledore stroked his beard. “I fear your parents would not listen to me though, nor to you. What would you suggest?”

John hesitated. What would he suggest? He’d wait till next year, let the chamber of secrets open, and put his brother back where he belonged, back in Azkaban. Suddenly, images of Ginny cuddling into Harry’s arms flashed across his mind. His eye twitched. But if he waited then Harry could corrupt Ginny even more. He might lose Ginny forever, and, even worse, the timeline could become changed beyond recognition. If Harry was from the future, he might try to stop the chamber incident from happening to keep himself from being put in Azkaban. Harry could even realise what the diary was and take it away from Ginny!

John took a cautious breath. “Azkaban?” For a moment, John thought he saw a look of triumph shoot through the Headmaster’s eyes, but a split second later he was sure he’d imagined it.

Dumbledore frowned sadly, looking every year his old age. “John. Azkaban is a very serious recourse.”

“Yes, but …” John scrabbled in his mind for good reasons. “But, if Harry is as dangerous as you say, isn’t it critical that he’s somewhere he can’t become another Voldemort?”

The headmaster slowly nodded, as though thinking it over. “Yes. It is. And it might not be impossible.” The headmaster looked over his desk at him. “But it would require your help, a lot of planning, and total secrecy.”

John eagerly nodded. Anything to sort out this mess. He’d get Harry back in Azkaban and everything would be back to how it was supposed to be. His eyes sharpened. But not before forcing the truth out of his evil twin, right after he got out of here.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry felt a respectable aura of rage moving towards him. He looked up from the book he was reading in the library, and raised an eyebrow.

John was storming towards him, a look of intense anger on his face.

This should be interesting.

“You!” John shouted, the moment he got in range, causing several dozen students to look up sharply from their books.

“Mister Potter!” Madam Pince shrieked. “Volume! Get out! Now!”

John ignored her and made to grab Harry’s arm, which he shoved off.

John glared at him. “We need to talk, now!”

Harry looked up at the wide eyed crowd watching. He shrugged, packed up his books, and followed his fuming twin out of the library, Madam Pince admonishing them both all the way. As soon as they were alone in an empty classroom John turned around and glared at him, again. “You came back with me!”

“What?”

“You came back with me! Don’t try to deny it. At the end of the tournament, something happened and you came back!”

Harry’s eyes widened in disbelief. Not even a privacy charm. His eyes darted around the classroom. Now, the question was did he cast a privacy charm himself, go along with his brother’s accusation, and finally drop the chummy brother act, which would have certainly happened after John got his ass handed to him at the duelling tournament anyway, or did he just continue to deny everything for the time being?

“How did you time trav—”

Okay, the first option. Harry shoved his hand over John’s mouth, whipped out his wand and cast a privacy charm while John shoved his hand away and flicked a wand into his face, which Harry then smacked away, leaving them both a few feet apart from each other, and not currently pointing any wands.

John looked at Harry’s wand in shock. “What was that?”

Harry glared at him. “A privacy charm, idiot. You do realise that long term time travel is illegal, right? Like, lock-you-up-and-dissect-you-in-the-department-of-mysteries illegal? It’s not the sort of thing you just go around talking about in empty classrooms! Please tell me you haven’t told anyone else.”

John ignored him and glared right back. “How did you come back?”

“I don’t know,” Harry snarled. “One day I was happily minding my own business, letting demons from hell rip all good feelings from my head—you know, the usual—and next I’m sitting back in the cupboard under the fucking stairs!”

“What cupboard?”

Harry ignored him in turn. “And then I was like, ‘oh wow, I’m back in time. Maybe this time I can make it through second year without being framed for letting a bloody great snake out on the school.’ He glared at John.

John glared back. “Ginny is mine.”

“I think you’ll find, that Ginny is hers. Time-travel.”

John’s glare became momentarily confused. “What?”

Harry smiled a smile of zero warmth. “Just a bit of insurance. I know memories can’t be used as evidence in criminal cases, but you can’t be too careful. Considering the penalties we’d incur if what happened to us became public, I’m pretty sure neither of us want this conversation shared with anyone else, mmm?”

John didn’t say anything for a few moments.

“Nothing else?”

“Who is Lord Slytherin?”

Harry frowned. “The hell if I know.”

“You don’t?”

“Of course, I don’t! Why would I? You think I’m chummy with him, do you? When he’s in the habit of sticking his wand under my chin and threatening me in front of the whole school?”

“But … but something must have happened to change the timeline. He wasn’t here last time around.”

Harry rolled his eyes. “You’ll understand it if I don’t have a great memory for the ins and outs of the wizarding world’s social circles from last time around. Maybe someone else came back with us too?”

John groaned.

“How did you come back anyway?” Harry asked. “Whatever it was must have pulled me along as well.”

John stiffened. “I’m not telling you.” He sneered and waved his wand in Harry’s general direction. “You won’t get away with this.”

Oh, he did not just say that. Harry looked at John with half-lidded eyes. “And what exactly am I supposed to be getting away with? Not being sent to Azkaban for a crime I didn’t commit?”

“You’re changing the timeline!”

“And that’s bad, how?”

“Huh?”

“I said, ‘why is that a bad thing?’ ”

John narrowed his eyes. “I’m not telling you anything. You’d probably help him.”

Harry shrugged. “Well, until you’ve got something more useful to talk with me about, I suggest you keep yourself to yourself.”

John walked his way towards the door, but before he opened it, he turned back, fixing Harry with a nasty smile. “You’ll see. I’ll do what needs to be done and show everyone that they were right about me—and that you don’t deserve anything.” John opened the door, steeped through it, and slammed it behind him.

Harry stared at the door for a moment. Wow. Then he cast a tempus and grinned. Oops, almost time for him to take his place on the Hogwarts Board—that was a something more than anything, wasn’t it?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Thirty minutes later, Lord Slytherin walked into the Hogwarts grand meeting room and surveyed the inhabitants.

There was Lord Malfoy and Lord Parkinson who made up the small Dark faction on the board. There was Lord Woodcroft—the man who owned his Hogsmeade apartment—talking to Lord Jacob Greengrass, the two of them together making up the Gray contingent. And finally, the Light—Lords Hawking, Smith, Blott, Fowley, Black, and Potter, along with the only non noble present, Ambrosius Flume, who acted as chairman. Despite being allowed to sit as a silent witness, Dumbledore was surprisingly not present.

The inhabitants turned from their own private conversations, some standing, some sitting, and briefly regarded him with varying degrees of wariness. Jacob waved and grinned.

Ambrosius Flume cleared his throat. “Well, now that we are all here, perhaps we should get down to business?”

Harry took a seat in between Jacob and Woodcroft, directly opposite his father who was staring at him with a look of deep suspicion.

“Right,” Flume started, “minutes of the previous meeting—”

“Ah, one moment, Mister Chairman.” Lord Potter put a finger up. “A point of protocol. I think we’d all be interested to hear our newest member’s opinion on the proper protocol for board members to be on school grounds when a meeting is not in session.”

Harry inclined his head. “A house matter, Lord Potter. Perfectly within the rights of a Lord of the Wizengamot.”

“Shoving your wand in my son’s face is your house matter, how?”

“The boy was attacking my betrothed. I was merely administering a verbal warning.”

“You come to me if you wish to communicate a warning. Harry is my son, not yours.”

Harry couldn’t help a note of annoyance slip into his voice. “Oh, really? And when was the last time you communicated with the little squib exactly? Ten years ago?”

James Potter opened his mouth angrily to retort, but was cut off by Flume.

“—I think that this has moved far enough from a mere point of protocol now, thank you, my lords.” Flume’s voice was firm and both Harry and Lord Potter quietened. “Now, as I was saying, minutes of the previous meeting …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John was still angry half an hour after confronting his brother, but that anger quickly left when he eventually ran into Susan who was practically vibrating with purpose.

“John, Granger is in Healer training.”

John hesitated. “So?”

“I saw Greengrass out near the lake with Davis, but then Davis left and now it’s just Greengrass.”

John suddenly realised what Susan was getting at. “You think we should do it now?” They’d been waiting for an opportunity to talk with Greengrass disguised as Hermione for days.

“Yes!” Susan whispered, eyes bright. “It’s perfect! Do you have the hairs on you?”

“Sure, they’re here.” John took out the small jar from his pocket.

“Right. Give me a few moments.” Susan took the jar and started fiddling with it. “Can you transfigure the crest on my robes into the Slytherin one?”

John frowned. “I thought I was going to do this?”

Susan gave him what he thought to be an unneeded patronising look, all the more irksome because of the cuteness of the face on which it was displayed. “John, you didn’t really think that you’d be able to pass for a Slytherin Princess, did you?”

John hesitated. That sounded like the kind of question that had no winning answer.

“C’mon boy-who-lived,” Susan smiled. “Chop chop.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry gazed around the room, his brain doing political calculus while Flume brought up the fascinating question of whether Charity Burbage should have her request for an updating of the muggle studies curriculum approved or, as was more likely, rejected. Over half the board members might be light, but they were still a mostly old and stodgy lot.

With the addition of Lord Slytherin there were now three Gray members, two Dark, and six Light, making eleven members, not including the chairman, who acted as casting vote in the event of any ties.

If Harry wanted to have any chance of swinging the board to his favour he needed to get at least one of the light members to switch sides on the eventual matter of Dumbledore.

His father was, of course, totally out. Lord Black, who looked bored out of his mind, was about as likely to split off from Dumbledore as Alexandra was to declare herself a lover of frilly pink dresses.

Lord Fowley was one-half of Wizarding Britain’s ministry enforced oligopoly on food trade with the muggle world, which might have been promising, if the other half hadn’t been the Greengrasses, making Lord Fowley entering a political alliance with the Gray highly unlikely—unless the man wanted the department of magical trade investigating them both for possible charges of breaking their charters.

Lord Blott was a possibility, but would have to have a very good reason to vote anti-dumbledore. The Noble House of Blott was one of the largest winners in the ministry’s long term effort to control the supply of information on magic spells and practises. There was a good reason why everyone bought their books at Flourish and Blotts, after all.

Lord Hawking was the undisputed king of space charms. His house had a stranglehold on the supply of trunks, tents, and all kinds of space expanded items, from pouches to ministry cars. If you wanted something to be bigger on the inside than on the outside, you had to go to a Hawking, something that wizards of other countries tended to resent. The Hawkings had been the subject of more foreign familicide attempts than any other in Wizarding Britain.

Finally, if you didn’t count Flume, there was Lord Smith, who sat in his chair like a retired warhorse, massive and armoured, with a moustache to rival Uncle Vernon’s. The armour was steel and concealed under his robes in a way that somehow drew even more attention to it. A large war hammer was propped up on the wall behind him. Lord Smith had three children, all married, one daughter and two sons. The sons had children of their own, two of whom were in Harry’s year—Zacharias Smith, and Sally Smith, both in Hufflepuff.

It was Lord Smith that Harry had his eye on as the man to sway. The Lord’s oldest son had already given his allegiance to the Gray, which must make for some interesting family gatherings. Lord Smith himself was known to be a heavily pragmatic man, and the Light were squeaking that he was going to be the next to jump ship, something the younger son, who was a fierce Dumbledore supporter, was supposedly desperate to prevent.

“All those in favour of Professor Burbage’s proposal for a reworked muggle studies curriculum?” Flume asked.

Harry raised his hand. So did Lords Black, Greengrass, Woodcroft, and Potter. All the Gray and two of the Light. His father raised an eyebrow at him. Harry nodded his head slightly. Hey, only one off … not bad.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Polyjuiced Susan walked out of the castle and out across the grounds, all the while trying to think like Granger, trying to copy that same purposeful yet graceful movement Granger had, as though the ground were made of the upturned faces of those she barely tolerated.

Susan sort-of glided out towards the lake and saw her quarry levitating blobs of water. She’d been watching how Granger and Greengrass interacted when they thought no one was watching, and she thought she’d be able to imitate the style quite well.

She moved towards her. “Daphne.”

Greengrass raised her head from where she’d been concentrating. “Hermione? I thought you had Healer lessons?”

“Madam Pomfrey cancelled them, something about an emergency at St. Mungo’s.”

“Oh. Well, I’m going to continue draining myself for a little while more. Want to join in for a bit?”

“Ah,” Susan hesitated, but it didn’t look too hard. “Sure.”

Greengrass nodded. “Our lord should be done soon, I think he wants a word with us after the board meeting.”

Susan suppressed a swallow. Meeting Lord Slytherin while polyjuiced as Hermione was not in her immediate plans. “Oh? Any idea what about?” She started to levitate a blob of water about the same size as the Greengrass heiress.’

Daphne looked around briefly and opened her mouth as though to say something, but no words came out. Instead she choked.

Susan had just enough time to raise a concerned eyebrow before Greengrass’ water blob fell into the lake with a splosh and the next thing she knew, Greengrass had her wand pointed straight at her.

Susan’s eyes widened, still with her wand pointed at the lake, her water blob still floating.

“Who are you?” Greengrass demanded.

A bead of sweat formed on Susan’s brow. How had Greengrass found out? “I’m Hermione, of course.”

Greengrass’ eyes narrowed. “Sure, you—”

Susan’s blob of water fell.

“—Are.”

Susan shielded and dived backwards just as Greengrass’s first spell hit. Easy. Another spell splashed off the shield and she dodged a third. Despite her heart thumping a drum beat in her chest, she wasn’t panicking. Another spell whizzed by. She wasn’t first seed on the Hufflepuff duelling team for nothing and she didn’t even need to beat Greengrass, just get away with her identity safe.

She dodged another spell, this one much closer. Adrenaline surged. Hah! Her eyes danced. Her heart raced. This is what she loved about duelling! That game of mere inches, where every split second counted, but this was no mere practise duel—no, this was the real thing and the stakes were much higher. Adrenaline coursed through her blood. Her eyes widened, taking in every bit of light they could.

Greengrass started yet another basic chain, her own eyes two ice-blue furious slits.

Susan instinctively countered it, months of practise making every motion automatic. Greengrass and her were about equal in terms of raw power, so they’d both be slowing down soon and at about the same time. That would give her the opportunity to get away. Her feet dug into the soft grass making indents in the soil.

Then, suddenly, two jelly-leg jinxes collided in mid air and Susan watched in horror as a long silver thread formed between hers and Greengrass’ wands. Greengrass’ free hand started to glow red, the silver threat strengthened, thickened with raw power, and before Susan could think another thought, she’d been yanked forward as though from the world’s largest reverse portkey. Greengrass flew towards her, connected by that silver thread, a bolt of red filled her vision, and she knew no more.

…

…

…

Susan awoke, bound in ropes and wandless, to the sight of Greengrass standing over her, smiling, her own wand pointed down at her.

“Well hello there, Susan Bones, Heiress of the Ancient and Noble House of Bones.”

Susan winced, Granger’s brown wavy hair falling down over her face. This was bad. “Look, I can explain.”

“Oh, do, please. You were this close to stealing House secrets.”

Susan grimaced and pushed Granger’s hair out of her face. “I wasn’t trying to—that was by accident.”

“Then what were you trying to do?”

“Look, Greengrass, Daphne,” Susan tried desperately. “Everyone’s worried, okay? No one knows what’s going on and it’s putting people on edge. The last time there was a mysterious wizard running around who didn’t want anyone to know his identity, it turned out to be you-know-who, you see that, right?”

“My lord is not the Dark Lord,” Greengrass said, her tone flat.

“I’m not saying he is, but you know, if we just knew a bit more about him it would put so many people’s minds at rest.”

“That is for my lord to decide when he is ready to release more information about himself, which I know he will do, but only when the time is right.”

Susan looked down at the ground.

“But about this situation …”

Susan looked back up.

“… I think three minor favours owed to the House of Slytherin by the House of Bones will suffice, don’t you agree?”

Susan quickly nodded her head. Three minor favours was the best possible outcome right now.

Greengrass smiled and released her ropes.

Susan collapsed backwards on the soft grass.

“Here.” Greengrass handed her back her wand.

“Thanks,” Susan muttered. She looked at her wand for a moment. “That was a wandless stunner back then.”

Daphne nodded.

Susan’s eyes widened. “Wow.”

“My lord is a good teacher.”

Susan let out a single laugh. “I’m jealous.”

“You should be.”

Susan grinned. “Mind you, John is a pretty good teacher too.”

A strange look crossed Greengrass’ face. “Oh really?”

“Yep! Me and him have been practising duelling for a few months now.” She looked back at her wand. “I guess it’s a good thing you’re not on the Slytherin duelling team. Fighting each other with these would be tricky.”

“I wouldn’t count your blessings until you’ve finished fighting who is on our team.”

“Oh, yes, Harry Potter. John really doesn’t like him.”

“Shocking.”

Susan looked down at her wand again. “Not that I’m complaining, but I do feel like I was kind of cheated on the wand front.”

“Oh?”

“Yeah, divination wands, right?” Susan laid her wand alongside Greengrass’ identical foci. Fat lot of good that is in a duel, or anytime, really.”

Greengrass looked down at her own wand as though seeing it for the first time. “Oh, yes,” she said, idly picking it up and turning it through her fingers. “How useless.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Profero oculus Kilrogg.”

It was the Saturday before the Duelling tournament and in a temporary fidelius charm, in the Hogwarts pipe network, just outside the muggle studies defence room, in the third floor corridor, Daphne sat, ‘useless’ divination wand pointed at a spot just a few feet in front of her.

Harry and Hermione watched her as a large green eyeball appeared in the spot.

Daphne’s world shifted. Her third eye opened.

In the last few weeks, they’d practised and practised for this moment—gone over everything that could go wrong and made fall backs, back up plans, and plan Bs, all sprinkled with a dash of contingency, not the least of which was the addition of setting up an additional magical shield around the mirror room once they’d entered, to stop anyone trying to blast their way in from the outside, if that was even possible.

All their other plans had taken a back seat while they focused on the one thing that mattered right now—securing the mirror room.

Harry didn’t say anything. There was no need for words between them at this stage.

Daphne moved the eye into the space Dumbledore’s fidelius charm would appear once they tripped the ward. She gave Harry the thumbs up.

Harry nodded back, turned to the pipe’s wall and whispered, “$Open$.”

The pipe opened a round, human sized hole, and the three stepped into the room beyond.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore sat in his office chair, sipping on a perfectly made cup of tea—perfectly made, with five lumps of sugar, three slices of lemon, and two tea bags, both of which were currently bobbing up and down against the cup’s fine china walls, humming a song about sailors.

At first he’d been worried about John’s extreme aggressive attitude towards Harry, but it looked like it would turn out useful in the end. Perhaps after Harry had been placed in the safety of Azkaban, he should take a personal interest in John’s education—power like that needed to be carefully managed.

He took another sip of tea.

Unfortunately, Harry being sent to Azkaban would render the third floor corridor project worthless. That was a disappointment. He’d been so sure that keeping Voldemort and Harry in the castle for almost a year together would have triggered some kind of confrontation, especially given Harry’s seeming instability, but apparently not. He’d have to deconstruct the defences and send the stone back to Nicholas …

He took another sip.

Or maybe he should see to it that the stone had an ‘accident’. Such a powerful artefact might be better off not existing—far too much of a temptation.

On the other side of the room, the empty perch that normally hosted Fawkes, was still empty.

Dumbledore looked at the familiar trinket on his desk that reflected Fawkes’ current life cycle phase. It was stuck on, ‘chick,’ and had been since Halloween. He sighed. Wherever Fawkes was, he doubted immortality was doing him much good at the moment.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione pressed the final required button on the VCR’s remote control and watched in satisfaction as a small flash of light filled the room and the door to the next room slowly ground open.

Harry gave her a proud nod, which made her visibly swell.

She and Daphne then spent the next thirty minutes twiddling their thumbs and going over their various plans one more time while Harry placed rune stones around the room and cast his own fidelius on the room.

Once Harry gave her the secret, Hermione glanced at the marauder’s map, on loan again from the Weasley Twins, and saw that Dumbledore was still in his office.

Harry stepped in front of her, took off his noble house ring, watched it vanish into thin air, and looked deep into her eyes.

Hermione took a deep breath, pointed her wand right between his eyes and said, “Obliviate.” Images and memories from Harry’s mental library shot through her mind, all fuzzy and indistinct, all but impossible for her to understand, but all related to her own current focus and all chosen by Harry before hand, everything about the philosopher’s stone, about the third floor corridor, about their current mission. One by one, those memories were blocked and locked, enforced by Harry’s own magic, like an autoimmune disease, a magical contract, or a particularly dark magical curse. There were two types of obliviate, memory locking and memory destruction. Memory destruction only worked on the most vulnerable—muggles, or those without intermediate level occlumency or noble house rings. This wasn’t that.

Hermione finished the spell and lowered her wand.

Harry looked at her in mild confusion. “Hermione?”

She passed Harry the first of the pre-written instructions, secured by Harry’s own fidelius signature.

Harry read the parchment, raised his eyebrows, and turned to Daphne. “Then lead on, my lady.”

Daphne tied a blindfold around Harry’s eyes, put on one half of the mirror ear piece pair and watched Hermione put on the other half.

Hermione turned and headed back to the pipe network where she would stay until the end of the mission.

Her last sight of Harry and Daphne was Daphne leading Harry over to the now open door, hand clutched firmly in his, eyes aflame and determined.

Hermione climbed back into the still open pipe and into their first fidelius charm. Dumbledore was still in his office. She sat herself down right in front of her first set of fidelius instructions and waited.

A minute went by and then … something tripped.

…

Huh? Hermione looked around, puzzled. Why was she here? Wait. What’s this? She picked up a piece of parchment that had been laying right in front of her and started to read.

Hermione Granger, this is Hermione Granger—code: step-by-step—signature: The second bookshelf in Harry’s trunk is located next to the first bookshelf.

Hermione’s eyes narrowed. So it was that, mmm? She took her wand, cut off the top of the parchment containing the code and fidelius signature, and burned it with a small incendio. She then started reading what was left.

Instruction one: Speak the following words—“Daphne, this is Hermione, I have found the step by step instructions.”

Hermione took a breath. “Daphne, this is Hermione, I have found the step by step instructions.”

A voice came back through her ear. “Good. This is Daphne. Fidelius ID: The first bookshelf in Harry’s trunk is located next to the second bookshelf.”

Hermione nodded to herself and read the second instruction.

Instruction two: Keep looking at Dumbledore’s position on the Marauder’s Map for the next hour or until Daphne says the word’s, ‘F Down—all clear’.

If Dumbledore’s position ever reaches the room left of the muggle studies defence room, speak the following words out loud, ‘Dumbledore has reached the Snape room. Cloak and evacuate.’

Hermione scanned the Marauder’s Map and saw that Dumbledore had left his office and was rapidly approaching the grand stairway. She scanned the rest of the parchment. Nothing more for her to do at the moment. She went back to watching Dumbledore.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

[Moments earlier]

Dumbledore’s eyes widened behind his moon shaped glasses. A warning light had flashed on his left lens. Someone, probably Tom, had tripped the fidelius charm again on the third floor. He stood up, put his tea cup down with a clink, and made for the door. He had to commend the man’s persistence if nothing else, even in the face of a perfect defence, for there was no way around a fidelius charm once it was in place. No way at all.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne gazed around the centre of the mirror room with her eye of Kilrogg while also gazing up at the massive stone statue of Severus Snape with her normal eyes. She kept her hand on Harry’s and led him over to the bench, both of them under the invisibility cloak. Thank Merlin they’d found this little trick. Doing this while she was also affected by the fidelius would have been ridiculous.

A voice came through her ear. “Daphne, this is Hermione, I have found the step by step instructions.”

Daphne nodded to herself. “Good. This is Daphne. Fidelius ID: The first bookshelf in Harry’s trunk is located next to the second bookshelf.”

She looked down at the parchment on the desk and at the small vial of colourless liquid sitting next to it. “Veritas affirmatio.” The vial momentarily glowed a faint green colour. It was authentic. She picked it up along with the dropper next to it and administered three drops onto her tongue, before corking the vial back up and pocketing it. Hey, it was hard to get hold of this stuff.

Daphne felt her noble house ring heat up as the ancient magics negated the Veritaserum.

The statue moved and Snape’s acerbic voice slimed its way through the room. “Speak, visitor. What is your name?”

“Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore.”

“For what reason do you seek the philosopher’s stone?”

“To protect it from Voldemort and return it to the Flamels.”

“What item does this fidelius protect?”

The secret flared in Daphne’s head. “The Mirror of Erised.”

“Correct.” Snape’s voice sounded almost disappointed. “Proceed.” The final door swung open and Daphne led Harry over to it.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore batted away an errand tentacle from the devil’s snare in the Herbology room, barged into the charms room, and stopped, and stared. All the stone warriors were still lined up on both his sides. There was no rubble. It looked like no one had been through here. And yet, the fidelius was definitely active, so someone had tripped it. He frowned. Someone had found a way to pass through this room without first defeating it. That was worrying—and more than a little annoying for him.

Oh well. Dumbledore raised the elder wand in front of him, narrowed his eyes and leapt across the activation ward and magical shield, immediately transfiguring the floor into a liquid stone shield, which wrapped around him and stopped several dozen cross bow bolts from turning him into a human pin cushion.

The stone warriors slammed into his defence and started to smash away at his stone egg.

Dumbledore summoned a stronger, pure magic shield closer to him, and banished the egg away in all directions, sending several tones of stone rubble colliding into the many warriors, utterly destroying some of them, and sending those who remained to the ground.

One warrior wielding an eight foot long Goedendag got to its feet quicker than its fellows and smashed its heavy weapon into the magical shield, only a few inches from Dumbledore’s face. Albus flicked his wand, smacking the warrior away and catching the Goedendag in mid-air with a levitation charm.

Several dozen more crossbow bolts ricocheted off his shield.

The other warriors had finished picking themselves up.

Dumbledore smirked, eyes twinkling, and flicked his wand again. The Goedendag rapidly spun itself in the air. The floor around him started melting. Oh, he’d missed this.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Blindfolded and helpless, Harry followed Daphne’s lead, keeping a firm grip on her hand and trusting her not to let him walk into something. He had no idea what was going on, but whatever it was, was probably important.

Occasionally he heard her gasp, or exclaim, or curse, or even emit a little chocked sob.

Whatever was going on out there must be quite dangerous. Some kind of mental trial perhaps? No! He shook himself. He shouldn’t be trying to think about what ever it might be. That was the point of the step-by-step protocol.

“Harry,” Daphne’s voice said.

“Yes?”

“I have placed all the rune stones in the correct positions around the area. You now need to cast a magical shield charm and tie it into the stones, using the magical power that comes from a nearby Herbology project, not the castle’s wards, understand?”

That sounded doable. “Yes, I understand.”

He felt Daphne’s hand close around his wand hand and guide it forward until he felt his wand push against something hard. “That’s the first ward stone, Harry. Good luck.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore strode out of the rubble of stone warriors, some of which were little more than melted piles of newly formed igneous rock, and into the next room.

The long bench against the wall next to him was loaded with glassware.

Oh, yes. This was McGonagall’s room. Trust his number two to come up with something like this when asked to, ‘really put some effort into it.’

He walked over to the first glass jar and saw that, indeed, the small iron ball was still there. Someone had bypassed this trial too. He smiled grimly, levelled his wand at the iron ball, watched it slowly melt, and started the delicate and tricky alchemy puzzle.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry tapped the final ward stone and muttered the final incantation. He felt the magic catch and stabilise into the new ward system, protecting wherever they were from magical attack from the outside of wherever they were.

“Right, Harry, now we’re going to set up a second set of ward stones to drain a set of ward stones that are already here, understand?”

Harry nodded. He understood that.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore eventually made his way into the next room, bathed in almost total darkness, having successfully navigated the iron ball through the glassware puzzle.

“Lumos.”

He walked straight over to the control panel and punched in positions of the stars and planets on his date of birth. The stars and planets on the roof started moving, and, moments later, stopped. A white light flashed and the darkness of the room vanished.

Right, next room …

…

He hesitated.

Wait.

He blinked.

He …

He frowned. Then his eyes opened in shock. He couldn’t remember where the next room was!

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“That was the last one, Harry.”

Harry stepped away from the last rune stone they’d placed on the floor of wherever they were.

“Now, Harry, you need to start an incantation to deactivate a three kiloflamel ward system and drain the charm into the rune stone system we just set up.”

Harry frowned. Three kiloflamels. Damn. Whatever they were doing was serious business. This definitely wasn’t practise.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore desperately legged it around yet another corridor corner and down into a secret passageway that he was sure only he knew about. He barrelled down the secret passageway, and emerged out into another corridor, this one so dusty that the dust pilled up in the corners almost like snow.

Hogwarts had some strange geometry, but it did usually follow some common sense rules—rules like, if a room has a wall, then somewhere, there has to be another side to that wall.

And the other side of the mirror room outer wall should be right about … here.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry focused every ounce of his will on making sure the magic drained out of the old ward system without causing what could be charitably described as a problem. When problems happened with this much magic you were lucky to get out of it staying the same shape. Mere explosions were easy to deal with compared to something as powerful as a collapsing defence system trying to turn you into a polka dotted frog with nine legs and a taste for only kangaroo.

Suddenly he felt something smack into the magical shield ward he’d just set up. “Daphne.”

“Yes, Harry?”

“Something just tried to attack the magic defence ward system.”

Harry heard Daphne’s intake of breath and subsequent rapid question. “Hermione, where is Dumbledore?”

He heard a tiny, tinny voice say, “He’s not on the map.”

Daphne cursed. “Harry, will this force be able to get through?”

Harry shook his blindfolded head. “It does feel strong enough to be Dumbledore or Voldemort, but they’ll never be able to get through alone, the ward system’s too powerful.”

Harry heard Daphne let out a sigh of relief. “How close is the ward to being drained?”

“Close.”

Harry continued to supervise the draining, while feeling what Daphne seemed to think was Dumbledore fruitlessly pounding on the magical shield surrounding the room. Eventually the pounder gave up.

The final few Merlins drained into the new ward system.

“Daphne, it’s done.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione’s head shot up from where she’d been staring at the Marauder’s Map. She remembered! Harry had done it! “Daphne!”

“Yeah, Hermione, it’s done! Get in here, now!”

Hermione jumped up and dashed though the still open hole in the pipe and into the muggle studies defence room.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore almost dropped his wand in shock. The fidelius was down! He stopped staring at the wall in front of him and dashed back the way he’d come. This was bad. Really, really, bad.

“Expecto patronum!” A silver phoenix appeared in front of him. “Minerva! The third floor defences have failed. I’m putting the castle into lockdown. Get the students to their common rooms.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione skidded into the centre of the mirror maze, trying desperately not to look at any of the reflections. Many of them prominently featured Older Hermione hanging from a prison ceiling without a head. “Harry!”

Harry turned to her, just as Daphne untied Harry’s blindfold. “Hermione?”

Hermione reached into her bag and brought out several flasks of memories. “Take these.”

Harry dutifully accepted the memory vials and started transferring the silvery strands back into his head.

Hermione pointed her wand between Harry’s eyes. “Memoria salutem.”

Harry’s eyes flicked for a few moments. Then he staggered. “Whoa.” He shook his head and looked around. “It worked!”

“Yes, but we now need—”

“—Fidelius charm, got it.” Harry sat down on the floor in front of the small rune stone in front of him and closed his eyes.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore reached his office at a dead run. He lunged for one of his devices prominently displayed in an alcove behind his chair, well away from preying little fingers, and slammed his hand down on it. “Castle lockdown!”

Magic swirled through the room.

His windows slammed shut.

There.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Sophie Roper looked up from her book in alarm as every one of the windows at the top of the tall library walls slammed shut one after the other. “What’s going on?”

Her fellow Ravenclaws, Lisa Turpin and Padma Patil, shrugged.

“Students!” Madam Pince strode into the normally quiet study area. “Back to your dormitories immediately! Quickly now! Go!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John halted Susan in the middle of their duel and watched with wide eyes as every window and door to the duelling arena slammed shut and bolted itself. Powerful magic rushed through the space, causing the hairs on the back of his neck to stand on edge. What the hell?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Chief Auror Sirius Black snatched his shield up from where it lay on by the door and bolted outside, almost colliding with Shacklebolt who’d rushed out of his office at the exact same moment.

A blaring siren was sounding, almost deafening him with its wail. The department’s normally soft lighting was pulsing pure red.

They both tap-danced down the department stairs to find the two dozen aurors of the main office already dressed and ready—game faces on, helmets, shields, the full nine yards.

Sirius strode into the middle of them. “Hogwarts is on lockdown! The moment we get a request for help, we leave.”

All twenty-two aurors nodded.

The floo flared green. Dumbledore’s face popped out. “Sirius?”

“Yes, Albus?”

“If I needed your help, do you think you could keep it quiet?”

Sirius goggled at his former Headmaster while the sirens of the department of magical law enforcement loudly blared around him. “If you need our help, you need our help!”

Dumbledore’s head seemed to concede this point. “Okay, I need help.”

Amelia Bones slammed though the department’s front door. “Situation!?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Tracey ran back to the Slytherin common room, trying not to panic, and failing miserably. The school was on lockdown! That hadn’t happened since the last goblin rebellion! Not even in the last war had the school gone on lockdown!

She quickly climbed into the room and scanned the room. Daphne and Hermione weren’t here! “Blaise!”

Blaise spotted her and walked over from where a bunch of older students were milling around with anxious looks on their faces. “Where’re Daph and Hermione?”

Blaise shrugged.

Tracey cursed.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione watched the Marauder’s Map for signs of trouble, occasionally glancing up to see Daphne still watching the still figure of Harry, who was sitting peacefully with his eyes closed in the middle of the mirror room. Everything was going well, but that was no reason to let down their guard.

Quirrellmort had left his office not long after Harry had taken down the fidelius and was currently heading towards the girl’s second floor bathroom. That was worrying. Dumbledore seemed to be glued to his floo, which was also troubling. Was he calling for help?

Suddenly, Hermione’s heart leapt into her throat. Name after name popped out of Dumbledore’s floo. Black, Shacklebolt, Robards, Scrimgeour, Knight, Dawlish, Proudfoot, and Savage. Eight in total.

“Daphne?” she called, a note of alarm seeping into her voice.

“Yes?”

The names followed Dumbledore down the stairs from his office until they reached the first corridor, where upon they quickly formed themselves into a column, two names wide and four names long.

“Oh,” Daphne said.

They both looked at Harry, still sitting with his eyes closed.

The names marched along corridor after corridor until they turned into what seemed to be a wall and disappeared off the map.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Sirius felt up the snow-drift-dusty wall and grunted. “Knight!”

Robert Knight, the team warder, stepped forward.

“What can you do about this?”

Knight stuck his wand into the space near the wall. “A standard magical shield ward. Yes, we can take it down, but it will take time.”

“How much time?”

“Thirty minutes, maybe?”

Dumbledore’s beard twitched.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The magical shield protecting them was weakening.

Hermione wasn’t panicking, but she really hoped Harry would finish soon. It wasn’t as thought they didn’t have an exit—the door leading back through the third floor corridor was right there after all, and beyond that were two up and ready fidelius charms—fidelius charms which could easily protect them from the small army currently battering at their shields, should push come to shove, but she really hoped push wouldn’t come to shove. They’d spent so much time and effort to get this far. To be forced to abandon it all, after getting here, with just the mirrors themselves left to defend the stone … Ugh.

She and Daphne were taking in turns to pour as much of their own magic into the shield wards as they could, anything to buy them just a bit more time, but it felt like trying to feed a furnace with matchsticks. They could feel it wasn’t close to failing yet, but it wouldn’t last forever and every minute that past felt like an hour. The room was oppressively silent—silent but for the occasional footstep from her or Daphne and the barely audible thrum of eight adult aurors plus Dumbledore on the other side of the wall, ripping through the wards. Hermione fancied she could even hear Daphne’s breathing. She could certainly hear her own.

Hermione gazed at Harry, still sitting with his eyes closed, looking as peaceful as a quiet spring morning, which was the opposite of how she felt.

Daphne kicked a pebble across the room.

It made a clirck, click, ditc noise.

Then, suddenly, Harry’s eyes snapped open, and he grinned.

Hermione’s heart leapt.

Harry stood up, drew his wand, pointed it at the stone in front of him and said in a firm, confident voice, “Fidelius Occultum!”

And all knowledge of where she was and what she was doing was swept from her mind like smoke by a gust of fresh, cleansing wind.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Knight looked up from where he was focusing the efforts of eight other wizards on … “Wait.”

The combined auror task force looked around, confused.

Knight looked at his wand. “What were we just doing?”

Dumbledore groaned.

—End of Chapter Thirty—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: As you can see, I’ve decided to split what I thought was going to be one chapter into two. So, we still have three chapters left until the end of season and book two. Yay! Next chapter—The Tournament.

A/N: As you can also see, I’m trying to get one chapter out a week at the moment. Hopefully I’ll be able to do this for the next two chapters, although I suspect that the season finale will be the usual two week deal.

… And the Tournament

Dumbledore felt inordinately smug.

You’d think, what with the mirror room now under a hostile fidelius, that he’d be down one defence professor and facing the prospect of immediate war with a resurrected dark lord, but no—Tom had yet to leave his teaching post and, far from being the endless fount of dry, dark humour that would indicate a good mood, seemed more annoyed than ever. Clearly, Nicholas’s devilish mirror and his own additions were doing their job.

There was one thing that puzzled Dumbledore though and it was with this puzzle in mind that he gently knocked on the door to the defence professor’s office.

“Enter.”

Dumbledore opened the door and stepped through.

“Ah, Headmaster.” Quirrell’s body looked up and Tom directed him to an empty chair. His manner was impassive, if a bit surly. “How can I help you?”

“Quirinus,”—Dumbledore took the seat offered—“I was wondering if you could help me with a little mystery.”

Tom tilted Quirrell’s head. “You know I will give you any help I can, Headmaster. I understand you are extremely busy at the moment.”

Dumbledore’s beard twitched. He’d spent most of yesterday afternoon and evening dealing with the fallout from calling eight aurors out and locking down the castle for reasons that neither he, nor the aurors, could fully remember—and those bits he could remember, he had no desire to tell. “It is about my being busy that I wish to ask. You remember yesterday that I put the castle into lockdown?”

Quirrell’s left eye twitched. “I would find it incredibly difficult to forget something like that.”

“Well, during that time, the wards recorded you as leaving the castle, despite the fact that such a thing should be impossible during a lockdown.”

“How interesting.”

“And what’s more, I can understand the fact that you were not in the castle. That is to say, my brain allows me to process that information.”

Tom’s surely expression momentarily shifted. His eyes flickered with dark amusement. “Ah, the fidelius charm. Such a useful piece of magic.”

Dumbledore tensed.

Tom laughed. “I really wish I could help you, Headmaster, but unfortunately, I cannot … remember.”

Dumbledore’s eyes widened in shock.

Tom’s face became surely again. “Yes, annoying, isn’t it?”

“But …” Albus tried to comprehend what he was hearing. “Who?”

Tom’s lip curled upwards, eyes instantly shifting back to dark amusement. “I’d say, ‘you-know-who,’ but clearly that isn’t true.”

Dumbledore fixed Tom with the same severe look he used to give him in transfiguration.

“Oh, come now, my dear Dumbledore. I’m sure that I, a mere former muggle studies professor, doesn’t need to spell out what to you should be obvious—that the binary game is no longer.”

And then Dumbledore suddenly realised what Tom was suggesting. He, Albus, was the Light Lord and Tom was the Dark Lord, that much was obvious—but that there might be a third—his eyes widened—and that Tom seemed to believe that third was worthy of being classed as their equal.

Tom smirked. “The Gray Lord.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

After an evening assuring Tracey that they were fine and just training down by the lake, Daphne Greengrass stood, once again, in the fideliused mirror room, in front of a mirror that was certainly not the mirror of Erised, although exactly what it was, was up for debate.

In the mirror, Daphne’s reflection kissed a giggling Hermione on the cheek, before enthusiastically waving a red stone at her, ducking out of the mirror’s frame, and into the mirror next to her. Behind mirror Hermione, a million reflections from a hundred other mirrors in the mirror maze did what ever it was they did in their mirrors, sometimes to or with each other. Red stones featured prominently.

The mirror next to her contained an older Daphne sitting on a throne made of ice, eyes glowing blue, face stern, regal, and cruel. The red stone holding Daphne from the other mirror proceeded to have an argument with ice throne Daphne—an argument which ended when a smaller Daphne reflection from another mirror jumped in between them and summoned an older Harry reflection, who made a grab for red stone Daphne, but missed. Reflection Harry then proceeded to jump ice throne Daphne and started doing things that made real Daphne blush.

Red stone Daphne, meanwhile, had flittered away to yet another mirror, although which one, she couldn’t tell. There were just so many of them.

Daphne tried to ignore the mirror next to her and instead ran her fingers along the mirror in front of her, attempting to feel the magics that wove it together, like Harry suggested she do. It was tough going, especially with reflection Hermione constantly giggling at her.

“This one,” said Harry’s voice from across the room, “this one is not the Mirror of Erised.”

Daphne abandoned her experiments with magic sensing and joined Harry at one of the many hundreds of other mirrors, followed moments later by Hermione.

“I should hope not,” said Hermione in a disgusted voice.

Daphne felt sick. In the mirror, Lord Walter Slughorn—fat, ugly, and without a hint of compassion—did unspeakable things with her terrified seven-year-old self. She didn’t know what Harry or Hermione were seeing but if it was anything like her’s then she didn’t want to know.

Harry pointed his wand at it. “There doesn’t seem to be any trip lines or traps.” He conjured a large rock in midair. “Stand back please.”

Daphne and Hermione scurried backwards.

SMASH!

The mirror fell over backwards and what remained of its cracked surface exploded upwards, a million little shards falling out of their frame.

Hermione snickered. “Seven years bad luck.”

Daphne winced. “Oh, Merlin, don’t say that.”

“Yes, well.” Harry stepped over the wreckage, crunching a stray bit of glass under foot. “There will be a lot of broken mirrors before we’re done here.”

It took hours.

Harry carefully analysed each mirror, occasionally showing Hermione and her an interesting point or two about what he was doing. After he’d confirmed that the mirror wasn’t the one they were after, he smashed it with the now traditional floating rock, and then she and Hermione swept up the remains into an ever growing pile in a corner of the room.

Eventually, they were left with just one mirror—The Mirror of Erised.

Daphne looked into the mirror.

Her parents were there. So were Astoria and Tracey. So was Hermione. So was Harry. And Harry was tall. All of them were older, and standing in some exotic location, if the many tropical trees and grasses were any indication. Harry looked so happy. In his left hand he held a blood red stone, and with his right, he proudly ruffled Reflection-Daphne’s hair. Reflection-Daphne looked embarrassed but also deeply happy with flushed red cheeks, downcast eyes, and a huge smile.

“Any luck?” Harry asked.

Daphne tore her eyes away from the image, shaking her head.

Hermione’s voice was quiet when she spoke. “I see … I see you with the stone, Harry. I see a lot of other things too, but the important bit is that you’ve got the stone. You’re not doing anything with it, though, just holding it.”

“Mine’s like that too,” Daphne added.

Harry nodded. “Same, although in my case, the stone isn’t in my hands, but rather on top of a Midas-worthy pile of gold in the reflection’s background. I guess that’s the mirror’s way of saying that I don’t meet the requirements to retrieve the stone.”

Daphne took a step back. She was finding it difficult not to keep staring at the mirror. “So, what do we do now then?”

“Hermione is going to retrieve the stone.”

Hermione started. “M-Me?”

“Yep. Or, more specifically, I’m going to use various mind magics on you to temporarily alter your desires. The idea is that the mirror is like a combination safe and only a specific combination of desires will unlock it.”

Hermione bit her lip, but did nod her head.

“I’ll need you to completely drop your occlumency.”

Hermione nodded again and closed her eyes for a few minutes before opening them again. “Done.”

Harry nodded and levelled his wand between Hermione’s eyes. “Confundus.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione shook herself. That felt weird. Err … what were they doing? Oh yes, she had to find the stone. She had to find the stone and this mirror was the key.

She gazed into the mirror. The reflection showed a huge library, massive, ancient, and overflowing. Her older reflection sat reading on a sofa with an older Harry sitting next to her, arm wrapped comfortably around her shoulders, holding the stone in his free hand, occasionally giving her blushing reflection a light kiss on top of the head.

Hermione frowned. This wasn’t her deepest desire. She needed to find the stone!

Reflection Harry caught her eye, smiled, and shook his head while idly tossing the stone up and down.

Something felt wrong here. A tiny voice in the back of her mind was getting louder and louder. Something about Harry. Something about wanting. …

“Confundus.”

Hermione shook herself. That felt weird. Err … what were they doing? Oh yes, she had to find whatever it was that this mirror was protecting.

She gazed into the mirror. Sofa bound Harry lightly kissed a delighted reflection Hermione on the cheek, gave real Hermione a playful wink and waggled a single admonishing finger at her through the glass.

Hermione frowned. This wasn’t her deepest desire.

“Confundus.”

Hermione shook herself. That felt weird. Err … what were they doing? Oh yes, she had to stop Voldemort getting the stone. That was critical!

Reflection Harry rolled his eyes at her.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daily Prophet Front Page [29 th March, 1992]

HOGWARTS ON LOCKDOWN!

Yesterday, at two o’clock in the afternoon, the students and staff at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry experienced something that has not happened since the last goblin rebellion. Headmaster Albus Dumbledore, Order of Merlin - first class, Chief Warlock of the Wizengamot, and Supreme Mugwump of the ICW, placed Hogwarts castle on lockdown and summoned a task force of eight aurors to the school. In a statement released to the Prophet, Headmaster Dumbledore said that, ‘The situation is under control and our children are in no danger.’

Despite these assurances, the school remains in lockdown, and we at the Prophet have to wonder what kind of situation would cause the Headmaster to take such an action. Neither he nor the DMLE is currently willing to disclose details.

What does lockdown mean? The lockdown status of Hogwarts castle is a warding protocol that prevents anyone or anything from leaving or entering the school grounds through any normal entrance or exit other than a single point controlled by the Headmaster. Lockdown is the second highest level of security the school can assume and because of the large drain of magic, can only be maintained for a week. Continuing his earlier statement, Headmaster Dumbledore said that, “The annual Hogwarts duelling competition will take place as normal and the lockdown will be lifted before the event. As it stands, the lockdown is only in place as a precautionary measure.”

This begs the question, ‘what is going on at Hogwarts School?’. Readers will recall that in September of last year, a fully grown mountain troll breached the school’s defences and roamed the school unchecked until defeated by a group of first year students. Some might say it is reassuring that the Headmaster is now taking threats to our children’s safety more seriously, while others would question the headmaster’s right to keep such a security concern secret.

At the time of going to print, a related twenty-four hour block on all owl communication with the castle has been lifted.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore sat invisibly in the empty stands of the duelling arena, watching the Slytherin duelling practises with a calculating gaze.

For his age, Harry Potter really was a genius—definitely at the level he and Tom were at when eleven, if not better. Indeed, the young boy was more teaching than practising, even with the seventh years, something his older peers seemed to accept, if barely.

The tournament would be the perfect opportunity. It was violent, public, and who knew the lengths a young boy would go through to win against his famous brother. Jealousy was such a terrible thing.

In the ring below, Mister Potter let off a particularly well coordinated spell chain. A long distance smoke illusion, followed by a zero friction charm aimed at the floor, and finished up with a low powered area of effect stunner, the kind of thing that could reach around a hastily cast shield, if the target wasn’t paying attention—an interesting combination—and one the young Potter seemed quite fond of.

White—Pink—Brown

White—Pink—Brown

Hmm … that area of effect stunner spell at the end looked rather similar to a certain dark high-powered blasting curse, didn’t it?

White—Pink—Brown

White—Pink—Brown

Dumbledore watched for a few more minutes before nodded to himself, getting up, and leaving. He had what he needed.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

By Thursday, Harry felt he was running out of immediately useful ideas. The mental manipulation on Hermione was a dud. The Mirror of Erised was obviously more sophisticated than that. He sat alone, crosslegged in front of the mirror, probing the artefact with his magic and looking for any loopholes in its design.

In the mirror, an adult Harry sat in the middle of what could only be described as an ocean of family. All the girls were there, all grown up with dozens of children playing around them in the grounds of a proud and unbreakable Slytherin Manor, in front of which, was a mountain of gold, on top of which sat a single red stone, taunting him with its closeness.

By Harry’s feet, the book on mind healing lay open to the page on how to fight a phobia using occlumency.

He’d had an idea.

The first step in curing a phobia with occlumency was learning to create a second personality that would live in his mind—a split personality. This personality would serve multiple purposes, the first and most immediate being to wrestle control of the body while the main personality suffered from the phobia induced panic attack.

This was a less than ideal solution, but it provided the set up for the second step of the treatment—using a split consciousness controlled mind-scape to simulate the conditions of the phobia and gradually desensitise the main consciousness to it. He needed a second consciousness, because, as Harry told Ginny all those months ago during their dreamland training, if you want something in your dreamworld, you have it, which makes it impossible to recreate the conditions of a phobia since, the moment you don’t want that massive spider to be crawling all over you, it will disappear.

Harry found it deliciously ironic that the most important step in curing his phobia of being trapped was to learn to create and use another, even more serious mental condition.

He’d been practising in every free moment that he wasn’t ether dealing with Lord Slytherin business, training with the girls, or dealing with those Harry Potter obligations he couldn’t hand wave away. In that practise time, he thought he’d managed to get the first step working.

Harry looked away from the mirror, reached deep into his occlumency, putting everything that he was into a neat little package, and split it as though it were a mitosis intended microbe.

Something sparked into being inside him.

Well, hello there, Harry.

Harry mentally grinned. He had an alternate consciousness.

Just call me Alt.

That sounded fair. Were they ready to give it a go?

Yes, we are.

Harry steeled himself and looked back up into the mirror.

In the ocean of family, two identical Harry Potters stood looking very confused at each other. All around them, their children squealed and giggled, pointing and tugging at their mother’s sleeves, who looked rather bemused by the sudden appearance of an extra husband in their midst.

Harry looked down. He was going to bring them back together.

I’m quite okay with that.

Harry slowly moulded his two consciousnesses back together.

The little spark inside him went out.

Right. Now he had to create the same split, but this time with a slight change in his alt. He needed his alt to only want the stone, not to use it or give it to him or anything like that, just to get it.

Harry formed that neat little package again, but while it split he reached across the slowly forming divide between them and dove into the newly forming consciousness, erasing just those few small motivations. It was all he could manage before the split finalised, he leapt back across the divide, and that special something sparked back into being.

Well, hello there, Harry.

Harry mentally nodded. Hopefully this would work.

Ah, there might be a slight problem there.

Harry frowned in real life. A problem?

Yes, I suggest you look into the mirror.

Harry looked. The two Harrys were now having an argument. One furious Harry had his hand pointed towards the gold-swimming stone while the other had his arms crossed, stubbornly shaking his head.

What?

I want to find the stone, but I don’t want you to have it, Harry. Nor do I want you to use it. I’m sorry, but I won’t retrieve it for you.

Harry leaned forward and hit his head on the open book.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

In Dumbledore’s office, John fingered the rune dense duelling robe in his lap with not a small amount of trepidation. “How much will this hurt? You know, on a scale of one to the cruciatus?”

Dumbledore gave him a look over his moon shaped glasses. “I fear that wouldn’t be a useful scale for you, John.”

“One to ten, then?”

“Quite low. The blast will knock you unconscious almost immediately. The real pain will come during recovery.”

John nodded. “I’m quite used to pain during recovery.”

Dumbledore smiled slightly. “Ah, yes. I doubt that will be as bad as what you went through after the broom incident.”

“Fine then.”

Dumbledore fixed him with his over the glasses firm stare again. “Now, I don’t need to remind you about the consequences of what will happen if what we’re doing becomes known?”

John mentally rolled his eyes. “Yes, Headmaster, I understand.” And he did. The headmaster had tied himself to John, and if either of them went down, they’d take the other with them. John knew the headmaster did things in the name of fighting evil that would be heavily frowned on if they came to light, and Dumbledore knew that he, John Potter, wasn’t the true boy-who-lived, something he wanted never to come out. He might not be a Slytherin, but this kind of mutually assured destruction arrangement was brain dead obvious even to him.

“Why don’t you try it on?” Dumbledore asked.

John dutifully stood up and slipped on the duelling robes. It fit perfectly. No surprises there—they were the ones his father had bought him for his birthday, slightly altered by the headmaster. Runes covered the inside lining, embroidered in the lining’s own colour, making them very difficult to see, and at regular intervals, thin strips of similarly coloured enchanted parchment had been sown. “What’re the parchment strips for?”

Dumbledore smiled. “Ah, one of my more clever little ideas, if I do say so myself. Have you ever signed a notification contract?”

John shook his head.

“If you perform a certain action that’s against what’s written in a notification contract, your name appears on another piece of parchment, letting the other party know of your transgression. Quite useful to make sure people are sticking to their agreements.”

“So,” John held the open robes open, making the parchment strips a little more obvious. “Why?”

“I managed to alter the way the contract spell works so that instead of writing my name, it writes something else, in this case, it will write runes. The parchment strips sown into your robes are spaced so that when the runes appear, the parchment runes will line up with the runes already sown into the robe’s lining, triggering the blast.”

“So, you’re going to trigger it?”

“Indeed.” Dumbledore brought out a Gringotts contract parchment. “I just need you to counter sign here and everything will be set.”

John picked up a quill. “And there’s absolutely no chance that I might accidentally die from this?”

“John, if there was such a chance, I would not have even suggested it.”

John nodded and placed the quill on the signature spot, quickly reading the basic contract.

Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore agrees not to eat red Bertie Bott’s Every Flavour Beans during the Hogwarts Duelling Tournament on April fourth, 1992.

Signed: Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore

Signed: _

“Red beans, huh?”

Dumbledore smiled.

John signed.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The day of the tournament dawned and for the first time in a week, the oppressive lock-down magics filling Hogwarts lifted. Harry walked alone down to breakfast as though today were just another day. He still hadn’t had any luck with the mirror. If this kept up, he’d have to start considering more extreme measures.

The duelling teams of all four hoses sat together, all dressed in formidable looking duelling robes, even his fellow first years. He caught sight of Su Li at Ravenclaw table, staring down at her food as though she expected it to start flinging spells at her if she looked away.

Harry settled himself at the edge of the rest of the Slytherin duelling team.

Romulus Volf frowned. “Where’re your robes, Potter?”

Harry glanced down at his standard plain black Hogwarts robes. He’d cut a slit from the waist down at the both the front and back so they sort-of imitated the duelling robes of those worn around him—but even then, they still looked pretty scrappy, especially with the muggle jeans under them, well fitting that they might be. “I’m wearing them.”

Volf scowled. “Stop dicking around, Potter. I know you have better.”

“Yes, I do, but I will wear these for the moment.”

“Why?”

“Its all part of cunning Slytherin plan.” Harry shrugged. “Besides, I thought you were complaining you weren’t going to get to actually duel in the main event?”

Volf grumbled a bit but didn’t object any more.

At the far end of the table, Daphne held court with Hermione around the other Gray students, both doing a good job of not showing the anxiety Harry knew they felt. He’d warned them to be on high alert during the tournament. If something was going to happen, the tournament could be a perfect time for it.

Breakfast came and went. The team rose from the table, receiving a round of cheering and applause from their fellow Slytherins as they left the great hall. Harry might currently be isolated, but that wouldn’t stop the house supporting their team.

The stroll down to the duelling arena was relaxing and Harry couldn’t help reflect on this moment in the second timeline. He’d been in the stands, watching his brother—who’d had the advantage of time-travelling from the first time-line—plough through the first five members of Ravenclaw before finally succumbing. James and Lily Potter had been in the stands on the other side of the arena and Harry had so desperately wanted to go and talk to them, but was too afraid. They’d looked so proud of his brother. That memory had been a hard one to stop caring about, but constant exposure over ten years of hell had done it.

Before he knew it, Harry was ensconced in the Slytherin holding area under the large, currently open-air, duelling arena.

From outside he heard a magic enhanced voice bellow, “Welcome, My Lords and Ladies, wizards and witches, to the annual Hogwarts Duelling Tournament!” An approving roar from two thousand throats filtered through the ceiling and walls to them.

Harry gripped his holly and phoenix feather wand and grinned. They wanted a show? He’d give them a show.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore made his way along the rows of seats while the commentator’s voice sounded around him.

“The Hogwarts Duelling Tournament is an international Class A standard rules tournament—that means no transfiguration, weapons other than a wand, and no curses—just hexes, jinxes, and other charms!”

He saw what he was looking for. “Good morning, Madam Pomfrey.” Dumbledore settled himself next to the healer in the front row where he’d have a good view of the arena.

Madam Pomfrey looked pleasantly surprised to see him. “Oh, Good morning, Headmaster.” She turned back to the arena. “I do hope they don’t do anything too stupid this time.”

“Youth needs to learn its lessons.” He drew a paper bag out of his pocket. “Care for an every flavour bean?”

Madam Pomfrey eyed the bag warily. “I think I’ll give it a skip, if it’s all the same to you, Headmaster.”

Albus shrugged, eyes twinkling, and popped a yellow bean into his mouth. Mmm … lemon.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“The duellists will face each of their opponents in turn, starting with the youngest, until they lose! Then their next oldest team member will step forward to attempt to vindicate them! Once all seven members of their opposing team has been defeated, they will go through to the final round!”

By the entrance to the arena, a large floating board showed the scores and the current lineup.

Round 1: Gryffindor—0 vs. 0—Ravenclaw

Round 2: Hufflepuff—0 vs. 0—Slytherin

Semi Final: ?—0 vs. 0—?

Final: ?—0 vs. 0—?

“Well, Lovegood?” Lord Smith sat down heavily on the wooden bench beside the eccentric young lord, causing a slight shockwave to travel through it. “What’s this all about then?”

Xenophilius Lovegood smiled and nodded his head towards the arena. “I suspect we might well see something both instructive and entertaining.”

Lord Smith snorted. “Children fighting with pretty lights—not a hint of good steel anywhere—not even my own children—nor yours for that matter.”

“Hi!”

Lord Smith started, but only a little bit.

A small whisp of dreamy witch had seemingly materialised in front of him, dipping down into a shallow curtsy before rising again.

He ruffled his moustache.

Lovegood chuckled. “Lord Smith, I don’t believe you’ve met my daughter, Luna?”

“I haven’t.” He smiled at her. “And how old are you, young lady?”

Luna smiled brightly. “Eleven. I’m going to Hogwarts next year.”

From somewhere in the arena, bagpipes started playing.

Smith laughed. “Well, why don’t you sit down again and watch a bit of what you’ll be learning next year?”

Luna grinned. “Okay!”

Unseen by Smith, Xeno’s smile flittered into an amused smirk before instantly reforming back into his usual look of good natured knowing.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Just do your best and stay safe, you hear me, Susan?”

“Yes, Auntie.” Susan nodded into the Bones House magic mirror.

“Good—and no matter how it turns out, I’m incredibly proud of you.”

Susan smiled and wiped a tear from her eye. “Thanks, Auntie.”

“Right, you’d better be off then.”

Susan nodded again. “Bye—Mirror off.”

Her Aunt’s image in the mirror vanished, replaced by her own. She looked into her reflection’s eyes and steeled them. If Harry Potter was anything like John, then she’d need every advantage possible to stand even a hope of losing well. The rest of the Hufflepuff duelling team seemed to think the rumours about John were just that—rumours. Even Hannah and Sally thought she was exaggerating John’s abilities. She knew better.

“Right!” Team captain Tonks clapped her hands together. “Let’s kick some arse! Badger power!”

Everyone shouted, “Badger power!” Susan joining in.

She placed the precious mirror into the specially charmed section of her bag, slung the bag over her shoulders, and followed the rest of her determined team out into the arena.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The crowd roared.

Daphne watched the Hufflepuff team walk into the arena and take their seats in one of the four quarter seated areas for the duelling teams, painted in Hufflepuff yellow and black.

“And finally here is the Slytherin Team!”

The crowd roared again, although Daphne couldn’t help notice that a small chunk wearing scarlet and gold were booing.

“There’s Harry!” Hermione waved, pointing to last figure in the team.

Tracey looked glumly at her other best friend. “I don’t know what you’re so chipper about. We’re not his friends, are we?”

Daphne smirked. “I guess now might as well be as good a time as any to tell you.”

Tracey’s eyes sharped. “Tell me what?”

“Harry is Gray.”

Tracey’s mouth dropped.

“He’s been Gray for ages, but it’s still a secret, so don’t tell anyone, okay?”

Tracey’s eyes narrowed. “You’re calling him ‘Harry’—and how long is, ‘ages?’ ”

Daphne shrugged, but her eyes shined. “A while.”

“Before the thing with Lord Slytherin?”

“Way before then.”

“But …” Tracey seemed to be trying to wrap her mind around something. Her voice dropped to a fierce whisper. “But, you were kissing him!”

“I was.”

“And you have a contract!”

“I do.”

“With Lord Slytherin!”

“Yes.”

“The leader of the Gray!”

“He is.”

“And you’re saying Potter is Gray!”

“I am.”

Tracey collapsed back in her chair and stared at the sky before turning back to Daphne and narrowing her eyes again. “I thought it was out of character for you to suddenly start kissing some random boy.”

Daphne smiled.

“What really happened?”

“You were right to be so obsessed with bringing Harry to our side, but you were far from the only one to notice.”

Tracey watched her closely, clearly expecting her to continue.

Daphne smiled sweetly. “I promise to tell you all about it before next term starts.”

Tracey groaned. “Daaaappppphhhhhhhhh.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Our first duel will be Gryffindor versus Ravenclaw!”

John stopped scanning the crowds in a seemingly futile attempt to find his parents. They didn’t seem to be here. He stood up from where he sat among his fellow duellists, all giving him thumps on the back and encouraging shouts as he passed them.

“Heir John Potter of Gryffindor, the boy-who-lived, will be matching up against Ravenclaw Su Li of the Chinese House of Li—by the standards of Britain, an Ancient House at least, going back over three thousand years!”

He thought they would have. It kind-of hurt that they hadn’t. He descended the couple of steps to the dirt of the arena, moved towards the centre and looked around. The arena was a wide open circle littered with various obstacles—a huge log, a clump of boulders, even a small pond.

“How will the defeater of you-know-who fare in his first ever duelling match? That’s what we all want to know, and something I’m sure Miss Su Li is raring to find out too!”

Opposite him, Su Li narrowed her eyes, bowed, and adopted an oriental duelling pose. Her duelling robes looked to have more acromantula silk than dragon hide and were inked in bright patterns of white and blue.

John bowed in return, planted his legs firmly in the dust, and thrust out his wand in front of him as if it were a sword.

“Quiet please!”

The crowds slowly quietened.

Silence.

A bagpipe sounded a note.

Su Li charged. “Rictumsempra!”

John smirked, “Protego!” Li’s tickling charm harmlessly splashed against his shield.

“Tarantallegra!”

John jabbed his wand at the rapidly closing Asian girl. “Ceciditque!”

Li’s dancing legs jinx splashed off his shield again, her eyes widened in shock, and a split second later she lost her footing as John’s spell smashed into her. She crashed into the ground and John was on her, snatching the wand from her unresisting hand.

A man at the side of the arena raised a wand and shot out white sparks.

“Winner, John Potter!”

The crowd clapped and cheered.

John grinned at Li as she staggered to her feet.

She groaned and gave John an appraising gaze. “That was my most powerful jinx and your shield absorbed it and my first spell.”

John shrugged. “Never underestimate your opponent—I suggest you go tell your second year seed that.”

Su Li nodded tersely and walked off in the opposite direction.

The commentator’s voice boomed around the arena. “Well, how about that? John Potter takes the first win for Gryffindor!”

The board flashed.

Gryffindor—1 vs. 0—Ravenclaw

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry watched his brother walk out of the arena with predatory eyes. It looked like John had decided to ease into the tournament—not show anything too flashy at first. He smirked. That was fine with him.

“A simple combination of hexes, jinxes, and shields leading to an outright win for the boy-who-lived in record time! Miss Su Li obviously wasn’t expecting Heir Potter’s shield to hold up, but it did!”

Harry watched the Bones Heiress stand and start to make her way past the rest of the Hufflepuff duelling team on the other side of the arena.

Volf thumped him on the shoulder. “Go get ‘er, Potter!”

Harry stood.

“And now! We have the first Hufflepuff versus Slytherin match—and another first match for another Potter! Yes, that’s right, the younger twin of John Potter, I give you, Harry Potter!”

The crowd cheered and clapped, if only politely.

Harry made his way into the centre of the arena.

“And facing him, we have the Heiress of the Ancient and Noble House of Bones! The niece of the Head of the Department of Magical Law Enforcement, hoping to make her aunt proud, Heiress Susan Bones!”

The cheering this time was rather more enthusiastic.

Heiress Bones gazed at him with eyes alight with fire. “I warn you, I’m not like Su Li—I won’t underestimate a Potter.”

Harry felt a strange kind of déjà vu. For a moment, he could’ve sworn the words were almost Ginny’s, spoken in one of their many dreamland training sessions. He inclined his head. “Then I shall do my best not to underestimate a Bones, Heiress Bones.”

They both jumped into duelling stance.

“Quiet please!”

The rumble of the crowd died.

A bagpipe sounded.

Harry shouted, “Protego!” and was rewarded a split second later when a tripping hex splashing against it.

Susan dashed forward. “Ictus!” But unlike Su Li, Susan didn’t rashly charge into the duelling dead-zone, where dodging became all but impossible. “Colovaria!” Instead, she flittered at its edge, throwing hex and hex, jinx after jinx, playing the back and forth long game of assault and retreat that all duellists played with more powerful opponents. “Slugulus Eructo!” Not a bad strategy. It certainly let her last longer when her opponent was only throwing first year spells.

“Locomotor Wibbly!”

“Tussis!”

“Protego!”

“Crescere unguem!”

And she wasn’t bad for a first year, was she?

“Wingardium leviosa!” A rock levitated and hovered protectively in front of Susan.

Harry raised an eyebrow. “Ictus!”

Susan ducked behind the rock. “Petrificus totalus!”

Harry re-shielded and returned fire. Susan ducked behind the rock again, using the time to get off two hexes in a row, both of which splashed against his shield.

Harry smirked. A desperate strategy that. He continued to trade jinxes and hexes, waiting for an opening in his casting lineup. There! “Wingardium leviosa!” Rocks from all around Harry’s feet rose up and spun around him like moons orbiting a planet.

The crowd let out a small gasp.

Susan’s eyes widened. A sudden torrent of hexes and jinxes flew towards her. She dodged and shielded as best she could, but with Harry now not bothering to shield, was soon overwhelmed.

“Petrificus totalus!”

The full body bind clipped her side, her whole body seized up, and she collapsed backwards into the anti-impact charmed ground of the arena.

A man set off a stream of white sparks.

“Winner, Harry Potter!”

The crowd roared.

“Did you see that! Mister Potter countered his opponent’s expert use of levitation shielding with an even more impressive display of his own! That had to be second year level, at least!”

The board flashed.

Hufflepuff—0 vs. 1—Slytherin

Harry cast a finite on the Bones Heiress and helped her to her feet. “You fought well.”

Susan grimaced. “Not well enough.”

Harry shook his head. “No, but I’m sure that if this were any other year apart from this one, you would have been the best of the first years, without doubt. That levitation shielding skill is tricky to make work.” He paused as though to think. “… Although there are safer options in a real fight.”

Susan nodded. “That’s what my aunt said, but I figured since I didn’t have the skill or power for them yet …”

“Oh, certainly.” He smiled at her. “I suggest you get back now. If I stay here talking to you any longer, I fear my brother will bust a blood vessel.” And indeed, John was glaring at them from all the way across the arena.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

In the stands above the Hufflepuff team, Miss Sally Smith, daughter of the Light branch of the Noble House of Smith and Heiress Hannah Abbott of the Noble House of Abbott, watched their close friend trudge back to her team.

“I can’t believe Susan lost,” Sally said, absentmindedly fiddling with a tiny ornate hammer hanging on a chain around her neck.

Hannah eyed the tiny hammer with a longstanding twinge of envy. Her friend sometimes carried the full sized version at formal gatherings—something she’d always wanted to do ever since she’d first seen Sally with it at her fifth birthday party, dragging it along the floor the way other girls would drag a favourite doll. Some noble houses got all the fun toys. She drew her eyes back to the arena. “I can’t believe Slytherin Potter managed that trick with the rocks.”

The two girls looked at each other.

“You don’t think …” Sally started.

“… that Susan wasn’t exaggerating about the Potters?” Hannah finished.

They shrugged and turned back to the arena.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John’s second opponent had swaggered into the centre of the arena, confident in his ability to take care of the lucky first year. Oh, little Su Li might have gone on and on about how he shouldn’t underestimate him, but really, he’d been training like a madman all year. He doubted the boy-who-lived could even pull off a stunner or a disarming charm.

The bagpipes sounded, the duel began, and the second year Ravenclaw soon realised something horrifying. The boy-who-lived could do stunners, could do disarming charms, and seemed fucking possessed, seemingly not even fighting against him, but against his own brother, if the kid’s determination to float enough rocks around him to damn a moderately sized stream was anything to go by.

A stray disarming charm slammed into him and launched him backwards with enough force to roll him across the ground like a rag-doll. Ouch.

The board flashed.

Gryffindor—2 vs. 0—Ravenclaw

The crowd roared.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry shot his brother an amused look as he strolled to the centre of the ring for his next duel. “Trying to prove something?” he called to John’s retreating back.

John turned and gave him a self satisfied smirk before continuing to walk away.

Heh.

The second year Hufflepuff regarded him with determined, yet wary, eyes.

Harry gave him an encouraging smile. “Just do your best.”

The bagpipes sounded and they started. It soon turned out that the second-year-Hufflepuff’s best wasn’t even on par with the Bones Heiress’. Harry mentally sighed as he revived the stunned boy from the ground, conscious of the now far more enthusiastic roar of the crowd.

“Lords and Ladies! Witches and Wizards! Both John Potter and Harry Potter have defeated two of the opposing teams and will go on to face the third years! An amazing performance!”

The board flashed.

Hufflepuff—0 vs. 2—Slytherin

—DP & SW: TFoP—

In a front row seat, Dumbledore reached into his paper bag, withdrew an orange bean, and ate it. Tangerine.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Of course, all winning streaks have to come to an end, and our John Potter is going to find the going tough against his next challenger. With two whole years on him, has luck run out for the boy-who-lived?”

John Potter smirked up at the commentator box and made a dismissive gesture towards it.

“Oh! He seems confident! That’s what we like to see!”

The boy opposite him watched him with eyes as hard as beads.

John took his stance and waited.

The bagpipes sounded and a column of enchanted fire scorched itself straight towards him. Oh yes, third year—elemental charms. He flicked his wand and bellowed, “Ventus divinum!” (Divine Wind)

A gust of magical wind surrounded him in a whirlwind of power, bending the flames away and giving him the opening he needed. He ducked under the moving flame column, rolled into the clear, jumped up, deflected another column of fire, and ran straight at his shocked beyond belief opponent. “Stupefy!”

The fire stopped.

The thud of a human hitting the ground sounded all around the arena, louder than a blasting curse in the total silence.

A man at the edge raised his wand and shot out white sparks.

The commentator seemed to hesitate. “I … I didn’t just see that, did I?”

The board flashed.

Gryffindor—3 vs. 0—Ravenclaw

Silence.

Then the cheering started.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Can you believe that?!” Ron Weasley jumped up and down, pointing and screaming at the top of his lungs. “I never knew John could do all that! Why didn’t he tell me!”

Beside him, Seamus Finnigan and Neville Longbottom looked equally flabbergasted.

“Those were third year spells,” Neville almost whispered, but still loudly enough to be heard. “Third year.”

“And mighty impressive ones, as well.” Seamus added.

“Do you think he’d be willing to teach us?” Neville asked.

Ron shot him an incredulous look. “You want extra lessons? You’re mad, mate.”

“What I want, is not to be bottom in year.” Neville said quietly. “Even the muggleborns do better than me.”

Seamus shot him a look. “Nev, Granger is beating everyone in the rankings—least that’s what I heard from one of the claws.”

Neville smiled weakly. “She doesn’t count. She’s pureblood in all but blood.”

“Guys!” Ron shouted at them, “Focus! John is kicking Ravenclaw arse!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry walked out into the arena for round three without fuss.

Suddenly everything had gone very quiet. He could feel the anticipation, the expectation, the wonder of two thousand people gazing down at him—would this Potter also be able to match a third year?

His opponent stood opposite him wearing long strawberry blonde hair tied back in a ponytail and eyes that warily said, ‘don’t even think about it because that CANNOT happen to me.’

“If I might suggest,” Harry began, “a strategy of taking me down as quickly as possible with as little time messing about as possible.”

The Hufflepuff witch’s right eye twitched.

They took their stances.

The bagpipe sounded, and both Harry and the girl shouted, “Ventus divinum!” (Divine Wind)

Minor gale force winds smashed into each other, each wrestling for advantage, spinning tiny tornadoes off around the arena, kicking up dirt and dust, obscuring the crowd’s view and bringing a worried expression to the girl’s face.

Somewhere out there, the commentator shouted, “Magical Merlin!”

Now slightly hidden from both the crowd and his opponent, Harry smirked and pumped rather more than a third year’s power into the spell. The storm quickly intensified and Harry suddenly sensed a panicky intent-to-stay-still ripped from its footing and helplessly dragged around the arena. “Stupefy!”

The magical intent vanished.

He cut his own elemental charm.

The dust storm slowly started to settle.

An unconscious third year lay on the far side of the arena.

The man at the edge of the arena shot white sparks into the air.

As with his brother, the crowd stayed silent for far longer than normal before sporadic clapping chained into uproarious applause.

“Lords and Ladies! Mister Potter! Mister Potter will go onto his fourth year opponent! Gryffindor and Slytherin are steamrolling the competition!”

The board flashed.

Hufflepuff—0 vs. 3—Slytherin

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John Potter eyed his brother leaving. Those were third year charms. Harry shouldn’t know third year charms. Harry had been a second year when he’d been sent to Azkaban. … Unless of course, his twin had spent the last year practising forward, just like he himself had. Yes, that would be it.

“Oi, kid.”

John shook himself and looked around to see his next opponent. The height difference was now extremely noticeable. Oh, yeah. He had a fourth year to beat. Better start taking it a bit more seriously.

The bagpipes sounded.

He flung an over-powered banishing charm straight at his opponent who, predictably, threw up a shield, clearly thinking that enough for whatever John could throw at him. The banisher smashed straight through the shield and John’s follow up stunner sailed right on-through, completely uncontested, straight into the fourth year’s stomach.

John might only theoretically be a year older than the boy, but he knew his power was now closer to that of a seventh year. He had been chosen in a fair comparison by the goblet of fire, after all, despite himself being only a fourth year at the time.

His fourth year opponent hit the ground with a thud.

At the edges of the arena, the Gryffindor and Slytherin teams sat in unsurprised resignation, while the Ravenclaw and Hufflepuff teams goggled.

“I … I …” The commentator seemed lost for words. “John Potter defeats his fourth year opponent and goes on to his fifth year challenger.”

Instead of breaking into applause, the crowd just stared.

Somewhere outside the arena, a cricket chirped.

John Potter rolled his eyes. “Come on!” he bellowed into the silence , pumping a fist into the air. “Don’t tell me that wasn’t worth a round of applause!”

More silence.

Then, it started, slowly and hesitantly, as though unsure if others were going to join in, before picking up speed and crashing around the arena in a thunderous round of applause.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

At the still empty healing station, Madam Pomfrey clapped politely. “Milking it, isn’t he?”

Dumbledore watched John Potter jump around the arena encouraging the audience to ever greater and greater roars of approval. “Genius such as that often comes with a large ego—so long as it’s controlled I dear say it’s fine to let children have their moments of triumph.”

Pomfrey chuckled. “Indeed—and it’s good he’s only used stunners to finish off his opponents so far. I greatly dislike it when they start chucking around elemental magic—fire and lightning especially.”

Dumbledore nodded and reached into his paper bag for another Bertie Bott’s Every Flavour Bean, absentmindedly withdrawing a red one.

Madam Pomfrey eyed it suspiciously. “Do be careful with those, Headmaster. I once had one just like that—turned out to be cayenne pepper—really blew up in my face.”

Dumbledore looked at the bean with slightly wide eyes. “Oh, dear me.” He put it back in the bag. “Yes, pepper—wouldn’t want that.” He withdrew a green one and popped it in his mouth instead. He chewed thoughtfully before making a face. “Envy.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Can Harry Potter match his brother’s performance! Next to try and take down the seemingly unstable twin forces of Gryffindor and Slytherin is Hufflepuff fourth year, Cedric Diggory!”

Harry walked into the centre of the arena, controlled and stoic, an obvious contrast to the exuberant and loud attitude of his twin.

Diggory smiled at him. “We should have listened to Susan. I guess that’s what you get for not taking seriously the words of someone on your side—most un-Hufflepuff of us.”

Harry bowed. “How would you like this? Quick and painless or long and drawn out?”

Cedric’s eyes sharpened. “John Potter won because his opponent made the mistake of thinking a first year banishing spell could never breach a fourth year shield. I now know better.”

Harry nodded. “And yet, there may still be things you do not know. Just like your second year seed thought he’d learned all he needed to know from watching my fight with Heiress Bones.”

Cedric smiled again and made a gracious arm sweep. “That, I cannot deny.”

“Quiet please!”

The crowd quietened.

Harry’s eyes narrowed. This guy seemed a decent sort. Long and drawn out it was then—complete with opportunity to impress.

The bagpipes sounded, both Harry and Diggory shielded, and Diggory made an immediate dash for the pond, his long legs carrying him faster than Harry’s shorter ones could. “Aqua anima!” (Water animation)

A large blob of water rose from the pond’s surface and formed itself into a vaguely human shape.

The crowd made appreciative ‘Ooooooo’ noises.

“Oh! A fourth year using water animation!”

Harry caught up and started trading hexes and jinxes.

“It seems it’s not only our twin Potter phenoms who can cast above their weight!”

The water golem covered the distance between the pond and Harry, made a wild swing at him, and found it’s fist connecting not with him, but with a large boulder levitated straight up off the ground. Its fist splashed into unformed water.

Harry ran at Diggory and continued to push him back.

The water golem reformed and made the short trip across the arena to where Harry was now playing with his tiring opponent.

Harry dodged a particularly close hex and shouted, “Ventus divinum!” (Divine wind!)

Diggory seemed barely able to stand on his feet and was clearly running straight from his core. He desperately flicked his wand and directed his water golem to deform, acting as a shield against the savage wind.

Harry’s eyes lit up. Opportunity. He cast a powerful banishing spell at the water shield, watched it splash into the fourth year puff, and shouted, “Fulgur Stupefy!” (Lightning stunner)

Crack!

In an instant, a thin bolt of magical lightning arced onto a patch of wet ground and travelled up onto the now soaking boy.

There was a moment of silence, the remaining water collapsed onto the ground, and Diggory followed moments later.

The board flashed.

Hufflepuff—0 vs. 4—Slytherin

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The crowd erupted.

Sophie Roper hung over the railing, trying to get a better look at what was going on from the other side of the arena. “That’s the boy that beat Hermione in the Slytherin tryouts!? No wonder Hermione lost! I mean, look at him go!”

Lisa Turpin laughed and whooped. “I told you! I told you Harry wasn’t just some loser! I bet Slytherin House is quaking in their boots!”

Padma Patil watched with a worried expression. “This isn’t normal. John and Harry Potter—they shouldn’t be able to do things like this. It’s too much. It’s like something out of an Arthurian legend.”

Lisa shook her shoulder. “Come on! Stop being a worry wart. Granger can do amazing things well above year, can’t she?”

Padma gave her a look. “Yes, but she still couldn’t go toe to toe with someone of those years. There’s a difference between having the skill to cast spells, and having the power needed to fight with them.”

Sophie leaned over the railings to stare at them. “Will you stop it, Padma! Look at Hermione!”

They looked over to where Granger was cheering and shouting her lungs out with the other Slytherins.

“If Hermione isn’t worried, there’s probably nothing to worry about.”

Lisa gave Sophie a half-lidded look. “Not that I don’t want to agree with you, but I sometimes think you put too much faith in Granger.”

Sophie giggled. “Lies!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Another water golem lumbered towards John Potter, slightly larger than the one Harry fought against, Diggory’s magical power not being quite on the level of his now fifth year opponent.

John jabbed his wand at the ground. “Terra golem!” (Earth Golem)

The dirt slowly rose up and formed itself into a vaguely humanoid shape, slightly larger even than the water golem.

The crowd gasped again.

The two golem’s crashed together, water pressed against dirt, the resultant mud occasionally breaking away from the animation charms, and splatting down onto the ground.

John ducked around the wrestling golems and sprinted towards his wide eyed opponent.

The resultant jinx and elemental duel wasn’t as easy as the ones before, but the result was the same.

The fifth year Ravenclaw thudded into the ground and the water golem fell like a dropped bucket, the liquid forming a small wave and quickly spreading out into a giant puddle.

John bent over and leaned on his thighs for a moment, breathing hard before standing up and pumping his fist in the air.

The board flashed.

Gryffindor—5 vs. 0—Ravenclaw

The crowd went wild.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Pansy shouted and screeched “Draco! This is nuts!”

Draco Malfoy could only agree. Hearing about John and Harry Potter defeating their entire Duelling teams was one thing—seeing it actually play out in front of him was something else. Terrifying was the word that sprung to mind. Suddenly, he couldn’t help feeling that he’d been missing something important since coming to Hogwarts. The way Harry Potter walked, maybe? The way he spoke? Something anyway.

Why oh why had father insisted he distance himself from Potter?

“Well, Draco?” Theo gave him a sideways glance before returning his eyes to the Gryffindor first year basking in glory in the middle of the arena.

Draco frowned. He didn’t know what to do. Every political instinct in his body, drilled into him since he was old enough to speak, was screaming at him to get Potter back on their side, immediately—but on the other hand, father said Potter was to be isolated. “I …” He swallowed. “I’m not sure.”

Theo and Pansy gaped at him.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry dodged a stunner hex chain, shielded against a stray banishing charm, and continued to casually side step his way towards the massive log on the far side of the arena.

His opponent’s earth golem caught up with him and raised its fist over him like the hammer of Thor.

“Wingardium Leviosa!”

The golem lifted off the ground, its fist connecting with nothing but air, and proceeded to flail uselessly in mid air.

The crowd gasped.

Harry reached the log, shielded another jinx chain, flicked his wand, and in-between dodging and shielding, yelled, “Diffindo! Diffindo! Diffindo! Diffindo! Ligna Golem!” (Wood Golem)

The log sliced apart into twelve pieces. A large wooden golem formed itself and stood up, its joints nothing but air, and roared.

The commentator stammered. “Oh, now he’s just taking the piss! I … I mean …”

With the earth golem still floating helplessly in the air, the wood golem charged at the fifth year Ravenclaw wizard who shouted, “Depulso!” (Banishing charm), watched his spell bounce off the rapidly approaching wooden monster, squeaked, threw his wand away, and put his hands up, rapidly backing away and yelling, “I GIVE UP!”

Harry lowered his wand.

The board flashed.

“Hufflepuff—0 vs. 5—Slytherin”

“That was incredible! Lords and Ladies, wizards and witches! Surely, the kind of performance we’d expect from a talented seventh year! Just how much are the Potter twins holding back on us?!”

Harry resisted the urge to duck his head like a sheepish boy caught in the sweetie jar. Perhaps he had overdone that one just a little.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“YES! YES! YES!” Hermione jumped up and down screaming and shouting, paying no attention to the nearby Slytherin’s giving her odd looks. “GO HARRY! GO HARRY! GO HARRY!”

Daphne gave her friend an amused look, barely containing a massive grin of her own. “How much of this is an act and how much is you genuinely unable to control yourself while watching Harry pound random people into the ground? “

Hermione grinned at her in return before adopting a fake look of snooty indifference. “Heiress Greengrass, as a prominent member of Slytherin house, it is your duty to support its champions in their struggles to win us glory.”

Daphne’s badly contained grin broke into a full on ear to ear affair. “I guess you are correct, vassal, it is only right and proper.” She leaned over the railings and screamed, “GO HARRY!”

Tracey goggled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John was sweating. Things were getting a lot more difficult now and his opponent not having to speak her spells made everything that much tougher. He’d been practising like crazy all year, but he still only had half his repertoire down silent so far.

Hexes and jinxes flew all over the arena.

His opponent was using every advantage she could.

John could feel he was still more powerful, if barely, but the athletic witch opposite him had clearly been training physically for years. While he was starting to tire, she still danced around his spells as though she’d only just started. Blue, green, red, pink, white—lights of every colour flashed between them.

John barely managed to shield a stray stunner while banishing away a trio of tiny dirt golems, circling around him like sharks waiting for the chance to strike. Right. He scowled. Enough was enough.

He pointed his wand, made a complicated wand movement, summoned every thought and feeling of righteousness he could muster, and shouted the spell his father had taught him to deal with the dragon in the first task of the Triwizard Tournament. “Rectus Patronum!” (Knight Patronus)

Silvery mist shot out of his wand and swiftly formed itself into a seven foot tall knight in armour, complete with sword and shield.

The crowd made appreciative gasps and OOoooos.

“Wow! Look at that!”

The misty knight darted in front of John and deflected away a hex with its shield.

“The famous knight patronus of the Ancient and Noble House of Potter!”

John used the space in his casting line up to start pushing his determined opponent back.

“One of the most famous Potter family spells! Not seen in public since the last war!”

More and more spells bounced off the misty knight’s shield.

“Are these two ever going to stop surprising us!”

John found an opening in the girl’s guard.

A stunner landed.

She fell.

The crowd exploded.

“I guess not! John Potter wins!”

The board flashed.

Gryffindor—6 vs. 0—Ravenclaw

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry watched his brother leave the arena with a thoughtful expression. Potter family magic. Just what kind of other goodies did his brother have access to in the Potter library? He sure didn’t know. Maybe that would be his next project once they got the stone?

“Quiet please!”

Harry snapped back to the present. Where were they?

The boy opposite him scowled.

Oh, yes. Year six. Silent casting.

The bagpipes sounded.

They both raised their wands and began a formidable duel of hexes, jinxes, charms, elemental magic, and animation magic, all in total silence.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lord Smith watched with wide eyes as this little Harry Potter—and that James and Lily had a second son who was also Jonathan’s twin was news, wasn’t it?—He watched as this little Harry Potter, with his handmade duelling robes and muggle clothes, wiped the floor with the much larger sixth year Hufflepuff boy using sixth year spells that even his brother seemed to be having problems with.

“You know,” Lord Smith said, turning to the young Lord Lovegood as the crowd erupted into hysterics again, “If you’re trying to win me over to the Gray, you’re not really selling it very well. The way I see it, the future is with the Light.”

Lovegood smiled. “Harry is Gray.”

Lord Smith’s eyebrow rose in surprise.

“James and Lily Potter dumped him with magic hating muggle relatives and the boy has little love for them. Combine that with the fact that neither his father nor mother have said or written him a single word since he returned to the wizarding world and … well … I think you see the picture.”

Lord Smith frowned. “That seems … rather out of character.”

Lord Lovegood shrugged.

Lord Smith returned his gaze to the arena. “Hmmmm.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And here we are! This has been a first round for the record books! We are watching history here! No doubt about it! But can the Potter twins complete their unprecedented win streak and beat ALL SEVEN of their opponents without their team mates having to even lift their wands?”

John Potter scowled.

“We’re about to find out!”

Harry wasn’t supposed to be this good. Yes, they should be equally powerful, but he had a full two years on Harry. This was supposed to be his moment of glory.

“Quiet please!”

He focused onto his opponent. He’d just have to beat this guy and stomp Harry into pieces in the finals before sending him where he belonged.

The crowd quietened.

The seventh year Ravenclaw didn’t scowl. He didn’t growl or make any threatening movements. His entire being seemed focused on the fight about to start.

Bagpipes sounded.

The Ravenclaw immediately hit himself on the head with his wand and shimmered into the background, all but invisible.

“Homenum Revelio!” “Ventus divinum!” (Divine Wind)

The duel started in earnest. John used his detection spells every few seconds, keeping his opponents location pinned as well as he could while using area of effect spells to flush him out, relying on his elemental wind charm to hinder the claw’s movements.

Seeing that his strategy wasn’t working, the claw gave it up, quickly reverting to a more standard duel.

“Rectus Patronum!” (Knight Patronus)

“And there it is again!”

Back and forth they went. John would tire and his opponent would take advantage, only to be fended off by a still bright, but slowly dimming misty knight. Then his opponent would tire and the tables would turn, only for his opponent to make use of his longer legs and put enough space between him and John to rest up and return again.

John panted. His lungs felt like they were going to collapse. This wasn’t good. If it hadn’t been for his family magic, he’d have lost already.

Water swirled out of the pond and formed itself into a medium sized golem.

John’s heart leapt. That he could use! He desperately ran straight into his opponent’s dead-zone, abandoning his misty knight, shielding against every spell flung against him, feeling his magic rapidly depleting, urging his burning limbs forward, casting one overpowered banishing charm at the water golem, and then, just like he’d seen Harry do, put the last remains of his magic into his wand and bellowed, “Fulgur Stupefy!” (Lightning stunner).

There was a massive crack, the Ravenclaw captain stilled, limbs limp in the air and underneath, and then he fell, forward, hitting the ground like a sack of coal.

Silence.

The board flashed.

Gryffindor—7 vs. 0—Ravenclaw

John gave a weak smile, vaguely aware of people shouting and cheering, before collapsing forward in an exhausted heap.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry watched John and the seventh year Ravenclaw being carried off to the healing station. It looked like John wouldn’t be watching his final duel. Shame. Just so long as he was up and about for his arse whopping when Slytherin came to duel Gryffindor.

In front of him stood a witch with short pink hair and a look of mild awe on her face. Something about her was ringing bells in his head. He gave a little bow. “Looking forward to this, Miss … ?”

The girl shook herself and grinned. “Tonks, just Tonks—and hell yeah I am!”

Tonks … Tonks … Harry’s eyes widened. The metamorph auror! He smiled. “Same—hey, is that colour natural?”

“What, this?” Tonks pointed at her hair, mischief shining in her eyes. The hair shifted to lime green. “You prefer?”

“Can you do emerald green with silver streaks?”

Tonks stuck out her tongue at him. “No, but I can do this.” Her hair shifted to yellow with black streaks.

“Fitting.”

“Sure is!” Tonks looked around quickly. She turned back to him. “Just between the two of us, kid—Holy crap, you kick ass.”

Harry couldn’t help but grin. Oh, he liked this one. “I’m sure you, ‘kick ass’, too.”

Tonks winked at him. “Might have a few tricks up my sleeve.”

“Quiet please!”

Ahh. Time. He took up his position and watched Tonks do the same.

The bagpipes sounded and Tonks immediately jumped into four copies.

Whoa. High level illusions.

The two started trading silent jinxes and hexes, Harry simply ignoring every spell thrown by one of the illusions, grinning all the while.

Tonks cursed. “What the hell!”

Harry couldn’t help laughing. He spun his wand and jumped into four copies of his own. “Have fun!”

Tonks’ eyes widened. She immediately summoned what seemed to be half a rockery and banished them towards the illusions.

Harry let them go straight through them, only bothering to shield himself.

“Hah!” Tonks disillusioned herself.

Harry cancelled his illusions and disillusioned himself. “Hah, right back at you!”

Then he sensed Tonks forming intent to stun from only a few feet away. He shielded, stepped forward, tripped her up, and cast a finite on her, watching her shimmer incredulously back into view.

He danced away, cancelling his own charm, smiling widely, and giving her time to get up. Now, This was just like his times with Ginny.

The announcer voice cut through his fun. “Well, will you look at that! Young Mister Potter giving his opponent time to get up! No doubt he could have had her then!”

Tonks now stood and watched Harry, eyes shining. “Morgana’s saggy tits! Fighting you is like fighting the wind!”

Harry flicked his wand in the air. “Oh, it is, is it?”

A wind stirred.

“Crap!”

Harry laughed and gave it a good amount of umpf—good for what he could do with this wand, anyway.

Tonks fought for her footing, not casting anything of her own, just letting the storm rush past her, shielding her face from the dirt and dust with her forearms.

Eventually, seeing she wasn’t going to take the bait, Harry let the storm die down. “Not going for it?”

Tonks smirked. “I’ve seen you do that trick before. It’s nothing new.”

“Oh, you want to see new stuff, do you?”

“Sure—and don’t think you’ve seen all I can offer either.”

The crowd listened with baited breath. The commentator stayed silent.

“Well,” Harry swept his arm to the stands. “We are here to put on a show.” He turned back to Tonks, raised his wand, grinned, and immediately spat out three spells at Tonks, one white, one pink, one brown. White—Pink—Brown. Instantly, a large smoke cloud filled the space where Tonks stood, there was a loud umpf sound, the kind of sound someone might make when the fall on their bum, and a loud crack sounded around the arena.

Silence.

Harry tilted his head and quickly shielded as a torrent of hexes and jinxes spat themselves out of the cloud illusion.

The illusion faded to reveal what looked like Tonks stepping over his zero friction charm on animated stepping stones made of animated dirt, continuing to hail down spells on him all the way. Harry could tell it was just another illusion though.

He stayed still and continued to shield against the incoming fake spells, all the while keeping track of the real Tonks, who’d disillusioned herself, slipped out of the back of the cloud illusion, and was now making her way around Harry’s flank.

Harry smirked, shield still facing forward. He then felt intent to stun from the real Tonks and a stunner flew straight at him from a seemingly empty patch of air.

And for his final trick …

He turned and swatted the stunner away, dispelling the shield and letting illusion Tonks’ spells pass harmlessly through him.

Tonks shimmered back into sight. “Oh, Come ON!” Clearly frustrated, she fired another stunner at him.

He swatted it away.

She tried again.

He swatted it away again.

It quickly devolved from there. Tonks walked slowly towards him like an inferi, eyes narrowed, casting spell after spell and making no effort to defend herself against anything.

Harry just stood there, swatting away everything. Eventually she stood just six feet away, and not a single spell had landed on him. He could see the incredulity in her eyes, the utter disbelief of what was going on in front of her. Time to end this. “Tonks?”

Tonks continued to chain spells as fast as her core would let her. “Yeah?”

“Good fight.” And from only six feet away, he spat a mild stunner straight at her, hitting her in the chest and crumpling her on the ground.

Silence.

Not even the shoot-white-sparks-man moved.

Harry didn’t shout like his brother. He didn’t scream and pump his fist in the air—instead, he stood there in his plain, homemade duelling robes, turned to each of the four quarters of the duelling arena in turn, and bowed.

Then the applause started—and it was deafening.

The board flashed.

Hufflepuff—0 vs. 7—Slytherin

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry Potter could spell swat. Dumbledore sat amid the clapping and cheering crowd. How had he missed that before? Had the boy been hiding it, or had he just not being paying attention? As soon as Harry had started letting Miss Tonks’ illusion spells pass straight through him, the fact that the boy could sense magic was obvious. Suddenly, a lot of little mysteries about the boy seemed to make a lot more sense. For starters, that he could disillusion himself solved the mystery of how the boy was so effectively able to evade him. Also, it was now clear that Harry’s occlumency wasn’t just an enclosed steel wall as thick as a mountain—no, it was far more sophisticated than that.

Dumbledore popped a brown bean from his paper bag and chewed. Blurgh … dirt.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

From way up in the back of the arena stands, a certain purple turban wearing individual politely clapped, a slight smirk playing around his cold dark face.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

All around the arena, frantic whispers and excited shouts fought with each other for attention.

Students ran all the way up the grounds to the castle, to all four common rooms, to shout the message to all those who’d not bothered to show to the tournament. John Potter and Harry Potter had both defeated all seven of the Ravenclaw and Hufflepuff team members and would be facing off against each other in the next match in less than an hour! Those students who were lazing around in the common rooms frantically shoved parchments and books into bags and stampeded for the arena. Those who didn’t immediately follow, first rushed to their dormitories to grab friends and dorm-mates before joining the mad scramble.

They squeezed into the arena anyway they could, plopping themselves down wherever they could find a seat. Those unlucky enough to arrive too late, lined the entrances and walkways, making the already filled to capacity arena, standing room only.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John frowned. After waking up and frantically checking that all his special clothing was still in place, only to find Dumbledore had surreptitiously cast a bunch of notice me nots all over it, he watched the gathering crowd with mixed feelings. Harry had also managed to beat his seventh year opponent. He hadn’t seen the fight, but apparently it had been pretty good. His teammates wouldn’t shut up about it. They all seemed worried. Well, they needn’t be.

Hufflepuff faced off against Ravenclaw. Ravenclaw put up a good fight, but in the end, Hufflepuff carried the day with Tonks knocking out her Ravenclaw counterpart with an expertly executed illusion ambush.

The twenty minute break came and went and he felt ready again.

“Lords and Ladies! Witches and Wizards! We will now begin the finals!”

The crowd roared.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“We will now begin the finals!”

The crowd roared.

Harry stood up from his seat among his fellow Slytherins.

Volf eyed him warily. “Oi. Take him out good and hard, you hear?”

Harry nodded and made his way down the steps.

“For Slytherin—Mister Harry Potter!”

The crowd roared again.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

From where he watched in the stands, Dumbledore reached into his paper bag and picked out a red bean.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And for Gryffindor—Heir John Potter!”

John quickly made his way down the steps and out into the arena, crowd screaming in his ears.

In the centre of the arena, he met Harry’s steady gaze with a glare of his own. “Ready to lose?”

Harry smirked. “Ready for anything, but I don’t anticipate losing today.”

“Quiet please!”

John jumped into his duelling stance and watched Harry do the same.

Silence

Then, a bagpipe sounded.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

For anyone watching, it quickly became obvious who had the upper hand. Harry ducked and dove and weaved and swatted with the elegance of a dancer. John pulled out everything he had, but everything he had wasn’t good enough. Even his trump card, his highly effective family spell, the patronus knight, which Harry, for some reason, didn’t also use, barely slowed Harry’s onslaught.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

What the hell! John Potter barley dodged another carelessly flung stunner from his brother. He can’t be better than me! He can’t be! His patronus knight winked out of existence, magic exhausted. I’m Fate’s chosen! NOT HIM!

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore rolled the red bean in his fingers, carefully watching the duel in front of him, straining his magic senses to their very limits for that telltale first sign.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry grinned, happily enjoying totally obliterating his brother so thoroughly that everyone watching could have no doubt who was playing with who. The look on John’s face. That totally out of control panic and denial, and Harry wasn’t even using all the tricks he’d used against Tonks! He carelessly swatted away a stray jinx that John had managed to slip out of his otherwise full on defensive fight.

Heh, well, let’s see how he fares against this! Fumi umbra! (Smoke illusion) A white light shot out towards John’s feet.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore’s eyes sharpened. There! He brought the red bean to his mouth.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Nil frictio Tabul! (Zero friction floor) A pink light shot towards john.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore popped the red bean into his mouth.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Magnus Stupefy! (Area of effect stunner) A brown light followed it.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore bit down, hard.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The brown light shot towards the obscured John Potter and flew straight into the cloud illusion. And a split second later, an explosion blasted out from the illusion, big enough to shake the ground and cause every spectator to instinctively duck their heads.

The cheering immediately stopped.

Harry froze. What the hell? He instantly dispelled his smoke illusion.

The crumpled body of John Potter lay on the floor of the arena, half naked, clothes shredded, and in a rapidly expanding puddle of his own blood.

His expression hardened. “Healer!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione knew instantly that something was wrong. “Daphne!”

“I know!” Daphne had already slung her bag over her shoulder.

“What?” Tracey asked.

Hermione could see Dumbledore starting to make his way towards Harry. She turned to Daphne. “Good luck!”

Daphne nodded back before darting off along the stands.

“Whats going on!” Tracey shouted.

Hermione dashed to the edge of their row of seats. “Just stay here!” Then, without looking back, she leaped down the steps, over the railing, into the arena, and sped towards Harry, only one thought in mind, ‘protect my lord.’

She arrived only a few seconds before Dumbledore got in casting range.

“We need John’s clothes,” Harry hissed while handing her his wand—making it very obvious to everyone watching what he was doing—and slipped his shrunk trunk into her pocket, making that far less obvious.

A red bolt of light shot towards Harry.

Hermione jumped in front of him and shielded. The spell shattered her shield but did deflect it enough to miss its target.

“Miss Granger!” shouted Dumbledore, “Step away from Mister Potter!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The crowd whispered and muttered while Daphne made her way through the them as quickly as possible towards her target. “Heiress Bones!”

The Bones Heiress looked up at her from where she sat among the rest of the Hufflepuff duelling team, looking rather distressed.

“Heiress Greengrass?”

“As the betrothed of Lord Slytherin, I’m calling in one of the three minor favours the House of Bones owes the House of Slytherin. We need your Aunt here, now!”

Susan started, but quickly nodded, reached into her bag and drawing out a mirror. “Amelia Bones.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Miss Granger, step away from Mister Potter and surrender that wand!”

Hermione glared at the old man. “Not a chance!”

“Miss Granger, Mister Potter just tried to commit murder!”

“Harry would never do that! And you have no right to remove Harry’s wand from me now that it is in my possession.”

Another red light shot towards them, brighter this time. Hermione felt Harry’s hand on her forearm and a rush of magic flowed through her.

The stunner bounced off her shield.

Hermione scowled. “Cease your attacks on my person immediately, Headmaster!”

“You are aiding Mister Potter’s resistance of detainment!”

“You have no right to detain Harry!”

“I am the chief warlock of the wizengamot!”

“And you still have no right to detain Harry!”

“I have the right to contain what I believe to be threats to the school and its students!”

“And I have Harry’s wand! Ergo he is not currently a threat!”

“A wand that you are required to surrender to me!”

“I am required to do no such thing! I am only required to surrender it to an on duty member of the department of magical law enforcement, which I shall do once they arrive!”

“You are interfering with evidence!”

“No, I am merely holding it. There are two thousand people here who can see this.” Hermione glanced to her side and saw that Madam Pomfrey had long since reached John and was waving her wand over him. She ground her teeth together. C’mon Daphne.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne rushed back down to the arena from the nearest floo point, Susan and Madam Bones in tow. She barged through a group of milling spectators to see what was going on down in the arena. “There!” she called to the Bones Regent.

Harry and Hermione were in the middle of a tense stand off with Dumbledore and looked like they had been for quite some time. John Potter was lying in the healing station, looking half dead with half a dozen healer trainees bustling around him and Madam Pomfrey.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Miss Granger, your lord would not approve of your actions!”

“It is not your place to speak for my lord, Headmaster! You are not my lord!”

Harry glanced around to see Daphne bearing down on him with the Bones Heiress and Regent Bones behind her. He leaned into her as she arrived. “We need to get those clothes from John into evidence.”

Hermione held up Harry’s wand as Regent Bones stepped into speaking range. “One piece of evidence, Director Bones.”

Daphne stepped over to Susan.

Regent Bones neatly plucked the wand from Hermione’s hand. “Thank you.”

“Amelia!” Dumbledore called. “A word, if you please?”

“Susan,” Daphne whispered. “I’m calling in the second minor favour. We need what’s left of John Potter’s clothing requested as evidence.”

Susan nodded and went to speak with her Aunt who was engaged in a quiet discussion of her own with Dumbledore.

Regent Bones nodded to her and sent her off towards John, much to Dumbledore’s seeming puzzlement.

“Mister Potter.” Regent Bones turned to them, voice crisp and professional. “You are under arrest under suspicion of attempted murder and attempted heir usurpation.”

In Harry’s mind, a second personality immediately leaped onto his dominant one, wrestling it into submission and forcing the rapidly panicking Harry into a space where his out of control intent could be contained.

He took a deep long breath, eyes closed, his arms and shoulders seeming to shudder, and held up his wrists.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“So, was this part of the sales pitch you had planned?” Lord Smith quipped to his younger companion, watching the Potter boy being led away in magical handcuffs.

Lord Xenophilius Lovegood tilted his head. “Let’s call it, one part of a longer campaign. In any-case, I invite you to join me for the trial. If my suspicions are correct, I think you will find it just as interesting as the tournament.”

Lord Smith chuckled as Lovegood stood up.

“And now, if you’ll please excuse me, I think I have a few urgent and important matters to attend to.”

“Of course, of course.”

As Lord Lovegood left, his daughter followed him, pausing only to turn and give him a cheerful parting wave.

Luna Lovegood, wasn’t it?

—End of Chapter Thirty-one—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: Next chapter—Hearing in the DMLE.

A/N: In case anyone cares, Albus’s first experiments (that we know of) into parchment rune activation of larger rune systems resulted in the fidelius tripwire system that Harry voiced his admiration/annoyance for back in chapter twenty-one.

The House of Potter vs The Ministry

Justice in the wizarding world is a recipe gladly served but rarely enjoyed—one part truth to two parts power, add a dash of misdirection and a sprinkling of judicial procedure and bingo, a three star verdict with zero repeat customers. There are few trials by jury. The only wizards privileged to be tried by their peers are peers—and lords tend to stick together. Many minor crimes in the nobility are judged by the accused’s own lord—fine when a lord’s fief contained hundreds or thousands of people, most of them muggles, but less than great when many lords these days ruled over only the members of their own houses.

Attempted murder and heir usurpation, however, were not minor crimes, and thus it was that Albus Dumbledore strode towards the Slytherin common rooms trailed by several DMLE security wizards to secure Harry’s dormitory space before the department of mysteries turned up.

The Slytherin common room opened to the Headmaster’s presence and the little party marched down to the first-year boy’s dormitory. “Topsy!”

A Hogwarts house elf popped in front of the headmaster. “Yes, Headmaster, Sir?”

“Which one of these beds is Mister Potter’s?”

The elf pointed to the far-most bed and before the DMLE security wizards could start setting up the wards around it, Dumbledore performed a quick, unseen switching spell on a candle stick by the bed, replacing it with a special, recently bought and rather dark book hidden in the folds of his robes.

“Thank you, Headmaster,” said one of the security wizards, “we can take it from here.”

Dumbledore smiled a grandfatherly smile. “Of course. Please do let me know if you need anything else, won’t you?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione, Daphne, and Tracey arrived in the Slytherin first-year girl’s dormitory in a swirl of combat ready determination. Well, Hermione and Daphne did, anyway—Tracey just trailed after them, confused and out of breath.

Daphne whipped Harry’s trunk out of her pocket. “C’mon, we don’t have much time.” She put it on the floor and expanded it.

“Time for what?” Tracey’s eyes widened at all the locks on the trunk’s front. “Dear Merlin, Daph. When did you get that!”

Daphne opened the lid. “It’s Harry’s”

Hermione started climbing in.

“It’s Potter’s!?”

Daphne started climbing in after Hermione.

“But I thought his parents had like, all but officially disowned him? That thing must cost a fortune!”

Daphne’s hand appeared over the edge of the trunk and waved at her. “Are you coming?” she called.

Tracey shook herself, climbed into the trunk, and down the first few steps. What she saw next made her eyes widen further. She stood in a small sitting room, complete with comfy looking chairs, bookshelves filled with books, and a writing desk—all old wood, silver fixtures, and emerald green upholstery. Her voice came out as a whisper. “Damn …”

Daphne and Hermione ignored her, already starting to pile up books on the desk and move things about.

She finished the short journey into the room. “I think I’m starting to appreciate Potter’s taste.”

“Here.” Daphne ignored her and chucked Hermione two leather bags.

Hermione angled around Tracey and made a beeline up the stairs again and out of the trunk.

Tracey sat down on the small sofa. “So, what’s going on?”

Daphne briefly paused from where she was thumbing through one of the many books. “We are getting ready to take our leave.”

Tracey blinked. “What?”

“Take our leave. Split. Get out of dodge. Evacuate.”

“You’re leaving! Why?”

Hermione quick-stepped back down the steps—Freekey clutching at her shoulder—and dropped the two leather bags on the floor, now full of assorted clothes, books, and associated detritus.

“Officially, we’re about to be disciplined for being bad little girls.”

Hermione flashed a smirk. “Our lord really isn’t happy with us.” Her face slipped back into stony faced determination before withdrawing a trunk of her own and expanding it on the floor.

Tracey could only stare as Hermione carefully dropped one of the clothes filled leather bags into it. The little monkey jumped down from Hermione’s shoulder, across the trunk, and up onto Daphne’s.

“But that was less than twenty minutes ago—and I still can’t believe you faced down Albus Bloody Dumbledore!”

Daphne looked up from where she stood with the book, idly scratching a chirping Freekey. “Word travels fast.” She snapped the book shut, moved over to Hermione’s trunk and stuck her head inside. “Grandmother, is Father on the way yet?”

An older and distinguished female voice said, “Yes, Daphne, Dear. He left some while ago.”

“Thank you.”

Daphne’s head become visible again. “He’s on the way.”

Tracey eyed Hermione’s trunk with suspicion, mind racing. “So … what’s the unofficial reason you’re leaving?”

Daphne and Hermione shared a glance.

“Sorry, Trace,” Daphne said, “we can’t tell you, but we’ll probably be gone for a while, maybe a few weeks, maybe longer. Hopefully we’ll be back to take the exams.”

Hermione shivered.

Tracey frowned. “You’re going to miss so much.”

Daphne opened her mouth to respond, but a ghostly voice interrupted them. “Miss Greengrass? Miss Granger?” The see-through face of the bloody baron appeared at the trunk’s entrance. “Your head of houses are in the entrance hall to remove you from the school until further notice.”

Daphne turned back to Tracey and handed her the book she’d been inspecting. “Here.”

Tracey looked at the book in confusion.

“Records of all my political doings in the house. Until I’m back, you’re the new leader of the Gray.”

Tracey now looked at the book in sheer panic.

Daphne smirked. “Good luck.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore sighed while sitting in the Potter Manor sitting room. Opposite him sat the distraught Lord James and Lady Lily Potter. He’d done his best to calm them and, importantly for the moment, persuaded them not to grab John and run off to the hall of prophecies. The longer he could put off that phase of the game, the better.

But perhaps most importantly, he’d gotten what he really needed—appointment by Lord Potter to be Harry Potter’s defence council.

Lady Lily conjured another handkerchief and blew her nose again before dropping it on the slowly forming mountain of multicoloured cloth beside her.

He stood up to leave.

Lady Lily sniffed. “Just make sure you do what’s best for our sons, okay?”

Dumbledore smiled a sad smile. “Of course, Lily.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Early next morning, Daphne and Hermione, dressed in grey silk robes with large, face-concealing hoods, walked up a side alley in Hogsmeade village and turned into a street lined on each side by small cottages.

“Number six …” Hermione muttered under her breath, “Number eight. Here it is.”

Daphne stepped over both the fidelius and ward lines and felt the magics welcome her into the house. She walked to the door, opened it, and stepped inside. “Right.”

Hermione joined her, lowering her hood.

They both gazed around the small and simply furnished living room.

“First order of business, let’s get an owl sent off to Dumbledore, if we can.”

Hermione nodded and the two girls quickly found the study. One of the bookshelves contained shelf upon shelf of ornate looking envelopes, thick with parchment, already sealed with the Slytherin head of house ring, and organised alphabetically by intended recipient. Attached to each of the envelopes with a sticking charm, was a second parchment.

Hermione found the Ds, picked up the topmost envelope, and read the attached parchment.

Headmaster Dumbledore,

I must apologise for not being able to accept your invitation. Unfortunately, I have a prior engagement.

Yours with the best of will,

Lord Slytherin, Head of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin

Nope. She grabbed the next one.

On the other side of the room, Daphne had found the owl treats and was treating Macavity to an early morning snack.

Chief Warlock,

I do not tolerate interference in my affairs.

Lord Slytherin

Nope. She tried the next one. It wasn’t until some half-way through the row that she found what she was looking for.

Headmaster Dumbledore,

I apologise for Daphne and Hermione’s behaviour. They will be disciplined.

Lord Slytherin, Head of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin

“There.” She handed the sealed envelope to Daphne. “That should hold him until your Dad can meet him.”

Daphne read it and nodded. “Yes, that should do it.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Lord Greengrass?” Dumbledore raised a surprised eyebrow. “I was expecting to meet Lord Slytherin.”

Lord Greengrass sat himself in the chair in front of the headmaster’s desk. “Unfortunately, my good friend is in the middle of a rather delicate project—one that requires his utmost attention, and he asked if I could be here in his stead.”

Dumbledore’s mind flashed. The mirror—it had to be. Frustrating though it was, there was literally nothing he could do about it. He tugged at his beard. “Well, I hope he’s remembering to take care of himself.”

Lord Greengrass gently nodded his head before leaning forward. “Let’s get straight to the nub of the matter, shall we, Headmaster?”

Dumbledore nodded.

“Both myself and Lord Slytherin are extremely concerned with the Potter boy’s behaviour and, in particular, the influence he seems to hold over my daughter. While it may not have been any of our houses he attacked, it does show what he is capable of. We are worried of what he might become, especially with how powerful he seems to be.”

Dumbledore smiled grimly. “I fully understand such a concern, Lord Greengrass. Although I speak as his defence, I do see that the evidence is overwhelmingly against him.”

“The committee has appointed Crinolow Ogden, Lord Ogden’s daughter in law, for the prosecution, and we intend to push for the harshest sentence possible.”

Albus Dumbledore nodded along.

“The veil.”

Dumbledore froze. His eyes widened. “Lord Greengrass? You cannot be serious!”

“We are serious, Headmaster.”

Dumbledore slumped back in his chair. Harry Potter could not be allowed to go through the veil. No one truly knew what was on the other side. What if the horcrux remained intact? It was unthinkable. “Jacob, the boy is just a child.”

“Best time to do it. I dread to think how difficult it would be to restrain him once he is older.”

Dumbledore rubbed his temples. “Couldn’t you be persuaded to at least push only for life in Azkaban? It means the same thing and Harry Potter would still no longer be a threat to your daughter. Not even the worst of our death eaters got the veil, and if you try to push such a sentence on a boy only nearing twelve, the judges may well balk.”

Lord Greengrass sniffed. “What are you going to be pushing for?”

Dumbledore steepled his fingers. “I believe a sentence of three years in Azkaban would serve the child.”

“Three years! You want to release him back into my daughter’s company as a fifteen year old? Absolutely not!”

“Lord Greengrass, I find it highly unlikely that Harry would still hold the same sway over your daughter after three years apart for her and three years of dementor exposure for him.”

“Maybe, but it is not something I intend to find out. No deals. We’re pushing for the veil.”

When Lord Greengrass eventually left, Dumbledore stared hard at the closed door. Wonderful. Now he had to make sure, not only that Harry was found guilty, but also that the boy wasn’t executed. How did Slytherin manage to be so frustrating even when they were momentarily on the same side?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The sitting room of Greengrass Manor had rapidly become mission control. Several extra desks had been found from the various spare studies and now formed an outer ring with the various sofas and low tables in the large room’s middle. The defence lawyer, Mrs. Crinolow Ogden, much to her bemusement, found herself working aside Daphne and Hermione, who themselves shared a desk next to Luna.

Xeno and Pandora Lovegood also had desks of their own next to Luna’s, although they made use of them far less than their daughter.

Jacob and Sunny Greengrass kept most of their work upstairs, but when working on, ‘The Harry Situation,’ they tended to sit in one of the middle arm chairs, their parchments strewn across one of the low tables in front of them.

The Greengrass house elves kept up a constant stream of tea and biscuits for the many guests who dropped by—some summoned, others merely curious, but all sworn to secrecy by their respective heads of houses.

And finally, sitting alone on Mrs. Ogden’s other side, sat a lonely, empty desk with a small plaque reading, ‘Lord Slytherin.’ It focused the minds of those in the know far better than any pepper up potion could.

Pandora Lovegood scampered into the room, jumped up on one of the middle low tables, bushy tail twitching furiously, and transformed back into a human, fist held up in the air, face scrunched up in a scowl. “I have news.”

Mrs. Ogden looked up from her parchments. “Go on.”

Daphne, Hermione, and Luna all also stopped what they were doing.

“The department of mysteries has a piece of evidence relating to Harry’s case that we didn’t know about. They found a dark arts book by Harry’s bed that contains the curse that Harry allegedly used.”

“That’s ridiculous!” Hermione slammed her hands on the desk in front of her, and stood up, chair shooting backwards. “Harry would never keep something like that by his bed!”

Mrs. Ogden whistled. “Must have been planted before hand.”

“That goat bastard!”

Pandora hopped down from the table and handed Mrs. Ogden and the girls copies of the DoM analysis.

Daphne took the parchments and started to read, biting her lip in worry. It had already been a week. One week for Harry alone and confined in a lower grade version of his own personal hell. She hoped and prayed he was doing okay.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The cell was not uncomfortable—certainly a lot better than Azkaban. There weren’t any soul sucking demons here, which was a plus. On the other hand, in Azkaban he’d never felt like half of him was struggling to rip the other half apart. He sat on his little cot, hands trembling, heart alternating between calm and pounding, trying not to focus on anything in the room—the walls, the door, the bars, anything that would remind him he couldn’t get out. Instead, he practising wandless conjuration the way other prisoners might make paper cranes.

It wasn’t the most productive use of his time, but every second focused on trying, and mostly failing, to form magic into solid objects was an extra second his out-of-control self, currently curled up and whimpering deep in his head, wouldn’t have control of his body.

So far, he’d managed to conjure a tiny glass bead. He played with it in-between trembling fingers, before they lost their tenuous grip and the bead bounced away across the cell, towards the door.

Fuck.

And then he heard footsteps coming from outside. He straightened on his cot.

A white-bearded head with moon-shaped spectacles appeared briefly behind the door’s window bars. There was a clank noise, the door opened, and a purple booted foot carelessly crushed the glass bead lying on the floor. “Good morning, Mister Potter.”

Harry summoned the kind of will power that could just about fend off a legilimency attack from an older Voldemort after five sodding years of steadily escalating, dementor fuelled, mental arms race, and said, “Good morning, Headmaster.”

Dumbledore conjured himself an arm chair. “While I’m shocked and greatly disappointed in your actions, I’m pleased to be able to tell you that your parents have appointed me to be your defence council.”

“Yay.”

Dumbledore ignored his flippancy, took off his glasses, and rubbed his eyes. “Unfortunately, Harry, the evidence speaks for itself and it’s almost certain that you’re going to be found guilty.”

Harry stared blankly at the old man in front of him. Best to struggle at least a bit. “Veritaserum?”

“Veritaserum may not be used on members of noble houses in court.”

“But why not now? At least then you could learn that I am innocent.”

“Even then, the law says that I cannot.”

“I thought my father could authorise it as the head of a noble house with the ministry?”

“No, only pureblood houses—Potter is not a pureblood house.”

Harry’s lip curled. “What about my wand?”

“Unfortunately, someone made a mistake, and I won’t be able to submit that as evidence.”

“How convenient.”

“The prosecution is going so far as to push for the veil—so I’m going to focus my efforts on ensuring that you get the most lenient sentence possible.”

“What is the veil?”

Dumbledore hesitated. “It’s an archway in the department of mysteries—no one knows where it goes, but the legends says it links the land of the living with the land of the dead.”

Harry said nothing.

“So, if you’d just sign this, I can focus on making sure that doesn’t happen.”

Dumbledore handed him a parchment and Harry read it. It was a full confession. He made to hand it back with shaky hands. “No.”

Dumbledore frowned, not accepting the parchment. “Harry?”

“I’m innocent. I’m not signing anything that says otherwise.”

“Mister Potter, I’m not sure you understand the severity of your situation. You have attempted to murder the heir to one of the most powerful houses in magical Britain—your own brother. Even if you don’t get sent through the veil, you could easily be looking at life in Azkaban, unless I am able to convince the court otherwise.”

Harry carefully tore up the parchment as though solving a complex problem and threw it in Dumbledore’s face.

Dumbledore sighed, silently stood, and left, closing the door behind him with another loud clank.

Later that night, Harry lay down in his cot, exhausted, closed his eyes, and thought of the one thing keeping him sane. His world shifted, there was a feeling of movement, and he opened his eyes again. He stood in front of a Mesoamerican pyramid. The world was dark. Lightning and thunder crashed in the sky. Rain whipped around him. Trees bowed and rose like terrified subjects before an evil king. And way above him, a cage containing his other self swung in the air, magic swirling around it like wind around the eye of a tornado.

“Harry!”

Harry turned, shaking, even here, but managed to let his face relax into a smile, just before a red-headed witch collided with him, warm arms wrapping around him, bringing new strength and determination to his otherwise tired mind. “Ginny.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Your ten o’clock is here, Director.”

“Thank you, please send them in.” Director of the Department of Magical Law Enforcement, Regent Amelia Bones leaned back in her chair and waited.

The door opened and a much shorter than expected witch stepped through.

“Miss Greengrass?”

Heiress Greengrass smiled. “Regent Bones.” And made herself comfortable in the chair opposite her.

“What can I do for you?”

“I wish to call on the third and final minor favour owed by the House of Bones to the House of Slytherin.”

Amelia raised an eyebrow. She loved her niece like her own daughter, but sometimes the trouble she got herself into. … Although, arguably, making those kinds of mistakes was exactly what Hogwarts was for. Make them and learn from them where they didn’t matter so much. She observed the young witch in front of her. “Well?”

“You will soon be one of the magistrates sitting in judgement in the case of Harry Potter.”

Amelia frowned. She didn’t like the sound of where this was going. “Yes … ?”

“We wish to use our third minor favour to have you ensure a completely fair trial.”

Amelia blinked. That hadn’t been what she’d expected. “You do realise this is something I will do anyway?”

“Nevertheless.”

Amelia frowned again. “In fact, you’ve used every single one of your minor favours to ensure I do things that it is my job to do anyway.”

Miss Greengrass shrugged. “Then you will have no problems ensuring that the trial is fair?”

Amelia sat in silence for a moment. It seemed a reasonable use of a minor favour, but was there anyway this could backfire on her? Wait … “Miss Greengrass,”—she took a deep breath—“are you asking me to break the law?”

Miss Greengrass quickly shook her head. “No, I would never ask you to break the law—I merely ask that you see your way possible to bend it.”

Amelia narrowed her eyes. “Bend it how?”

“However you see appropriate to ensure a fair trial.”

“However I see appropriate?”

“However you see appropriate.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Sirius Black made his way down to the holding cells of the DMLE. He’d never meant it to turn out like this, but things had just happened, mostly Alex. Alex had happened, and continued to happen on a fairly regular basis.

He checked in with the on-duty guard. “Anything I should know?”

The security wizard shrugged. “He’s pretty quiet most of the time. Tries to put on a strong face, but we can all tell he’s barely holding it in. He shakes all the time and cries out in his sleep.”

Sirius nodded grimly and made his way down the lines of cell doors until he arrived at one towards the end. He knocked on the solid iron and rune covered door. “Knock, knock.”

An eleven year old voice on the other side said, “Come in.”

Sirius opened the door, stepped inside, and couldn’t help the faint in-draw of breath. Merlin, he was identical to John.

The boy on the cot looked up.

Sirius took another step and felt something crunch under his foot.

The boy managed a smile. “Sorry about that.”

Sirius looked down. Hundreds of what looked to be small glass beads littered the floor. Before he could stop himself his inner auror said, “Where did you get these?”

The boy held up a shaky hand, concentrated, and produced a small glass bead in a bright white glow.

Sirius’ eyes widened. “Wow, Harry.”

Harry looked up sharply.

Sirius hesitated. “Ugh, I guess I should tell you who I am, huh?”

Harry slowly shrugged. “You are Lord Sirius Black of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Black—Chief Auror of the Department of Magical Law Enforcement.”

“Ah, yeah, yeah I am.” He took a deep breath. “Do you … do you mind if I take a seat?”

Harry shook his head, so Sirius went back outside and grabbed a chair from one of the many that lined the wall down the hall. Once sitting down back inside the cell he looked Harry in the eyes.

Harry seemed to be in no rush to ask about his sudden appearance, just stared at him as though trying to solve a complex puzzle.

Sirius rubbed the back of his head. He had to admit that he wasn’t sure what he had expected. If the boy sitting in front of him were John, he’d be asking questions faster than Sirius could answer them.

The silence dragged on. Eventually Sirius opened his mouth to speak, but before he could, Harry finally decided to instead.

“Are you my godfather?”

Sirius shifted on his seat. He suddenly found it difficult to look into the kid’s eyes. “Kinda.”

“I had wondered. I knew that you are my brother’s”

“Yeah.”

Harry let out a shuddery breath. “So, why the visit? You choose the most interesting time to become reacquainted.”

Damn, those eyes. Like Lily’s, like John’s, but so old. The kid’s hands still shook. “Are you okay, Harry?”

“No. I’m not okay. I’m soon to be tried for attempted murder and heir usurpation—I’m in a cell I can’t get out of—and I have cleithrophobia.”

“Cleithrophobia?”

“The irrational fear of being trapped. It’s what caused me to blow up one of the Hogwarts classrooms. Right now, I’m using advanced occlumency to stop myself going full Atlantis, but there’s a part of me, deep inside my mind, that’s constantly whimpering in terror.”

Sirius widened his eyes. “What are you doing in here?”

“I’m a prisoner. What am I supposed to do? Tell the guards I’m afraid of being in a cell? Ask if the presumed attempted murderer can have a room at The Leaky Cauldron instead?”

“—You didn’t try to murder John.”

Harry stilled before staring at him for an age. He tilted his head slightly to one side. “Do go on.”

Sirius shifted uncomfortably. That hadn’t been the reaction he’d expected. “I read the report the DoM filed on your wand—just a basic spell chain, it said.” He couldn’t help let out a slight laugh, “Or rather, a really advanced spell chain—Also saw the memories of you and John in the tournament—Couldn’t believe it—Had to get some friends in the DoM to tell me it was all real.”

Harry continued to stare at him.

“So, anyway, it’ll be fine, and you’ll be out of here in no time. Dumbledore will see to that.”

Harry smiled, although Sirius couldn’t help thinking it looked somewhat forced.

Sirius cleared his throat. “So, Harry, I was wondering … once Dumbledore gets you off—”

Harry made a disgusted face.

“—Sorry. I mean, once Dumbledore gets you acquitted, if you’d like to spend some time over the summer with me?”

“Yes, I’d like that.” Harry made a thoughtful face. “Why?”

“Well, it would be a chance for you to spend some time with John, and—”

“—You do know that we hate each other’s guts, right?”

“Maybe you just need some quality time together?”

Harry gave him a half-lidded look. “You’ve seen what we’re capable of. How do you imagine that quality time would go?”

Sirius ignored his new found godson whose dry speech and blank expressions were so different to John’s. “It would also give you a chance to get to know your godfather better—and you could get to know my daughter, Alexandra. She’s going to Hogwarts next year—and you could …” he hesitated, “… watch out for her—you know—if she winds up …” he trailed off lamely.

Harry smirked. The first sign of mirth Sirius had seen on the kid’s face. “In the evil dark snake pit?”

Sirius nodded.

“Sure.”

Sirius let out a small sigh of relief. As much as he dreaded thinking about it, he couldn’t help coming to the conclusion that Alex was going to be sorted into Slytherin House. He’d recently found his daughter sitting cross-legged in the sitting room, clipping articles about Lord Slytherin from the Daily Prophet and Witch Weekly for a moving, magical collage. More than a little disturbing. Hopefully Harry—prodigy, Slytherin, duelling-master Harry—would be able to at least distract her a bit.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

In the following weeks, Daphne and Hermione could think of little else but Harry—all alone and suffering in the dark, willing to endure his own private hell just to manoeuvre the enemy where they needed him.

To keep from going insane, they busied themselves with delving into every little aspect of the case, plotting out every possible point, how to counter it, and how the headmaster might counter their counters. Whenever they weren’t working on the case they kept up with classwork or else practised duelling with Luna, only to find, much to their dismay, just how far behind the shorter blonde witch they were, even when she didn’t have a wand.

Their determination and work ethic did not go unnoticed. “Are you two planning to go into law when you graduate?” Mrs. Ogden asked one day, pouring herself a cup of tea while the girls argued with each other about the finer points of countering a claim of wandless magic.

Jacob was then halfway through telling Mrs. Ogden about Hermione’s healer training when a steely eyed Xenophilius Lovegood walked in.

“No luck,” the Lovegood lord said.

Everyone groaned. Ever since they’d gotten the DoM report back on John’s duelling robes, they’d been trying to pin down exactly how Dumbledore had pulled off that explosion exactly when it needed to happen.

Mrs. Ogden set her tea-cup down with a decisive clink. “We’ll just have to do the best we can with what we have then.”

Everyone nodded.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

[May 20, 1992—The day of the trial—10:00am]

Albus Dumbledore stepped into the court room, old tome and stack of parchments under one arm, looked around, and raised an eyebrow. He supposed he shouldn’t be surprised. The visitor’s gallery held rather more than one would expect for a trial of this type, although, admittedly, few trials had the boy who lived in the witness box as the subject of an attempted murder.

He’d tried several more times to get Harry Potter to confess, even going so far as to stall the trial to give the boy longer to stew down in the cells. His contacts told him the boy didn’t seem to react well to such an environment and he’d hoped that would sway him, but it was all to no avail. The boy had stubbornly refused to sign anything.

At the front of the room, Regent Bones, Madam Marchbanks, and Regent Longbottom sat in the judges’ chairs.

Dumbledore walked to his lectern on the left side of the room, opened the book in front of him, and shuffled his parchments. He looked around at the visitor’s gallery again. Even Lord Malfoy was here … he hadn’t expected that.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lucius Malfoy carefully watched Albus Dumbledore watching him, painfully aware that he was the only member of the Dark in the room. The other watchers were either members of the press, the Light or the Gray.

He held his wand-concealing cane slightly tighter in his hands.

Over a month ago, Draco had sent him the memory of Harry Potter duelling in the tournament. Impossible he’d thought. No mere eleven year old could be that good. Then he’d analysed the boy’s fighting style and came to the same blood chilling conclusion he’d come to with Lord Slytherin—a conclusion that nevertheless explained just how Harry Potter could be so much better, even than his own twin brother. Harry Potter was also Dark Lord Voldemort. He was another memory, just like the diary. When he’d told the diary what he’d found, Riddle had immediately ordered him to cease their current plan—planting the diary on an unsuspecting first year to unleash the beast within the chamber of secrets. They needed more information, he’d said. They needed to find out just what his other selves where up to.

The quiet babble of conversation washed around him from the other gathered spectators.

It was a question that terrified him. Why had Voldemort changed his identity to Lord Slytherin? How had he? And why had he gone to the trouble of forming an entirely new faction out of the former neutrals? Did Voldemort believe him and all those who evaded Azkaban to be traitors? Did the Dark Lord believe them all to be failures who’d one day need to be hunted down just like he’d once upon a time hunted down mudbloods and blood traitors? Or had he just formed the Gray with the intention of integrating it into the Dark at a later date? But if so, then why not tell him? Lucius shivered.

Hopefully this trial, and subsequent cooperation with Slytherin—and presumably, Potter—would shine some light on these questions in his favour.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Took them long enough,” Lord Smith said to his companion with the air of someone settling down to watch a good quidditch match.

Lord Lovegood, who’d just arrived, politely inclined his head. “I believe the defence has been stalling for time. No idea why though.”

“You seem very confident your boy will come out of this with nothing to worry about.”

“I am.”

“And if they find him guilty?”

Lord Lovegood smiled. “Then I suspect my daughter will level Azkaban.”

Lord Smith chuckled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John Potter hated this. His parents had been fussing over him from the moment he’d woken up and hadn’t let up since.

“Now, straighten your robes.”

“Yes, Mum.”

“And remember to say nothing but the truth when they call you.”

“Yes, Mum.”

His mum looked around the court room, distracted, nervous, and seemingly near tears.

His dad put a comforting hand around her shoulders. “It’s okay, Lily. Albus won’t let him go through the veil.”

“He should.” John blurted out.

“John Potter!” his mum hissed at him so as not to be heard over the background hum of conversation. “You will not speak about your brother like that!”

“I just don’t understand why you two aren’t angry at him!” John bit back, scowling and sticking his hands in his robe pockets. “He tried to kill me!”

His dad looked at him sternly. “But you are not dead, and he’s going to get plenty of time to think about what he did wrong—and by the time he’s out, things may well have changed, and we might even be able to spend time with him again.”

John had to keep himself from gagging. Didn’t they understand just how dangerous Harry was?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry conjured another glass bead. Conjuration was a lot more difficult than transfiguration and required more magic, but the results lasted longer. While transfiguration was limited by the material the magic flowed through, conjured items were magic.

Thousands of glass beads littered the floor of the ministry cell. Spaced out among them sat the occasional more ambitious piece—here, a tiny glass apple, there, a tiny glass snitch, and right in front of where he sat, a tiny glass ice-cream cone, complete with three scoops of ice-cream, the culmination of over a month of practise.

The door clanged and opened. “Mister Potter?” said one of the guards. “It’s time.”

Harry took a deep breath and stood up, crunching glass beads as he left. The guard attached himself to him with a chain, and together they walked through the hallways of the ministry in relative peace—although the occasional worker did give them a second glance.

The doors to the courtroom swung open and all heads turned to him.

He was led into the middle of the courtroom and deposited into a horribly familiar chair. Instantly, magical chains leaped up and curled themselves around his wrists and ankles. His hands started to shake again.

In front of him, and on the left side, stood the defence—Dumbledore—and on the right side, stood the prosecution—a woman he recognised as Mrs. Crinolow Ogden. Directly ahead of him sat three woman he had no problems remembering—Regent Bones, Regent Longbottom, and Madam Marchbanks—the same three judges who’d sentenced him last time around.

A good start, that.

Regent Bones raised her wand and a small canon blast came out of it. “We are now hearing the case of The Ancient and Noble House of Potter versus The Ministry of Magic. Harry James Potter, you are accused of attempted murder and attempted heir usurpation, how do you plead?”

Dumbledore cleared his throat. “My client pleads …”

Harry almost thought he heard Dumbledore sigh.

“… Not guilty.”

Regent Bones nodded. “Very well. We’ll first have the defence and prosecution read their opening statements—Albus, if you would?”

“Your honours, while the evidence, unfortunately, speaks for itself, I intent to show that Mister Potter should not be held to the same standards of punishment that might usually be meted out for such a crime. Since Mister Potter has entered our world, he has shown himself to be a talented and resourceful student who, unfortunately, has allowed envy to fester into magical mental instability and dark arts experimentation, and then to make the terrible misjudgement we are here today to judge on.”

Harry glared at him. Oh, how he’d like to light that stupid beard on fire.

“I would further go on to make the case that Mister Potter can, and should, serve only minimum sentence before being placed in long term mental care in St. Mungo’s.”

Amelia eyed Dumbledore for slightly longer than one might expect before turning to Mrs. Ogden. “Prosecution, please.”

“Your honours …” Mrs. Ogden glanced at Dumbledore. “… Given the clear and cut nature of the evidence available, we find it very difficult to push for even a paucity sentence …”

Harry glanced at Dumbledore’s face as Mrs. Ogden carried on. Shock, confusion, slowly forming anger. Heh.

“… Thus we intent to show how what the evidence we do have seems to suggest …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

What the hell? Dumbledore stared as Mrs. Ogden went on and on. Red mist descended as he realised what was going on. He was being set up. All those conversations with Greengrass had just been diversions! The Gray had no intention of sending Harry through the veil. But why! The Gray shouldn’t want anything to do with Harry—he’d made sure of that. A bead of sweat ran down his neck. Unless Harry’s performance at the duelling tournament had convinced Lord Slytherin to recruit the boy, even despite the business with Miss Greengrass. Ugh. This wasn’t good.

“… With a full exoneration.” Mrs. Ogden wrapped up her opening statement.

Dumbledore’s beard twitched. On the other hand, Amelia did not look happy with the prosecution, did she?

All around the court room, a faint muttering could be heard.

Amelia glared between him and Mrs. Ogden. She looked to her two other judges who nodded back before sounding another blast with her wand. “Okay, stop. I want to know right now why the defence is playing prosecution and the prosecution is playing defence.”

Albus jabbed a finger towards Mrs. Ogden. “Your honour, the prosecution assured me they would be pushing for the veil—”

Gasps sounded around the court room.

“—And I prepared my defence based on avoiding that. This is hugely irregular!”

Mrs. Ogden glared. “And how regular is it, may I ask, for the defence of a client to be handled by someone who admits in their opening statement that all the evidence points towards their client being guilty?” She looked towards Regent Bones. “How is someone supposed to get a fair trial when their own defence believes them to be guilty and is pushing for that result despite their own client’s plea of not-guilty—even when there is plenty of evidence clearly showing them to be, in fact, not guilty.”

Dumbledore’s nose flared. They were going to use the wand as evidence, weren’t they? Damn it. He needed to think of someway around that. He needed—

“Dumbledore?” Amelia’s voice cut through his thinking. “Is there evidence that shows Mister Potter to be innocent?”

He grit his teeth. “Your honour, the interpretation of the evidence might, in certain circumstance, lead one to cast a doubt over Mister Potter’s guilt, but the unfortunate reality of the situation—”

Bang! Amelia gave yet another blast on her wand, cutting him off. She leaned forward and rubbed her temples with the tips of her fingers before straightening. “I can’t believe I’m doing this.” She sent a mild glare towards Lord Greengrass who watched intently from the visitor’s gallery, before speaking again. “Mister Dumbledore, Mrs. Ogden, please step away from your lecterns.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry watched from the middle of the room, still chained to the chair, as Amelia Bones ordered Dumbledore and Mrs. Ogden to step away from their lecterns. What was she planning to do? Hopefully not rule a miss-trial. That would suck.

A visibly agitated Dumbledore snapped his book shut with such force it snapped a clump of his beard too, causing the headmaster to flinch and Harry to smirk.

“Now, please walk forward and don’t stop walking until I tell you to.”

Dumbledore and Mrs. Ogden walked forward in total silence. No one in the court seemed to be even breathing.

“Stop.”

They stopped.

“Now please turn around and walk to your new lecterns.”

They did so, Dumbledore looking both annoyed and uncertain. He put the book down, still closed, on the lectern and Harry’s eyes sharpened with the unrealised and unknown talent of a snitch seeking prodigy. Several hairs from the headmaster’s long, white beard were trapped in the book’s pages, just visible against the black leather of the book’s cover.

“Now.” Amelia smiled primly. “Prosecution,” she turned to Dumbledore, “if you would please start submitting evidence.”

Harry tore his eyes away from the hairs and back towards Amelia Bones, a small smirk playing across his lips.

Dumbledore breathed out sharply in exasperation. “Your honour, you can not be serious. I am not prepared to act as prosecution, regardless of what they“—he motioned towards Mrs. Ogden—“might have you believe.”

“This is our court room, Albus, I am totally serious. You were going to try and prove that Mister Potter here—an eleven year old child—should be given several years in Azkaban. I’m sure some would say that if you came here ready to push that, then you came here ready to be prosecution.”

“I was appointed by Lord Potter—”

“—We will not have our courtroom become a circus! Nothing has changed except where you stand, and what I’m calling you.” Regent Bones glanced towards Harry’s parents who he noticed with interest looked extremely confused. “Now, please get on with it.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John watched with mounting unease as Dumbledore quickly had a word with a court assistant who scuttled off on some unknown errand, before submitting a dark arts book as evidence, followed by Ogden submitting both Harry’s wand and the tattered duelling robes John had worn during tournament. This wasn’t good. Dumbledore’s whole plan was based around the fact that the wand would never see the inside of a courtroom. And as for the clothes … cold sweat started to form on his neck. Ogden hadn’t figured anything out, had she? If she had … if the new defence could prove it … he swallowed. In the quiet courtroom, it sounded very loud.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Fine, we accept Lady Blott’s position as a magical expert.” Amelia blasted her wand. “Dumbledore, if you could please present the case for the prosecution.”

Dumbledore took a deep breath. This wasn’t going to be easy, but in the time he’d had while submitting evidence, he had remembered an important little detail that could hopefully cast doubt on the validity of using the wand as evidence, but for that to work best, he’d need a witness he hadn’t counted on needing, and that court assistant hadn’t arrived back with him yet. Hopefully, they would, and soon. “I’d like to call Mr. Flourish as my first magical expert.”

An old man with short brown hair stood up and made his way to the high chair next to his lectern. After swearing an oath that was in no way magical and signing a contract that did little but confirm he was who he was, Dumbledore started his questioning.

“Mr. Flourish, where were you on April 4 at around eleven a.m.?”

“I was watching the Hogwarts duelling tournament.”

“And what happened during the match between Mister Potter and Heir Potter?”

“Mister Potter seemed to be winning, then he cast a brown spell into a smoke illusion that caused an explosion.”

“The court has already heard your qualifications in the realms of books and spell identification, Mr. Flourish, could you please identify the spell Mister Potter used.”

“Well, based on the spell’s colour, speed, shape, etc, it could have been one of half a dozen, but given the effects on Heir Potter, we know it to be a dark blasting curse, specifically the creptus curse.”

“Could you please inspect this book and tell us if you recognise it.”

Mr. Flourish took the book in gloved hands and inspected it. “Yes, I do, Joseph Krinkelheit’s Compendium of Prussian Dark Arts. Fortieth Edition, it looks like.”

“Does this book contain the creptus curse?”

“Oh, yes. In fact, this was the first book that published it back in the 1700s.”

“Thank you, Mr. Flourish.” Dumbledore stood aside.

Amelia shot a questioning look at Mrs. Ogden who nodded, walked to the high seat, and asked a few questions of her own.

“Mr. Flourish, you said before that you saw Mister Potter cast a brown spell that caused an explosion?”

“Yes.”

“What was the spell Mister Potter cast immediately proceeding that spell?”

“It was a zero friction spell.”

“And before that?”

“It was a smoke illusion spell.”

“So, the area around Heir Potter was concealed?”

“Well, yes.”

“So, you didn’t actually see the brown spell cause the explosion?”

“I saw the spell enter the smoke illusion and then an explosion happened.”

“But you didn’t see the spell cause the explosion?”

“No, I didn’t directly see the spell cause the explosion.”

“Thank you.”

Dumbledore watched Mr. Flourish walk away with a slight frown. Almost perfect, but he could have done without him casting doubt on the spell’s effect at the end there. He glanced towards the door. And the court assistant still wasn’t back yet. He needed that other witness.

“Dumbledore?” Amelia looked down at where he stood. “Are you ready for your next witness?”

He nodded. “My next witness is Mr. Cecil Chuffney”

A thin and extremely nervous looking young man from the department of mysteries stood up and made his way to the high chair.

“Mr. Chuffney, could you tell the court where you were at 11:30 a.m. on the day of the incident?”

Cecil Chuffney licked his lips. “I’d been called out to Hogwarts to collect evidence from Mister Potter’s dormitory.”

“And what did you find there?”

“Not much. Boy didn’t seem to live off of anything, really—a few spare sets of robes in the closet, socks, underwear, a few school books, and the dark arts book.”

“You are referring to the book Mr. Flourish just identified to us?”

“Yeah.”

“And where did you find it?”

“On the bedside table.”

“On Mister Potter’s bedside table?”

“Yeah.”

“Thank you, Mr. Chuffney.”

Amelia looked towards Mrs. Ogden who shook her head.

Mister Chuffney hopped off the chair and scuttled away. That went about as well as it could.

Just then, the court assistant stepped back through the door to the court room, trailed by another figure and Dumbledore smiled. Just in time. “My next witness will be Lord Sirius Orion Black.”

Sirius looked around briefly, face hurried, and after swearing the oath and having his lords ring authenticated in lieu of an identification contract, sat down in the high chair.

“Lord Black,” Dumbledore said, “could you tell the court what first transpired when you visited Mister Potter in his ministry cell on May 2?”

Sirius nodded. “I knocked on the door, unlocked it, let myself in, and found the floor covered in glass beads. I asked Harry where the beads came from and he showed me that he’d learned to conjure them without needing his wand.”

A few gasps were heard around the room.

“Then we talked for a while about personal matters and a few things pertaining to this case, and I left.”

“So, Harry has the ability to conjure items wandlessly?”

“I only saw the glass beads—and a few other glass shapes—there was also a tiny glass peach, I seem to recall.”

“Impressive ability for an eleven year old.”

Sirius beamed. “Indeed.”

“Thank you, Lord Black, that will be all.”

Amelia turned to Mrs. Ogden. “Do you wish to ask Lord Black any questions?”

Mrs. Ogden shook her head.

Sirius hopped off the chair and made his way over to the Potters.

“My next witness will be …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Hey, Prongs,” Sirius whispered when he got to the nearest bench. “What’s going on?”

James turned to him, confused and agitated. “I don’t know. It started off as we expected and then everything went weird.”

Dumbledore turned to face the court. “My next witness will be Harry James Potter.”

Sirius frowned. “Weird? Like how?”

“Like the prosecution seems to want to let Harry go.”

“Well, that’s good isn’t it?”

“I don’t know. Dumbledore believes Harry is guilty.”

“But … but that’s nonsense. Harry isn’t guilty. I saw the evidence.”

James looked sharply at him.

Sirius glanced towards where Dumbledore stood in the middle of the court. “Least, I thought I did.”

Harry’s chair had floated up and made its way to occupy the space where the witness high chair was situated.

James’ frown deepened. “Anyway, now Dumbledore is acting like the prosecution and the prosecution is acting like the defence.”

Sirius stared blankly. “Wait … you mean … I just testified against Harry?”

James nodded slowly.

“Whoops.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry slowed his breathing as the chair he sat in levitated up from the ground and floated into the spot the other witnesses had sat in. The chains bit into his wrists. He felt every set of eyes on him.

“Mister Potter,” Dumbledore started, “we’ve heard of your abilities to perform wandless magic, perhaps you can tell the court what other spells you can cast wandlessly?”

Harry sniffed and caught the eye of Mrs. Ogden who gave him an encouraging nod. Oh, well. All in. “I can cast the stunning charm, the incendio charm, the summoning charm, the shield charm, and the banishing charm wandlessly.”

“What about conjuring?”

“Yes, I can also conjure small glass objects, such as those Lord Black saw, and you stepped on.”

A few chuckles sounded around the room.

“Could you demonstrate for the court some of your wandless abilities?”

Harry’s eyes flickered briefly to where Dumbledore’s book still lay on the lectern. He smiled. “Yes, but I am rather constrained at the moment.”

Dumbledore looked to Regent Bones who nodded towards two on duty security wizards. The two wizards approached the chair and pointed their wands at Harry, who suddenly felt the chains around his wrists loosen. He flicked his hand up with a grin and caused Dumbledore’s book to sail across the room, generating a susurration of murmuring around the room.

Dumbledore nodded. “Well done, Mister Potter, if we were in class I’d award points.”

Harry carefully took the book in both hands, smiling all the while, closed two of his fingers around the stray white hair still trapped between the pages, and offered the book back to Dumbledore with a flourish. As the headmaster accepted the book back with a frown, Harry felt the tiny pluck as the white hair between his fingers snapped in two. His hand fell to his lap and casually slid into his pocket.

“Now, Mister Potter, I notice that the creptus curse wasn’t included in that impressive list of spells you can cast wandlessly. Are you saying you can’t cast that spell without a wand?”

“That is what I’m saying.”

“So you deny being able to cast that curse.”

“Without a wand? Yes.”

“Without a wand? So you could cast it with a wand?”

“I dare-say I could if I tried. I never have though.”

“Do you deny learning dark spells?”

“No, I don’t deny that. Most of the hexes and jinxes used by duellists are dark by the magical definition.”

“Have you ever performed a dark ritual on yourself?”

“No.” He mentally smirked. Not yet.

“Thank you, Mister Potter, no further questions.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore nodded to himself as Harry’s chair floated back to the middle of the room, chains and shackles once again snaking themselves around his wrists and ankles.

“I call my next witness, Professor Minerva McGonagall.”

McGonagall sat in the high chair.

“Professor, could you tell us the events that led up to the incident with Mister Potter on January 28 in Hogwarts classroom 219?”

“Well, I was in my office marking papers, when I suddenly felt a large build up of magic coming from somewhere off in the castle. I made haste to investigate, and found the door to classroom 219 bolted shut and I heard you shouting to get the students away from the area.”

“And after the magical build up had died down?”

“I entered the classroom to find it completely destroyed, you standing in the middle of it, and Mister Potter unconscious on the floor. I then levitated him to the hospital wing.”

“Thank you, Professor, that will be all.”

His next witness was Healer Pomfrey who explained about what had transpired in the room, about Harry’s magical meltdown, what magical meltdown was, and how Harry’s control over his core had snapped.

After her, Dumbledore called another healer from St. Mungo’s, who explained some of the causes of magical meltdown.

Dumbledore glanced towards Harry. “So, if someone had experienced magical meltdown, how likely would it be that it was the result of a dark ritual?”

“Quite likely.”

“Why?”

“Well, we don’t get many cases of it, but most that we do get are the result of experimenting with dangerous magics.”

“Thank you, Healer, no further questions.”

Mrs. Ogden then took the floor. “Healer Uptown, you said that one of the ways that magical meltdown could happen was as the result of trauma?”

“Yes.”

“If you learned that a patient had a phobia and was exposed to the conditions of that phobia, would you consider that to be a likely explanation for a case of magical meltdown?”

“Yes, yes I would.”

“Thank you, healer, no further questions.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“We’ll now take a short break before the defence presents their case.” Amelia Bones fired a blast from her wand and the three judges took their leave through a back door.

Dumbledore hurried out of the courtroom, hoping to get away before,

“Albus!”

He sighed. No luck. He turned, beheld a confused and agitated Lord and Lady Potter, and quickly hurried them into a waiting room.

“Albus,” said James Potter once the door was closed. “What was all that about?”

“James, the prosecution assured me they were planning to push Harry for the veil.”

“Yes, but what about after that?”

“I don’t know what they’re playing at, but Harry is guilty, all the evidence that I’ve seen supports it.”

“What about the wand? Sirius just told me the report said it didn’t have the curse on it.”

“James, you’ve seen his wandless capabilities, you’ve seen what he’s capable of. It would be the easiest thing in the world for him to learn that spell and cast it as though from his wand, but not actually passing through it—and he clearly had access to the spell to learn it.”

James and Lily stood in silence for a moment. Lily in particular didn’t look happy.

“Okay, we’ll see what the new defence’s case is,” James said eventually. “You assured us all the evidence supported Harry’s guilt. I’ll wait to see what they have to say before saying anything more on this.”

Dumbledore nodded and watched the Potters turn to leave, but before they did, Lily turned back to face him, eyes narrowed. “Even if Harry is guilty, Headmaster, I still hold you responsible for allowing him to get his hands on such a dangerous book. You’re supposed to be keeping a closer eye on him than that.” And with that, she stepped through the door and shut it behind her.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Is anything normal around that boy?” asked Lord Smith chuckling and shaking his head.

Lord Lovegood smiled and led him towards a familiar object. “Harry tends to have a lot of interesting experiences.”

“I’ll say. Okay, I see you’ve got the pensieve set up. What is it you want to show me?”

“An extended version of the events of Halloween.”

“You don’t mean the troll that got into Hogwarts do you?”

“I do—although I’m more interested to show you what happened after that.”

“Righto, show away.”

Lovegood nodded. “We have cut out some bits to preserve family secrets, though.”

“Understandable.” Lord Smith touched the silvery liquid and felt the familiar jerking sensation, pulling him down into the memory.”

John Potter jumped on the troll and blasted its head off.

Lord Smith chuckled. “You can see the power already, can’t you?”

John Potter dashed off and, after saying good bye to the other girls, the Greengrass heiress and the muggleborn followed him.

He soon found himself standing in a destroyed corridor. “Fwhoa, what a mess—did the troll do this, too?”

Lovegood shrugged in a half gesture that committed to nothing.

The Greengrass heiress walked around the corner and the memory faded a new section of castle into view, spotlighting a rather large corpse on the ground.

Lord Smith stared.

Five minutes later, he exited the pensive, unable to see anything but rage. By his side, his trusty war hammer started glowing metallic red. “A chimaera! A Merlin damned chimaera! In a school with my grandchildren! What was he thinking!”

Lord Lovegood watched him from the side.

Lord Smith turned on him. “Why haven’t you said anything about this before!”

“We checked the files—all the correct paperwork was filed, albeit in a place no one would look unless they were really trying hard to find it—there wasn’t anything Dumbledore did that was actually illegal—the threat had been dealt with and there was no chance of removing Dumbledore from his position as Headmaster by a simple vote of no confidence.”

Lord Smith scowled. “You don’t think a public enquiry into this wouldn’t have worked? Illegal or not, the parents would have gone Atlantis on his arse.”

“Maybe, maybe not … but there is an opportunity to remove the headmaster at the end of the school year by simply deciding not to renew his contract. That merely requires a simple majority.”

“But an enquiry—”

“—Lord Slytherin is not particularly enthusiastic about becoming subject to a public enquiry—and he certainly could be asked to testify if one came about. Many things could come out—things the Gray would rather not—at least not right now.”

Lord Smith frowned. “If I voted against Dumbledore in such a matter without a good public reason, I might as well shout that the Smiths are now unashamedly Gray at the top of my lungs in the middle of the damn Wizengamot. I do still have business with other Lords of the Light, you know.”

“I believe that the general result of this trial will cast enough public doubt on the headmaster to function as a valid reason for your sudden change of heart, although, of course, we’d still welcome your support in the Gray on a more ongoing basis.”

Lord Smith narrowed his eyes. “I want to know who Lord Slytherin is.”

“That is a matter of extreme trust.”

“Then I at least want to meet him. I sure as hell do not plan on joining without some guarantees.”

“After the trial, that can be arranged.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Mrs. Ogden motioned to the full-again court room. “Mr. Chuffney, was it you who performed the analysis on the dark book found in Mister Potter’s dormitory?”

The young man shifted nervously. “Yes, it was.”

“And what were your findings?”

“We could find no fingerprints and no polyjuice evidence to link the book to the boy. In fact, there were neither fingerprints nor polyjuice evidence at all.”

Mrs. Ogden handed the man a parchment. “Could you read the court this passage from your report please?”

“The book appears to be in near mint condition and contains the publishing number is 0087620–12031992-02–0202.”

“What did you mean by that?”

“I meant that it looked barely used—and that it had that publishing number.”

“Thank you, Mr. Chuffney.”

Mr. Chuffney scooted back off to his seat among the many rows of the courtroom.

“I call my next witness, Mr. Reginald Quickspell.”

Mr. Quickspell sat down in the high chair. “Mr. Quickspell, you are here as an expert on learning magic outside of the formal education system, and on wandless magic in particular—could you please tell the court how long it takes to learn to cast a spell wandlessly?”

“Around 200 to 250 hours is a good time, not counting the normal time.”

“What does, ‘good time,’ and, ‘normal time,’ mean?”

“Well, everyone is different. Some people learn faster, some slower. The best students I’ve seen take a little over two hundred hours—that’s the good time. The normal time is how long it would take you to learn the same spell if you had a wand—add the two together and you get the total time it takes to learn a wandless spell.”

“And how many hours a day can a student practise?”

Mr. Quickspell pursed his lips. “Five hours is the most that’s realistic, any more than that and you get burnout.”

“So, what would be the shortest time period, measured in days for a student to learn a new wandless spell?”

“Forty to fifty days.”

In the middle of the room, Harry had to keep himself from smirking. Ginny had mastered a completely unknown wandless spell much faster than that.

“Could a student learn a wandless spell in twenty days?”

Mr. Quickspell scoffed. “Absolutely not.”

“Thank you, no further questions.”

Next in the high chair was Madam Pince, although how Jacob had roped her into this, Harry had no idea.

“Madam Pince, could you please explain to the court how publishing numbers work?”

“A book’s publishing number contains four separate numbers that identify the book’s international ID, date of crafting, the family that crafted it, and the wizard or witch either of the family or employed by the family who crafted it, in that order.”

“So, you could tell me exactly when a book with this publishing number was crafted?” Mrs. Ogden handed Madam Pince the DoM report on the dark arts book.

“Yes.”

“Please do so.”

“This book was crafted on March 12, 1992.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore’s eyes widened for a fraction of a second before quickly returning to normal. Only twenty days before the tournament … Oh, bugger.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Could you now please demonstrate the priori incantatem effect for this wand?”

The DoM worker responsible for the analysis on Harry’s wand held the wand up and said, “Priori incantatem.” Several shadows drifted out of the wand’s end.

“And could you identify these spells, please?”

“Well, like I said in the report, the last spells used by this wand were an area stunner, then a frictionless charm, then a smoke illusion, in reverse order.”

“So, not a dark blasting curse?”

“Not a dark blasting curse.”

“Is there anyway this wand could have been interfered with or tampered with after these spells were cast?”

“Only if you wish to accuse one of the DMLE or DoM wizards of tampering with evidence.”

“What about the girl who touched the wand after Mister Potter used it?”

“She was in clear view of two thousand people. We’ve analysed memories and there was no chance of her casting any of those spells before she handed it to Director Bones.” The DoM worker glanced towards Regent Bones who nodded back at him.

“Thank you, no further questions.”

With no word from Dumbledore to cross-examine, the DoM worker left and Lady Dorothy Abbott took the high seat.

Mrs. Ogden held a tray containing the tattered remains of John’s duelling robes up for the court to see. “Lady Abbott, you are here as an expert on clothing and the use of runes in clothing. You have had a chance to inspect the remains of the duelling robes worn by Heir Potter. What can you tell us about what you found?”

“There were many runes embroidered on the inside of the remains. Many of them were extremely difficult to make out, owing to having been almost burnt clean off, but many others are still recognisable.”

“What function do you believe these runes would have served?”

Lady Abbott sniffed. “I have no idea. I’ve never seen runes like them in those combinations and patterns anywhere near anything that is designed to be worn.”

“So, they are not standard clothing runes?”

“No, they most certainly are not.”

“Thank you.”

And minutes later, John Potter sat in the high chair.

“Did you know your robes had these runes embroidered on the inside?”

John shakily shook his head. “No, I didn’t. They were the robes Dad bought me.”

“Did these robes ever leave your sight after you received them?”

“Yeah—of course—all the time. I barely used them. They were duelling robes, not wear all the time robes.”

And minutes after that, an expert on runes of all kinds.

“Were you able to identify any possible function that these runes might play?”

“Yes. One of the runic arrays that we found around the back contains a three part runic cluster found specific application.”

“What application?”

“Defensive wards. Dark defensive wards. Defensive wards that would be happy to leave you going home in a match box, if you know what I mean.”

Mrs. Ogden let out a sigh. “Could you spell it out for the court, please?”

The runic expert smirked. “Explosions.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

A loud muttering filled the court room.

Bang! “Quiet please!” Amelia Bones shot off a small cannon blast from her wand.

Lord Malfoy surveyed the room, eyes narrowed in calculation. Potter was going to be let off—it was clear. The evidence was far too cut and dry and Regent Bones was hardly the kind of witch to bend in the face of obvious evidence.

Dumbledore had tried to pull some kind of stunt here and failed. Lord Slytherin had out manoeuvred him, and he’d done it with expert witnesses, all oh whom were Light—and now all of Magical Britain would know it. He could almost feel the subtle shift in power rippling out from the room, even as he sat there. It didn’t look like much, but even now, various Light lords were giving Dumbledore funny looks. The Potters in particular did not look happy.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“And so,” Mrs. Ogden finished, “we can clearly see that Mister Potter has been the victim of an attempt to frame him for the attempted murder of Heir Potter, and although we have been unable to identify the exact mechanism used to trigger the runic array in Heir Potter’s clothing, it is clear that the robes were what caused the explosion, not any spell cast by Mister Potter.”

Amelia Bones and the two other judges rose from their seats. “Thank you, Mrs. Ogden—Dumbledore. We will now take a short recess to deliberate before reaching a final verdict.” They filed out.

Harry sat there while the voices of the court washed over him. The minutes ticked by. People got up and moved around, stretching their legs after several hour of sitting. Harry of course, didn’t have that luxury.

Mrs. Ogden walked up to him. “I wouldn’t worry about it, Mister Potter. I’m certain you’ll be let off.”

Harry mouth firmed. “I certainly hope so and thank you very much for your help in all this. I will not forget it.”

The door to the back room opened again. The three judges filed back in and took their seats. Regent Bones shot a small canon blast from her wand. “We will now give our verdict.”

The room silenced.

“After careful deliberation, we hereby pronounce the defendant not guilty of all charges.”

The court room broke into a loud round of babbling.

Bang! “In addition!”

The room quietened again.

“In addition, we feel that this case could have been a whole lot simpler than it turned out to be. We’re not sure what you were trying to pull, Albus, but your role as defendant should have been rather obvious. Be assured that you and I will be having a little chat later on.”

Dumbledore nodded meekly.

“Thank you all. Court closed.” Bang!

The chains holding Harry’s wrists and ankles instantly slid off. He stood up and stretched, feeling lighter than he had in a month. Then, without pausing to even look around, he made a beeline for the door—to the outside world, and to freedom.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lily Potter made for the door Harry had just left by. “I’m going to go talk to Harry.”

“Wait!” James desperately grabbed at her wrist.

She tried to shake him off. “Let me go! I don’t like the way Dumbledore was acting. It didn’t feel right.”

“Lily!” he hissed so no one else could hear, “We still don’t know the prophecy! We might mess everything up!”

Lily stiffened, then slumped against a nearby pillar.

James let go of her wrist.

“Okay, fine,” she said. “But the moment John gets off the Hogwarts Express, we’re taking him down to the Hall of Prophecies, regardless of what Dumbledore says.”

James reluctantly nodded and looked around. Dumbledore, it seemed, had quietly slipped out of the court room. He frowned. He hated not trusting his leader and old Headmaster, but the man had been acting very strangely, even if you took into account an unknown prophecy in play. James couldn’t imagine what kind of prophecy would have the headmaster acting the way he was. It was about time they found out—and Merlin damn the consequences.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Back in Greengrass Manor, after being dog-piled by three relieved and crying witches, Harry managed, finally, to stand up.

“Harry, here.” Jacob tossed Harry a green and black mask.

Harry caught it with a smirk.

“You’ve got a lot work to catch up on.”

Harry grinned and thought of the single split white hair still nestled safely in his pocket. “Yes, I do. So do we all. We’ve got press releases to send out, a whole lot of lords to court, and a brand spanking new politically advantageous situation to exploit.” He looked around at Daphne, Hermione, and Luna. “But first, we’ve got a final project to finish up on back at Hogwarts.”

Daphne smirked. “I wonder how Tracey’s been doing without us? It has been almost seven weeks.”

Hermione’s eyes suddenly widened and she let out a small ‘Eep’ sound. “Oh no!” She put both her hands over her mouth in horror. “Exams!”

—End of Chapter Thirty-two—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: Only one more chapter to go before the end of the season, the end of Hogwarts year one, and the wrapping up of the Philosopher’s stone story arc! This one won’t be published this Sunday. I hope it’ll be published the Sunday after, but it may well turn out to be the Wednesday after next … I’ll keep you updated on my twitter account as normal.

A/N: This was the first court scene I’ve ever done. I’m not an expert on the little intricacies on how these things work—never even watched court room dramas—so I’ve probably made all sorts of mistakes in how things work, but, on the other hand, this is the freak’n magical world, so I hope I’ll be allowed a bit of leeway by those who truly are familiar with the profession (Joe Lawyer, I’m thinking of you especially, you amazing reviewer).

A/N: For everyone asking or wishing to ask if I’m going to ‘redeem’ the Potters (which I should have realised was going to happen), I ask you not to think in such terms. This story is a tad more complex than that.

The Philosopher’s Prophecy

“Mister Potter!” Deputy Headmistress Minerva McGonagall glared down at Harry in front of the main Hogwarts gates. Her lips were one thin line. “Where have you been? Do you have any idea the worry you caused when you just disappeared after the trial like that?”

Harry’s face took on the look of the mildly curious. “No, I do not. Perhaps you could enlighten me?”

McGonagall’s nostrils flared. “Your parents were greatly concerned when no one could say where you’d gone.”

Harry snorted.

“So?” McGonagall asked, looming over Harry as only a middle school teacher can. “Where have you been?”

“I was in Diagon Alley.”

“What for?”

“Shopping.”

“Shopping for what?”

“A new set of robes so I can appear in your classroom like the tidy and responsible young wizard I am. It seems the ministry won’t be returning the ones the DoM took as evidence until it passes through three sets of departments and gets stamped in triplicate .”

Professor McGonagall’s eyes narrowed. “Are you trying to be cheeky, Mister Potter?”

Harry’s voice became so dry it could soak up an ocean. “No, Professor. I’m sure I’d do a better job of it if I actually tried.”

“Detention, Mister Potter.”

“Yes, Professor.”

“Get along to your common room.”

“Yes, Professor.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“—And then Bole tried to bully me into siding with him against Keendle, but Keendle had already told Richardson that I’d told him about the business with Parkinson, and then Gibbons and Carthile started threatening to blow the whole thing open if I didn’t side with them against Keendle, but they still refused to have anything to do with Bole because of that time before Christmas!” Tracey was slouched in one of the armchairs near the Slytherin throne in the Slytherin common room, half on and half off, glass of pumpkin juice in one hand, hand over tired eyes with the other.

Daphne and Hermione listened attentively, sitting opposite their friend in the unofficial student throne of the Gray and a small sofa respectively. The general hubbub of the common room washed around the small Gray grouping.

Tracey swigged back her drink in a most un-lady like fashion before reaching for the ceiling with both hands. “I mean, come on!”

Daphne smiled to herself. Oh, the joys of leadership. One thing she hadn’t missed much during their seven week evacuation. She leaned forward. “But you did solve it.”

“Oh, I solved it, sure, but it took so much stupid stuff.”

“Welcome to the world of politics.”

Tracey eyed her like a drowning man eyes another, more buoyant looking, drowning man. “Well, you can keep it, Daph—it’s all yours again.”

“As you wish, Miss future Lady Davis.”

Tracey groaned. “Please don’t remind me. I don’t know how you and Hermione find the energy to do all the stuff you do on top of all the political stuff we have to worry about.” She straightened on her chair. “Now, are you going to tell me what the hell happened at the trial? And why isn’t Potter back yet if he got off?”

Daphne gave a small wry smile. “We’d have told you earlier, if you hadn’t immediately decided to unload on us.”

“Well, I’m sorry!”

Suddenly, the door creaked open and all attention seemed to draw, inexplicably, towards it.

Harry stepped through the common room door, as though he’d just got back from lunch. He looked around, walked past their court, giving her a small nod as he passed, and sat down several chairs away where the Dark had their little court going.

“Why,” Tracey whispered, “is Potter sitting with the Dark? If he’s Gray, I mean.”

Hermione leaned forward and whispered, “Recruitment.”

“Recruit—Hermione, you can’t seriously believe that he’ll be able to bring any of them over to our side, do you?”

Hermione smiled.

Daphne smirked.

“Possibly.” Hermione looked over to where Harry sat.

Daphne followed her eyes. Harry sat among the Dark as though he belonged there. Moments later, he stood up and made his way over to them. He sat himself down with a grin. “Just saying hi to our friends over the way.”

Tracey looked incredulously at him.

“What?” said Harry, a small twinkle in his eye. “No welcome back?—no, ‘I’m glad you were exonerated?’—not even a, ‘Why the hell didn’t you tell me you were Gray before so I might not have looked so silly for several months?’ ”

Tracey snorted. “I’m insulted you think I might not have worked that last one out on my own.”

Daphne reached into her pocket and handed over the tiny trunk Harry had entrusted Hermione with from before.

Harry took it with a smile. “So, what’s been going on while I was away?”

Daphne and Hermione winced.

Tracey took a sharp intake of breath. “Oh! let me tell you …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry sat down in one of the three chairs in his trunk. “Wow, that girl knows how to weave a story. It’s a pity we don’t still have bards as a tradition. I’m sure she’d make a fine one.”

Daphne smiled apologetically as she and Hermione mirrored him and the three made themselves comfortable. “Tracey’s always been like that—ever since we first met—must have been when we were three or something like that.”

“I’m not knocking it,” Harry said. “It’s a useful skill. But now let’s talk about other things.”

Hermione perked up. “The stone.”

Harry nodded. “The stone, indeed.”

“What are we going to do about it?” Daphne asked.

Harry tapped his fingers idly on the low table between them. “We’ve only got a few weeks until the end of the year and exams—”

Hermione nodded fiercely.

“—And it’s important that both of you score top in them.”

Hermione started. “What about you?”

“I mean top apart from me.”

Hermione relaxed and nodded.

Harry continued. “You will, however, have to beat out John.”

Hermione scoffed.

Harry grinned. “Which I know you’ll be able to do, but do remember that he does have four years on both of you, and the last time I checked, you, Hermione, were only just starting fourth year spells, and you, Daphne, were only just starting year three.”

Daphne glanced to her side and caught Hermione’s eye. They’d both solidified into twin burning embers. She turned back. “And the stone?”

Harry sat in silence for a moment before speaking. “Dumbledore will be getting more and more suspicious. I think, we’ll need to wait until he can do little to no harm and then use an already proven method.”

Daphne frowned. “What proven method?”

Harry reached into his pocket, drew out a small bottle containing a single white hair and set it down on the table. “The boy who lived, of course.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lord Smith sat in the large armchair that was the seat of the Noble House of Smith. The seat of the Noble House of Smith sat in a corner of a sitting room, which was itself situated on the second floor of a three story monstrosity of pure granite, carved into the side of Ben Nevis, and hidden from muggles by an ancient set of wards mostly untouched since they’d been set up over seven hundred years ago.

The seat now creaked as Lord Smith shifted his considerable weight, most of it muscle, despite his age, and made only heavier by the steel armour he wore. He wasn’t nervous. No, he damn well was not nervous! He’d survived everything that life had thrown at him. Even He-whom-it-was-unwise-to-name. Not something many of his peers could say—certainly not where they were now. So what reason did he have to be nervous of some little upstart lord who wore a mask? None at all!

The chair creaked again.

He rose irritably from the ancient oak seat like a building taking flight and started pacing.

A ping shot through the wards.

He stopped pacing.

A house elf popped into being by the sitting room’s front door. “Master, Lord Slytherings has arrived.”

Lord Smith’s moustache twitched. “Good. Show him up please.”

A minute later, the door opened and Lord Smith found himself gazing into the now famous green and black mask. “Ah, Lord Slytherin, come in, come in, please sit down, why don’cha?”

The masked lord swept into the room behind him. “Thank you, Lord Smith.”

The two sat themselves down.

Smith smacked a goblet filled with red wine down in front of Slytherin. “I dare say you know why I requested this meeting?”

Lord Slytherin inclined his head. “I dare say you know why I accepted.”

Smith barked a laugh. “I’ve got some questions to ask before I’ll sign my family into your alliance.”

“Fire away.”

“Who are you?”

“I am Lord Slytherin.”

“You trust Lord Greengrass with your identity.”

“Jacob is family.”

Smith smirked. “I’m not signing Sally over to you just to see your face.”

“I wouldn’t ask you to. I have quite enough on my plate to be getting on with.”

“Smith snorted. “Rather you than me. I love Margaret, but I wouldn’t be able to handle two of her—not a chance.”

Slytherin said nothing.

Smith turned serious. “Okay, you don’t want others to see your face, I get that. But there is one thing I insist on knowing before joining.”

“Go on.”

“What is all this for?”

“All this?”

“The secrecy. The Wizengamot blockade. What’s it all in aid of? Several years ago the Gray didn’t even exist, it was just a bunch of families who didn’t want to get too involved doing what little they could do to stop the more extreme policies of the Dark and Light becoming law. Now it’s this rising third power. But rising for what?”

Slytherin swirled his goblet idly before taking a sip.

Smith watched the way the mask’s lips moulded themselves around the goblet, forming a small mouth as it went. It was an impressive piece of magic.

Eventually, Slytherin spoke. “I don’t agree with the way the Light does things. I don’t agree with the way the Dark does things either. They are both on the path to bring our world to ruin. And both are led by overly powerful wizards capable of speeding up that ruin if they are not neutered first.”

“Dumbledore? I wouldn’t have believed it a month ago, but now. … He seems to be trying to keep as low a profile as possible after the debacle at your boy’s trial—couldn’t even arrange a meeting of my own with him, and I know plenty of the other heads of houses have tried and failed too—never a good sign, that.”

Slytherin nodded. “Dumbledore is one of them.”

“And the other is?”

“A wizard believed by many to be dead, but who, unfortunately, has a bad habit of not quite making it all the way across the river Styx.”

Smith frowned. “Who?”

“The Dark Lord.”

Smith’s heart clenched in his chest. His breathing felt shallower. “He’s alive?”

“Unfortunately.”

Smith’s hand gripped the goblet hard enough to leave marks in his palm. So that’s why Slytherin didn’t want his identity known. The room suddenly felt a lot colder than before. Suddenly everything made a lot more sense. The man was preparing for a war against someone who would quickly have him killed if his identity was known. “How is the he not dead?”

“Dark magic.”

Figures. “Why not go public with this? The Light would surely fight against the Dark.”

“You forget I’m not only fighting against the Dark. There are forces within the Light who would also be happy to see my personal destruction if they could wrangle it.”

Okay, now that was interesting.

The two sat in silence for a moment.

Smith took a gulp of wine. “Fine.” He put down the goblet with a thump. “Got any other explosion curses to land on me?”

Slytherin reached into his pocket. “Take a look at this.” The young lord chucked him something round and metallic.

Smith snatched it out of the air on instinct. His eyes widened as his mind caught up with what his eyes were seeing. It was a small sphere of aluminium, perfectly round and engraved with hundreds of what looked like tiny geometrically perfect runes. He looked up at Slytherin with incredulity. “There’s no way these are accurate to the necessary precision.”

“I assure you, they are.”

Lord Smith felt a slight sweat form on the back of his neck. The implications of something like this … “How? Who?”

“A family secret. Friends of mine.” The metal ball flew back into Slytherin’s gloved hand with a small smack sound.

Smith stared. His mind whirled. Weapons. Shields. Armour. Oh, the possibilities. “Okay, now you’ve got my attention.” He gave Slytherin a small wry smile. “Still sure you wouldn’t consider taking another consort?”

Slytherin chuckled. “No, Lord Smith. I’m quite happy, thank you very much. But I’m sure our houses can work together in the future.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Inside the mirror room at the end of the third floor corridor, Harry pointed his wand at yet another broken mirror. “Diffindo.” The mirror started to separate until the top half of it’s tall bronze frame was completely separated from its bottom half. He took another angle and once more started another cut. The metal cleaved itself under his wand and soon the broken mirror was in four—much smaller pieces than before, but still not small enough. He looked around.

Across the room, Daphne levitated the remains of her forth or fifth mirror into his trunk before collapsing on the ground, panting heavily.

Hermione, it seemed, had given the magic a break for the moment. She carried her latest piece of bronze mirror frame to the trunk, chucking it in with a loud crashing noise. She turned around and wiped her brow before suddenly frowning, as though struck by a confusing thought. “Harry?”

“Yeah?”

“Why do we even have to do this? Why can’t we just bring the Mirror of Erised to your brother, rather than bringing your brother here?”

Harry smiled and ambled over towards the girls, happy for the chance to let his magic rest a bit. His own pile of scrap bronze already dwarfed Hermione and Daphne’s. “An excellent question. You tell me.”

Hermione bit her lip and descended into deep thought.

Daphne looked between him and Hermione before getting up off the floor and brushing herself down. She paused. “Is it something to do with the fidelius?”

Harry nodded. “Well done.”

Hermione looked at Daphne, mildly annoyed.

Daphne continued. “It’s the secret, right? I remember when I came through here when we first took down the original fidelius and put up the new one. The secret said that the Mirror of Erised was hidden in this room.”

Hermione’s face lit up in understanding. “Oh! I see! So, if we took the mirror out of the room, the fidelius would fail?”

“Yes,” Harry said, “and only I could do that anyway—as it would constitute as, ‘telling the secret,’ to the whole world—although breaking the mirror would have the same effect.”

Hermione nodded before looking around and then into the trunk. “So, what are we going to do with all this bronze?”

Daphne smiled wryly. “How about a life-sized statue of Lord Slytherin on the front lawn of Slytherin Manor?”

Harry made a disgusted face. “I’d go through the veil before letting that happen.”

Hermione giggled. “So, that’s a ‘yes’ then?”

“It’s just an expression.”

“What about one of Harry Potter?”

“No.”

“Perhaps in an overly heroic position, like holding a sword straight up in the air?”

“No.”

“While Daphne lays at your feet, clutching one of your legs?”

“N—”

“—Or” Daphne cut in, eyes narrowed. “The girl could be you, kneeling before your lord swearing life long fealty.”

“Um,” said Harry.

“I wouldn’t mind that,” Hermione said, slightly smug.

“What about before your Lord and Lady?”

“Oh, that is—!”

Harry let out a brief flare of magic, cutting both of the slightly startled girls off in mid flow. He smirked. “How about a statue of you two and the others in mid-fight against that troll at Halloween?”

Hermione and Daphne looked at each other before turning back and nodding. “Okay.” / “I’m good with that.” Then they both giggled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione stood next to the pensieve in her trunk, watching as the members of The Founders Club emerged from the courtroom memory one after the other.

Justin Finch-Fletchley looked at her with a worried expression. “And he’s our magical guardian?”

Hermione nodded.

Sophie Roper dusted herself down after almost falling over. “It was almost like he wanted Harry to go to prison.”

“No almost about it,” Justin said.

Kevin Entwhistle stood in the middle of the room, the only one seemingly unaffected by the spinning pensieve trip. “You’d have to be blind not to see Harry was all right. What’s his game?”

The three looked questioningly towards Hermione, just as Dean finally emerged from the memory bowl. “Okay, what the hell was all that about?”

Hermione took a deep breath. “Dumbledore has built up a picture in the wizarding world as being this great good wizard who fights for justice and equality.” She looked into each of her fellow muggleborn’s eyes, each pair fixed unmovingly on her, before continuing. “The reality, however, is quite different …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

And before long, the exams were on them. Harry took great pleasure in watching the memories of Hermione and Daphne utterly obliterate every practical exam they took. He’d spent several years working with them by now and it was amazing to see just what several years of prep work with Tom Riddle developed occlumency could accomplish. He found it deliciously ironic that he, Harry, had built his power base in part with the techniques that Voldemort had been the most unwilling to share with anyone else.

Professor McGonagall had them all turn a mouse into a snuffbox. Harry decorated his snuffbox with gold filigree and tiny opals, depicting a scene of a Nemean lion and a runespore teaming up to battle a chimaera—a chimaera with the head of a goat and the body of a wolf. She’d given him a level gaze, a congratulations on an excellent transfiguration, and a mild warning to respect all his professors.

Professor Flitwick had almost fainted with excitement when Harry had made his pineapple not only tap-dance, but then also perform as far as Odette’s first revelation in Swan Lake before needing to stop for the next examinee. “Most well done, Mister Potter. Not even your brother managed something quite as wonderful.”

Potions had been a surprise. Instead of the Headmaster, they’d walked into the potions lab on the day of the exams to find an un-petrified and extremely short tempered Professor Snape. He swooped around the classroom glaring at Harry’s yearmates and occasionally shooting him a calculating look. No doubt someone had shown him memories from the tournament or similar.

History had been boring and easy. So had astronomy.

For defence against the dark arts, Harry had hid under the Potter invisibility cloak and followed Hermione and Daphne into the classroom when they had their practicals. He wouldn’t put it behind Tom to try to pull something this close to the end of the year, but he needn’t have worried. Quirrellmort seemed to be on his best behaviour for some reason. The man did look extremely sick though. Far worse than this time in the last timeline. Even his skin seemed to be sluffing off.

Then came Harry’s own turn at defence.

“Why don’t you try and impress me, Potter?”

“What would you like me to do, Professor?”

“Why don’t we start out with spell swatting?” Quirrell fired a rapid chain of spells at him, which he swatted out of the way—every single one.

“Good.” Quirrell made a motion for him to go.

Harry eyed him warily. “That’s all, Professor?”

“Yes, Potter. You are an advanced spell swatter. There are likely no more than two dozen people in the country that are at your level and a good number of them are aurors who’ve been working on it for years with access to restricted books from the department of mysteries. Only the top professional duellists can pull it off perfectly, and that’s not for lack of wide-eyed hopefuls who’d like to be able to. Giving you anything less than an O with full marks would be an insult. Now go. I’m sure you’ve got more productive things you could be doing.”

Harry nodded, thanked the rapidly deteriorating dark lord, and left.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“I have learned that Dumbledore is scheduled to address the ICW conference on international magical crime in two days.”

Across the table from Harry, Hermione and Daphne exchanged glances.

Hermione raised a hand. “I thought we didn’t want to use that strategy because Dumbledore would link it to Lord Slytherin?”

Harry nodded. “We haven’t, but less than twelve hours after he leaves, the board will meet to discuss his contract renewal. Once that meeting is concluded, and we’re all back on the train less than forty-eight hours after that, the headmaster will no longer be headmaster.”

Daphne pursed her lips. “So, in other words, we don’t care.”

“Exactly.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry sneaked through the corridors of Hogwarts as quiet as a ghost—or at least, as quiet as the ghosts who weren’t talking, shouting at each other, or rattling chains up the astronomy tower.

He made his way to the gargoyle guarding the headmaster’s office and carefully let himself in, checking all the while for hidden runes and concealed trip-lines. He found none—at least until he got to the very top of the stairs and opened the door. His magical sensing drew his attention to a minute amount of magic swirling through the doormat, sat innocently on the floor in front of him, emblazoned with the words, ‘Home Sweetie Home’.

He knelt down and felt for intent. There was none. He frowned. That was odd. There was certainly magic there, but no spell. He lay down on the floor, withdrew a folded piece of parchment from his pocket, folded it twice more, and carefully slid his make-shift spatula under the mat.

Nothing.

He started to lift it.

Suddenly, a spell started to form.

He quickly dropped the mat.

The spell died.

Interesting. He glanced around the office. What would happen if he turned it? He tried. The mat refused to turn. Mmmm. He stepped over the mat, constantly checking for other possible traps, and crouched down facing the mat again. He then slowly started to transfigure the floor around the mat to a transparent glass and what he saw increased his grudging respect for the old man another notch.

The mat was attached to two thin, flat, and rectangular metal plates, each one covered in runes, and slid into two slots in the floor. The very floor below the mat was likewise covered in runes, and as the plates lowered or rose as someone either stood on it, or tried to pull it away, the runes would align in different patterns forming different spells and using the minute amounts of magic pulled from the wizard who stood atop it. Ingenious.

Harry let out a silent sigh. As much as he’d like to spend hours examining the mat, he did need to sweep the rest of the room, and Dumbledore was asleep not fifteen metres away. It certainly wouldn’t do to be caught in here.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The morning of the truth dawned. Harry woke up, climbed out of bed, put on his muggle exercise clothes, disillusioned himself, and went for a jog around the lake, making sure to stand out of the way as he passed his brother going the other way. He arrived back at his dorm room to catch his year mates in various states of readiness for the day.

Nott looked up as he walked back in. “Merlin, Potter, you do know we’re finished for the year, right? You should be relaxing!”

Harry smiled. The reactions of the Dark children since he’d returned had been one of cautious friendliness with attempted hidden undertones of awe. “You can relax if you like, I’ve got stuff to do.”

Draco also looked around from where he sat in front of his mirror, wanding down his hair. “Let him be, Theo. Potter can do whatever he wants.”

“Indeed,” Harry said.

On his bed on the other side of the room, Goyle was reading a comic book titled, ‘The Adventures of Martin Miggs, the Mad Muggle.’

Crabbe still hadn’t woken up.

Just then, Blaise Zabini walked in from the dorm bathroom, naked from the waist up and wrapped in towel. “Oh, hey, Harry. Tag you’re in.”

“Thanks.” Harry walked into the bathroom.

“Hey!” Goyle called from behind him. “I was next!”

Twenty minutes later, Harry and Blaise had dressed and made their way down to breakfast. Harry sat himself down in the medley of Gray students at the near-end of the Slytherin table and helped himself to a slice of toast. Everyone happily made space for him. “Morning all. Where’s Tracey?”

A few people said morning in reply and Hermione shrugged. “Don’t know. We think she went off to do something.”

“Well, could you let her know that I’ve got something to discuss with her if you do see her will you?”

Hermione nodded.

On the other side of the table, Daphne was deep in conversation with Flint about quidditch. Slytherin had squashed Ravenclaw in the final match, but Gryffindor had still been ahead on points and so had taken the cup, much to Harry’s annoyance. Flint also wasn’t happy.

Romulus Volf, on the other hand, sitting all the way at the other end of the table with the Dark students, was happy. After Harry had been led away in handcuffs by Regent Bones, the Slytherin duelling team had gone on to dominate their Gryffindor opponents, with many of their seeds taking their upper year opponents and the Slytherin sixth year successfully defeating the Gryffindor seventh year.

The entire castle had that end of year feel. Everyone was relaxing and enjoying themselves—even the fifth and seventh years, who’d finished their OWLS and NEWTS just days earlier.

All around the table, plans for summer were being drawn up. Trips to people’s houses were being negotiated and even the occasional group holiday came up in the flow.

“You should really drop by some time,” Blaise said to him. “I’m sure my mother would love to meet you.”

“I’m sure she would.” Harry said, making sure to leave even the tinniest hint of drollness out of his voice. Mrs. Zabini had what could only be described as a ‘reputation’—five dead husbands, all of them rich. Lord Slytherin would no doubt be considered the ultimate prize for the black widow. “I’ll see what I can do—no promises though—there’s a good chance I might be tied up this summer with other projects.”

Blaise nodded and returned to his breakfast.

Harry didn’t say what those projects were, but he certainly knew what he hoped they would be.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Deep in a trunk, hidden in the fidelius charmed spot in the Hogwarts Library, three children gathered around a small vial of muddy looking liquid.

“You ready?” Hermione asked.

Harry nodded.

“Good luck.” Daphne added.

Harry took a small white hair out of another glass jar and let it settle into the vial of polyjuice. The potion bubbled. He drank.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John sat by the side of the lake, lounging in the middle of his fellow Gryffindors, enjoying the warm summer sun and cooling lake breeze. Since his brother’s supposed murder attempt, Lily Moon, Fay Dunbar, Lavender Brown and Sally-Anne Perks seemed to have formed a pact of some description to keep a protective eye on him, which was kind of cute if not really needed. Ron, Neville, and Seamus on the other hand, were in awe of him. Only Dean seemed to not be fully onboard team Gryffindor. He frowned.

Just then, a paper bird fluttered over and alighted on the ground in front of him. He stared at it. Then, suddenly, the bird chirped once and a voice that he instantly recognised as the headmaster’s started to speak from it. “John, could you please meet me in my office? It’s urgent. I am rather fond of cockroach clusters.”

The others all looked up. “The headmaster wants to see you?” asked Fay with wide eyes. “Are you in trouble?”

“Oh, no it’s fine.” He waved the concern away while getting up. “We often talk about stuff. Comes with the territory.”

“I’ll come with you.” Lily Moon started to stand up too.

“No, it’s okay.”

“You’re sure?”

“Yeah.” And with that, he left the rather anxious group of girls behind him and walked back up to the school.

“Cockroach Clusters,” he said to the gargoyle at the bottom of the rotating staircase. The stone statue leaped aside and he made his way up the stairs. The door opened.

“Good Morning, John. Please mind the floor.”

John looked down. The floor had been covered by rough floorboards floating a few inches above it.

“I had a bit of an accident with a little project of mine and the floor now turns anyone who stands on it into a rabbit.” He smiled twinkly eyed at him.

John laughed. “You wanted to see me?”

Dumbledore turned serious. “Yes. I have a meeting with the ICW that I have no choice but to attend, but I have discovered something grave in the meantime. You remember the third floor corridor that I told students to leave alone at the start of the year?”

John’s heart lurched. This was about the stone. He’d completely forgotten about that! How had he completely forgotten about that? “Yes?” he said.

“I’ve been using it as a kind of safe to house an extremely valuable magical artefact. Last night, I learned of a threat to the artefact and decided the best course of action would be to remove it from the safe. Unfortunately, when I went down to claim it, I found that my final defence was just a bit too clever for my own good. It is a test that only the pure of intent can bypass and, it seems that I, much to my shame, am not pure enough.” Dumbledore suddenly looked extremely tired. “I would never ask you to do this under normal circumstances, but time, unfortunately does not allow me any alternative. I must leave now, but I need you, John, to succeed where I have failed.”

John’s mind raced. Dumbledore needed him to retrieve the stone. Had quirrell attempted to go after it again and failed? Had Flamel decided to take it back? One thing was clear to him, he could not fail.

“You are looking for a red stone, about the size of your fist.” He handed over a piece of paper. “Please read this.”

John read the paper. It read, ‘The Mirror of Erised is located at the end of the third floor corridor.’ Suddenly, memories flooded back into his mind.

“Now you should be able to navigate your way to the room the stone is hidden in. Please make haste. I fear that if the artefact should fall into the wrong hands, the consequences will be dire.”

Quirrell. No, Voldemort! John handed the paper back to the headmaster. “Yes, Sir. I won’t let you down.” He turned and dashed down the way he came.

“Please by careful, John!” called the Headmaster from behind him. “The defences are not to be taken lightly!”

John thought furiously. This was his time to prove himself. Yes. He’d find the stone and prove to the world he was the true chosen of Fate, not Harry.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry tugged Dumbledore’s beard and watched John go. All around the room, the portraits snoozed, all charmed asleep. He reached into his pocket, took out the Dan and Emma Granger rune enabled magical earpiece, and slipped it into his ear. “He bought it.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione watched on the marauder’s map as John Potter hurried away from the headmaster’s office and away from the little dot marked ‘Harry Potter’. Dumbledore’s voice spoke into her ear. “He bought it.”

“Excellent, now we don’t have to kidnap him.”

On the other side of the small table, Daphne raised her eyebrow. “Harry said that if we tried to force him the mirror might not have given him the stone.”

Hermione covered the ear mic with her hand and mouthed, ‘I know,’ to her friend.

But Daphne wasn’t watching her. She was watching the map with narrowed eyes. “It would appear that our cat’s paw is not going to the third floor.”

Hermione snapped her head down and spoke into the ear piece. “Cat’s Paw has veered away from the corridor that leads to the third floor and is heading towards …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John descended the stone steps that led to the dungeons, paused outside of a stack of barrels, and waited. He didn’t have long to wait. A message given to an older Hufflepuff later and Susan emerged from the Hufflepuff common room. “John? What’s going on?”

He motioned her to follow him. “Dumbledore gave me something important to do and I need your help.”

“Really?” Susan started to walk behind him. “Do I need anything?”

John shook his head. Last time, it had been Hermione who had solved Snape’s riddle and he wasn’t taking any chances. “Just your mind.”

They marched up past the third floor and headed towards Ravenclaw tower. Eventually, the tower door opened in response to another student carried message and Padma, Turpin, and Roper exited. “Hi Padma, we need your help for something.”

Padma looked curious. “What?”

“It’s err …” he glanced towards Turpin. “It’s Light related.”

“Ah. Do I need anything?”

He smiled “Just your amazing singing voice.”

Padma blushed.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry, still polyjuiced as Dumbledore, stood at the pathway just outside the third-floor corridor under a disillusionment charm. “Where is he now?”

Hermione’s voice spoke into his ear. “Now he’s heading towards Gryffindor tower.”

Harry made a cluck sound with his tongue and continued to wait.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Ron! The Light needs your chess skills!”

Ron Weasley looked up and grinned. “Sure thing, John. Be with you in a moment.”

“Now!”

“Oh okay, okay”

Five minutes later, they stood outside the door to the third-floor corridor.

“Okay, John,” Susan said, hands on her hips, “are you going to explain what Dumbledore asked you to do now?”

“We need to get something that he’s been protecting because he can’t do it himself.”

“What?”

John opened his mouth to say, but choked instead. “C-can’t say.” He grimaced. “Protected. By magic.”

Susan, Padma, and Ron all made oh faces.

Padma pointed to the walls and ceiling. “Whatever it is, it’s protected quite well—look at those.”

John and the others looked up.

Rune stones lined the walls and ceiling.

John nodded. “Yeah, okay, but that’s not the only defence. The first defence that we need to get past is a large animal that can be put to sleep with music, so you, Padma, will need to sing it to sleep.”

Padma bit her lip. “Sing what?”

“I don’t know—anything should work. You ready?”

They all nodded.

“Okay, let’s do this.” He reached for the door.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Professor McGonagall walked down the Hogwarts main stair case with a stack of parchments under her arm. She reached the third floor and idly glanced along the corridor. Something about that corridor felt wrong, but whenever she tried to think about it, the thoughts just wouldn’t stick. Something inside her brain slid away. She gave her head a little shake. Err … What had she just been thinking? Wait! She suddenly caught sight of a group of first years led by a very familiar figure milling around outside the third-floor corridor with their backs to her. Up to no good by the looks of it. She turned and took a step towards them.

“Confundus.”

Something unseen hit the transfiguration professor. She blinked. Err … what was she doing? Oh yes, she needed to get these exams to the ministry for filling in the records—and after that maybe she’d go down to the three broomsticks for a dram. She turned back and started walking down the stairs again, paying no attention to the four first years who’d just slipped through the third-floor corridor door.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry lowered his wand as he watched McGonagall leave and nodded to himself. Close one, that.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione whispered into her ear peace. “Cat’s Paw and friends have passed through the gender ward and are now in the first room.” She and Daphne had abandoned their trunk and now sat under the invisibility cloak in the muggle-studies defence room. Now they just needed to wait for their unwitting helpers to pass through.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John looked in puzzlement around the room. There was nothing here.

“John?” Padma asked, sounding nervous, “Where’s the huge beast?”

John frowned. “It’s not here. That’s odd. It’s supposed to be here.” He shrugged. “Oh, well. On to the next room.” He walked over to the door on the far side and opened it. They stepped into a room filled with plants. It was like a miniature rainforest inside the school.

“Should have brought Neville,” Ron commented as they made their way through the brush, he would have loved—AGHHHH!”

Something had grabbed onto Ron’s leg and hauled him into the air. The girl’s squealed and John watched as a tentacle started to wrap itself around Ron’s waist.

“Hold on, Ron!” John brandished his wand and shouted, “elementa ignis! (elemental fire)” A column of fire burst from his wand and engulfed the aggressive devil’s snare. The magical plant let out a pained cry and dropped Ron, withdrawing its many tentacles that had been sneaking around him and the girls, and retreated into a corner of the room.

Slightly shaken, Ron and the two girls followed him to the door. “What’s in the next room, John?” Susan asked.

“Well, this room was the devil’s snare, so the next room should be the flying keys.”

He opened the door. It wasn’t flying keys. Instead, a flat open room greeted them, and at the end of the room, stood a lone stone warrior, holding a massive halberd.

Padma bit her lip. “This doesn’t look like flying keys.”

John frowned. “No, it doesn’t.” What was going on here? Had all this changed too?

“What do you suppose the statue does?” Padma asked. “Will it attack us if we get too close?”

John shrugged. “Only one way to find out.” He stepped forward.

Suddenly, the statue leapt into life and rushed him, halberd raised, it’s intent clear.

John only just managed to get a shield up before the heavy weapon smashed into it.

Padma and Ron screamed.

Susan pointed her wand at the statue and shouted, “Ictus!” (Stinging Hex), which had about as much effect as a tickling charm.

The statue turned towards her and raised its weapon.

“Bombarda!” John’s blasting curse smashed into the statue and flung a pile of rubble away from them and across the room.

Silence.

Eventually, Ron said, “Merlin that freaked me out.”

Padma nodded voice shaking. “It’s a good thing John is so powerful. That thing would have killed us otherwise.”

John smiled. “Don’t worry, guys. Dumbledore would never have sent me against something I couldn’t handle. You’re safe with me.”

Susan smiled back at him.

“We ready to continue?” he asked.

They all nodded.

The next room seemed to be nothing but a stone passageway. John frowned. “This was supposed to be a massive chess set.”

Ron grinned. “For me?”

“Yeah.”

“Why do you suppose it isn’t what you thought it was supposed to be?” Susan asked. “Did Dumbledore tell you what the defences were?”

“No …” he said slowly, “Not exactly.”

“Then how—”

There was a click noise, and the door at the far end of the corridor swung open.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione whispered into her earpiece. “Cat’s Paw and friends have passed through our tunnel in the transfiguration room. They’re now in the astronomy room.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Its dark in here,” Ron’s voice said.

Stars shone over head.

“Try and find a light?” John asked.

Susan’s voice spoke in an exasperated tone. “Try and find a—John! You are a wizard!”

Padma giggled.

“Oh, right. Lumos!” A bright light—far brighter than any other first year, saving Harry who didn’t count, could produce—filled the room.

“Ooooo,” said the girls.

Ron rolled his eyes. “Tch. Show off.”

John smirked. “Let’s try and find what we’re supposed to do here. This room was supposed to be a troll.”

Padma made a little squeak. “T-troll?”

John turned to her. “Yeah, you shouldn’t have any problem with that? You did take one down after all.”

“Yeah!” she half shrieked, “And I still have nightmares about that!”

Susan stepped beside Padma and put a calming hand on her shoulder. “Well there’s obviously no troll here so let’s find out what there is, okay?”

A few minute later they found the star controller, along with written instructions.

Susan read the parchment aloud. “Using the books provided, move the stars to the position they should be in on June 30, 1881.” Next to the parchment on the table, stood a row of books.

“Oooo!” Padma said, clapping her hands together, “I can do this one! I’m really good at astronomy.”

John nodded, “I’m glad one of us is then.”

Ten minutes later, they were through.

The next room held little more than what looked like a muggle television and a plastic box of some kind below it.

John read the instructions. “To pass through to the next room, set the muggle VCR to record a television show between the time of 7:00pm and 7:45pm on Sunday on Channel One. Please use the instruction manual provided.” He looked up at his friends. “Ron, your dad is big into muggle stuff, right? So this should be a piece of cake for you.”

“Umm …” Ron picked up the controller looking extremely uncertain. “I don’t know about that, but I’ll give it a go.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“This is painful,” groaned Hermione to Daphne under her breath, watching from the far side of the room under the invisibility cloak.

The three Light purebloods and single Light halfblood had now spent the better part of thirty minutes trying and failing to set the VCR.

“I thought that book your parents sent you told you how to do it?” whispered Daphne.

“It does! … sort of.”

Harry’s voice—still disguised as Dumbledore’s—growled into Hermione’s ear. “We don’t have time for this. I’m going to intervene. Get ready to give me instructions.”

By the open door to the astronomy defence, a patch of background crept across the room towards the arguing Light students, moving about as quickly as a sloth on dreamless sleep.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Look! Just give it to meee!” Padma made to snatch the controller out of Ron’s hand.

Ron held it out of the shorter girl’s reach. “I can do it! I just—” He stumbled as though hit by something.

“Just what?”

“Wait! I’ve got it!” Ron hit a button on the controller and then looked around as though confused.

“Well?” John asked.

Susan stood off to the side tapping her foot.

Ron looked down at the controller and then tapped another button. Something on the muggle television changed. Then he tapped another button, and then another, before too long, there was a click sound and the door to the next room swung open.

John thumped him on the back. “Well done, mate! Knew you had it in you.”

Ron smiled uncertainly. Yeah, he’d done it, hadn’t he.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John stood in the empty next room and shrugged. So much for Snape’s potion riddle. The open door beckoned him. “I’m going to head on ahead now.”

Susan, Padma, and Ron looked at him in confusion. “Go where?”

“Ahead.”

Ron tilted his head. “You’re not making any sense, mate.”

John rolled his eyes. Of course, they hadn’t been given the secret had they? He opened his mouth to explain, but choked again. “Ah, sorry, Susan, Padma, Ron, it seems like the magic will let only me finish the rest of the task Dumbledore gave me.”

They looked at him with worried eyes.

“Just, stay here until I get back, okay?”

“Back from where?!” shouted Susan as he walked away.

And then he was gone.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione heard Harry’s disguised voice speak into her ear. “Girls, head back to the trunk, you’ve done all you can here. Ring only communication from here on.”

Hermione nodded though she knew Harry couldn’t see her. “Understood.” She turned to where she could feel Daphne standing beside her. “We’ve been ordered back to the trunk.”

“Then let’s move,” Daphne’s voice said.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

And John Potter stood in front of the Mirror of Erised.

In the reflection, a slightly older John stood on top of a slain dragon’s head at the end of the first tri-wizard tournament task. In his hand he held a sword, which he pointed up to the sky in a pose of triumphant heroism. All around him, witches and wizards from all over the world applauded his latest heroic deed.

Ginny hung off one of his arms, looking up at him with adoration while Hermione hung off the other. Susan, Padma, Hannah, Fey, Lavender, and many others all crowded around him, all congratulating him for saving the day yet again. Even the other two Hogwarts champions—Alexandra Black and Cedric Diggory—looked mildly impressed, standing off to the side, holding swords of their own, and clapping, if only grudgingly in Alex’s case.

Then, the sword wielding John looked at him, withdrew a red stone from his pocket, winked, and put it back in—and John felt the stone’s weight drop into his real pocket. He reached into his pocket, withdrew the philosopher’s stone, and smiled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hidden by the door, Harry pointed his wand at John from near the entrance to the mirror room and cast a summoning spell at the stone now held in his brother’s hand. Nothing. It didn’t budge. The stone was non-summonable—probably non levitatable too—and he certainly didn’t intend to find out how breakable it was. Rats. He frowned. Oh, well. Plan B it was, then.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John heard clapping from behind him. He whirled around, heart hammering and let out the breath of relief when he saw it was Dumbledore. “Merlin, Headmaster, you nearly gave me a heart attack.”

Dumbledore smiled. “I do apologise, John, but it does my old heart good to see youth triumph where the aged have failed.”

John looked at the stone in his hands. “Yeah.” He frowned. “I thought you had a ICW meeting?”

Dumbledore frowned. “So did I—and I rushed off in a bit of a hurry, didn’t I? But when I arrived it suddenly occurred to me that the place I should really be was the place I had just left.”

John turned back to the mirror.

Mirror John enthusiastically waved his sword.

“Headmaster, what are we gong to do about my brother?”

There was a pause from behind him before Dumbledore replied, “We continue as we have been.”

John frowned and tore his gaze away from the mirror.

Dumbledore had moved to stand almost right in front of him, holding out his hand for the stone.

“We cannot continue on like this!” John shouted.

Dumbledore dropped his hand. He sighed. “I understand, John. You are frustrated, but our position demands patience.” He offered his hand out again. “Together we will ensure your brother is no longer a threat.”

John hesitated, stone still clutched in his hand. Something about this didn’t feel right. Something about this felt very, very wrong. “H-headmaster?”

“Yes?”

“Do you remember that explosion last summer at the Burrow?”

Dumbledore tugged his beard in thought. “I do.”

“I think that … I think that Harry might have caused it.”

“… What makes you think that?”

John’s heart skipped a beat.

What happened next seemed to slow down time itself. John’s eyes finished widening. He stumbled backwards and hastily brought his wand hand up, casting a shield at the exact moment that the imposter Dumbledore narrowed his eyes, rose his empty hand and shot a wandless bright red stunner at him.

John’s shield held and the stunner bounced off. He stumbled back another step and hit the mirror, which rocked threateningly.

Imposter Dumbledore cast a shield of his own with his other empty hand and stepped forward.

John strengthened his shield and got his balance, just in time to absorb another two stunners. He dodged around the mirror, clutching the side of the heavy bronze to counterbalance his weight, stone still clutched in a white knuckled grip, and successfully put the massive artefact between him and the unknown imposter.

“Accio John Potter!”

And a huge magical pull tugged him straight towards the mirror, toppling it over, shattering it on the ground with an earsplitting crash, and skidding him across a painful plane of broken glass and bronze.

Imposter Dumbledore swept down on him and gabbed the stone with one hand.

John desperately shoved his wand at Imposter Dumbledore and shouted, ‘Stupefy!’ only to watch in horror as the spell was intercepted as though by divine intervention by the imposter’s free hand—all five fingers glowing red—bouncing off and harmlessly flying away.

The imposter pressed his free hand firmly to John’s chest.

There was a flash of red.

And John’s world went dark.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“This kind of aggressive action cannot be tolerated!” The Prussian delegate to the International Confederation of Wizards banged his fist on the table. “Prussia will not stand by and allow ourselves to be bullied by these kinds of …”

Albus Dumbledore relaxed in his high back chair and let the words of the conference on international magical crime wash over him. At least here, no one was sniping or sniggering or asking awkward questions—Especially about the damn mirror room on the third … floor … corridor …

His eyes widened. He could remember! The fidelius was down! He stood up and made towards the exit, muttering an excuse as he went. International crime could wait—inner school crime was a much more pressing issue.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Back in the chest in the library, Hermione gazed down at the Marauder’s Map.

Daphne watched from the other side of the table. “I do wish he’d hurry up.”

Hermione couldn’t help agreeing. Having Harry off-map was driving her mental.

Suddenly a point of interest started moving. She jabbed her finger at it “Look!” Quirrell was exiting his office at a dead run.

“Forget that, look at this!” Daphne jabbed her own finger down at the third floor corridor. Harry and John’s dot had reappeared on the map. The mirror room was visible again. She glanced back towards where Quirrell’s dot was running.

The dot stopped by a nameless stretch of wall, and vanished.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Headmaster?”

Harry turned and saw Susan Bone’s head poking uncertainly around the door.

“What’s going on? Where’s John?” She suddenly caught view of John, lying unconscious on the floor badly cut by the glass spread all around. She gasped.

Harry spoke quickly. The polyjuice didn’t have much longer to run. “Miss Bones, Mister Potter needs to be taken the hospital wing, immediately.”

She nodded and moments later was joined by Padma Patil of Ravenclaw and Ronald Weasley of Gryffindor.

“What happened?” Susan asked.

Suddenly, Harry felt his lightning bolt ring start to vibrate.

‘LV.’

“John was helping me to extract an important artefact, which I was keeping here for safety,”

‘INC.’

Harry’s mind raced. Voldemort was coming. Getting his classmates out of the way was now even more important. “Unfortunately, John failed to listen to one of my more explicit instructions and was injured.”

“What!” Susan shouted.

Padma leaned over John and started cleaning him up.

“He needs medical attention, Miss Bones. Use your levitation charm to take him to the medical wing, now.”

Susan hesitated. “Wouldn’t you be able to do it better?”

“I have another matter to attend to—one which is extremely urgent. For Mister Potter’s sake, go now!”

Susan flinched back, but between them, the three first years did manage to get John moving out of the room. Harry followed with them until they left the muggle studies defence room. He then turned to the secret parseltongue passageway, hissed, $open$, and scrambled inside.

He’d only got a few metres when the blood red stone, still clutched firmly in his free hand, started talking to him.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione watched Harry disappear off the map. “He’s out of there.”

“Yes,” said Daphne, a mild note of panic in her voice, “but we don’t know where the Dark Lord is.”

Then, another dot appeared in the Headmaster’s office. Dumbledore had just re-entered the castle.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry stilled.

“Hello there,” said a congenial voice, speaking from the stone as though through a brick wall. “This is Nicholas Flamel. You have just removed my stone from the vicinity of my mirror. How clever of you.”

Harry’s heart lurched. He stopped and stared at the stone as though suddenly holding a bomb.

“This is just a recording, of course, but I thought it might be a good idea for you to know a few things. If this is you, Albus, then I am extremely disappointed in you. You asked for my stone for a project of yours on the condition that you would not need to touch it, inspect it, or in any way interact with it. That you have gone to the effort to try to bypass my mirror and have succeeded in doing so, shows that I have misplaced my trust in you.”

Harry bit his lip.

“If this is you, Tom Riddle, then I give you nothing but my highest scorn and disdain. I have lived over six hundred years and you are nothing but a worm to be squashed. That I have not done so is merely because I see it as the job of younger men than me to fight for the Wizarding World.”

Harry gazed at the stone, nonplussed, but the stone wasn’t done yet.

“There is, of course, a third person that might have removed the stone, but I currently consider that to be a remote possibility. Nevertheless, if this is you, Lord Slytherin, then congratulations—I shall keep my eye on you far closer in future.”

Harry cursed.

“Whichever of you succeeded though, matters not. Albus may believe in priming a trap with live bait, but I do not, and I did not live six hundred years by being stupid. The stone is fake. Sorry about that.”

Harry let the stone fall to his side and stared at the pipe wall.

“Toodles!”

The voice cut off.

Harry groaned. Damn. Damn, damn, damn. He took a deep breath, counter plans quickly forming and reforming in his head. He still had enough money to last him until next Winter Festival. And he had all of summer to track down a new source of income.

As Harry planned, he started to feel the polyjuice run out. His beard receded, his body shortened, his hair turned back to black.

He also still had one half of his drugs business and that would hopefully keep him solvent for another few months, but he would have to hold off on buying that second house elf, which would suck, but it would free up twelve thousand galleons (£600,000), and he could hire out house elves for the Slytherin Manor finishing party next Winter Festival and persuade Jacob to lend him a few more for the kitchens. … He let out another breath. Yes, it wouldn’t be easy, but he could probably keep Slytherin House afloat. He just needed to hustle like he’d never hustled before.

He took a step up the pipe, turned the corner, and stopped dead.

“Hello, Mister Potter,” said Quirrell, eyes glowing red, skin flaking off his body, wand held casually off to his side.

Harry mentally shrugged, shielded, and turned to escape.

“Or should I say, Lord Slytherin?”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore marched swiftly down a hallway towards the third floor corridor, wand out and ready. He turned a corner and almost walked straight into a panting Susan Bones and Padma Patil, both of whom were levitating a prone John Potter, physically assisted by the youngest male Weasley.

“Headmaster?!” Miss Bones looked over her shoulder before looking back at him. “But, we just left you!”

“You left me, Miss Bones?” Dumbledore’s eyes narrowed. “You mean you just met another me?”

“Yes.”

“Where!”

“Down in the third floor corridor.”

“Was I holding a red stone?” He asked urgently.

Susan hesitated, wand still pointing at a floating John. “Y-yes, I think so.”

Dumbledore cursed and hurried past them. If he was lucky, he’d be able to cut whoever it was off, Tom or Slytherin, or someone else, or both.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Back in the trunk, Hermione paced frantically, occasionally shooting worried glances at the map, which showed Dumbledore advancing towards the third floor corridor, but still no sign of Harry or Voldemort. “Should we ask him what’s going on?”

Daphne shook her head. “No. We shouldn’t distract him. If he needs our help, he’ll ask.”

“What about your Eye of Kilrogg?” Hermione asked. “If we got close enough to the pipework near the third floor corridor—”

“—No.” Daphne cut her off. “We shouldn’t put ourselves at any more risk than we need to. It won’t help Harry. Remember the unicorn. Remember what Harry said.”

Hermione slowed down and took a deep breath. “Yes, you’re right. The overall mission. Weigh risks and rewards. Don’t take unnecessary risks. I remember.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Or should I say, Lord Slytherin?” Voldemort sneered.

Harry froze. He hadn’t just heard that had he? He flexed his wand hand, ready to swat away any hostile magic the moment he felt the build-up behind him. “Professor?”

“Don’t play me for a fool, Potter—you will regret it. You know well who I truly am.”

Harry turned around slowly, wand now pointed at the fake stone, his threat very obvious. “Okay, so give me one good reason why I shouldn’t destroy your obviously weakened possessed corpse.”

Voldemort smirked. “Because I currently hold the life of one of your witches in my hand and can snuff it out faster than you could raise your wand.”

Harry heart lurched. What! He looked around, seeing nothing. How?

Voldemort smirked. “Oh yes, very protective, aren’t you?”

Hermione and Daphne were in his trunk in the library. Ginny and Luna weren’t even at Hogwarts, and although he’d still hesitate to think of Alexandra and one of ‘his witches,’ she was also nowhere near the castle. “You’re bluffing.”

“I assure you, ‘Lord Slytherin,’ I am not.”

Harry’s eyes narrowed, body coiled, wand still pointing at the stone. And how did Voldemort even know that?

Voldemort still had his wand pointed off to his side, although for some reason, Harry had difficulty understanding exactly what the Dark Lord was pointing at.

“You, Potter, are going to hand me that stone.” Voldemort said, tone calm and level.

“Go on.”

“Or, else, this pretty young thing dies.”

Harry’s eyes darted around the pipe. What was he talking about?

Voldemort laughed. A high pitched laugh that echoed around the metalwork. “Oh, I do beg your pardon. My manners, ‘My Lord,’ ” he said, mockingly. “Lord Voldemort’s secret pipe section is located fifty metres North-West of the mirror room at the end of the third-floor corridor.”

Suddenly half of the pipe seemed to invert itself from out of the metal work and a girl appeared, wrapped tightly in ropes, propped up against the wall and gagged, terrified eyes flittering back and forth between him and the decaying body of the defence professor, Voldemort’s wand pointing straight at her. To the girl’s side sat a currently expanded and open shrinkable multi-compartment trunk. It was Tracey.

Shit.

Voldemort chuckled. “Oh, dear. Not who you were expecting, mm? Who did you think I would target? Miss Granger? Miss Greengrass? Perhaps your Miss Lovegood? Because, ‘Lord Voldemort always targets only those closest to his targets? Correct?”

Harry’s head snapped away from Tracey and back to Voldemort. What?

“Yes, I know, Potter. I’ve known for most of the year. Did you honestly think that I, a genius, wouldn’t figure it out?”

Harry kept his wand trained on the stone. “Figure what out?”

Voldemort looked at him, almost disappointed. “I invented that form of occlumency, Potter. I created it to catch up to my peers after I leaned just how they were doing so damn well in classes—after I learned how they’d spent years practising it, years that I didn’t have. You know that. You know, everything. You took that accidental horcrux lodged in your forehead, somehow, and wringed it for everything it had.”

Voldemort thought Harry’d got his knowledge from the horcrux in his forehead.

Harry scowled. “The occlumency doesn’t leave that kind of trace. It doesn’t leave any trace at all. You know that.”

Tracey was still looking between the two of them, wide eyed and fearful.

“Indeed and had it not been for all the other little things, I wouldn’t have suspected anything.”

Other little things? Harry’s mind raced. He had to keep Riddle talking. Keep him not killing. He couldn’t let Tracey die. She was worth a lot more than a stupid fake stone. The lone heiress of one his houses dying on his watch would be a disaster—not to mention she’d proven herself capable in her own right. He needed her. So, what other little things?

“You can’t think?” Voldemort moved over to where Tracey leaned against the wall and gripped her arm in his free hand. “Such a pity, I do hope you aren’t just my memories. That would be such a shame. In any case, you’ll have plenty of time to think, because you are going to give me the stone, yes, but there’s something else you’re going to give me too.”

Harry said nothing.

Voldemort’s eyes narrowed in anger and Harry felt Voldemort’s fury brush through the link they shared for the first time in almost four years. The man’s eyes glowed darker as he spat, “You are going to go to wherever you’ve hidden them, and give me back my diadem, my ring, and my locket!”

Fuck.

“Yes, I found the diadem missing. Yes, I went and checked the others too. You are the only person who could have done this, and if you don’t start moving, this little lady is going to start losing bits!”

Tracey closed her eyes and whimpered.

Harry gritted his teeth. “They’re not in the castle.”

“Then have your servants go get them!”

“They don’t have the secret,” he bluffed, trying to buy time.

“Then summon them here and tell them it! I know you can, I’ve felt the magic come from you and to them more than once before.”

Harry cursed in his head. This had suddenly got a lot worse. Of course if Riddle figured out he was Lord Slytherin he’d link it to the diadem Harry had swiped at the start of the year. Tracey’s value in this equation had just dipped way off the other side. He needed to stall for more time. Needed to figure out a way to get the girl out of this without losing the soul jars to Voldemort. Could he have Daphne call for backup? No. Could he have them lay a trap? No. Could he lead Voldemort into a trap? No obvious opportunities came to mind.

“Any time you’re ready, Potter,” Riddle said impatiently.

Harry glanced at Tracey once more and, thinking furiously, started pulsing magic into his lightning bolt ring.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione straightened. Vibrations were coming through her ring. Harry was alright! She could tell by the way Daphne started at her without seeming to see that she too, was receiving Harry’s message, and was concentrating on decoding it.

Gradually, the feeling of elation faded, giving way to worry and dread.

“Tracey,” Daphne whispered.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“I’ve sent them the message,” Harry said. “They should be leaving the school soon.”

“Good.” Voldemort now had his wand under Tracey’s neck. His voice had lost its schizophrenic anger, returning back to the normal calm drawl. “Had any more thoughts, Potter?”

Harry scowled.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Dumbledore burst into the mirror room to find it empty, minus one destroyed mirror. “Homenum revelio!”

Nothing.

He cursed, turned, and ran back the way he came. Charging halfway across Hogwarts, he reached his office and lunged, for the second time in as many months, at the lockdown trinket. The windows slammed shut. Magic pulsed out around him. There.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne and Hermione, carrying two broomsticks, awkwardly crept along the sun baked grounds of Hogwarts, past any number of students lounging by the lake, and down the path to the closed Hogwarts gates. They ducked behind the first tree they found, whipped the cloak off, mounted the broomsticks, and flew up and over the gate, careful not to be seen by anyone, and out across the Scottish highlands.

The moment they crossed the ward line, they felt a huge surge of magic pulse just behind them.

“What was that?” Hermione called out.

Daphne cursed. “I hope it wasn’t lockdown. We’re locked out, otherwise.”

The two witches looked at each other, but there wasn’t anything else to do. They had their orders.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry desperately continued to try and think of a way out of this situation—preferably one that didn’t involve Tracey dying. He was sure he could take the weakened Dark Lord in a fair fight—which was obviously why he’d taken a hostage—but he was also certain that if he attacked Voldemort, the first thing that would happen was Tracey taking a killing curse to the chest.

A wave of magic washed over them.

Voldemort glanced around. “It would seem that Dumbledore has cottoned on to your fidelius failure, Potter.”

Harry glanced around the pipe. Suddenly, a possible answer came to him. “Dust.”

Voldemort raised an eyebrow. “Do go on, student.”

“I’ve been using the parseltongue only passageways. You can use them too. I must have left a trail of some description behind me, despite being very careful not to.”

Voldemort smiled nastily. “That was the first thing, yes. But It wasn’t so much what you did leave behind as what you didn’t.”

Harry paused, then sniffed in realisation, disgusted at himself. “Cleaning charms.”

“Indeed. Your trail was your lack of trail. And get moving. With the castle on lockdown we need to go to where we can still leave.”

Harry nodded. Of course, the chamber of secrets

Voldemort pushed Tracey and she stumbled forward.

Harry started backing away slowly, keeping the two of them at the same distance while keeping his wand trained on the fake stone.

“And that was it?” Harry asked. Keep him talking. Keep him distracted. “You knew there was a parselmouth in the school, therefore you knew it was me? Seems pretty far fetched.”

Voldemort snarled. “Of course there was more than that, fool. Dumbledore practically told me you were special—stupid old codger that he is.”

“Dumbledore doesn’t know that I’m Lord Slytherin.”

“No.” Voldemort conceded. “Most amusing it was too, watching him floundering about. I actually had to straight out tell him that Lord Slytherin was after the stone, can you believe that?”

“Strangely enough, I can.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne flew over yet another Scottish mountaintop at top speed, warming charms doing their best against the nippy windchill from this high up. They’d been flying for what felt like ages.

“I can’t tell you how glad I am for flying lessons now,” Hermione shouted from a few metres away.

Daphne nodded back and focused forward. Harry’s island vault shouldn’t be far now.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry paused at the end of the pipe tunnel. A huge hole sunk into the floor behind him.

“The first time I came here,” Voldemort said, back to his casual tone of voice, “I didn’t know how to fly. But then, that’s the point isn’t it? Only those of Slytherin magic are allowed to enter, so only those who can fly should be granted easy passage.”

Harry rose up into the air.

Voldemort mirrored him, clutching a terrified Tracey firmly to his chest around the waist. Together, they descended down into the pipe, down and down, until they exited the pipe and into a space containing the exits of over half a dozen such pipes.

“You should feel honoured, Miss Davis,” Voldemort said. “Very few ever get the chance to see this place. Do you know where we are?”

Tracey frantically shook her head.

“This is the chamber of secrets.”

Tracey let out another small whimper.

The three of them floated over the sea of bones until they arrived at the portal to the chamber proper.

Voldemort gestured with his wand hand. “Well, as the resident Lord Slytherin, perhaps you should have the honours, Potter?”

Harry turned slightly to the portal, making sure to keep Riddle in view, and hissed, “$Open$,”.

The stone snakes slithered over and over each other to unlock the door and the portal creaked open.

“Have you had any more thoughts, Potter?”

Harry frowned. He had. “You knew? Or rather, you suspected? You suspected, so you investigated and only then did you know.”

Voldemort’s lip tugged upwards. “Getting close, Potter—figuratively and literally.”

Literally … Harry looked around. All around him, carvings of snakes filled the hall. “Snakes.”

“Go on.”

“Parselmagic? Parseltongue? Magic that affects snakes, or things that are snake like—makes a snake intelligent so it can better serve the master.”

Voldemort raised an approving eyebrow.

Harry continued to think out loud. “You know that I know about you, or rather, you suspect that I know. Because of … Because of how I act in class?”

“Sitting in front of the same two girls, one of whom is betrothed to Lord Slytherin and the other whom is Slytherin’s vassal, pointing your wand constantly at me under the desk, aren’t the most subtle set of actions you can take, Potter.”

“Snakes are only intelligent after they’ve been affected by parselmagic.”

“Yes.”

“So, before they’ve been affected by parselmagic, they can …” The realisation hit him. “They can be in range of a non secret keeper speaking a secret and not trip the fidelius charm.”

“Well done, Potter. If I didn’t have my wand at your little friend’s throat, I’d clap.”

Harry frowned. “That wasn’t a weakness you knew.”

Riddle gave him a look of deep disdain. “Obviously, as soon as I suspected there was someone out there who had all my knowledge, I started developing new methods. What kind of fool would try to use only tricks the enemy already knows?” He gestured to Tracey. “What kind of fool would behave as he knows the enemy believes he will behave in? You believed I would only attack Granger or Greengrass.”

“So that’s how you found me out?”

Riddle scoffed. “No. Oh, I did hear a conversation between you and Miss Granger where she called you, ‘my lord,’ but that was the extent of it, and by then, it was just another confirmation of what I already knew. Keeping random snakes invisible and under confundus around the school in the hope that they might happen to hear something is actually a pretty stupid technique. It was a wonder I heard even that.”

“So, how?”

Riddle made an exasperated noise. “Potter! Do you not understand? Have you not yet heard enough? There was no smoking wand! There was no aha moment. There was no one thing that made me draw the conclusion that you are Lord Slytherin and the baby I attempted and failed to murder. You were suspiciously placed away from your parents, with muggles, yet you come to Hogwarts with large amounts of knowledge of the wizarding world. You display all the signs of being a trained occlumens, yet your occlumency shields would have me believe that they don’t even exist, something only my occlumency can accomplish. Your mind pretends to be innocent while your actions belie a cunning and ruthlessness that is the hallmark of Slytherin house. You display fierce protectiveness of those connected with Lord Slytherin while around me and only me. All three of my horcruxes that are readily accessible to an outsider are gone. The parseltongue passages in the school are under use. Someone else besides me and Dumbledore is making active use of the fidelius charm. Both you and your brother are vastly over powered for your age, yet you go beyond even that. John Potter is mostly just power—extremely talented power for a first year, yes, but nothing compared to your ability. The moment you leave the school, both Miss Greengrass and Miss Granger are pulled by their heads of houses and Lord Slytherin isn’t seen from again, rare though his appearances are, granted, until you are released from custody. Do I need to go on?

Harry shook his head.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne opened the lead box lined with acromantula silk at the back of the cave and, occlumency at full strength, and noble house ring confidently on finger, carefully withdrew the three items held within.

“So pretty,” Hermione sighed, reaching out for the diadem.

One stinging hex and an embarrassed pout later and the two girls were off and over the sea, black dragon roaring in territorial rage behind them, heading back to Hogwarts, and praying Harry had some way to come out of this without giving the Dark Lord back his soul anchors.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Deep inside the chamber of secrets, standing in front of the massive statue of Salazar Slytherin, Harry continued to rack his brain for someway out of this without giving Voldemort back his soul anchors. He still couldn’t think of anything—anything apart from the painful obvious way, of course. He glanced at Tracey, still held shaking in Voldemort’s grip.

“You know, Harry,” Voldemort said, conversationally, “despite having a leg up from my soul fragment, you are still a remarkable young boy. You have managed to forge a completely new political faction out of what used to be little but a bunch of pathetic fence sitters—and you started when you were just eight. Truly an achievement to be proud of. One I myself can certainly appreciate.”

Harry gave Voldemort a tired but knowing look.

Voldemort laughed. “Yes, Harry Potter, you certainly do know me well, don’t you? This is the bit where I offer you a place in my most trusted inner circle. And why would you not accept it? You and I are very alike.”

Harry clucked his tongue. “You know that’s not true.”

Voldemort glanced down at Tracey. He tilted his head. “I suppose not, at a certain level. After all, I would have not hesitated to kill my opponent and let the girl die.”

Tracey’s eyes met Harry’s, desperate and imploring.

“But in other ways,” Riddle continued, “we are similar. It’s obvious what your end game is … domination of Magical Britain.”

“You want to exterminate all muggleborns.”

“And yet, you, Harry, might have shown me a better way. You know that I have vowed to eradicate all muggle influences from the wizarding world.”

“Yes.”

“Now look at your Miss Granger. Born to muggles yet completely understanding of her place in our world. You did that. Truly fascinating. Join me, and together we will easily sweep aside all those who stand in our way and make a world we know to be better.”

“I brought Hermione to my side by mixing in generosity and friendship with my blatant manipulations—generosity and friendship, rather than cruelty and fear.”

Voldemort scoffed. “So you believe that the ends don’t justify the means, is that it?”

“The ends are the means, especially for you. You seek immortality. For someone with no end, there are only means.” He shrugged. “Besides, my way works better—and it’s not like I don’t understand the value of making my enemies fear me.”

Voldemort smiled. “We shall see. I may be weakened today, but if you cannot attack me just because I have one witch’s life in my hands, then what chance do you have of ‘vanquishing’ me when I hold the entire country to ransom?”

Harry frowned. “You misunderstand me.”

Voldemort waited.

Harry didn’t elaborate.

Eventually Voldemort scowled. “Well? How do I misunderstand you?”

“I do not plan to tell you—that would be foolish.”

Voldemort sniffed.

Suddenly, Harry’s ring vibrated. Dammit.

Voldemort gave him an expectant look.

Harry nodded. “They have them.” Dammit, he needed more time. “They are outside the castle. They can’t get back in because of the lockdown.”

Voldemort made a gesture to a nearby snake portal, carved into the very stone of the chamber. “Then let’s go out and meet them. Then you can have your reasonably precious Miss Davis back and I can have what is mine.”

“I should tell you right now, that one of them is fake.”

“What!” Riddle hissed.

“The locket. It was fake when I found it. It had a note from an RB in it—I assume that was Regulus Black.”

Voldemort eyed him through narrow calculating eyes. “If you are lying …”

“I am not.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Here it is.” Daphne touched down in a clearing on the outskirts of the forbidden forest.

“Right.” Hermione alighted beside her. “Now, let’s put the bag in the middle of the clearing and hide. Maybe we’ll get a good opportunity to take him down from the side or something.”

“Just don’t do anything stupid. Don’t forget Voldemort can sense magic like Harry can.”

They placed the bag on the dirt ground, whipped the cloak around themselves, retreated to the edge of the clearing, and lay in wait.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry kept his eye on Voldemort as the man kept his eye on him, all the way up through the pipe, out of the overgrown secret entrance, and through to the forest clearing.

He still couldn’t think of anything! If this kept up, he might have no choice but to let Tracey die. Even if he still didn’t know where the locket was, Voldemort not having the opportunity to hide another two Horcruxes was better than the alternative—even if Voldemort could just make another one if he wanted. Even if it wouldn’t make any difference if they couldn’t find the locket.

They soon found the clearing with the bag in the centre and before Harry knew what was happening, Voldemort darted forward in the air, Tracey’s muffled screams trailing after him. The Dark Lord snatched up the bag and shot twenty metres into the sky.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Hermione gripped her wand, huddled next to Daphne under the cloak and watched Voldemort floating far above her, Tracey hanging precariously off his arm. Dammit! That had happened so quickly, she hadn’t even had a chance to consider attacking.

Beside her, Daphne whispered a bad word.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry scowled up at Voldemort who floated in the bright blue sky, cloak fluttering, eyes triumphant, reaching into the bag and withdrawing a couple of priceless artefacts—imbued with dark lord soul—and a worthless trinket, which held naught but a mocking note from a dead death eater.

“Do come up and join me, Mister Potter!”

Harry readied his wand and rose up to meet him. He needed to attack now. Tracey’s life was not worth it. He needed to be ruthless. He needed to—

“When we get high enough, I’ll toss you the witch. You toss me the stone.”

They continued to rise up, higher and higher, until the trees below weren’t even recognisable as trees.

Harry shivered from the cold, holding the stone tightly in his hand. His breathing sped up. His pupils dilated.

Voldemort smiled. “Catch!” He dropped Tracey.

Harry screamed a curse of rage and frustration, chucked the fake stone, and dove—dove straight for the ground and the muffled screaming of the rapidly descending Tracey. Choice irrevocably made, he snatched her up with easily enough room to decelerate before landing on the ground and looked up, Tracey now crying and clinging desperately to the front of his robes.

He felt a short wave of triumph and exhilaration wash against his occlumency barriers before being quickly snuffed out in the manner of the master occlumens.

Voldemort had gone.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Nicholas.” Dumbledore gazed out of the floo into the dinning room of the ancient alchemist.

“Wulfric?” A man who looked to be in his late forties looked up from the dinning table. “What is it? Perenelle and I have business this afternoon.”

“Ah, yes.” Dumbledore shifted uncomfortably in the floo. His knees were really hurting on the stone of his office floor. “It’s about your stone.”

“Stolen—yes, I know.”

Dumbledore started. “You know?”

“Yes, I know. I received an alert the moment it was removed from my mirror.”

Dumbledore’s heart raced. “Then, do you know where it is? Can you track it? Can we save it?”

“Relax Wulfric. That will not be necessary.”

“But, if Voldemort or Lord Slytherin—”

“—Wulfric!”

Dumbledore hesitated.

“Sometimes, you can be really stupid. Now, please tell me how you’re being really stupid in this particular instance.”

Dumbledore swallowed. His old master had slipped into teaching mode. There was nothing to be done when he was in teaching mode except be silent and play along. “Well …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Tracey clung to Daphne weakly as the four made their way back up the secret passageway to the Chamber of Secrets. Her skin was soaked with sweat, her underclothes were wet and clingy. She felt like she’d taken a bath fully clothed in a lake of nectar. She was cold, sticky, shivering, and coming down from an adrenaline overdose the like of which she’d never felt before.

Potter was Lord Slytherin. Potter was the boy who lived. H-H-He who must not be named was alive. The Dark Lord had taken her hostage. She wasn’t dead. Potter had saved her. Potter had traded something very valuable, from the sounds of it, for her life. The revelations and implications came hard and fast. And still she couldn’t stop herself from shaking.

Suddenly, every thing about the boy seemed larger than life. How had she not seen it before, he practically radiated power.

Potter—or was that Lord Slytherin?—walked up ahead, muttering to himself, but still loudly enough for Daphne and Hermione to hear and occasionally add a comment to the rapid, mostly monologue. “We’ll have to start on tracking down all his old haunts as quickly as possible, but that won’t work, because he’ll know that I know about them. No, we’ll have to find some way to track them directly, possibly using one them as a catalysts for a ritual or something. Our libraries will hopefully provide, but only the ones that he doesn’t already know about, or at least ones he hasn’t already read through.”

Then, suddenly, the impossible child lord staggered, fell against the stone wall, clamped his hand to his scar, suddenly glowing red, and scrunched up his eyes in pain.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“FAAKKKKKEEEE!”

One long cry pounded against Harry’s mile thick occlumency shields, not standing a chance of getting through after five years of strengthening, but making a damn good effort.

“ALL! FAKE!”

Visions of Quirrellmort screaming in rage and frustration floated in front of Harry’s mind, eyes red, skin peeling, muscle and bone starting to show and even rip away. He didn’t try to stop them, painful though they were. He let them come. The Dark Lord was furious. Anger led to weakness—led to an opening in the mind—led to a loss of critical information—information that Harry needed.

Voldemort threw the red stone against a tree where it shattered into a hundred spiky shards. He ripped the locket apart and slammed it on the ground. And then, to Harry’s utter shock, the Dark Lord pointed his wand at the ring and the diadem, snarled, “Malus ignis totalus diabolus!” and watched, panting and raging, as black flames of three headed serpents tore into the supposedly priceless artefacts and melted them down into nothing.

What the fuck?

Then, seemingly unable to stand the sudden magical surge and ensuing emotional tirade, Quirrell’s body finally gave up the ghost, ripping itself apart and collapsing into dust, leaving only the fractured soul of Dark Lord Voldemort, who whirled around the random wooded clearing and faded away on a sudden gust of wind.

Harry carefully pushed Voldemort’s visions away from his mind and found the feeling in his body again.

“Harry! Harry!” A voice pierced through the fog. “Are you alright?”

Harry opened his eyes. Hermione’s face hovered a few inches in front of his. Off to the side, Daphne and Tracey watched him with wide eyes.

“Hermione?” He frowned and grasped at the only logical explanation he could think of. “You managed to create a fake diadem and ring good enough to fool me and Voldemort in just a few hours?”

Hermione looked around to Daphne with a confused look.

Daphne shook her head.

Hermione turned back. “No, we didn’t. We did just as you said. We went to the place and got the things and came back and put them in the clearing. That was right, wasn’t it?”

Harry was speechless.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The aftermath of the second lockdown was nothing like as drastic as the first. People were used to it now. The foursome made their way through the empty school to the Slytherin common room, and, without knowing the password that was supposed to let them in, Harry opened it himself, causing one or two raised eyebrows from those within but otherwise no comment.

Plenty of rumours circulated, but none came close to the truth.

Daphne took up her position again in the court of the Gray, flanked by Hermione and Tracey, the later, trying her hardest to give the impression that she hadn’t just had her world shaken to its very core, and soon enough, it was time for bed. Harry separated from the girls, made his way to his dorm room, climbed into bed, closed his curtains, and fell asleep almost at once.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

In the first year girl’s dormitory, three girls sat on one bed, crosslegged or sitting back on their knees, with the curtains closed and every anti-eavesdropping charm they knew carefully cast.

“So,” Tracey gave a weak smile. “Your hero is in fact, Harry.”

Daphne nodded.

“Suddenly, so many things make a lot more sense.”

Daphne and Hermione both nodded.

“Although certain other things make even less sense than before. Do you parents know?”

Daphne nodded. “Mine do.”

Hermione shook her head. “Mine don’t.”

“Still.” Tracey laughed quietly. “The great, mysterious Lord Slytherin is none other than the equally mysterious, Harry Potter. No wonder no one’s figured out who he is.”

Hermione leaned forward, voice deadly serious. “Tracey, you can not tell anyone.”

Tracey frowned. “You know that if my lord asks, I’ll have to tell him.”

“But only if he asks.”

“True.”

“And you know that Harry is going to want to make sure that what happened today can never happen again.”

“How?”

“I don’t know, but Harry will think of something. He always does.” Hermione smiled. “Sometimes, we help too.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The next morning, Harry woke early and snuck out of the school, paying absolutely no heed to the lockdown still in place and making sure to put a dummy ward presence like always before he left. He apparated all the way to his cave vault in the Hebrides, walked inside, strode straight over to the lead box lined with silk in the corner, opened he box … and found the diadem and the ring, still there and all intact, as if Daphne and Hermione had never been.

He lifted the diadem out of the box and studied it carefully. Yes. This was definitely the real thing. What in Merlin’s name had happened?

Last night, after he’d heard Hermione and Daphne’s story, he’d asked to see their memories. It had certainly looked like they’d lifted the genuine articles from the box. Only the three of them knew the secret.

What the hell? Had someone found yet another weakness with the fidelius charm? Like the one Harry and the girls had discovered with the Eye of Kilrogg? This so called ‘absolute protection’ was starting to accumulate more holes than Dumbledore’s character. But even if someone had found it, why give him back Voldemort’s Horcruxes? It made no sense. Whatever the case, he certainly couldn’t keep them here any more, not when he knew the defence had somehow been penetrated. But where to keep them now?

Harry frowned and caught the sound of a dragon roaring off in the distance.

It seemed he had yet another project for the summer.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

And then Lord Slytherin was walking into the board of directors meeting to discuss the renewal of Dumbledore’s contract. Dumbledore wasn’t present. Apparently he was dealing with the fallout from his latest lock-down of the school.

Harry walked out of the meeting an hour later with a stack of signed parchments under his arm and a slight smile playing around his mouth, hidden, as always, under his ever-present green and black mask.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

And then they were on the train, heading back to London after a year at Hogwarts that, all things considered, had gone far better than Harry’s first. The Gray all sat around them in the compartment, laughing and joking and swapping plans for the holidays. Tracey kept shooting him appraising glances, which he happily returned with interest.

And then, the train arrived at the station, everyone got out, said their final farewells, and Harry started making his way over to the Muggle side of the platform, pausing to give Hermione and Daphne one final hug.

“Stay safe, Harry,” Hermione said.

Daphne nodded too. “We’ll miss you.”

Harry smiled back. “I know. I’ll make sure to keep in contact when I can, but I am going to be really busy.” He looked around quickly before continuing. “Because—let’s face it—I’ve got some serious pocket money to make this summer.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

John Potter stared.

The hall was dimly lit. Shelves reached up the sides to touch the very ceiling, which seemed high enough, and vast enough, to play quidditch under. On every shelf, glass orbs sat by the thousand, each one containing swirly mist.

“Don’t touch anything, John,” his mum said, marching him along the shelves. At his side, his father looked similarly grim.

He licked his lips nervously. This certainly hadn’t happened in the last timeline. “Mum? Where are we?”

“Never you mind.”

John continued to follow his parents. The moment he’d gotten off the Hogwarts Express, both of them had fretted over him as normal after one of his brushes with trouble, and then immediately brought him here. He had no idea where here was or what they were doing. All he knew was that they were somewhere in the ministry.

They stopped by a shelf that looked just like any other.

His mum peered at the labels under the glass orbs. “This is the one, but … Oh, for pity’s sake!”

His dad leaned over and read it too. “Oh.”

John just had time to glance at the sign and read:

S.P.T to A.P.W.B.D

Dark Lord

Jonathan Sirius Potter

Harry James Potter

Lady Lily Potter

Lord James Potter

And before he could ask again what this was all about, his father’s hand clutched the sphere and plucked it clean off the shelf. “Right,” he said, “let’s get out of here—sorry, Son—looks like we didn’t need your help, after all.”

As they left, John looked over his shoulder at the massive room with the glass orbs. Well, that had been odd.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Ready?” Lord James Potter held the prophecy orb with slightly clammy hands.

Opposite him, on the other side of his private office’s small table, his wife sat with a determined look on her face. “Do it.”

James Potter took his wand and prodded a tiny amount of magic into the prophecy orb. Suddenly, a voice that wouldn’t sound out of place in the St. Mungo’s long term mind healing ward echoed all around the office.

The one with the power to vanquish the dark lord approaches,

Born to those who have thrice defied him,

Born as the seventh month dies,

Born as one half of a greater whole,

Born as the brother to the one who was not chosen,

And the one who was not chosen will know not those who thrice defied him …

—Will grow up separate and singled out by all—

—Barring the weight of his fate alone—

… Or the one who was not chosen will fall to darkness and know not the joy of life,

But if those who thrice defied him learn these of words spoken,

Then the one who was not chosen shall vanquish the vanquisher of the dark lord,

And the world be stripped of magic,

Only those who thrice defied him can control the one who was not chosen,

And save the world of magic from a fate most grim.

James Potter felt numb as the last words finished.

Opposite him, his normally warm faced Lily was shock white. “But if those who thrice defied him learn of these words spoken …”

James Potter felt sick. He put his head in his hands and let the orb roll across the table to his wife. “I think we just massively fucked up.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

In his Hogwarts office, Dumbledore smiled a grim smile, staring hard at a misty glass orb in his hand. His contact at the department of prophecies had just told him that the Potter’s had been and left with a prophecy orb. There was only one possible orb they could have picked up—the more convenient orb he’d left there in place of the real prophecy—the real prophecy, which he currently held.

The floo flared green and he quickly pocketed the true prophecy.

“Headmaster?” James Potter’s worried face pocked out of the floo.

He adopted his best grandfatherly expression. “Yes, James?”

“I, er … I think we owe you a bit of an apology for our behaviour. I think we might have just made a huge mistake.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lily Potter knocked on the front door of Privet Drive.

Behind her stood James and Dumbledore.

The door opened and Petunia stuck her head out. “You!” She made to slam the door, but Lily stuck her foot in it.

“Tuney, please. We just need to talk to Harry.”

“He’s not here.”

She frowned. “Where is he?”

“I don’t know. Out for the day.”

Behind her, Dumbledore coughed. “Lily, I’m afraid she’s lying.”

James made a small intake of breath.

Lily narrowed her eyes, still with her foot in the door. “Where—is—he?”

“I told you, I don’t know.”

Dumbledore stepped up to her side. “Lily? If I may?”

She hesitated, but then nodded.

The door easily swung open and Dumbledore marched in and stared deeply into Petunia’s startled eyes.

Lily watched the old man’s face whiten. “Dear, Merlin.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Images flew through Dumbledore’s mind.

Harry smiled up at him/Petunia. “Should be okay now, Auntie. I’ll be back at the end of Summer.”

The scene shifted.

He/Petunia looked down at a one year younger Harry Potter. ‘Business … ? What does a little freak like you have that could interest us?’

“Maybe I should come in and we can talk about it, rather than right here on your doorstep where I’m sure all the neighbours will be very interested.”

The scene shifted.

“Fifteen-thousand, Uncle.” Harry reached into a bag and slapped down a pile of muggle money. “And another fifteen-thousand over the next seven years, or until I reach my majority as recognised by my fellow freaks, whichever comes first.”

Vernon’s face twisted into a greedy smile.

Harry summoned the pile back from his uncle’s hand.

He/Petunia gasped.

“But,” Harry continued, “only if I’ve lived here for the last ten years.”

The scene shifted again.

Vernon leaned away from him/Petunia. “Okay, okay.” He turned back to Harry. “So, this money comes from your freakish parents?”

“Good god, no. It’s them I don’t want knowing where I’ve been. They’d probably throw a fit and do a whole bunch of freakish things to you and your house.”

Vernon’s eyes bulged.

Harry continued. “Let’s just say the money comes from a wealthy patron who has been taking care of me, and who doesn’t wish his name floated around all over the place.”

The scene shifted again.

“Please, Uncle Vernon!” A much younger Harry cried while getting whipped with a belt.

“We will not tolerate your freakishness!” Vernon bellowed.

The scene shifted again.

He/Petunia shoved the young Harry into a cupboard and locked the door. “And don’t think you’re coming out of there till Monday!”

Scene after scene after scene. Dumbledore stumbled backwards. Oh no. Shock reeled through him. It was like Tom Riddle all over again—it was Tom Riddle, but even worse. Harry hadn’t even lived here for four years!

“Headmaster?”

He vaguely heard someone calling to him, but he couldn’t think of anything else right now. Revelation after revelation piled up in his head. Harry had a ‘wealthy patron’ who didn’t want his name to be known. Given everything that had happened there was only one contender for that position. Lord Slytherin. Harry had known Lord Slytherin for almost four years.

Another realisation hit him like a hundred banishing charms. Lord Slytherin had heard the real prophecy. But if he’d known Harry for three years before he came to Hogwarts … had he realised that Harry was the true subject of the prophecy? Dumbledore started to sweat. Everything had been a setup. This entire year. Nothing had been real. Harry’s isolation, his gradual winning of friends and respect, his argument with Lord Slytherin over Miss Greengrass, the trial, it was ALL fake!

“Dumbledore!”

He started, looking around at Lily and James who were now both in the house, wands out and alert. Off to the side, Petunia had sat down in a chair, shaking with fear, anger, and impotence.

“Dumbledore, what is it?”

“James, Lily,” his voice shook. “I would seem that Harry has been abducted—”

“WHAT!”

“—possibly of his own free will, and probably by Lord Slytherin.”

James and Lily’s faces had both gone white.

“Amelia!” James declared, turning to the door. “And Sirius!”

“James, wait!” Dumbledore reached out his hands imploringly. “Just think for a moment first. We have no evidence. Yes, we will find him, but it does us no good to rush off without thinking first.”

“So, what do we do? Now that we know about the P word, we have to get him back!”

“Well, Harry will need to come back to Hogwarts, so if the worst happens we’ll know where he is then. There will be ample opportunities for you to ‘get control’ of him. And until then we have eight weeks to try and uncover—”

Dumbledore was suddenly interrupted when an owl swooped into the room and dropped an envelope on his head. Sighing with the accumulated events of the week, he opened the letter, and read.

Dear Mister Albus Dumbledore,

We regret to inform you that we have considered your position as Headmaster at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry and have decided not to renew your contract. We’re sure that your many years of service …

The words rambled on and on, but Dumbledore didn’t see them.

Slytherin had somehow gotten a majority vote from the board to oust him—on a board he thought he had rock-solid control of—and just when he most needed not to be away from the school. Attack piling on attack, deception piling on deception. Was there nothing that man wasn’t capable of?

He collapsed into the chintzy arm chair of the muggle sitting room and put his face in his hands, feeling the weight of total defeat settle on his shoulders, heavier than the chains he’d tried and failed to leash Harry Potter with. What was he going to do now?

—End of Chapter Thirty-three—

—End of Book Two—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: And here we come to the end of chapter thirty-three, the end of season two, and the end of book two. I hope you enjoyed the ride—I know I certainly have. My current plan is to post chapter thirty-four on Sunday, July 9th, 2017 (unless I do some bonus chapters—see below).

A/N: Next, I have some announcements to make.

Firstly,

Dodging Prison and Stealing Witches now has an audio version! Read by Soren Childs and available on Youtube—The first episode is up. Go check it out, like, subscribe and comment. He deserves it. You can find it either through my profile page, or …

Secondly,

… Through my brand-spanking new website, which I’ve created to act as a backup host for Dodging Prison and Stealing Witches, and as a platform for me to explore other projects. I’ve also set up a mailing list, so those who would like semi-regular updates on everything DP&SW—including schedule changes, sneak peaks, and the occasional bonus one-shot or exclusive missing scene—can get it sent straight to their inbox.

I’ll also let you be the first to know about whether I plan to upload bonus chapters during my six month break—like I did between season one and season two—and keep you updated on how Soren is doing with his audio version project. This is the best way to know that I am not dead.

[www * LeadVonE * com]

Interlude - Gairsay Island

For thousands of years, magicals traditionally considered technology the way a stern parent might consider a child’s finger painting—endearing at best, a waste of time at worst. It had been rather a shock then, when the European renaissance gave way to the enlightenment, and the finger paintings suddenly flashed into technical drawings for iron foundries, guns, star charts, and more. The wizards watched with growing uncertainty as their non-magical brethren enthusiastically unravelled the non-magical components of alchemy, and published journal after journal, dreaming of ever greater and greater feats.

In the end, one wizard was all it took. One wizard barging into the ICW main conference hall, waving a just-published copy of Sir Isaac Newton’s Principia Mathematica, the ramifications of which were clear to every present disciple of the magical art of arithmancy. For two whole years, the world balanced on a seesaw. A tiny force either way could have pushed the balance. But it just so happened that the wizarding world was fresh off the challenge of obliterating divination magics from the world, and thus had no shortage of memory altering expertise at the ready for the greatest mind control project the world would ever know—the enacting of the international statute of secrecy.

Such a draconically enforced cultural divide was not without it’s consequences. While the muggle world lost much of the knowledge of the magical world, surviving only in myth and story, so too did the magical world lose touch with the technological forces that had originally driven a wedge between the two worlds.

But so long as muggleborns were removed from the muggle world at the age of eleven, and their parents subtly persuaded not to get involved, none of this mattered—not until a time travelling someone decided to interfere, that is.

Daphne Greengrass stepped out from the floo at the rookery, grasping a copy of the Daily Prophet in one dainty clenched fist. A tiny wooden witch danced out of a clock on the wall and struck a bell with a tiny mallet.

“Midnight,” the wooden witch announced. “It is now June 23, 1992. Please enjoy another day of your life.” It then shifted into an even smaller kneazle and scampered back into the clock.

Daphne stalked out of the sitting room, past the many magical creature heads mounted on the walls, and up the spiral staircase that led to the bedrooms. She reached her intended destination and knocked on the door.

“Nargles!”

Daphne opened the door, took one step into the room beyond, and stopped dead. A thousand moving pictures filled her vision, waving, fighting, clapping, talking, dancing. Every surface of the room had been plastered with cutouts from hundreds of wizard newspapers—the walls, the ceiling, the furniture, the frame of the slightly open window, even parts of the floor. In the middle of the room, laying on her tummy and wearing a nightdress, was Luna, spoon in one hand, pudding in the other, bright smile all across her face.

“Hi, Daph.”

Daphne cast a final glance around the room, decided to ask later, and took another step into the room. “Luna, have you seen this?” She dropped the newspaper in front of her tentative friend and future sister wife, and sat down in the room’s only chair, careful not to disturb the intricate collection of newspaper cutouts pilled up and around the desk.

Luna stuffed the pudding filled spoon into her mouth and held up the newspaper to read. “Tomowwos, Daily Pwofet?” she asked around the spoon still in her mouth. “Hawwy Potter Missing,” she read. “Duellwing phenom, Hawwy Potter has been weported missing by Ward Potter.” Luna swallowed and removed the spoon. “This isn’t surprising, is it? We’ve known they knew he was gone for two weeks now.”

Daphne shook her head. “Keep reading.”

Luna’s eyes skimmed over the article. “Oh, you mean the bit where it says there is ‘no evidence’ that our lord did it?”

Daphne snarled. “Yes.”

Luna nodded. “I’ll make sure Daddy prints the lack of evidence of the Potters being involved in the rotfang conspiracy.”

“Right.” Daphne looked around the room again. “Now, what’s up with the newspapers?”

Luna pointed around the room in quick succession. “Britain, Europe, Africa, South America, North America, Middle East, East Asia, South-East Asia, Australasia,”—she pointed to an empty patch of wall—“Antarctica.”

Daphne gave Luna a half-lidded look. “Antarctica?”

Luna nodded. “Just in case.”

“Why?”

“It’s important to know what’s going on in the world.” Luna stuffed the once-again pudding-full spoon back in her face. “Did you know there’s a mwassive pwuffapod shortage in Mwagical Gweece?”

“I did not know that.”

Luna swallowed. “The Greek ministry banned their import because the Greek minister of magic’s granddaughter ate a bad puffapod and developed an acute case of magical animal magnetism.”

Daphne decided she didn’t want to know. The way Luna’s mind worked, it was bound to be something sexual. “You didn’t hear anything from Ginny, did you? Isn’t she supposed to be here by now?”

Luna nodded. “Yes.” She frowned. “I hope she didn’t run over anyone.”

They sat in quiet for a few moments, Daphne reading the rest of the paper while Luna snipped out the front page and magically stuck it to the British section of wall.

Then, suddenly, Luna perked up.

“Luna?”

Luna frantically waved her quiet and focused on the open window. A moment later, a small, innocent-looking stone flew threw it.

Displaying an impressive turn of speed, Luna dived, snatched the stone out of the air, jumped back on the bed, springing up and deftly placing the stone on the top of a ceiling mounted mobile of plushy magical creatures.

There was a shift in the air and forty kilograms of startled red-headed witch appeared where the stone had been, flailed around desperately and grabbed a nundu plushy, which, unable to hold her weight, ripped out of the ceiling, and dropped both mobile and witch onto the bed below, launching Luna roof-wards in direct consequence of Newton’s second law.

“Weeeee!” Luna arced through the air and onto the floor, just dodging a bright red stunner that whizzed by her head.

“Lunnna!” Ginny Weasley rolled off the other side of the bed, hand glowing red.

Daphne stared, wide eyed, as an impromptu wandless duel kicked off just a few feet from where she sat. Luna on one side of the bed, Weasley on the other. Paper flew everywhere. Ten seconds later, it was all over … with Weasley flat on the floor.

Daphne bit her lip. Ignoring the fact they were only using two offensive spells, such spell swatting at such close range at least looked as impressive as Harry’s duel with Tonks. No wonder she and Hermione hadn’t been able to match Luna.

Luna cast a finite on Weasley.

“Dammit!” Weasley arched her back from where she lay, snapped her whole body, and powered back onto her feet without touching the floor. “Again!”

Daphne cleared her throat. “Ginny Weasley?”

Weasley paused in mid hand-glow and turned to her.

“We do have things we need to do,” Daphne said levelly. “And I believe you have to be back home by a certain time?”

Weasley looked her up and down as though sizing her up. “Yeah, that’s true.” She nodded. “Okay, let’s go.”

“Oh poo.” Luna pouted as she looked around the mess of newspaper clippings left in the wake of the magical combat. “Now I have to put it all back together again.”

“You do that.” Daphne moved towards the bedroom door. “If we’re not back by six, you know what to do.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Up in a cheaply built watch tower, near the Scottish village of John O’ Groats, Convertible-Security of the Goldtooth clan surveyed the night-time sea in the vain hope that it might suddenly become more interesting than it had been the last thousand times he’d done so. No luck. He snapped his finger and the telescope folded itself up in his hands.

“Nothing?”

Convertible-Security looked around and down. His sister, Balanced-Payments, stared up at him with her hands on her hips. Convertible-Security snarled. “No, there isn’t. There wasn’t yesterday, there wasn’t today, and I’d bet my sword there won’t be tomorrow either.”

“Great Grandfather is certain the target account will try something incriminating,” Balanced-Payments said.

Convertible-Security shook his head. There was no point in arguing. He climbed down from the lookout post and strode past his sister, massaging the knots out of his shoulder. “I’m going to go prepare the patrol boat and then grab my smoke break—Who knows, maybe I’ll be lucky and a shark will attack me while I’m at it.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The village of Hogsmeade slept. The moon was not out. The stars did not twinkle. Cloud covered the night sky like a worn out dementor’s cloak, a boon for spies and smugglers.

Ginny frowned. She’d been told practically nothing about what they were doing tonight—just that Greengrass would need her particular set of wandless skills. She did know they were looking for something, but that was all she knew. That wrangled her.

Ginny stumbled again in the darkness. Next to her, the future Lady Slytherin closed the fideliused house door behind her and gracefully moved to her side as thought it were still midday. How was she doing that?

“Broomstick out,” Harry’s betrothed whispered.

Ginny reached into the pocket of her robes and withdrew her shrunken nimbus 1700.

“Disillusionment charms, if you please.”

Ginny felt magic and intent pulse through her body and directed it through the tips of her fingers, first to herself and then to the girl Harry was contracted to one day marry. Moments later they both became mere outlines in the air.

“Mount up,” Greengrass said.

Ginny swung her legs over the broomstick and watched as an heiress shaped shimmer moved behind her, slid onto the broomstick, and wrapped its arms around her waist.

The air roared around them. Once outside the village airspace, Ginny turned her head slightly. “Has our lord been teaching you duelling too?” she shouted over the wind.

“A bit!” Daphne shouted back. “Not as much as you and Luna though. We couldn’t beat her even together!”

“Who’s we?”

“Hermione and I!”

Ginny thought while the wind rushed through her hair. That probably meant she was the second best among those Harry was training—those she knew about, anyway. That felt good. Alex was slowly getting better, but still didn’t come close to touching her. She said as much to the witch sitting behind her.

Greengrass sniffed. “There are many different types of ‘best,’ Weasley!”

The flight to the north-most coast of Scotland took a little over an hour.

They touched down next to a cliff overlooking crashing waves and Ginny still didn’t know what they were doing here.

Greengrass sat down on the grass like a swan getting comfy on a bed of silk, closed her eyes, and started to pool magic.

Ginny sensed her carefully. She sensed the magic build up in the witch’s chest, as though being forced through a tiny ring, before dribbling down to her fingers and leaping outwards, spinning rapidly in the air, forming a ball of magic—strange magic—the intent was difficult to figure. She stared at the otherwise invisible magic sphere and couldn’t shake the uneasy feeling that the sphere was staring back. Realisation struck her. She gasped. “You can see through it?”

Daphne’s head-shaped shimmer nodded. “It is called the eye of kilrogg. I’ve been working on getting it wandless for over a month now.”

“That’s amazing.” Ginny’s mind raced through applications for such a spell. She licked her lips. “Could you teach me?”

Daphne slowly shook her head. “Probably not. It takes a special kind of magic that not everyone has.”

Ginny sighed.

Daphne continued. “It also allows me to see certain tricky types of magic that are otherwise all but impossible to detect.”

Ginny felt the magic sphere disappear.

“That is what our lord wishes us to do tonight,” Daphne said. “He has given me a route around the Orkney Islands which we are to scan for said magics.”

“What magics?”

“It is better if I don’t tell you.”

Ginny frowned. “But—”

“No.” Daphne held up a firm hand. “Please. It is incredibly difficult for me to even think about, even with my inner eye open and the eye of kilrogg activated. The magic protects itself.”

Ginny gazed up and down the Scottish coastline. Magic that protected itself? That sounded kind of like the fidel … the fidel … Ginny tried to grasp onto the thought, but it drained through her mind like water through a sieve.

Greengrass recast the spell, got up from the ground, and together they re-mounted the broom.

The eyeball spell hung below them.

Ginny then steered them along the many island coasts, occasionally stopping and landing when Greengrass needed to recast the eyeball spell. They continued for what seemed like hours. It probably was. A vague suggestion of dawn started to spill over the horizon.

She felt Greengrass tense up behind her.

“Daphne?” Ginny asked. “Did you lose your spell again?”

“No, that’s not it.” Greengrass sounded uncertain. “Can you land us again? I think I might have found something.”

They landed on what looked like an empty stretch of road near a relatively short cliff face.

Ginny’s first step off the broom had her tripping over a rock. She scowled as she sensed Greengrass daintily step over the exact same rock she had missed.

“How have you been doing that?”

“Night vision charm.”

“Night vision—” Ginny’s jaw dropped. “Please tell me that doesn’t also need special magic?”

Daphne put a finger to her chin and looked away. Her voice turned playful. “Mmm … I wonder if I should …”

Ginny breathed in sharply. “Pleeeease,” she wheedled. “You’ve no idea how useful that charm would be. My mum’s almost caught me sneaking out so many times.”

“I don’t know …” Even though Greengrass was still disillusioned, it didn’t matter—Ginny could hear the smirk in her voice. “Surely the second best at duelling doesn’t need my help? I am very busy being the best at divination, after all.”

Ginny pouted. “It would help our lord.”

Morning song birds trilled in a lone, nearby tree.

“That’s not fair,” Daphne whispered.

Ginny smiled impishly. “And our lord did say he was going to have us work on our teamwork this year.”

“Okay, okay, once we get to Hogwarts,” Greengrass said, in somewhat terse tones. “Now—silencing charms, if you would be so kind?”

Ginny happily cast a couple of wandless silencing charms on the pair of them and, holding each other hands to make sure they didn’t lose each other, they crept along the otherwise deserted road.

As they approached a hill ridge Daphne urgently tapped Ginny on the shoulder, grabbed her arm and quickly guided her off the road.

Ginny allowed herself to be dragged into a ditch. What was going on? She poked her disillusioned head over the top, trying to making out what had caused Daphne’s warning.

Suddenly, seemingly from nowhere, a goblin stood where before there wasn’t one. An actual goblin! Wearing a two-handed sword on its back! Here! In Scotland! It walked several steps down the road she and Daphne had been stealthily walking up, stopped, reached into a pocket, withdrew a packet of cigarettes, and, looking extremely bored, lit one up.

They waited for several more minutes while the goblin finished smoking. The moment it was gone, Ginny followed Daphne back down the road the way they came. When they were far enough away, Daphne tapped her twice on the shoulder—a signal to hide, sit down, and make herself comfortable.

Ginny felt divination magic swirl beside her. She felt it take the shape of a sphere, felt it zip off up the road towards where the goblin had disappeared, and then felt it slip into nothing. The magic didn’t disappear—Ginny’s sensing skill could still tell something was there—but her brain simply refused to co-operate with her skin.

“Ahhh …” Daphne let out a relieved sigh, having apparently dispelled the silencing charm. “Got it. Oh, that feels so much better.”

“So?” asked Ginny, dispelling her own, removing her broom from her pocket and expanding it. “Can you tell me what this was all about now?”

“Yes.” Ginny could just make out the disillusioned Daphne nodding in the pre-morning twilight. “A goblin clan, rivalled to the one we’re allied with, and the ministry are co-operating to snoop on everything being used to build Slytherin Manor.”

Ginny swung herself onto the broom and cast a wandless cleaning charm on the ground they’d been lying in.

“Once our lord’s stuff is on the island there’s little they can do,” Daphne continued. “but while it’s in transit, they do have the power to inspect, if they wish.” Daphne shuffled onto the broom behind her. “We knew they were using a … method, let’s say, to hide their inspection points. Until we knew where the inspection points were, we dared not try move anything of a questionable nature to the island.”

So that was it! Ginny felt a little thrill shoot through her. “And now our lord can do stuff he couldn’t before?”

“Yes.”

Ginny gently pushed off the ground and felt the wind stream through her hair. “So we really helped him tonight?”

“Yes.”

Ginny smiled brightly in the faint dawn light. Excellent. Hogwarts hadn’t even started yet and she’d already helped Harry with something important. Brilliant.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Only a few dozen miles away, under yet another fidelius charm, Emma Granger put down her morning cup of coffee, picked up her rivet gun, and fired yet another rivet into the side of large white van—a white van patch-worked on all sides with thin metal plates and runes.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Early morning gave way to late morning. Daphne sat down at a large, round table of finest oak. The table was divided into thirds—literally divided. The space between the thirds measured the distance of a severed human thumb. Outside the private meeting room’s only doorway, two Gringotts goblins stood on guard holding large battle axes.

Apart from Daphne, two other humans also sat around the table. All three of them wore masks. Each had been asked to give up their wand before being allowed in. Ironically, not one of them would have been able to use a wand in any-case. Two because they were underage, and one because he was a muggle. Only two of the three knew that last titbit though.

Daphne wore her potion-gifted grown-up form like she was born for it, which, of course, one day, she would be. She projected the poise and air expected of a lady, as she’d been trained to do since the age of five. Now she wore a real mask over her Slytherin one, and the added anonymity felt good. It made her feel powerful—secure—safe. “Let us begin,” she said.

The masked man to her right, whom Daphne knew to be Mister Daniel Granger, nodded at her. “Mister Buccaneer,” Mister Granger said, addressing the third individual. “Did you manage to charm the artefacts we gave you?”

Fred Weasley, who sat on Daphne’s left, nodded. He hadn’t bothered with an ageing potion. To be fair, he was tall enough to pass for a short adult. “Yes, Mister Settler,” he said.

Daphne couldn’t help smirking under her mask. Tall or not, the older boy still had several octaves left for the puberty fairy to come and take away.

Fred Weasley produced a shrunk trunk from the pocket of his robes and placed it with a flourish in the middle of the table where the three points of the three thirds met. “Twenty runed plates charmed with bubblehead alchemy spells.”

“Wonderful.” Mister Granger counted out eight chunky gold coins (£400) and placed them in the middle of his third of the table. “Best eight galleons I ever spent.” He turned to Daphne. “Miss? I assume that wasn’t all the business we have today?”

“No, Mister Settler,” she said. “I believe Mister Buccaneer would like to show us something he and his associate have been working on.”

Fred Weasley nodded and started fishing in a bag at his side.

Daphne smiled. The hidden identities in this little group were some of the most convoluted silliness she’d ever seen. Mister Granger knew who she was, but didn’t know who Mister Buccaneer, AKA Fred Weasley, was. Fred Weasley didn’t know who either she, or Mister Settler, AKA Daniel Granger, was—just that they were connected to Harry. She on the other hand, knew exactly who everyone in Harry’s growing little empire was—at least she was fairly sure she did, and if she didn’t … well then there was probably a good reason for it.

“Ahha! Here it is.” Fred flourished a large roll of parchment and unfurled it across the table. “Gentleman—Lady.” He gave Daphne something half way between a nod and a bow. “Allow me to present to you the first buccaneer product developed with settler runes.”

Daphne glanced over the parchment, on which four long rectangles were drawn, each containing hundreds of runes in elegant repeating patterns, and which might as well have been written in ancient Sumerian for all she could understand them. They clearly meant something to Mister Granger though, because he let out a little sigh like the last escaped air from a folded beach ball. “Of course,” he said, “so simple.”

Fred Weasley nodded. “We figured we’d start with the low hanging fruit.”

Daphne tapped an impatient finger on the table. “Could you please enlighten those of us who might not be rune prodigies?”

Mister Granger leaned over and jabbed a finger at the parchment. “It’s a magic recycler. It captures wasted magic and channels it into an associated rune matrix. Not much magic, but I imagine you could improve efficiency or power of whatever you attached this to by … maybe 5%?” He looked up at Fred, who nodded.

“5–10% actually,” Fred corrected. “Depending on how small we can make the runes.”

Daphne frowned. That didn’t sound all that amazing. “What would you attach it to?”

“Oh, there are all sorts of possibilities,” Fred said. “Really big magical artefacts already use them, of course, but now that we can make them smaller, we thought the best opportunity would be in the broomstick market. That’s why we’ve shaped the runes to fit on a ring, so they can easily attach to where the bristles affix to the shafts—or two rings, rather, one ring that floats around a second ring.”

“That explains our hover runes,” Mister Granger said, rubbing his chin.

Daphne lightly brought her finger tips together. Okay, she could see how that might be useful. The broomstick market wasn’t small and they were always coming out with slightly better models. It was also easy to see how she and Harry could help. “You’ll need our assistance to reach the manufacturers,” she said.

Fred nodded. “We know. And we’d need to sort out a manufacturing deal with ‘Mister Settler.’ ”

Mister Granger grunted. “Wrist sized aluminium rings filled with several hundred runes a piece? Should be able to do you for …”—he paused for a few seconds, clearly running numbers in his head—“three sickles, eleven knuts each (£10), and another one sickle, twenty-one knuts each if you need us to do the blood runes (£5).”

“And we can set up the deal for say, 25% of the gross value of the contract,” Daphne added. “Palms do need greasing.”

“Sounds fair.” Fred hesitated. “Could you do Nimbus?”

Daphne smiled under her mask. If he’d asked her only a few months ago, the answer would have been, ‘probably not,’ but now? “I think we can.”

“Brilliant,” Fred whispered.

They talked back and forth some more. Contracts were drawn up and signed, and several other pieces of business were gone through, not least of which was the official version of the original partnership agreement between Harry and the twins, which the twins had only just managed to persuade their father into signing. Quite a feat, considering how many blank spaces that contract had to preserve Harry’s anonymity. By the end of it all, the middle of the table contained several half signed contracts in addition to the shrunk trunk and several bags of galleons for various projects.

Daphne placed her hand on the table and in a loud clear voice said, “exchange.” There was a whoosh of magic and the items in the centre of the table jumped across the divides.

Contracts were picked up and signed, galleons pocketed, and the contents of trunks inspected.

“Well, good doing business with you both,” Daphne said, standing up and pushing back her chair. “We’ll be in touch.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Fred! George!”

George Weasley hastily ripped off his sweater with the large G on it and put on the one with the large F. He opened his bedroom door, yelled, “Coming, Mum!” and quickly made his way down the stairs to the kitchen where his mother and little sister were cooking lunch.

Molly Weasley turned just as the potatoes lifted themselves out of the pot of boiling water on the stove and started mashing themselves. She frowned. “Fred dear, where’s your brother? I really need the garden de-gnomed.”

“He’s out in the garden now, Mum,” George said, heading towards the kitchen door, and snatching the butter smeared copy of the daily prophet from the kitchen table. “I’ll just go tell him, shall I?”

His mum gave him a suspicious look as he passed. “I thought you were both in your room?”

“We were,” he answered, free hand now gripping the door handle, jovial grin on his face. “He just wanted to get some fresh air.”

“Fresh …” Molly Weasley turned and put her hands on her hips. “All right, what are you up to?”

George froze. “Nothing, Mum.” He tried to sound as innocent as possible.

“Oh, really?”

“Yes, we just—”

CRASH! The sound of a large porcelain bowl smashing down onto the ground drew Mrs. Weasley’s attention to a shocked looking Ginny, now standing in a small pond of peas and carrots.

“Oh, for pity’s sake!”

George took the opportunity to open the back door, watching his mum now fuss around Ginny.

Molly Weasley turned her back and, right then, Ginny winked at him.

Whoa. George gave his little sister a grateful look, slipped out, and started walking down the path. Ginny was getting more and more devious by the day. It was enough to make a big brother proud. He arrived at the front gate, hid behind a beech tree, unfolded the slightly messy newspaper, and read while he waited. He didn’t have to wait long. Only a few minutes later, his twin brother came jogging up the road from the direction of the Rookery.

“Did we get everything we needed?” George asked.

“We did.” Fred said, grinning and panting, slightly out of breath. “And then some.”

“Cleansweep? Comet? Nimbus?” George asked.

“Nimbus.”

“Wicked,” George whispered. “And the partnership with young Harry?”

“All signed and official.”

“And did we get to officially see the house he’s working for?”

Fred shook his head. “No, not yet.”

George made a ‘hmmm’ sound.

They stood in silence for a moment.

“Hey, Fred?” George said.

“Yes, George?” Fred answered.

George chucked his twin the Daily Prophet, which was running the headline, ‘BOY-WHO-LIVED’S BROTHER STILL MISSING’. “Do, you think we should tell Harry we’re pretty damn certain he’s working for Lord Slytherin?”

Fred smirked. “What do you think?”

They looked at each other.

“Nahhh,” they said in unison, before turning and walking in lockstep up the path, fully ready to continue the never-ending war for the Burrow’s gnome-infested lawn like the dutiful sons they were.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Emma Granger held her hands absolutely steady. The tip of a welding torch crackled and popped, scorching-hot-electrode-point melting and remaking the steel object in front of her.

A stone’s throw away, the sea rolled up and down the shingle beach.

“Delivery!”

Emma stopped, flipped her mask visor up, and turned around just as her husband walked up. He held a large package under his arm and a large grin on his face.

“Bubblehead alchemy plates,” Dan announced, setting the package down on a make-shift workbench. “Easiest sci-fi style oxygen and carbon-dioxide recyclers you’ll ever find.”

Emma smiled. “Excellent. Let’s start on getting them installed.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

A few days passed. Hermione started each day by shuttling her parents up to the tip of Scotland in a shrunk trunk, through the floo, to a carpark, where they’d left a car, and finished it by returned them back home when the work day ended. She still hadn’t seen what they were working on, but was willing to wait until they were done. It wasn’t like she didn’t have enough to do. Now back in Crawley for the night, Hermione stood in the middle of a ritual circle, drawn in the Granger garage, half embarrassed and totally naked. Off to one side, stood her mum, equally naked, but far less embarrassed.

Her dad wasn’t in the room. Hermione had put her foot down about that, getting more than a few sniggers in return from her parents about how their little girl was growing up, and that soon they’d be fending off boys on motorcycles—possibly one’s with messy black hair and green eyes.

Clare also wasn’t present. The risk of her confinement collar interfering with the ritual was too high.

Soft light illuminated the ritual circle through a window in the roof. Unlike a few nights ago, when the clouds blocked the night sky’s display, tonight, the moon was out, and it was full—that was important.

Hermione sat down cross-legged in the middle of the circle, which pulsed with magic from the already-completed first-half of the ritual. Her mum stepped beside her, knelt down, dabbed at Hermione’s arm with a swab of cotton wool, and drew a measure of blood with a syringe. She then handed the syringe to her and left the circle.

Hermione ignored the slight prickly feeling on her arm and focused on the object on the floor in front of her—Two small aluminium rings, each a little larger than her wrist. They were both completely smooth, but she knew that hidden inside were hundreds of tiny runes, and that right now, here, in this ritual circle, a few dozen of them in particular sang out to her like sirens on the rocks. She held the syringe over the rings of metal and dropped a single drop of blood onto each. The blood clung to the rings. Hermione pulsed magic into the ritual circle. The rings sucked her blood into them with a small slurping sound. The singing dimmed.

Hermione shuddered, stood, raised her hands up to the roof, and completed the words of the ritual. The ritual circle glowed faintly red; the metal ring glowed redder still—and then the glowing stopped and the world returned to normal.

For a moment the room was totally still.

Emma Granger let out a long breath. “Done?”

Hermione let out a small breath of her own, smiled, and picked up the outer ring. Even as she did so, she felt the tiny pull of magic from it, causing the smaller inner ring to float and spin independently of the larger outer one. “Yes,” she said, holding the ring up for inspection. “One blood-rune copy-protected broomstick power ring.”

“Good,” said her mum. “Let’s get this sent off to Lord Slytherin and then to bed. Your father and I need to get up early tomorrow.” She took the magic ring-within-a-ring from Hermione. “We still have plenty of work to do before we can make our first trip to Gairsay Island.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne sat in front of her bedroom vanity dresser in her dressing gown. On the small desk in front of her lay a magic ring-within-a-ring, a letter from Mrs. Granger, a plate of half eaten jam on toast, a couple of open books, and dozens of parchments, all filled with Daphne’s neat notes and scribbles. One of the books was titled ‘Updated Albion Contract Magic’. Sunlight flooded in from her large bedroom window. Hedwig perched on the backside of a nearby chair, drinking from a small bowl of water one of the Greengrass house elves had brought her.

Daphne scribbled another note, put down her quill, and looked at herself in the mirror. “No, Mister Whitehorn,” she said to her reflection, “Two galleons each for every broomstick you make, adjusted for inflation, for the next five years, in exchange for … for …” She cursed, looked down at her notes again, and then back up at her reflection. “Mister Whitehorn, the terms my lord will agree to are two galleons each for every broomstick you make, adjusted for inflation, for the next five years, in exchange for … an exclusivity agreement … and an annually improved model.”

Daphne nodded to herself, looked down at her notes, and made another scribble.

“Dear?”

“Mmm?” Daphne looked up. Her mum’s head poked around her bedroom door.

“It’s already noon, Daphne,” Sunny Greengrass said.

Daphne blinked. “Already?” She looked out of the window. The sun was indeed high in the sky.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

450 kilometres away, the high-noon summer sun beat down on Convertible-Security like a goblin forged hammer. “Fucking whore Boneslicers,” he muttered watching as another fully inspected knight-wagon full of building equipment and materials boarded the ferry to Gairsay island. He sucked on his cigarette, dropped it, and stubbed it out with a steel toed boot.

Next to him, the ministry inspection human, Geoffrey Perkins, sniffed. “I don’t understand how you can have so much animosity for them—aren’t you all goblins?”

Convertible-Security gave the snooty human an unimpressed look. “You’re all human and you fight like spogs in a fight pen. And why should you understand? You don’t know the history—the feuds—the power grabs—the backstabbing. The only times you know of them is when it spills over into your world, and then its called ‘rebellion.’ I bet you don’t even understand why we care about Lord Slytherin.”

“He’s rich?”

Convertible-Security snorted. Dear Gringotts he was bored. “Human,” he said, “has it never occurred to you to wonder why we want all your gold in our vaults?”

The human hesitated. He glanced at the huge sword Convertible-Security had slung over his back.

Convertible-Security could practically hear the man thinking, ‘greedy, simple-minded magpies.’

“Because,” the human said, seeming to choose each word as though a misspoken one might result in their already short-handed operation becoming literally even more so, even while managing to sound as snooty as ever, “you … value gold highly?”

Convertible-Security rolled his eyes. “The first thing every goblin gets taught in school—even before which end of an axe is the sharp one—is the diamond-water paradox, human. The very—first—thing. Gold doesn’t have much value when you’re alone in a desert, but water does. And gold piled in a vault doesn’t mean much if there isn’t some greater context surrounding it. It’s not like we’re allowed to actually touch any of your gold.”

The ferry carrying the knight-wagon full of Boneslicer goods and goblins pushed off from the pier.

Convertible-Security watched it carefully, magic tingling up and down his fingers, stretching his senses for any sign of something amiss.

“And?” the ministry wizard asked.

“And what?” Convertible-Security shot back.

“The context—why do you hoard gold?”

Convertible-Security turned away from the departing knight wagon, scowled, and started walking back to the fidelius watch point up the long shingle beach. “I never said I was going to tell you, human—just that you should wonder about it.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The table was round and divided into thirds—literally divided. The space between the thirds measured the distance of a severed human thumb.

Daphne Greengrass was once again sat at one of the thirds, holding a long package wrapped up in paper in her lap, trying to shake the feeling of being weirdly vulnerable without her ageing potion and mask, which was ridiculous. She was Daphne Greengrass! Current heiress Greengrass and future Lady Slytherin. She had every right to demand an audience with someone who was, at the end of the day, a commoner—regardless of how old she might be.

At the table’s other thirds sat Lord Smith and Devlin Whitehorn, boss and chief enchanter for the Nimbus line of brooms.

“Don’t tell me you’re not a little bit curious, Devlin,” Lord Smith said with a chuckle.

Devlin Whitehorn had the look about him of a man with places to be and things to do, and that here was not where he wanted to be, and she were not something he wanted to deal with. He tapped on the woodwork with his long fingers. “I would not be here, if it were not you that had requested it, Lord Smith.” He turned to Daphne. “Please, just get on with it, young lady.”

Daphne decided to get on with it. “Mister Whitehorn, my house has developed a line of magic rings to improve either the efficiency or power of a broomstick by between 5% and 10% with no loss of stability or slipperiness.”

Whitehorn rolled his eyes, stood up, and turned to Lord Smith. “Please don’t ask me to do this again, Sam.” He turned away.

Daphne scowled, took out the long package, and slammed it down on the table. “At least look at it.” She ripped off the paper, revealing a Nimbus 2000 broomstick.

Whitehorn spun back around, clearly annoyed. “Little girl, I don’t need to look at any—” he stopped. The larger aluminium ring floated and gently spun around the smaller one. The smaller ring was firmly attached to where the broom’s bristles met the handle. “It floats?”

Daphne held up her empty hands, showing she held no wand.

Lord Smith’s eyes flittered between Daphne and Whitehorn, amused and calculating.

Whitehorn approached the broom with a frown. He produced a long fork like instrument from the recesses of his robe and gently tapped the broomstick. His frown deepened. Another instrument was produced and more tapping and prodding done. At one point, the man took out a tiny, finger-sized broomstick. The finger broomstick leapt from his hand and did loop-the-loops all the way along the larger broom before returning to Whitehorn’s hand, making little whistling noises. He started muttering to himself. More prodding took place. Eventually, he picked up the broomstick and mounted it, right there in the Gringotts meeting room, doing several slow barrel rolls before dismounting. He sat back down at his third of the table and fixed Daphne with a hard stare. “How much?”

“Two galleons each for every broomstick you make, adjusted for inflation, for the next five years, in exchange for an exclusivity agreement and an annually improved model (£100).”

Whitehorn raised an eyebrow.

Daphne held his gaze.

“I’ve no idea the kind of work that must go into these rings,” Whitehorn eventually said, his tone of voice making it clear that this both intrigued and annoyed him. “We sell around 750 brooms a year. Will you be able to make that many?”

Daphne nodded. “We will.”

“Right.”

Thirty minutes later, they had a signed contract, and five minutes after that, Daphne found herself leaving an empty meeting room along side Lord Smith who smiled at her. “Very well done, young lady.”

“Thank you.” She nodded up at him. “And thank you for setting up the meeting. I will go to my account manager and see that your share is placed into your vault as soon as Mister Whitehorn transfers the gold to my lord’s vault.”

Lord Smith touched his forelock with the hand not holding his large war hammer. He then turned and left.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne stepped out of the floo in the sitting room of Greengrass Manor. “Afternoon, Father.”

Jacob Greengrass looked up from where he was reading the Daily Prophet. He smiled. “Afternoon, Daphne. Having a productive day?”

Daphne took out a rolled up parchment from the fold of her robes and nonchalantly waved it. “Just signed a contract worth six hundred galleons a year to Slytherin House for the next five years (£30,000).”

Jacob blinked. His head disappeared behind the newspaper again. “Your bride price was too damn low.”

Daphne smirked. “Aww, thanks, Dad.” And with that she ran upstairs to get changed for her afternoon outing.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Sophie has an afternoon outing?” Mrs. Roper was busy washing dishes when Mr. Roper mentioned their daughter’s plans.

Mr. Roper poured himself a cup of tea. “With some friends from school. They’re going to the cinema.”

“That’s nice,” Mrs. Roper said. “I’m glad they’re going to do something ‘normal.’ ” She rinsed a plate and put it on the drying rack. “How is she getting there?”

Mr. Roper shrugged and brought the cup to his lips.

Just then, the doorbell rang.

He put the cup down. “That must be the lady from the ministry.”

It was indeed the witch from the ministry. He led her into the kitchen and served her another cup of tea.

“This is just a regular call in,” the rather snooty woman said, inspecting the digestive biscuit Mr. Roper placed next to her tea-cup as though it might be poisoned. “How is Sophie doing after her first year? No troubles, I hope.”

“No, not really.” Mrs. Roper dried her hands on a teacloth before turning from the sink. “Sophie says she loves Hogwarts.”

The woman smirked. “As she should.”

Mr. Roper took a sip of tea. “Although she did mention that there were some problems with bullying.”

“Did she?” The ministry witch sounded shocked. She fixed him with a piercing stare.

Mr. Roper had the feeling his very soul was being examined. “She did,” he said.

The ministry witch smiled. “I’m sure it’s nothing.”

Mr. Roper felt a flash of annoyance shoot through him. “Now, see here—”

Suddenly, the world went weird. He looked down at his cup of tea. Wow, he’d drunk a lot without noticing, hadn’t he? “Err …” He tried to remember what they’d just been talking about. “What were we … ?”

The witch smiled. “You were just saying how proud you were of Sophie for doing so well on her end of year exams.”

“Oh, yes,” he muttered. “I knew it was something like that.”

Mrs. Roper nodded, beaming proudly.

“Is there anything else we need to talk about?” Mr. Roper asked. “Only I have an appointment I need to leave for soon.”

“Yes.” The witch’s expression grew more serious. “We’ve been asked to inform all muggleborn parents to be wary of a gentleman by the name of Lord Slytherin.”

“Oh?”

“Last year it became known that this wizard had targeted an unsuspecting muggleborn family and bound them to him as his vassals.”

Mr. Roper stared at the woman in wide-eyed indignation. “Vassals?! And we’re only learning about this now?! What the hell are you—”

The world went weird. He looked down at his cup of tea. Wow, he’d finished that quickly hadn’t he? “Err …” He tried to remember what they’d just been talking about. “What were we … ?”

The witch smiled. “You were just confirming that you’d be sure to contact me immediately should you be approached by Lord Slytherin or anyone working for him.”

“Oh, yes,” Mr. Roper muttered. “I knew it was something like that.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Waves crashed and lapped up the Scottish, shingle beach.

“Ready, love?” Emma Granger asked. She was wearing a red bikini and a lab coat.

Clare Cooper nodded. She was wearing a yellow bikini and her ever present imprisonment collar.

Dan stood off to the side. He was wearing a smile like a banana on growth hormones. Three steel boxes connected by steel tubing sat on the shingle beach’s only stretch of flat rock, affixed by extremely well tested sticking charms. One of the tubes faced out to sea. Another two tubes dipped into the water.

“Right.” Emma made a note on a clipboard. “Moment of truth. One stroke now—slowly, please.

Clare nodded and pressed her hands against the holes in the two boxes in front of her.

Moments later, a huge stream of water shot out of the tube facing out to sea as though a block in a fireman’s hose had suddenly been cleared. The water misted in the air and floated back towards them, soaking the three of them in a fine wet sheen.

Emma blinked.

Dan’s smile widened. “Test one—successful.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Somewhere else, in a land of lights and sounds and make believe, a group of muggles got out of a car and stumbled towards a massive beast, clearly dumbstruck by its sheer size and majesty.

The creature was huge. No, huge didn’t even begin to describe it. Its neck was as long as the Hogwarts astronomy tower. It leaned back on its hind legs and nibbled the top of a tree before coming back down to earth with such force, it rocked the very ground around it.

One of the muggles collapsed on the ground, shock overcoming his ability to stand. Orchestral music started to swell. The muggle looked up. The orchestral music built up further. A lake came into view, full of beasts—not all of equal size to the tree munching monstrosity near where the muggle now lay, but huge nevertheless. The orchestral music crashed and the muggle whispered to his guide in sheer, unadulterated awe.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The storm raged—rain pounded down—lightning flashed—tropical trees whipped this way and that—the muggle wards groaned—and the terrible wingless land dragon stepped through them, each footstep shaking the muggles sitting nearby in their their cars, frozen and terrified.

It roared.

The muggle girl scrabbled over the back seat of the broken car, grabbed the electric lumos device, and switched it on. Her brother shouted at her to turn it off, but it was too late.

Attracted by the light, the land dragon stomped over.

The boy closed the car door with a small thlump.

The sound caused the land dragon’s head to jerk around. It slowly inspected the car, its eye as large as the terrified muggle boy’s head, its teeth as long as a man’s arm.

Rain poured down the car’s windows.

And then, all hell broke loose.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The music died.

The vicious two-legged reptiles circled.

The muggles crowded together, the man desperately trying to shield the woman and two children from the predators closing in on them.

The lead reptile crouched down, ready to pounce.

The muggle man flinched back.

The reptile leapt, but before it could get halfway, was plucked clean out of the air by a much large set of jaws.

The music started back up.

The muggles all stared in terrified wonder as the huge land dragon, appearing seemingly from nowhere, ripped through the reptile that moments before had been about to rip through them. They ran for it, orchestral music swelling and swelling as they made their way out of the building and down to a car driven by their guide.

The land dragon ripped the second reptile off its back and threw it straight through a land dragon skeleton. The land dragon roared in victory and a banner fell down around it reading, ‘When Dinosaurs Ruled the World.’

Daphne unclenched her hands from the cinema seat rest, let out a long breath, and felt her heart start to slow down again. She left the cinema along side Hermione, Sophie, Kevin, Dean, and Justin, movie music still humming in her ears.

“So Daphne,” Sophie said, “what did you think?”

Daphne smiled, adrenaline still pumping through her body. “At least I didn’t get monster guts on me this time.”

Sophie giggled. “No, I mean what did you think of the cinema? Impressed with what muggles can do?”

Daphne smiled. “You seem to have me mistaken with pure bloods who’ve forgotten why we decided to hide from the non magical world.”

“What she means,” Hermione said, “is that she has a healthy appreciation for the power of technology that muggles wield.”

Sophie pouted. “But you must have learned something?”

Kevin, Dean, and Justin walked ahead of them, loudly discussing the movie, heading to a quiet spot where they all planned to practise occlumency.

Daphne considered her answer before answering. “Yes, I think so. I had no idea that muggles have blood technology—seems pretty dark too—especially with what happened when they messed it up.”

“I think genetics would be more gray than dark,” Hermione said. “It can be beneficial as well as harmful.”

Sophie nodded. “I think nuclear weaponry would be dark.”

Daphne hummed in agreement. “I also think it was interesting how the entire park failed just because one muggle in charge of security turned traitor—and the muggle arithmancer talking about chaos—that was interesting.” She turned to Hermione. “Was that a real muggle thing, or was it made up?”

Hermione hesitated. “I think it’s a real thing.” Her jaw firmed. “I’ll check when I next see Mum and Dad.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Some twenty minutes later, Hermione sat down next to Daphne on a park bench, watching the other muggleborns practise their occlumency in cross-legged pairs mostly hidden from the rest of the world by trees and bushes.

The principle was simple. Normally, only a great legilimens could help a novice occlumens build up their defences, and how those defences would be constructed depended on the legilimens.

The problem was they had a distinct lack of great legilimens that could be trusted to hand, and Harry simply didn’t have the time to invest in something so time consuming.

Therefore, Kevin, Dean, Sophie, and Justin were testing a new method that tried to emulate the method Harry learned from Voldemort. In this method, student became teacher and teacher became student. Since the major limiting factor was the skill of the legilimens, the student occlumens learned to help, gently ‘pulling’ the novice legilimens into their mind, as though they were a hostile attacker. Once inside, student and teacher would work together on the written exercises—exercises written specifically to emulate the process Harry would normally go through.

Harry had been quite thorough. There were hundreds of them.

“At least we don’t have to worry about the ministry casually scanning them now,” Hermione said.

Daphne nodded. “How long until the next step?” she asked.

Hermione shrugged. “At the rate they’re going? Six months, maybe?”

“Six months,” Daphne mused. “That’s twice as long as it took us to start on wandless magic.”

“We had our lord.”

“True.”

They sat in silence for a few moments.

Hermione sighed. “I wish we had our lord now.”

Daphne nodded.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Later that evening, after Hermione arrived home, Harry’s elf, Plato, popped into her bedroom, proudly holding a letter in his hand.

Hermione thanked the elf, opened the letter, and read.

Dear Hermione,

I can’t write as much as I’d like in case this letter is intercepted. I hope you’re doing well and that all our projects are progressing. I hear from Daphne that your parent’s solution to our little problem will be ready soon. I really wish I could be there for the first outing. It sounds impressive, considering what they’re working with. I see from the newspapers that Harry has gone missing. I’m sure you’re wondering if he’s okay where-ever he is. You two seem quite close. Don’t worry, I’m sure he’s fine. He’s a resourceful lad from what I’ve seen. I wouldn’t even be surprised if he suddenly turned up safe and sound at the chief auror’s very own house. By the way, I’m planning to be back in the country on Sunday, August 16.

Yours,

- Lord Slytherin.

Hermione finished reading the letter. August 16? She felt a slight fluttering in her stomach. But that was still three weeks away. She read the letter again. She then put the letter aside and returned back to her studies. She got through one whole paragraph before she glanced to where she’d stored Harry’s letter. She retrieved it, unfolded it, and read it again. Again, she felt the slight flutter in her stomach. She put the letter aside and got back to her studies.

This pattern repeated itself three times.

The sun set and moonlight started to shine through her window.

Hermione buried her head in her hands in frustration. What was wrong with her? Why couldn’t she focus?

Her gaze caught the spine of a book her parents had bought for her several years ago. A memory of twenty-two year old Hermione Granger and twenty-two year old Harry Potter flashed through her mind.

Hermione groaned, a light blush dusting her cheeks, as realisation hit home as hard and as brutal as the very thing she’d just realised—hormones.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

The morning sun shone brightly in the sky. A shape in the air glided through the summer Scottish air. It rode the wind currents like a bird—not quick and agile, but slow and majestic, like an albatross, eagle, or heron. The shape swooped down and alighted mere jumping distance from the North Sea.

Daphne Greengrass shimmered into view. The wind whipped around her hair and robes. The Scottish waters rolled up the shingle beach she now stood on. She dismounted from her brand new nimbus 2001 broomstick and heard two figures land nearby. Moments later, Hermione and Ginny shimmered into view, also dismounting from their brooms.

“Whew!” Ginny had a massive grin plastered all over her face. “I can never get enough of those long broom rides.”

Daphne smirked. “On this, Weasley, I couldn’t agree more.”

Hermione was busy rubbing her bum. “I’ve nothing against broomsticks, but for so long? Not my favourite way to travel.”

Ginny winked at Hermione. “Well, you’re done now. I need to get back before my mum notices I’m gone.” She waved her hand over herself, shimmering back into nothing but a shape against the background. “Good luck!” the shape of Ginny said, before zipping back up into the air.

“She seems nice,” Hermione said when they were alone, now apparently trying the massage life into her stiff limbs.

Daphne shrugged and started towards the cove that she knew to be hidden behind the next large rock and Harry-cast fidelius charm.

As they passed the boulder they also passed a large muggle car parked on the shingle.

They stepped over the fidelius line.

“Hermione! Daphne!” Emma Granger rushed up and hugged them both. “Dan! Clare! The girls are here!”

The face of Dan Granger appeared briefly over a large white van. “Biscuit break!” he said happily before popping back down.

Hermione grinned.

Daphne stared at the van. It didn’t look any different from any other muggle vehicle.

“Come on you two.” Emma Granger said, pulling them along. “Let’s give you the tour.”

Clare Cooper stepped out from behind the van, washing her hands with a towel, wand stuck out of the pocket of her jeans.

Daphne blinked. “I thought you couldn’t leave the Granger house?”

Clare smiled. The ministry confinement collar gleamed around her neck. “I got a special work permit. I’m on unpaid overtime, as it were.”

The waves lapped up against the van’s front wheels where it sat on the shingle. Emma Granger thew open the main doors to the van at the back. “All aboard.”

If the outside couldn’t have looked more muggle, then the inside couldn’t have looked more magic. Thin metal plates covered with runes blanketed the walls. They glowed faintly. Daphne had to clamber around a trio of mysterious rune covered metal boxes with various tubes sticking out of them. A comfy looking chair had been placed within arms distance of two of the boxes. A magic trunk sat off to one side. A ladder led up to another door cut into the roof.

Towards the centre of the van, a broomstick was attached to both the walls with metal rods, leaving the broomstick hanging at mounting height in the van’s middle.

Hermione gave the broomstick an uneasy look.

Emma Granger pointed at some of the different rune plates. “Unbreakable charms,” she said. Clare’s been working on that one for ages now. “I can’t tell you how giddy I was when I first learned that wizards could make things unbreakable. Do you have any idea just how insane that is?”

Daphne slowly shook her head.

Emma Granger smiled. “Well, it is.” She pointed at another set. “And you’ll remember these, of course.”

Daphne nodded. She easily recognised them as the bubblehead alchemy plates she’d helped Mister Granger acquire from the Weasley twins.

“Umm … Mum,” Hermione said. “What’s the broomstick for?”

Emma Granger grinned. “Ah yes, took us a while to come up with a solution for that. Direction control.”

Hermione turned to Daphne. “Dibs not it.”

Daphne rolled her eyes.

“Ah ah ahhh,” Mrs. Granger waggled a finger. “Daphne here is going to be on navigation duty. We’ll need her magic eye to see above the waves.”

Hermione frowned. “In that case, Clare can—”

“—Nope.” Mrs. Granger shook her head. “Clare already has a job that only an adult wizard or witch can handle.”

Hermione groaned.

Daphne smirked.

“Yes, young lady.” Mrs. Granger’s eyes were almost dancing now. “You are going to be a good little witch and get—on—your—broomstick!”

Hermione hung her head. “How long?”

“Only five hours.”

Hermione whimpered.

Daphne eyes momentarily widened in surprise. Five hours? She was going to have to keep the eye of kilrogg up for five hours? That wasn’t going to be light work. It almost made her want to trade with Hermione. “Mrs. Granger?” she said. “Is it really going to be five hours? I thought our island was only sixty kilometres away?”

Mrs. Granger nodded. “It is. But you can’t move nearly as fast underwater. The water gets in the way. Even if you have lots of power, and we don’t.”

Daphne looked at the lone broomstick hanging in the van. “If we used more than one broomstick, couldn’t we go faster?”

Mrs. Granger giggled. “Hermione’s not powering the whole van—my word, no. Those brooms only produce a little less than one horse power in a horizontal line, despite the weird as hell acceleration. We checked. No, she’s just steering.”

Daphne frowned. “Horse power?”

“Horse power is a unit used to measure power,” Hermione said. “Sort of like a flamel.”

“And equal to approximately 735 watts,” Mrs. Granger added.

“Which is a lot,” Hermione said.

“But not nearly enough,” Mrs. Granger finished.

Daphne looked at the broom. “I’ll take your word for it.”

Mrs. Granger edged her way around all the stuff on the floor and over to the mysterious pair of runed boxes that sat by the van’s main doors. “This,” she pointed to the boxes, “is how we’re going to power ourselves underwater.”

Hermione moved past her to stand by the boxes. “What is it?”

Mrs. Granger grinned a smug grin and held up a dramatic finger. “This … is the Granger Magic Trunk Engine!”

Daphne frowned.

Hermione gave her mum a deadpanned look. “The what?”

“Look.” Mrs. Granger pointed to the trunk which sat to the side. “Do you see that?”

Daphne and Hermione nodded.

“That is a half-size version of the trunks that are in these steel boxes.” She pattered one of the boxes. “The boxes are each one metre square, charmed unbreakable, and there is a small hole here, do you see?”

Daphne saw two holes in the boxes that looked like someone had filled in the hole with wood from the inside.

“The trunks are stuck to the inside wall of the box with a sticking charm.” Mrs. Granger pointed to a pipe on the other side of the box. “What happens is, a wizard or witch sits in the chair and puts his hands to the holes where the trunks are exposed. They then shrink one of the trunks. When the trunk shrinks, it creates a vacuum in the unbreakable box, which draws water in from the sea outside through an unbreakable one-way valve. Then, when the wizard unshrinks the trunk, the water is forced out through a different one way valve, into the main pipe, and through a twenty centimetre circular hole at 37 metres a second. They quickly alternate between the two boxes, constantly shrinking and expanding, creating a constant flow of high pressured water, producing almost fifty horse power of forward thrust.” She threw up her hands in the air. “One human! Fifty horse power! It’s nuts!”

Daphne bit her lip. “It sounds impressive,” she hazarded.

Mrs. Granger smiled. “Imagine being able to cast an aguamenti spell so powerful you could fill twelve whole baths in one second, and then being able to keep that up for hours on end.”

Daphne’s jaw dropped.

“Yeah, that’s what this is.”

Daphne’s mind raced. She stared at the … what had Mrs. Granger called it? … The Granger magic trunk engine. She felt her world slowly flip over—the exact reaction Sophie Roper had been disappointed she hadn’t had from the cinema. It hadn’t happened then because she knew muggles had technology, which was just like another kind of magic as far as she was concerned. The cinema was impressive, and the story very entertaining, but at the end of the day, a pensieve was objectively better. But this—this was wizard magic—her magic—and of such power—only the legends spoke of this kind of power—legendary magic—legendary magic, discovered by muggles—muggles under Harry’s purview. Daphne felt a shiver shoot up her spine. Had this been her future husband’s plan all along?

Mrs. Granger clapped her hands together. “Alright! Let’s get this show on the road, or in the water, or whatever.”

The whatever consisted of Daphne, Hermione, and Clare using every merlin of magic they had to levitate the van-turned-submarine across the shingle beach and into the bobbing water. Clare sat herself in the trunk engine seat while Hermione got onto the steering broom with a resigned sigh. Daphne made herself comfortable on the floor and summoned her eye of kilrogg. The world shifted as her magic eye opened. She directed it outside and a watery world opened up before her. “Forward!” Daphne called out.

A massive whoosh noise started and the craft pushed forward, out to sea, and out of the protective ring of the fidelius charm.

Daphne zipped her magic eye to the surface and gazed around. The coast line was still a stone’s skim away. The islands looked like they were on the other side of the world. They were also slightly to the left. “Left!” she called out.

The magic submarine van turned right.

“No, the other left!”

“That was left!” Hermione called back, but the submarine did slowly start to slow its rotation and then slowly started turning left. Soon the islands were in their sights.

“Stop!” Daphne called out.

The whoosh of the engine ceased.

“No, I didn’t mean—urgh.”

“Sorry!” Clare called.

The van continued to turn left.

“I meant stop turning left!” Daphne said.

The engines starting whooshing again.

“I have!” Hermione said. “This thing’s turning circle is atrocious! You need to give me, like, five seconds warning!”

Eventually, with much calling back and forth, and not a small amount of amused input from Hermione’s parents, the magic submarine ceased it’s wiggling path towards the islands and settled into something a bit more linear. Soon though, Daphne spotted something that would have caused her to narrow her eye, if the magic eye had eyelids to narrow. It was a row boat rowing itself. Its human looking passenger sat slouched in the wooden seat, smoking a cigarette. The crest on the side of the boat was clear to anyone in know. The Goldtooth Clan. “Enemy goblin patrol in row boat,” she called out, not quite so loud as before. “About two quidditch pitch lengths away.”

“Cut the engine,” Mister Granger said in a voice that brooked no argument.

The engine whoosh died.

Daphne watched as the goblin row boat got closer. The human had a two handed long sword strapped to his back. Probably a goblin under polyjuice. She zipped the eye over to investigate, getting as close as the eye’s range would allow. An ashtray sat next to the goblin, filled with a small mountain of stubbed out dog-ends. Then, suddenly, the goblin jerked up from its musings and started right at her, surprised and shocked.

Shit!

Daphne zipped the eyeball away to the side.

“Contact,” she whispered.

She heard a sharp intake of breath from inside the submarine, turned the eyeball around, and watched the goblin look wildly around. It had clearly spotted something about the eye. Hopefully it hadn’t identified anything important. Soon the goblin settled back down in the small boat, shrugged, and tapped its finger to the oars, which once again started rowing all by themselves. It gave no more indication it was suspicious of the eye, and certainly not of the submarine sitting hidden, far below the waves. Eventually, the goblin patrol was gone again.

Daphne let out a long breath. “Clear,” she said.

Long breaths were let out all around her.

“Forward,” she said.

The whoosh of the trunk engine started up again.

“What was that?” Mister Granger asked.

“I don’t know if it could see me,” Daphne said, still watching the retreating rowboat, “but it could definitely sense something.”

“Goblins aren’t allowed to use wands,” Hermione commented. “Maybe there are more of them who are skilled at wandless magic—like Uagadou—African wizards are supposed to be really good at that—all sorts of other things too.”

“Could be,” Daphne hazarded.

Hours slowly floated by. A whale passed the sub—so close Daphne could see inside its blowhole. It didn’t seem to be a threat. She giggled as the water sprayed over the eye, and sighed as it swam out of sight. They stopped several times to rest and eat. Clare started looking quite the worse for wear. She had by far the most magically draining job of all of them. They moved around the largest island in the Orkney’s and started towards their intended target—Gairsay island

As they closed in, Daphne kept her eye upon it. Even with what little magic sensing training Harry had given her, the build up of latent magic on her skin brushed across said senses like rose petals on said skin. The last time she’d seen the island, it had been bare—an empty hill of land. Now, small trees, bushes, and long grasses lay smattered all over the island. But it was the hill top that had most changed. The top had been flattened, and a huge building in solid looking white stone now stood atop it—Slytherin Manor—her future home.

They slowly edged around to the far side of the island and surfaced as close as they could, Hermione holding the van steady with about half a foot poking out above the faintly lapping waves. Daphne dismissed the eye, climbed up the small ladder to the door in the roof, climbed out, mounted her broom, and quickly made the tiny jump from the van onto the land where she was immediately met by a gobliness of the Boneslicer clan—Floating-Interest, Ragnok’s daughter and project lead on the construction.

Ten minutes later, the van had been lifted from the water and hidden under a tarpaulin. Mister and Mrs. Granger held an exhausted Clare steady between them.

Daphne stood next to Hermione, gazing up the long path through the greenery towards the shell of Slytherin Manor. It didn’t have windows yet. A part of one side was still under construction. Little cranes and scaffolding covered it all over.

“It’s amazing,” Hermione said.

Daphne agreed, but decided to dig anyway. “What’s amazing about it?”

Hermione glanced towards her parents, who’d wandered off in the direction of the Granger plot of land. She turned back and lowered her voice. “That our lord can make things like this happen.”

Daphne nodded. Yes, that certainly was the most impressive thing about all this. Slytherin Manor wasn’tmuch bigger than Greengrass Manor, but it hadn’t been her parents who’d build Greengrass Manor. Greengrass Manor had been built over four hundred years ago. Standing here felt like standing at the start of something far larger than just herself. The manor was Harry’s stake in the ground. A statement that here he was, and here he’d stay, regardless of what anyone else in the wizarding world might do or want.

The Grangers and Clare soon returned and Floating-Interest led them up to the manor proper, saying that they had, “sent the house elves off for the rest of the day.”

They made there way past a small clearing of yellow daffodil-like flowers that all closed the moment they got near and opened up again as they passed. They reached the top of the hill, and, as they made their way across the front lawn, saw a scowling young goblin grappling with a whomping willow sapling in a massive flower pot. A sea of flower pots surrounded them, all apparently ready for planting. Many of the other plants seemed to be egging the young whomping willow on. The goblin spotted them as they passed, gave Floating-Interest a sudden, enthusiastic wave, and was rewarded with a branch whip to the head.

They trooped up the wide circular stairs to the large double-story front doors. Floating-Interest opened the smaller door set into the large doors and they walked through a reception room, through another set of large doors, and into a huge open circular space with a wide staircase at the far end and a balcony that ran all the way around the second floor overhang. Daphne could already hear the ballroom music and see the hundred-odd wizards and witches watching the dancers from their lofty seats—and one day, one of those dancers would be her—with Harry.

Floating-Interest led them through the many rooms of the manor—sitting rooms, kitchens, dining rooms, even the house-elf quarters, where everything was in miniature, from the doors to the windows, and they had to crouch to get through, the Grangers and Clare more so than she and Hermione.

They saw the workshop, the offices, and even the gym, which was notable as being the only room in the Manor that was already furnished. Daphne didn’t know how even half the iron structures were used, but the iron weights laying all around gave her enough of a clue of what they were for. In one corner, a goblin lay flat on his back on a bench, pushing a bar with iron plates attached to it up and down, making obscenely loud grunting sounds while doing so.

Floating-Interest smiled a wry, seductive smile, one pointy tooth jutting out over her lip-stick red lips. “The boys can’t help but try to impress.”

They backed back out into the long corridor that circled the ballroom, and Hermione actually let out a little squeal when Floating-Interest opened the next set of set of doors and declared the large empty space beyond to be ‘the library.’

The private quarters on the top floor weren’t yet finished, so instead, Floating-Interest showed Hermione and Daphne to the basement and then left with her parents and Clare to see to the unpacking of the test-run goods from the submarine van. The basement was a wide open floor interspersed by the occasional mighty stone pillar.

“This wasn’t on the plans,” Hermione whispered gazing around the huge, cavernous space. Her voice reverberated back at her. “What are we going to do with all this?”

Daphne shrugged. “The plans had to be filed with the ministry. Our lord said this was for, ‘creative expansion’—whatever that means.”

“Stockpiling room?” Hermione asked. “Duelling room? Ritual room?”

Daphne shrugged again. “No idea. Whatever it is, it can’t be too expensive. The six-hundred galleons from the Nimbus contract is a lot of money, but it doesn’t come close to the eighty-thousand galleons that we still owe for this (£4,000,000).” Daphne turned to her friend, who was now busy nibbling on her bottom lip, and smiled. “Our lord will be back soon. I’m sure he’s come up with something.”

—End of Chapter Thirty-four—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: Yes, I am aware that a certain Steven Spielberg thriller came out summer 1993, not 1992—this is sometimes an AU of the real world as well as the canon one ^^

A/N: In case you’re curious, Gairsay Island is a real place. Harry’s deeds also give him ownership of the two smaller islands to the South and North-East.

A/N: Over 400 people signed up for my little Gray mailing list experiment. Mind blown.

Sticky Note: I now have original fantasy fiction published. You can find it by following the bread crumb trail in my profile page. If you can’t wait for my next fanfic chapter release, you might like to check that out to tide you over.

Interlude - Blood Money and Blood Magic

[Five weeks ago, at the start of summer break.]

The Hogwarts Express had pulled into the station. Harry was saying his final goodbyes.

“Stay safe, Harry,” Hermione said.

Daphne nodded too. “We’ll miss you.”

Harry smiled back at Daphne. “I know. I’ll make sure to keep in contact when I can, but I am going to be really busy.” He looked around quickly before continuing. “Because—let’s face it—I’ve got some serious pocket money to make this summer.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Way on the far side of the platform, doing his best not to be seen doing so, Lucius Malfoy watched and observed as Harry Potter left Platform 9¾.

“Greetings, Father—Mother.”

Lucius tore his gaze away, turned, and nodded. “Draco.”

“You’ve grown.” Narcissa smiled. “Come—let’s be out of this mob.”

They flooed home and Narcissa proceeded to quiz Draco during dinner. His son had ranked sixth in his year. Not bad by some standards, but unacceptable for a Malfoy. The fact that Harry Potter could well be one of Lord Voldemort’s horcruxes did mitigate circumstances somewhat, but scoring below thevassal girl, of all people, was just disgraceful.

After dinner, Lucius made himself ready to head out again.

“Going out, my lord?”

Narcissa stood in his bedroom doorway, hands on her hips.

“I am,” he said. “Dumbledore’s eviction from Hogwarts presents us with a timely opportunity. I need to set the wheels in motion.”

Narcissa’s eyes widened slightly. “You don’t mean … ?”

Lucius adjusted the cuffs of his robes and strolled over to the door, kissing his wife on the cheek as he passed. “Yes, Narcissa, I do.”

The sun had yet to set on Knockturn Alley. Late enough for the daily shoppers to have fled, but early enough for the night-time wanderers to still be inside. The street was deserted. Lucius knocked a pattern on a nondescript door and waited. The door opened and he was quickly ushered inside. A half-dozen moving wizarding photos lined the other-wise drab walls, all filled with smiling wizards and witches, and all with comments written beneath like, ‘Quick, easy, and painless, the wizarding world is where I want to be,’ and, ‘I never fit into the muggle world, and now I don’t have to.’

“Lord Malfoy,” the man who’d ushered him inside sat behind a desk.

“Mister Jeremy Bemthan.” Lucius sat down in one of the plush armchairs. “I have need of your services.”

Mister Bemthan raised an eyebrow. “I was not aware you were in that market.” He was a large man, round and bald—and obviously bald by choice—no wizard was bald unless he wanted to be.

“I am not in that market.” Lucius couldn’t help let out a slight sneer. “But nevertheless, I find myself in need.”

Mister Bemthan took out a parchment. “Go on.”

“I need a girl.”

Mister Bemthan started scribbling.

“Muggleborn, obviously,” Lucius continued. “She needs to be fit, healthy, of fair features, eleven years old, magically powerful—that she be a virgin goes without saying—and she must to be obtained legally.”

Mister Bemthan held up a hand. “Lord Malfoy—going to have to stop you there. You’ll be lucky if there’s even one body that fits this description in the whole country, and the ministry won’t—”

“—I expect you to look further afield. In fact, I require it.”

Mister Bemthan smiled grimly. “That turns the job from impossible to merely extremely expensive. Getting them when they’re adults is relatively easy. Tidying up all the loose ends when they’re this young requires a lot more work.”

Lucius looked away. “I also require memory charms for all involved parties, with signed agreements not to tamper with them.” He looked back. “Including of yourself.”

Mister Bemthan nodded slowly. “We could do all that—it would take time though.”

“You have one month.”

Mister Bemthan sucked in his breath before letting it out. He closed his eyes and opened them again.” It will be close, and I still can not promise results—not for something like this—but we can give it our best shot. Five-thousand galleons—half up front and half on delivery (£250,000).”

On hearing that, Lucius actually had to take a deep, calming breath of his own. Five-thousand galleons was nearly a quarter of his total yearly income before expenses, donations, or anything, but the alternative was far too dangerous. He gripped his cane in tight fingers. “Do it.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

[three weeks ago]

In the woods surrounding Potter Manor, a stag and a grim raced through the tress—one flowing with tall, graceful strides, the other powering forward with shorter, faster ones.

The two animals reached a clearing. The grim darted in front of the stag and barked. The stag screeched to a halt and lowered its massive, antlered head, one hoofed foot digging aggressively at the ground.

Somewhere up in the trees, a bird tweeted.

Then, suddenly, the two animals transformed, wands came forward and spells flew. For a hundred heartbeats, the two wizards traded magic before Lord James Potter collapsed to one knee, panting furiously, one hand held up, palm forward. “Give!”

Lord Sirius Black lowered his wand and grinned. “You’re losing it, Prongs.”

“Rubbish!” James glared at his auror uniformed friend. “You’ve just got better. Some of us don’t get the luxury of training half of every day.”

Sirius roared with laughter. “Still making excuses, eh?”

“Excuses?! You should be thanking me on bended knee for saving your lazy arse.” James got to his feet and brushed an imaginary speck of dust from his robes. “I bet if it were you playing lords and ladies in the Wizengamot, you’d tub out before you could say, ‘finger-food.’ ”

Sirius strolled over to his friend. “And if it were you playing auror, you’d get your stubborn arse fired before you could even put on your badge.” They started walking together through the woods back the way they came.

“How’s your muggle-wizard drug smuggler hunt going?” James asked.

Sirius grunted. “Dead. Almost got him several times since summer started. But every time, he somehow managed to slip away. Hasn’t been a peep from him in over a month. I think he’s given up.”

“Surely that’s a good thing.”

Sirius shrugged. “I don’t like it. Who knows what trouble the slippery bugger might be up to. Not that I’m complaining too much.” His face darkened. “You wouldn’t believe the things Shacklebolt sees in some of those muggle’s minds—they make our criminals look cuddly.”

“What about Harry?”

“No change. Amelia says we’ve done all we can do and now it’s a waiting game.”

“So, you haven’t heard anything?”

“You mean from Harry directly?” Sirius shook his head. “Apart from for Alex’s birthday party, no.”

James scowled and ran his hand through his hair. “It’s just so frustrating! Who does that man think he is!?”

Sirius said nothing.

“I mean, does he think that Harry is hisson?”

Sirius still said nothing.

“Padfoot, say something!”

Sirius sighed. “Prongs, I’m really not sure what to think.”

James’s shoulders slumped. “I just … I really wish I knew where he is, and that he’s not in any trouble.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

[August 5, 1992—the present]

Gunfire roared all around him. Harry ducked behind a wall, ignoring the semi-automatic weaponry rounds pinging off the cheap concrete, and concentrated on not being seen as he re-cast his projectile shield. He heard shouting from up the mud track and from inside the compound behind him. He ducked around the wall, caught a glance of his target, and, suddenly, where before there had been air, now there was a large bullet, hanging in mid air and gently spinning an inch away from his face.

Harry slapped the projectile away, still ignoring the shouting, and launched himself in the direction of his fleeing target. More bullets zipped towards him, but all stopped dead before the could reach him.

His target reached a parked pick-up truck with a machine gun mounted on the back and, screaming at the driver, jumped in.

The pick-up skidded on the muddy path and slowly started accelerating away.

Harry scowled, saw the building some hundred metres in front of the escaping truck, fixed it into his mind, threw himself behind a nearby bush, disillusioned himself, and disappeared with a loud crack sound, appearing in front of the building, just soon enough for him to cancel his disillusionment, and take a literal flying leap onto the bonnet of the now passing truck, landing hard enough to dent the already badly damaged metal work.

The shouting driver swerved, clearly trying to dislodge him.

The target screamed and started reaching for something in his jacket, but it was too late. The car careened off the sorry excuse for a road and straight into one of many thorny bushes. Harry swung around the side and knocked the driver out with what to anyone else would look like a punch but had in fact been a pointblank range wandless stunner.

The target scrambled out of the pick-up truck, pointed his hand-gun over the bonnet, and fired shot after shot. One would have actually hit, if it hadn’t been for the shield, but the target didn’t seem to notice this and soon ran out of shots.

Harry vaulted over the bonnet and punched him. It wasn’t the most wizardly thing to do, but he was uncharacteristically pissed off.

The man fell to the ground, shook his head to clear it, and snarled up at him. “Why you do this? We had a deal! Your Russian rockets for—”

Harry punched him again, cutting him off. “Your war is with a military! With helicopters! Not with whole villages of random people!”

The man spat blood on the ground. “You know nothing! If we do not kill them, they will kill us first! They’ve done it before! Our families will all die!”

“The women?”

The man sneered. “They get no less than they are worth.”

The two men stared hatefully at each other. The faint sounds of shouting were starting to get closer. The muggle glared defiantly up at him. “You will never get out of here alive.”

Harry smiled a smile with zero humour. “We’ll see.” He stepped towards the muggle laying in the mud, gripped his arm, and apparated the two of them into a plush looking office.

The man looked around wildly. “My off—how? What?” He looked at Harry in horror. “Oh god, you’re one of them.”

What? Alarm bells rang in Harry’s mind.

The man stumbled backwards and fell backwards on the floor again. “You shouldn’t be here—they said—No! Please. My son. Don’t hurt my—” Harry stared as the man devolved into incoherent whimpering, all defiance gone.

“—I’ll do anything, just don’t—”

Harry stamped on the man’s chest, causing him to let out a large omff sound. “—I’m not going to hurt your son, you fuck. Who is they!?”

The man stilled. His voice came out, much quieter. “I can’t. I mustn’t.”

Oh, fuck this. Harry locked gaze with the man and dove right in—or rather, he tried. To his utter shock, his legilimency probe bounced off a light shield that flashed into being. Magic whirled around the man’s finger—a ring—just like the one he’d given the Grangers.

The man looked at his finger in horror. “Oh, god. You’ve done it now. He’ll know. He’ll come.”

Harry groaned. “Who is he?!”

The man continued to babble nonsense.

Harry reached down and grabbed the muggle warlord’s head in both hands. He didn’t have time for this. What he was about to do wasn’t going to be pretty, but if there was anyone who was worth bloodying his hands for the first time in his existence, it was this sick bastard.

Harry’s magic poured out of him, overwhelmed the defences on the ring, and ripped into the muggle’s vulnerable mind like a combine-harvester in a field of mouldy wheat.

He saw a robed figure—tall and terrible, murdering the muggle warlord’s wife with a single point of his hand and a curse.

He saw the frightened muggle warlord giving out orders that anyone with ‘demonic’ abilities was to be rounded up.

He saw the murderous robed figure taking the clearly magic children away, never to be seen again.

He saw the warlord’s own son display accidental magic.

He saw the warlord desperately try to get the child to suppress the demon inside him, saw him try everything from exorcism to self-flagellation.

He saw the warlord’s efforts work. After little over year, the boy never displayed magic again.

Harry pulled back and watched the man collapse down onto the floor, eyes white, drool slipping from his mouth, arms and legs limp, mind totally scrambled, not quite dead, but close enough to make no difference.

“Why?”

Harry stilled, then turned slowly. A boy stood in the office doorway. He couldn’t be much older than eight, but he wore the military uniform all these people wore. His hair was close-cropped, his hands trembled, and his eyes were wide. It was the son he’d just seen in the man’s memories.

Ugh. Harry had no clue what to say. He needed to finish up this deal and get out, no matter just how fucked up it had got. Angry shouts filtered into the room from the compound outside.

“Why?” the boy repeated.

Harry stood up from where he’d been kneeling over the braindead muggle. “I’m sorry, kid. Your father was not a nice man.” His payment would probably be in a safe somewhere, if he could just find it.

The boy started crying.

Harry sighed and pointed his wand at the boy. It was better this way. “Obliviate.”

The spell vanished an inch away from the boy. Harry frowned. What the hell? That hadn’t been a ring shield. He took a cautious step forward.

The rumbling of a large truck outside stopped as the driver cut the engine.

“I’ll kill you.” The boy’s words came out barely more than a whisper.

Harry narrowed his eyes, looking over the child for a clue, a hint, anything, but there was nothing—it was like his spell had connected with some kind of magical event horizon.

“I’ll kill you.” The words were louder this time. The boy’s crying had stopped.

Harry cast a cautionary shield spell.

The boy screamed, “I’ll kill you!” Magic flared—more magic than Harry had ever felt from a single being.

Harry stepped backwards. A memory flashed through his head—a memory of a young Tom Riddle reading in the Hogwarts library, self righteousness over his own unrestrained behaviour at the orphanage roaring through him like a furnace.

‘And great care must be taken not to encourage magical children to suppress their magic, else a magical parasite will form and feed on that suppressed magic. The parasite will grow and grow, eating away at the child’s sanity, causing mayhem equal to the most powerful magical creatures, until eventually the child dies, the parasite following soon after.’

Harry took another step back.

The boy’s head whipped up, his body disintegrated, and where before there had been a human child, now there was a huge white cloud of enraged destruction plowing straight through the office, ripping through furniture and files, and aimed straight at him.

Obscurial.

Harry apparated straight out of the room, into the courtyard outside, and right into the middle of a convoy of surprised muggles all carrying heavy weaponry.

“It’s him!” one of them yelled, but before they could bring their semi-automatic rifles to bear, the office window above blew open in a rain of glass and concrete and the obscurial descended on them.

Harry made to apparate away. The last thing he saw before doing so, was a man unlucky enough to be standing nearest the explosion, grabbed by the rampaging parasite and flung sideways with such force that the crack of his neck was heard all around the compound.

Harry appeared in a field several miles away. He could still hear the sounds of screaming. Not far enough. He apparated again, and again, and again, until he was all the way up in the mountains in a clearing overlooking the forest and plains of the surrounding countryside. He leaned on his knees and breathed deeply. Apparating so many times in quick succession certainly took it out of him. He straitened up. Okay, now he would wait until the obscurial had finished its rampage so he could go back and grab his payment. Despite the monumentally fucked up way things had turned out, he had delivered on his end of the deal, so the payment he took from these fucks shouldn’t show up as stolen to Gringotts anti-theft charms.

He sat down cross-legged on the ground, and waited, letting the small build-up of magical toxins seep out of him.

Then, suddenly, Harry’s skin tingled, minute traces of magical intent caressing his senses, far too subtle for most wizards to detect, but which might as well have been a warning siren to him. Harry frowned. It seemed that, despite not arriving here long ago, he wasn’t alone. The faint brush of a weak anti-apparition ward washed over him. Mmmmm … and this didn’t feel like an auror sting, Merlin knew he’d been in enough of them in the last few weeks …

Harry stood, pointed his disguised wand at the rocky, uneven ground and gave it a twirl, conjuring a pair of slightly modified versions of his customary arm chair, each facing the other. He sat down in one, crossed one leg across the over, and continued waiting.

Not much later, a man emerged from the trees, dark-skinned, tall, bald, reasonable young, maybe in his mid-twenties, and dressed in bright flowing robes of many colours—bright oranges and yellows, but also purples, reds, and blues—they all overlapped in sharp geometric shapes, a broken stain-glass window of silk and magic. The man casually wandered to the empty chair and sat down.

Harry remembered the muggle warlord looking at his ring finger in absolute terror.“Oh, god. You’ve done it now,” the man had said.“He’ll know. He’ll come.”

The two men watched each other.

Harry felt a brush against his occlumency barriers. He firmly pushed it away.

Eventually the other man spoke. “You are in my territory.”

Harry pursued his lips. “My apologies. I did not realise. I will finish my business here and depart henceforth.”

The man snorted. “Who are you?”

“My name is No One.”

The man rolled his eyes before fixing Harry with his gaze again. “You killed one of my pawns.”

“He was an evil man,” Harry replied. “He butchered whole villages of people who had done him no wrong and who were no more guilty than the next random group.”

The man inclined his head. “Unfortunate, but their value was not high enough to warrant my intervention.”

Harry twitched. “He cut off the arms of a muggleborn boy when he raided his village.”

The man suddenly looked more interested. “Where is this boy?”

“In a safe place.”

The man huffed. “Well, I suppose he wouldn’t be very useful without his arms anyway, but that doesn’t change the fact that you killed one of my more useful muggles. For that I am going to have to have you put down.” He actually sounded sorrowful.

Harry raised an eyebrow. “A bold statement to make, mister … ?”

“Tebola, Gray Lord Tebola.”

Harry’s mind stalled for a second before re-starting. “Gray Lord?”

“As in Gray Lord Slytherin.” Tebola stared off into the distance, hand under his chin. “That man has the right idea. Muggleborns have a valuable place in our world, if only we can get them past the stupid notions their parents feed them.” Tebola turned back to Harry. “You’re British—I can tell. You don’t know him, do you?”

“No.”

Tebola sighed. “Shame.” He snapped his fingers.

Harry heard rustling in the bushes around him.

Behind Tebola, a girl stepped out of the undergrowth. She couldn’t be much older than thirteen. Harry could feel two others behind him. It wasn’t difficult. Killing intent had a very distinct feeling.

Harry frowned. “Uagadou students?”

Tebola nodded. “Muggleborn orphans of the civil war. Everything went to hell when the Soviets pulled out, but there have been benefits—magicals united—helping and supporting each other—looking out for each other.”

Harry looked at the girl standing behind Tebola. Her eyes shone with the zealous fervour of a fighter with a cause to die for.

Tebola slowly stood up. “It’s been nice having this conversation, Mister No One.” He stepped away. “Kill him.”

Harry felt three killing curses shoot towards him and saw the sickly green light leap from the girl’s bare hand. He moved, banishing the chair into the path of one, dodging a second, and bringing his wand up just in time to swat away the third.

A wall of rock shouldered its way out of the ground and split him off from the two assailants behind him, leaving only him, the girl, and Tebola, who’s eyes now betrayed his shock, even as he reached for his own wand, not quite managing it before Harry slammed a wall of raw banishing magic into the girl, so powerful she was thrown backwards into a tree and instantly knocked unconscious.

Unseen by Tebola, but felt and commanded by Harry, two massive rock snakes ripped themselves from the wall of rock behind him, and started on his two other assailants.

Harry and Tebola traded spells, each trying to get a feel for the other. It quickly became obvious that the Lord Slytherin copy cat was strong, quick, and talented, all things considering.

A scream behind him signalled that his rock snakes had finished off the other two unfortunate muggleborns and, moments later, the snakes formed themselves into a huge rock lion, leaped up onto the wall, roared, and launched itself towards Tebola, only to be met halfway by a huge earth golem. The two constructs grappled each other, while Harry and Tebola, circled, cast, dodged, shielded, conjured, transfigured, charmed, and swatted. Soon enough, Harry’s flame whip clipped the earth golem, severing it’s right arm clean off and giving his rock lion the purchase it needed to start systematically pounding it into dust.

Tebola growled and, before Harry could grasp what was happening, turned into a huge wild boar with ash-coloured fur, massive spiked tusks, and vicious looking hoofs. The beast vanished from sight and charged at Harry, far faster than he’d expect, forcing him to physically shield. Not even one second later the huge creature hit the shield with a loud dong sound. Harry felt the shield vibrate and only just hold. He could feel the magic in front of him, even if he couldn’t see anything. It wasn’t that Tebola was an Animagus—that wasn’t surprising for a graduate of Uagadu. No, Tebola was a magical animagus—a tebo—an XXXX magical boar that could turn invisible at will and had high magic and physical resistance. That was impressive.

The tebo leaped back and made another charge. Harry sent his flame-whip hurtling towards the beast, only to watch in resignation as the cord of magical fire had all the stopping power of a lover’s caress. He shielded again just as the invisible beast arrived and was rewarded again with a loud dong that vibrated through the shield, up through his wand, and even into his teeth.

Animal and wizard duelled like bull and matador. Tebola’s skin proved to be just as magically resistant as reputed for a tebo and everything Harry threw at it just bounced off. He tried trapping him in a transfigured spike pit, but Tebola could clearly still sense magic, even in his animal form, and just avoided those areas. Eventually, it took a combination of four separately transfigured rock lions, each one a quarter of the size of his original, and close to a dozen conjured flying swords to pin the pig down.

Sensing he was trapped, Tebola seemed to panic, transformed back into his human form and tried to apparate out, only to bounce off the muggle born trio’s apparition ward. For Harry, that was more than enough of an opening. Seconds later, Tebola was wandless, tied up, and hanging upside-down with a dozen floating swords pointing straight at him, ready to impale him should he try and transform again.

Tebola was breathing hard and fast in little gasps and pants.

Harry smiled grimly. Not bad at all. Nowhere near on par with Dumbledore or Voldemort, but he certainly wouldn’t have let any of the girls go up against him, even all together. That magical animagus form had been a nasty surprise. He pointed his wand at the bound, would-be Gray Lord.

“Gold!” Tebola screamed.

Harry stilled, wand mere inches from the man’s face.

“Gold!” Tebola shouted again. “The muggles around here make all make their money from diamonds! They pay me in exchange for protection! It’s not stolen! All legal!”

Harry’s mind raced. He already had a good chunk of Gringotts legal payment waiting for him back at the compound, but this could be the opportunity he needed to go one step further. “What would I sell you?” he asked. “Payment in exchange for the owner’s life still counts as stealing.”

“Weapons!” the man shouted. “You’re an arms dealer, right? Sell me muggle weapons and I’ll make you one of the richest wizards on Earth!”

Harry grimaced. Every neurone in his brain told him that selling muggle weapons to a rising Gray Lord was up there with splitting your soul six times on the bad-fucking-idea scale. “No, I don’t think that’s going to work.”

“I’ll buy something else! What else do you sell?”

Harry thought back to his stalled drug dealing business. “Well …”

Then, suddenly, his skin tingled. He frowned. “Did you feel that?”

The still upside down wizard quickly shook his head.

Whatever it was, it was getting closer, and fast. Harry turned around, eyes narrowed. Birds cried and flew up in the middle distance. He could hear sounds of crashing and ripping, starting faint, but quickly getting louder.

Harry’s eyes widened. “Oh, sh—”

The obscurial burst into the clearing, dragging enough broken wood behind it to damn a river.

“—it!” He dove to the side, ignoring Tebola’s screams as the obscurial rammed straight through his conjured blades, snatched Tebola up and carried him, still screaming, up into the air. Harry ran as fast as he could to get to the perimeter of the now fading apparition ward. Moment’s later he was through. The obscurial roared. He heard a loud crack. Tebola appeared at his side, one arm bloody where a conjured sword had pierced it, a second wand in his off hand, fear replaced with rage. “Avada Kedavra!”

Harry apparated away with a loud crack before the spell reached him. Tebola appeared beside him again, not bothering with the killing curse this time, just peppering him with low level curses, forcing him to dodge, shield, and swat while the obscurial continued to bear down on the two duelling wizards—a runaway freight train of pure destruction, blasting apart trees and ripping them aside like so much tissue paper. Harry and Tebola were forced to stop trading magic several times, just to focus on outrunning it.

Halfway back to the muggle compound, Tebola shouted something Harry didn’t catch, but which sounded awfully like a cry of triumph, and apparated away from the fight. Harry didn’t see him again in the whole subsequent trip, made much faster now he didn’t have to save so much magic to defend himself with.

Harry appeared in the warlord’s office, right in the middle of two soldiers having a loud argument with each other. Shocked, they pulled guns on him, and got two chest stunners in return. Harry then proceeded to demolish the room until he found a safe which he opened with an alohomora, grabbed the small bag within, opened it to find a small pile of raw diamonds that looked like it would cover his payment, and apparated into the courtyard outside the building, just as the obscurial caught up with him again.

Harry apparated away from the rampaging parasite just as it was about to plough through him, and appeared right behind one of the Russian ground to air missile systems he’d originally delivered to the warlord, not even twenty-four hours ago. He aimed it at the fast approaching whirlwind of destruction and fired. There was a massive explosion and a boy fell out of the sky, landing on the ground with a loud thump.

Harry moved fast. Sprinting over to the downed boy, he pulled out his shrunk trunk, expanded it, opened it up, and climbed inside.

Another boy with no arms looked up at him with wide eyes from where he sat on the couch. “We there?”

Harry reached into a desk draw and took out a vial of living death. “Not yet. Eventually. I promise.”

The boy nodded.

Harry quickly made his way back out of the trunk and forced the draught of living death into the obscurial boy’s mouth. He then carried him into the trunk. “Get up!”

The armless boy jumped to his feet as Harry lay the obscurial boy down on the couch. “Don’t touch him,” he said. “He needs to rest.”

The armless boy nodded, Harry exited the trunk again, and was just finishing up closing and pocketing the trunk, when a group of soldiers appeared and started taking pot shots. This wouldn’t have been a problem if, moments later, two African aurors hadn’t appeared in the middle of the street accompanied by a victorious looking Tebola.

“Surrender!” One of the aurors shouted in a thick accent, shielding against the rain of gunfire now pouring down on them all. “You are under arrest for murder, violations of the international statute of secrecy, and illegal muggle-wizard trade!”

Harry groaned and apparated several miles away, landing at a respectable jog, but getting only a few steps before the three wizards predictably apparated nearby, forcing him to start swatting away stunning and disarming spells. He apparated again, and again they followed. His three assailants worked together to constantly keep him busy. He’d never get the time to put on his cloak. He couldn’t reveal that he could fly. Uagadu was almost five-thousand kilometres away. This was going to be a long chase.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

When someone says the word ‘dungeon’ it might be easy to imagine a sprawling labyrinth of rooms and passageways—a place in which an unfamiliar soul could easily lose themselves, first in the darkness, and then to some unknown monster that prowls the maze. The dungeon below Malfoy Manor was not like that. It was instead, a single bare room with a heavy iron door, wedged in between the ritual room and the wine cellar.

Lord Lucius Malfoy pulled open the heavy door, stepped inside, withdrew a shrunk trunk from his pocket, placed it on the floor, and expanded it.

Lady Narcissa Malfoy stepped in behind her husband. “And they made sure that everything was legal?”

Lucius tapped on the top of the trunk’s lid. “As legal as they could make it.”

Narcissa sighed. “I still don’t like it.”

“We have done everything we can,” Lucius said. “Be grateful we wrangled as many concessions as we were able to.”

Narcissa nodded reluctantly.

Lucius gripped the trunk’s lid, opened it, and peered inside. A small trembling girl was hunched in a corner, dressed in muggle jeans and a thick coat made of some plastic-like material. She looked up, tear stains covering her otherwise aesthetically pleasing face. Blond hair and blue eyes—perfect.

“W-Where a-a-am I?” the girl sniffed. “What are you—”

Lucius shot a silencing spell at her.

She gripped at her throat, eyes wide in terror and tried to burrow herself deeper into the corner.

He turned to his wife. “All yours, Narcissa” he said, before leaving.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Julia Olsson tried to burrow further into the corner, clutching her throat when noise refused to emerge, fear flooding through her. These people were just like the others. The ones that could do magic. She didn’t know how long she’d been trapped in this empty basement room, but it felt like months. She had no clock, no way of telling the time. It might have been months for all she knew. Different people had come down to check on her—to give her food and water and clean out the pot that served duty as a toilet. At first they’d all spoken Swedish, but soon a different group of people were seeing to her, and those people only spoke English. She knew she couldn’t have been here for years because her finger nails hadn’t grown all that long. She hadn’t changed her clothes even once since being forced in here. Who were these people! What did they want with her? Her parents and friends must be worried sick. She wasn’t sure where she was, but Stockholm couldn’t be far away—It hadn’t been that long between being grabbed from her bedroom and being shoved in here.

The rich looking man left and an equally well-off looking woman, apparently called Narcissa, replaced him on the other side of the square hole in the roof. “Get up,” she said. “Out here, now.”

Julia didn’t move.

The woman frowned and pointed her stick at her. Julia flinched back. Those sticks scared her. She felt a force pull on her whole body and flailed around in useless panic, heart beating wildly, as she was unwillingly hauled through the air, towards the roof, up through the trap door, and into a tiny room, bare, but for a small cot chained to a side of a wall. She was dumped on the floor in a limp heap.

“You stink,” the woman declared, looking her over and scrunching her nose up in disgust. “Get out of those horrible things. Now!”

Julia didn’t move.

The woman flicked the stick and Julia felt something half-way between a slap and a punch slam into the side of her face, sending her backwards onto the floor. Pain flooded through her face.

“When I tell you to do something, you do it! Understand?” the woman snarled.

Julia nodded quickly, tears forming and running down her now puffy cheeks. She quickly discarded the coat, and then slowly peeled off the rest of the cold and clammy clothes that hadn’t been washed in god knew how long. What was going to happen to her? She was soon standing in front of the woman, totally naked, head held low, sniffing and sobbing. Her question was quickly answered when the woman pointed her stick at her and cold water gashed from the end, hitting her body and making her gasp in shock.

The woman threw her a brush. “Get scrubbing! Quickly now!”

Julia complied. Eventually she’d been cleaned to the woman’s satisfaction and dried with another flick of the stick. The woman threw her a pair of clean underwear and a large pillowcase with holes in it for her head and arms. She put them on—not daring to comment about the strange choice in clothing—and sat on the cot with her hands wringing in her lap.

“You will be quiet when I or my husband are not here, understand?”

Julia nodded.

“You will not ask the servants any questions, understand?”

Julia nodded again. Then her eyes widened in shock when the woman tapped the trunk that led to the basement, shrunk it to the size of a matchbox, and put it in her pocket, leaving no trace in the floor of where the basement had been.

The woman then turned, left, and slammed the large iron door behind her, plunging her into darkness. Julia swallowed. That basement room she’d been in had been a magic box. Was she even still in Sweden? Was she even still on Earth? Julia drew her knees up to her chest and quietly sobbed all over her pillowcase.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Magical exhaustion. The build up of toxins in the body, resulting in lack of focus, tiredness, lethargy, and one hell of a hangover for those not sensible enough to not drink enough fluids. Despite having gone nuclear twice in the past, Harry could never remember feeling so drained.

After an epic ten hours chase, he’d finally managed to shake his pursuers with only one thousand kilometres to go before he got to Uagadou. Thank Merlin.

By the time he actually arrived, he could barley walk in a straight line. Uagadou was a clay baked monument to wizarding learning, standing proud on top of a tree covered mountain shrouded in perpetual mist. Each individual brick was charmed against physical force, magical force, scrying, map making, damp, fire, lightning, and many, many more things beside.

He half stumbled up to a massive gong just outside the fearsome wards and struck it once with an arm that felt all together too heavy.

Several minutes later, a pair of African woman dressed in colourful robes, not dissimilar to the style that Tebola had worn, descended the path from the school.

“Can we help you, sir?” one woman asked.

“I have an orphan in distress for you,” he answered.

Uagadou’s great hall wasn’t anything like Hogwart’s. While Hogwarts had four tables for their four houses, Uagadou had just one table—a table that wrapped around the edge of the massive circular space before spiralling in to the centre in ever tighter and tighter coils. Unlike Hogwarts in summer, this hall was bustling.

The schoolmistress sat in the centre of the spiral. Getting to the centre took ages.

“His name is Jengo,” Harry said to the old woman when he finally arrived, forcing down every instinct that was screaming at him to find a bed and not leave it for a month. “I found him on one of my journeys. He had the misfortune of having both his arms cut off.”

The old woman’s eyes dimmed. “I am sorry. We cannot take someone with such a disability.”

Harry shook his head. “I can fix that problem.”

The old woman fixed him with a suddenly sharp look. “You can?”

“I can.”

The sounds of a hundred students feasting filled the momentary silence between man and woman.

“Show me,” the woman said.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

After crying herself to sleep, Julia woke up, shivering cold, to find some additions had been made to her prison room. A stool by her cot held a small pile of books and a pen, along with a glass of water and a plate of food that could only be called so because snot was green and this was black. There wasn’t any cutlery.

Julia sat up. She hadn’t been starved, but she hadn’t been well fed either. She picked up the plate in trembling hands, scooped up some of the unidentified goop with her hand and fed it into her mouth. She made a face. Revolting. She finished it anyway, accidentally dropping some of the goop onto her pillowcase. She scooped up what little she could, making a smear on the cloth, and ate the tiny extra glob.

She then turned her attention to the glass and downed the whole thing. She put the glass down with a thump and briefly entertained the idea of smashing it to create a weapon, but quickly discarded the notion as incredibly stupid.

With nothing else to do, she picked up the first book in the pile, titled, ‘Wizarding Geography and Territory,’ opened it, and her eyes widened. All the pictures were moving. She checked the rest of the books, pausing only to pick up an empty, thin, black book that fell out of the second-to-last-book in the pile. It seemed all of the books were like the first. She started reading and a whole new world opened up before her. Was this all real? Was this part of what she had fallen into? The people who had kidnapped her. They were wizards?

She looked over to the pile of books again and her eyes landed on the empty, thin black book. Then they landed on the pen. Then back to the book. Well, it was something to do, wasn’t it? Her hands reached out and grasped the empty book in one hand and the pen in the other. She opened the book to the first page, glanced up at the iron door, half expecting the nasty people to barge back in again the moment she defiled one of their things, and wrote, ‘Why me?’

The ink glistened for a moment before fading as though sucked into the page, and was quickly replaced with, ‘A question many people have asked. Who are you? How did you find me?’

Julia stared at the words, hand unmoving, suddenly afraid again.

Eventually the words faded away and a new set replaced them. ‘Don’t be afraid. I’m not going to hurt you. I’m just curious how you found me. It’s been a long time since anyone talked to me.’

Julia bit her lip. Held the pen over the page, and wrote, ‘My name is Julia. I’m being held prisoner! Can you help me?’

The book wrote back, ‘I’m sorry, Julia. I’m just a memory stored in a diary. I can’t interact with the outside world. Where are you being held prisoner?’

‘I don’t know!’ she wrote. ‘I was kidnapped from my home one day and I haven’t seen my mum or dad in ages!’ A tear fell on the page and disappeared as quickly as the writing did.

An ink doodle of an older boy appeared, crouching beside an ink doodle of a girl that looked kind of like her. The ink doodle boy wiped away tears from the doodle girl’s face.

Julia couldn’t help but crack a small smile through her still flowing tears.

The doodles vanished and the book wrote, ‘My name is Tom.’

—DP & SW: TFoP—

In the Uagadou hospital wing, the schoolmistress stared, stunned, at the silvery arm now affixed to a beaming seventeen year old girl. “What about her animagus training?” she asked.

Behind them, Jengo, the orphan boy Harry had brought with him, was picking things up and putting them down with a pair of the same silvery arms as though he couldn’t believe his eyes.

“It won’t be a problem,” Harry said, leaning against a wall for support and smiling. “The animagus transformation is a full body and full soul affair. These limbs are now as part of their bodies as their heart and lungs.”

“It is incredible,” said the schoolmistress. “I cannot thank you enough.”

Harry was about to reply when there was a pounding of footsteps from just outside and what he assumed was one of the Uagadou teachers burst into the room, wand pointed straight at him.

“Schoolmistress—!”

Moments later, said teacher was wandless and hanging upside-down from the ceiling, arms bound behind his back.

Harry clutched at his suddenly throbbing head.

“What is the meaning of this?” the schoolmistress shouted at the now hanging man. She’d only just got her own wand out.

“Schoolmistress, the aurors are outside!” The hanging man struggled against the ropes. “They’ve surrounded the school and are demanding we hand over this man on charges of murder!”

The schoolmistress looked sharply at Harry.

Harry shrugged. “The muggle responsible for this,” he gestured to Jengo, who was still happily playing with his new arms, “might have pissed me off quite a bit.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

‘And there was this really nice dress that I was really hoping to get daddy to buy me, but I guess it’s gone now.’

‘Why would it be gone?’

‘Sales don’t last long, Tom. There’s always new stuff coming in. That’s why you have to grab what you can when it’s there.’

‘That doesn’t make any sense. Surely if someone wants to buy it, they should sell it?’

‘I don’t know. It’s just how it is.’

‘I think you’d have looked amazing in it.’

Julia giggled. ‘Stop. You’re making me blush.’

‘Truth is beauty, oh flower of the snowfields.’

Julia giggled again.‘What did you do before you were a diary?’

‘I was a student.’

‘Did you want to be a diary?’

There was a pause as though the book was considering its answer. Then it wrote.‘I was not expecting to become a diary, even as I cast the magic to become so.’

‘So it was an accident?’

‘No—not an accident—I just didn’t expect it to turn out quite the way it did.’

‘Did you want to be something else instead?’Julia asked.

‘I wanted to become a great wizard. The greatest wizard who ever lived.’

Julia smiled. ‘I think you’re pretty great, Tom.’

‘Thank you, Julia—that means a lot to me. What do you want to be when you grow up?’

Julia bit her lip. She looked at the iron door and her heart fell. ‘I don’t know,’ she wrote. ‘I don’t even know what’s going to happen to me.’

‘Do you remember anything about the people who took you?’

‘No, I—’ Julia paused. Hadn’t that man called the woman something? Narcissa? Wasn’t it? She put the pen back on the paper. ‘I think the woman is called Narcissa.’

‘Narcissa! Did she have long blonde hair with a black streak in it?’

Julia stared wide eyed at the page. She wrote, ‘Yes! She did! Do you know her?’

‘I know her,’ Tom wrote. ‘She is the wife of a man called Lucius Malfoy.’

‘Do you know what they would want with me?’Julia wrote back in an urgent scribble.

‘I can guess,’Tom wrote, ‘you said that they dressed you in a pillowcase?!’

‘Yes.’

‘It is a good thing you found me. Wearing a pillowcase is a symbol of slavery in the wizarding world.’

Julia gasped.

‘When they come back, you will tell them that Tom said they should treat you better.’

Julia’s eyes widened in terror. ‘I can’t say that! They’ll kill me!’

Tom’s writing became larger, bolder, firmer.‘They WILL see the wisdom in my words. I may not be able to free you, but they are wrong to treat a guest such as yourself in this way, and they know it. Tell them, ‘Tom said to treat you better.’ I promise they will not hurt you for it.’

Julia trembled with the diary in her hands. She didn’t know what to think. She couldn’t do it. She couldn’t. Every time she’d tried to resist or even ask questions before, she’d paid for it. How could the word of a small black book change anything?

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry looked out of one of the many windows overlooking the many valleys leading up to Uagadou. Security wizards from the Union of African Ministries where everywhere, interspersed with the occasional auror duo. Right. He’d stalled for enough time. His head now felt less like a mattress under two mating hippogriffs and more like a one under a small pair of enthusiastic nifflers. He stepped away from he window and turned back to the schoolmistress. “They’re looking quite determined, aren’t they?”

The schoolmistress sadly shook her head. “I’m sorry about this.”

Harry shrugged. “Don’t worry about it. Can you show me to the roof?”

The schoolmistress looked at him in puzzlement. “You will never be able to outfly them,” she said. “They have aurorbolts.”

Harry smiled. “I do not intent to outfly them.”

Once on the rooftops, he said his goodbyes, waited for them to leave, then retrieved his invisibility cloak from his trunk. The problem with his cloak was that—while it made him immune to homenum revelio—magic cast underneath could still be detected, and if he knew anything about these African wizards, it was that they all learned wandless magic as part of their education—a trade-off between that and wand magic. It made them far easier to defeat, as they weren’t nearly so skilled with their wands, but far harder to subdue, since you couldn’t be sure that disarming them would make them safe. That was why he had to assume that a good number of those wizards down there could sense magic, which is why this was going to be a speed run.

Harry disillusioned himself, wrapped the cloak around him, and took a running leap off the school roof, hurtling towards the ground, before pushing his magic through him, and bottoming out before he hit the ground, zipping back up, up, and away. The moment he’d started accelerating away, three broomstick riding wizards stationed around the school turned and started gaining on his position.

Harry landed on the ground in the middle of a valley. Mist surrounded him. He ran a half-length quidditch pitch and apparated with a silent crack. He then shot up into the sky, and, before the first broomstick auror caught up to his first apparition point, apparated again. He landed lightly on a small path some halfway up another of the nearby mountains. The path was lined on one side with huge rocks thrice the size of a man, carved into the shape of long dead alumni of the thousand year old African school of magic. Harry quietly crept away, occasionally cleaning up his scent trail as he went.

It bothered him that he hadn’t been able to do something about that Lord Slytherin copy-cat. He’d gotten greedy and been forced into a marathon chase that no wizard—save himself, Dumbledore, or Voldemort—would have been able to outlast, and in his case, only just. At least he’d gotten what he needed, although the whole slaughtered villages thing had left a bad taste in his mouth, but at least it hadn’t been his weapons that had done that. He nodded to himself and thought to the bag of uncut diamonds in his shrunk trunk. Yes, the next time he needed a cash injection, he’d probably leave muggle arms dealing alone.

It was several minutes before the aurors picked up Harry’s apparition trail and appeared on the mountain path themselves, but by that time, Harry was long gone.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Julia looked up, staring eyes fixed on the iron door as footsteps sounded down the hallway outside. She swung her bare legs off the cot, still shivering. The thin pillowcase didn’t even reach her knees. The lock unlocked without a key being turned and the door swung open.

The woman, Narcissa, stood in the doorway, wand held in one hand, pointing at the floor. “You ate,” she said, staring at the empty plate. “Good.” She turned to go.

Julia gripped the diary tightly in her hands. “W-Wait!” There—she’d said it. Her heart hammered as the woman turned around slowly. “What did you say?” she asked in a low dangerous voice.

Julia swallowed. “T-Tom said …”

The woman’s eyes widened a fraction.

“… T-Tom said you were to treat me better than this.”

The woman stood still.

Julia’s heart felt like it was trying to beat its way out of her chest.

The woman crossed her arms, wand now pointing at the ceiling. “He did, did he?”

Julia nodded.

“Well then, I guess you’d better come with me, hadn’t you?”

Julia hesitated before standing up, straightening the pillow case as best she could, and, clutching the diary to her chest and doing her best not to shake, followed the tall woman out of the cell.

One hot meal later, Julia was frantically writing in the diary on top of a warm, comfy bed with real sheets, and wearing a real dress—the dress was cut such as she’d never seen before and for some reason had a hood, but it was a real dress. The room she’d been put in had a massive window overlooking a grand manor garden, and the furniture reminded her of when she’d been taken to see the Kungliga Slottet back in Stockholm. ‘It worked, Tom!’ It worked!’

‘See?’ Tom wrote back, ‘I told you it would. You just need to trust me.’

Julia smiled.‘Yes! I’m sorry for ever doubting you.’

‘That’s okay,’Tom wrote.‘why don’t you tell me more about your future dreams? Maybe I can help you some more.’

—DP & SW: TFoP—

It was Alexandra Black’s birthday. Harry, disguised as Lord Slytherin, descended the stairs to the basement of Slytherin Manor. He wandered over to the far corner where four miniature fidelius ward stones mapped out a small room, about the size of a bedroom, but with no walls, within which were several silk lined, lead boxes all packed together and all against the far wall, right in the very corner—the horcruxes.

Harry withdrew his shrunk trunk from his pocket and retrieved the still drugged body of the obscurial boy. He laid him on the floor.

“Plato.”

Some thirty seconds later, Harry’s house elf popped next to him, all dressed in flowing black robes with the Slytherin crest shown on the chest. “Master Lord Slytherin is back! What does Master Lord Slytherin wish of Plato?”

“I have a new task for you.” Harry gestured to the boy. “This is Amadi. He is under draught of living death and must remain so until we can find someway to extract the obscurus within him—control it, kill it, or something. Understand?”

“Plato understands, Master. Demon boy stays sleepy until we fix demon boy. What is Plato’s task?”

“You are to take care of him. He needs feeding and watering thrice a day, and you are to renew the draught once a week. It shouldn’t be needed but we’re not taking any chances.”

Plato hesitated. “Plato has a problem, Master. Master’s Grangys have Plato often working in Crawley. Plato can pop to Master that far, but journeying to Slytherin Manor three times a day on my own is difficult.”

Harry stared at the wall. That was an issue—one he wouldn’t have if he’d been able to snag a second elf already. He thought to the large suitcase of diamond money he’d just deposited in Gringotts. Fat lot of good that did if there weren’t any females on the market right now. He turned back to Plato. “Would twice a day work better?”

Plato bowed so low his nose touched the ground. “Yes, Master Lord Slytherin. Plato can be doing that.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lord Lucius Malfoy finished drawing the last rune on the floor of the ritual room in his wife’s own blood. It was time.

Off to the side, Narcissa sat on a chair, nursing an arm that had just been used to extract enough blood to leave an uncared for wizard dead. Several empty bottles of blood replenisher stood on the bench beside her. “Ugh, I hope he appreciates this, even if something goes wrong,” she said. “I’ve warned him. Trying to force a soul process like this isn’t wise. He can’t complain if it goes wrong.”

Lucius wondered who she was trying to reassure. He stepped out of the circle and kissed her lightly on the lips. “Shh, it will be okay.”

Narcissa softly broke the kiss, took a deep breath, collected herself, stood up and made her way into the circle. “Do you want to go get the girl?”

Lucius walked to the door. “Not particularly, but I will.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Julia woke in darkness. Not the darkness of a room without light, but the darkness of a blindfold pressed against ones eyes, and that wasn’t the only thing. She couldn’t move. She was lying naked and spread eagled on her back against something hard and cold. Her hands were tied to ropes, as were her legs. Something had been shoved in her mouth. She could feel her drool dribbling around it. “Mughh!” She started to panic, pulling at the bindings on her arms and legs, but it was no good, she couldn’t even turn her head. What were they doing to her?

“Relax, girl,” said a voice that she instantly recognised as belonging to the woman, Narcissa. “It’ll all be over soon.”

Over? Soon? No. Please no! The woman started chanting words she didn’t understand, again and again. She felt something whirl around her, like a wind, only not, sending shivers down her spine, and what hair she had to stand on end. “Mugghh!”

The chanting sped up and a lance of pure pain stabbed into her chest. “MUGGHHHH!” A voice, faint through the searing heat, filtered through her mind.

Hello Julia.

What was that? The pain spread out through her body, all the way to the tips of her fingers and toes.

How does it feel to become one with me?

What? One? Pain!

You should be honoured, Julia, to become one with the greatest wizard who ever lived.

Greatest? Tom?

Yes.

The pain got worse. Please, Tom! It hurts! It hurts so much!

Yesss.

IT HURTS!

YESSSSS!

The pain reached more than she could bare. She felt herself crawling inwards, everything that she was being shoved aside, compressed, imprisoned, and Tom was everywhere—everything. She could feel Tom and Tom could feel her—could feel her pain and fear. Tom could feel it all, swirling through her body, he felt it. Every tingle in her fingers, every beat of his heart. Tom felt it and owned it, before collapsing back on the cold stone under him, letting the tension drain from his limbs, letting his body relax from the pain. It was done.

The gag was removed—the blind fold, taken off.

Tom Riddle looked up at the curvy figure of Narcissa Malfoy, standing over him as naked as the day she was born. Not a bad way to awaken.

“My lord?”

Riddle smiled. “Yes, Narcissa,” he said in the small girl’s voice. That would take a lot of getting used to. He wasn’t enthusiastic about being female, but the Malfoy’s would never have agreed to his plan otherwise, even considering what his other self had become. He cleared his throat. “You will untie—”

Tom?

Tom Riddle stiffened.

Tom? *sniff* It’s stopped hurting.

Oh, no.

Oh no, what? What happened? Why did you do that?

Riddle groaned.

“My lord?” Narcissa said.

My lord? Why did she call you that? Why is she naked? Tom! What’s going on?!

—DP & SW: TFoP—

A hundred or so kilometres away, in a well to do suburb of London, Hermione, Daphne, and Luna walked down Grimmauld Place towards number twelve.

Hermione nervously clutched a suspiciously book shaped birthday present colourfully wrapped up in paper with a bow on the top. “Is this really going to work?”

“Of course it’ll work,” replied Daphne, carrying a more box shaped wrapped gift. “They’ve been looking for him for weeks. They’re not going to do anything to risk chasing him away again.”

Hermione bit her lip. “What if they grab him and we don’t get to see him?”

“Harry can take care of himself,” Daphne said. “He set up the Black Library fidelius charm at the start of summer. He can use that, if necessary.”

Luna hummed happily beside them. Her present wasn’t a box, but rather a big bowl of something, and anyone that knew Luna could tell you what that something was.

They reached the front door of number twelve Grimmauld Place.

Daphne turned to the other two. “Now, we all remember the plan?”

Hermione and Luna nodded.

Daphne tuned back to the door, stuck her wand in the ward, and pulsed.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

From the sofa in front of the fire, watching Alex and Ginny play exploding snap in wizarding party hats, Lord Sirius Black felt a pulse in the wards—a pulse in the wards from the front door! Harry! He leapt to his feet and crossed the distance to the entranceway, grasping the door handle, and pulling it open. It wasn’t Harry.

“Good morning, Lord Black!” sang three girls in perfect unison.

“Luna?” His surprised gaze flittered from one wide-eyed smiling face to the next. “Miss Greengrass?”

“We’re here for Alex’s birthday.” The Greengrass heiress held a colourfully wrapped gift box in front of her.

“But—”

“Luna has told us so much about you and Alex!” said the brown haired girl, eyes dancing with excitement. “I so hope she likes what I got her.”

A faint memory of a sword wielding Slytherin first year fighting a troll flashed across Sirius’s memory. “I’m not sure if—”

“Pleeeeaaassssssseeeeeeee, Lord Black.” Luna Lovegood pouted up at him, eyes watering faintly. “I know they’re not officially invited, but I want us all to be friends.”

Sirius groaned. He could never deal with Alex when she used to be like this, but three all at the same time? “Fine,” he said, drawing out the word like a grumpy accordion. The girls whooped and giggled, then skipped past him towards the living room. Well, Luna skipped. Sirius noted the other two quickly falling into walk number seven, variant C from the pureblood etiquette playbook for young ladies—adorable saunter with touch of victorious sass. Sirius shook his head. Perhaps this was for the best. It certainly increased the chances that Harry was going to show up.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Riddle resisted the urge to tear his new, long blonde hair clean out of his skull.

‘It’s better swept to the left! No, not like that!’

He’d shouted at her, and that had worked for a while. Then he’d threatened her, and that had worked too, but not for long.

‘Can’t you magic up a better hair clip?’

As soon as she’d realised that he didn’t actually have anything he could threaten her with, she’d quickly switched over from being the meek little girl to giving her opinion on absolutely fucking everything. He’d briefly thought of casting torture curses on himself just to get her to shut up, but quickly dismissed the idea as incredibly foolish. She wasn’t like his old classmates that he could curse and then dismiss. No, he’d just have to manage her as though she were one of the Hogwarts teachers or one of his many female admirers. She was only an eleven year old girl, after all. It wouldn’t be that difficult. He’d already managed to block off his most private thoughts with occlumency, but that did still leave many of his surface thoughts open.

‘And you’re sitting all wrong! Girls don’t sit like that! If you were wearing a skirt, boys would be able to see right up it!’

Riddle sighed. ‘I’m sorry, okay? I know you’re angry.’

‘Angry!? You tricked me and stole my body! I hate you!’

Riddle stood up from the mirror and made his way to the door. ‘Look at it this way, now you’ll be able to go to magic school and see all sorts of things a Swedish muggleborn would never be able to see. Doesn’t that excite you?’

‘I want to go home!’

‘I’m afraid that’s not possible. I really wish I could help you.’

‘Liar!’

Riddle made his way down the many flights of stairs towards the ritual room. He stepped inside and looked around. Narcissa looked up from where she was drawing chalk runes on the freshly cleaned floor. “Ready for the second ritual, my lord?” Her voice shook.

“I am ready,” he said.

‘Humph.’

Riddle felt a presence behind him. It was Lord Malfoy. Together, the two of them made there way over to the desk and started draining their blood into separate beakers. Soon enough, they had nearly half a litre of each of their blood.

Narcissa picked up a paintbrush. “My lords, I’ve outlined places for you to lay. Please dis-robe.”

Riddle did so. He felt Julia mentally recoil.

‘You can’t just let him look at me!’

Riddle ignored her and lay down where the chalk indicated alongside Lord Malfoy. He stared at the ceiling while Narcissa painted their bodies and the circles around them with interlocking runes of both their blood.

Magic swirled.

Narcissa started chanting.

‘Is this going to hurt again?’Julia asked in a small voice.

‘No,’Riddle thought.‘So long as you do not interfere, you should feel no pain.’

“Lord Lucius Malfoy,” Narcissa intoned. “Lord by the Albion Magics, Head of the Noble House of Malfoy, do you accept to take a daughter of common birth to your house, to raise and protect her as if she were your own?”

“I do.”

“Lord Lucius Malfoy, lord by the Albion magics, Head of the Noble House of Malfoy, do you wish to grant a name in gift to your new child?”

“I do. She will be called Virgo Druella.”

‘Virgo?’

‘Shh.’ Riddle felt the ancient magics swirl around him.

“Virgo,” Narcissa continued. “You have been offered elevation from the common to the Noble House of Malfoy. Do you accept your new responsibilities to the Albion Family Magics—to honour your family, and”—her voice shook again—“to protect your new brother?”

‘Brother?!’

‘Shh!’ “I do.”

The magical build up roared. What had been a breeze, turned into a tornado. The blood runes painted on the floor tore themselves free and swirled around the room. Moments later, the magic hit a crescendo and a faint warmth surrounded his left ring finger.

The magic died.

He sat up and looked at his finger. There sat a noble house ring—the ring that had eluded him for the entire time he was at Hogwarts—that ultimate symbol of his rightful place—among the best—where he belonged. His disgusting muggle father’s blood no longer ran in his veins. He was a pureblood now. The daughter of a Malfoy and a Gaunt.

His new adoptive step-mother presented a mirror in front of him. Julia’s ice blue eyes had darkened a shade, the cheeks had raised slightly, little details here and there had shifted, but not by much. The girl had looked fairly similar to a Malfoy to begin with.

Virgo Druella Malfoy smiled.

‘You do know your new name means virgin, right?’

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Harry sat down in an armchair in one of Grimmauld place’s many sitting rooms. He could hear the faint sound of the girls laughing upstairs.

Sirius sat down opposite him and put his hands under his chin. “I’m glad to see you safe, Harry. You upset a lot of people when you disappeared like that.”

Harry tapped a pattern on the chair’s arm rest. Sirius Black was a difficult case to work with. On the one hand, he was a Dumbledore supporter. On the other hand, he was Alex’s father. On the other, other hand, he was extremely Light. On the other, other, other hand, he was chief auror, and on the other, other, other, other, hand, the man wanted to have some kind of friendly relationship with him and did fall into the category of ‘people with whom I had no relationship with in the last timeline,’ for good or bad—such a mess of conflicting possibilities and problems.

Harry shrugged. “I’ve been disappearing for years. The only thing different this time is that someone noticed.”

Sirius frowned. “Lord Slytherin … did he … ?”

Harry’s expression didn’t budge. “Lord Black, I have no intention of disclosing where I have been or who I might have been with, I’m sorry.”

Sirius sighed and massaged his temples with one hand. “I don’t suppose I could at least persuade you to call me ‘Sirius’, could I?”

Harry cracked a small smile. “That, I can do, Sirius.”

Sirius smiled briefly before turning serious again. “I will need to tell your parents that you’re here. You’re not going to run away again, are you?”

“You asked me before the trial if I would spend time here over the summer. So long as I can spend most of my days here for the rest of the Summer, I will not run away.”

Sirius frowned. “Harry, you can’t just threaten to run away again to get what you want.”

Harry tilted his head and fixed Sirius with a hard stare. “Sirius, my parents have not spoken to me once in my entire life—not once—not a word, not an owl. It may not be exactly the same, but … I am Sirius Black. You are Fleamont Potter.”

A flurry of emotions passed across Sirius’ face—shock, anger, sorrow, resignation, understanding.

Harry just watched.

Eventually Sirius nodded. “Fine. I’ll talk to your dad about it.”

“That’s as much as I can ask.”

Sirius stood up and gave Harry a weak smile. “Does this mean that those pretty girls are your marauders?”

Harry’s face cracked into a grin.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Riddle lounged in a chair in the Malfoy library, reading a copy of a book on mindscapes like a prince. Oh, if only he’d had access to these when he’d first entered the wizarding world.

‘But it’s so boring!’

His grip on the book tightened.

“Virgo?”

Riddle looked up.

Narcissa was standing in the doorway.

‘I wish I had the figure for that dress.’

‘It’s a robe.’ Riddle frowned. “Yes, Mother?”

‘That’s not a robe.’

“Um, I was wondering if I could talk to you before your father gets back with your Hogwarts letter?”

‘I mean, yes, it has a hood, but look at it!’

‘You must learn to forget your muggle knowledge.’ Riddle gestured to a seat opposite him.

‘Why?’

Riddle ignored her.

Narcissa quickly sat down, fidgeting slightly with the silk of her robes. “How are you adjusting?”

‘Wow, she’s nervous.’

‘Quiet, Julia. Just observe.’Riddle closed the book. “Well enough. Why?”

“It’s just …” Narcissa looked away before looking back. “If we’re going to present you to the world as our daughter, there are certain expectations …”

Riddle raised an eyebrow. “I am quite familiar with pureblood customs. I made a study of them during my time at Hogwarts.”

“Yes, but that was a long time ago. Things do change in that time, even in proper society. And besides that … you’re a … well a—witch—now.”

Riddle frowned. “Is that a problem?”

“No, no, not a problem. It’s just—your aura—your stance—the way you walk, it’s all so, masculine.”

‘It really is, you know. See the way she sits?’

Riddle narrowed his eyes. “I walk and stand so as to project power—to show the world that I am to be feared and respected. Are you telling me I cannot do that?”

‘You should be sitting more like that.’

Narcissa shook her head. “No, my lo—I mean, no, Virgo, I don’t mean that. I mean that witches show the world they are to be feared and respected in different ways. Wizards are like staffs—loud, obvious, and blunt. We witches are like daggers—quiet, subtle, and razor sharp. We work behind the scenes to position our enemies for a perfect stab in the back, or, when that fails, we secretly clear the way so our men folk can get an open line of shot for a one hit kill.”

‘Oh my god, she’s so evil!’

‘There is no such thing as good and evil, only power and those too weak to seek it.’

Julia went quiet.

Riddle pursed his lips in thought. “You wish to teach me how to be a dark lady instead of a dark lord.”

“I am a daughter of the Ancient and Noble House of Black. I have guided my lord and husband for fifteen years and raised the Noble House of Malfoy to be the richest house in the country. There is no one better to teach you than I.”

‘Hopefully she’ll teach you to sit like her,’Julia said, somewhat sullenly.

Riddle’s fingers tapped a rhythm on the arm chair rest. “Second richest.”

“Sorry?”

“Second richest—according to Witch Weekly’s Witch Rich List.”

‘You look like you’re trying to hide the whole chair with my body!’

Narcissa coughed. “I do not believe that Slytherin’s position on that list is anything more than smoke and mirrors.”

“A loud, obvious, and blunt display of power, you mean?”

“Yes.”

“And even if Slytherin is another one of me, I am the dagger rather than the staff?”

Narcissa leaned closer. “Given how we have gone about doing things, and your uncertainties about Slytherin and Potter, I would recommend that to be the most effective way, yes.”

Riddle nodded. “Very well, Mother. You will teach me.”

“Good.” Narcissa snapped her fingers and a house elf appeared beside her. “Let’s start with how to sit.”

Hah!

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lord James Potter strode into the sitting room where the wards had alerted him to a floo call.

“Prongs.” Sirius’ head was in the fire.

“Hey, Padfoot. Any news?”

“Yes, he’s here!”

“Harry?”

“Of course.”

James straightened. “I’ll go get Lils!” He turned to leave.

“Wait!” came Sirius’ voice from behind.

James turned back. “What?”

Sirius’ looked uncomfortable. “I had to make a few promises to stop him from bolting.”

James frowned. “Go on …”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Ancient toys were crammed on every shelf on every square foot of wall. Alexandra Black sat on a small child’s chair in the playroom, half giddy and half anxious. Four other witches sat in a circle with her, two of whom she knew well, and two of whom she didn’t.

Her birthday had started out normally. She’d pestered her dad to let her have Ginny and Luna over, and to not have John Potter around. He’d caved surprisingly easily.

Ginny had arrived first and they’d spent the time playing exploding snap while discussing duelling in hushed tones whenever her father left the room.

Then Luna had arrived with a big bowl of pudding, and she’d brought the troll slaying witches with her, Daphne Greengrass, the other girl betrothed to Lord Slytherin, and Hermione Granger, a vassal of Slytherin house—people she’d been looking forward to meeting for ages. They’d dragged her from the living room to the play room and set up the small chairs in a circle, each one of the four taking a seat, and sitting her down in a fifth.

Opposite Alexandra on the far side of the circle, Daphne had placed an empty, sixth chair. It drew Alex’s attention like a recently missing tooth.

“Flitwick’s fine,” Daphne said, carrying herself with enviable ease and elegance. “He teaches well and doesn’t mind if you read ahead.”

“What about the defence teacher?” Ginny asked. “Any idea who it’ll be?”

“Our lord mentioned in an owl that it would be Snape.”

Our lord. All four of the other girls referred to Lord Slytherin as ‘our lord.’ Alex shifted forward in her chair. It made the whole thing feel like a secret meeting or council. One where important things were discussed and the fates of men decided.

“Snape!” Hermione scowled. “Did he say why?”

“He is Dumbledore’s spy. Our lord wishes us to turn him.”

Alex’s eyes nearly bugged out. Dear Morgana, this was awesome!

Hermione folded her arms. “Who’s going to be doing potions then?”

“We don’t know,” Daphne said.

“What about the new headmaster?” Ginny asked. “Percy said the transfiguration teacher would have been doing the job until they found someone.”

Daphne was about to answer when the door creaked open and four heads swung around. Alex was already facing the right direction.

“Harry!” Hermione, Ginny, and Luna leapt up from their chairs, and rush-hugged the John Potter look alike. Daphne Greengrass rose with considerably more grace, but did mirror the other three once they’d finished.

Alex stared at the spectacle, then hastily stood as Potter walked over to her. “Happy birthday, Miss Black.” He took her hand in his and brushed his lips along the knuckles. “I hope your training is going well?”

A year ago, she’d have bitten back with some sarcastic comment, especially at being addressed as ‘Miss’ rather than ‘Heiress,’ but that had been before she’d been continually smashed into the ground by both Ginny and Luna, before she’d seen Hermione Granger and Daphne Greengrass take on a full grown mountain troll, and most definitely before she’d read the daily prophet article about a certain mysterious boy who’d smacked down the entire Hufflepuff duelling team, and then proceeded to pound John Potter into the dirt so badly that he’d been accused of attempted murder.

Harry Potter was powerful, as were all of those Lord Slytherin had taken into his confidence. Alex nodded and reclaimed her hand. “Well enough, Potter. The Black library is quite the treasure trove.”

Potter smiled. “I’m sure it is.”

They all sat. Alex couldn’t help notice that all four of the other girls looked expectantly at Potter who was fishing in his robes for something. Even Daphne Greengrass seemed to be waiting for him to start.

Alex fidgeted with the skirt of her robes. The very air in the room seemed to have changed.

“Alexandra,” Potter eventually began once he’d found what he’d been looking for. “Our lord asked me to read you a letter he wrote, do you mind if I go ahead?”

A letter? Alex shook her head, indicating that she didn’t mind.

“Excellent.” Potter cleared his throat. “Alexandra Black, Heiress of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Black,

Greetings on your eleventh birthday. I hope Harry and the girls are keeping things interesting.

Firstly, your birthday present. I’m sure you’re expecting a book or similar. Most of our discussions in the past have revolved around our stores of magical knowledge. However, not this time. Your help at the winter festival with Angelystor, and your loaning us of your family’s communication mirrors were both invaluable gestures. I’ve also been hearing good things from Luna and Ginny about your practical training and our letters clearly show your drive to expand your magical toolbox.

Therefore for your birthday present, I, Lord Slytherin, grant you a, non-conditional, guaranteed invitation to Slytherin House during the sorting—

Alex’s heart leapt. “YES!” She jumped to her feet and fist-pumped the air.

Hermione, Daphne, and Ginny all gave her wry smiles.

Luna clapped. “Congratulations, Alex. We all get to be together for the next seven years!”

“Ah, yeah.” Alex sat down again, suddenly feeling a bit sheepish. Had that looked too enthusiastic? It probably had. This was supposed to be a Slytherin meeting. She coughed. “Do please continue, Potter.”

Potter continued.

“… Secondly, a house matter. I would ask you to look around you. Daphne, Ginny, Luna, Hermione, and Harry all have my confidence. They have each proved themselves in their own way and you’ve seen for yourself how capable someone needs to be to achieve that. I—as Lord of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Slytherin—would like to extend that confidence to you as the Heiress of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Black—a confidence that will hopefully see our respective houses become firm allies. Let Harry know if you’re interested and he’ll continue reading, otherwise, have a Happy Birthday.

- Lord Slytherin”

Harry looked expectantly up from the letter.

Alex hesitated, but only for a moment. She couldn’t not accept. The last time she’d refused one of Lord Slytherin’s offers she’d regretted it for years. She nodded.

Harry smiled, put the letter away, pulled out another one and unfolded it.

Alex bit her lip. Another letter. What would have happened if she’d said no?

Harry started reading.

“Excellent! Right, third order of business. Occlumency, as you now know, is critical in many branches of magic. You’ve already been practising three of them—mental defence, wandless magic, and magic sensing. Another use that many people in Europe choose to ignore is the animagus transformation. This year, Harry will be leading an experimental group project to achieve animagus status by the winter festival. I’d like to invite you to join this project.”

Alex sucked in her breath. That would be sooo cool. What would her form be? Would it be a panther? Or maybe a grizzly bear? Or would she be one of the oh so lucky ones to get a magical animagus form? Maybe she’d—

Harry coughed.

She caught his eye.

He was grinning.

Alex immediately schooled her features and sniffed. “That sounds interesting.”

Potter nodded and continued, still smiling. “Secondly, each one of my Slytherins has a project that they’re working on. A project that will push forward the Gray and make our long term goals easier. I have one for you—one that makes use of your particular talents and brand of family magic, if you feel you are up for it?”

Harry looked up from the paper again.

Alex set her jaw and nodded. This was what she’d been waiting for.

Harry looked down again. “Your project, Alexandra Black, is to usurp Draco Malfoy as leader of the Dark.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Draco Malfoy was certain of many things in life. He was certain purebloods were superior to halfbloods, who were themselves superior to mudbloods. He was certain that the noble houses were superior to the common houses, although he didn’t voice this certainty where his family’s business associates could hear. He was certain that rich wizards were superior to poor ones, and that the Dark would ultimately triumph. But most of all, he was certain that he was the only child of a pureblood, noble house that also happened to be the richest in the country, and the leader of the Dark, and was, therefore, the most important person in the world.

Not five minutes ago, one of those beliefs had been slowly turned on its head and he had no idea what to think about it.

“I have a sister?”

His father had looked at him impassively over his ornate office desk. “We sent Virgo away when you were both very young. We thought she was a squib. We were wrong. She is, in fact, exceptionally powerful.”

Draco had said nothing.

His father leaned forward slightly. “Your mother and I expect you to introduce her to our friends and make sure she is accorded the respect a daughter of the Noble House of Malfoy deserves.”

“Yes, Father.”

“And one more piece of advice.”

“Father?”

“Virgo grew up in exceptional circumstances. You are my heir and the future Lord of this house, but do not presume anything about your status in regards to Virgo. Do not look down on her. Do not talk down to her. And above all else, do not threaten her.”

Draco had left the study soon after that feeling somewhat disturbed. He now walked through the many bookshelves of the Malfoy Manor Library, looking for this so-called sister of his. He turned a corner and there she was, sitting elegantly in an alcove, reading a book and balancing three other books on her head.

Draco smirked. He remembered doing the same exercise when he’d been much younger. He walked over and in a bored voice said, “Father said you might be in here.”

The girl, who certainly looked like a Malfoy, turned a page in her book, and, not bothering to look up, said, “Did you want something?”

“I am Draco, your brother, Heir of the Noble House of Malfoy.” He stuck out his hand. “Father said I was to introduce you to our family’s friends so I wanted to know if you know how to act like a real pureblood.”

“I’m sure I shall manage,” Virgo said, in a voice equally as bored as his. Not moving from her chair.

Draco frowned, hand still outstretched. “Mother hasn’t taught you proper greetings yet?”

Virgo finally looked up and their eyes locked.

Draco breathed in sharply and took a reflective step backwards. Magic flared off the girl in front of him in exactly the same way it had off of Lord Slytherin in the Slytherin common room at the start of last year—not nearly as strong as Lord Slytherin, but just the fact that his sister could do it at all …

For what felt like an age, but was actually closer to twenty-five seconds, Virgo held him there like a mouse held in the gaze of a snake.

Eventually the magic stopped and Draco let out a deep, shaky breath.

Virgo smiled. The three books hadn’t moved from where they still sat on her head. “Why don’t you tell me about proper greetings, Brother?”

“Uh, yeah,” Draco sweated. His sister was nundu scary. “Yeah, sure.”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lily Potter trekked up the stairs towards the play room, mentally preparing herself for the coming confrontation. She stood outside the door and listened. Children were laughing. A good start. She took a deep calming breath, cautiously opened the door, and peered around it.

Harry was sat in the middle of a huge game of gobstones, wide smile on his face as Luna squealed and punted a triple into her stone sphere.

Her heart clenched. Harry looked so happy.

He looked up and met her eyes, smile never leaving his face.

“Hello, Harry,” she said, far softer than she’d meant to, opening the door fully and stepping into the room.

Her heart beat harder. Something didn’t feel right.

All the girls quietened and looked around at her, shooting her looks that suggested she was something nasty they’d stepped in.

“Hi, Mum,” Harry said happily, standing up and brushing himself down. “Time to go home, is it?”

The girls continued to stare.

“Y-Yes, your father and I thought it might be nice for all of us to eat out—you know—a family thing.”

Harry grinned. “Sounds great.”

The whole situation felt surreal. Like she wasn’t meeting him for just the first time—like she’d just come to pick him up as normal, as if everything was normal. She’d expected sullenness or awkwardness. She’d expected shouting and accusations, or possibly even tears and crying. She hadn’t expected this.

Harry walked over, waved goodbye to the girls, slipped past her through the doorway, and made his way back up the hallway, footsteps light, gait confident, as though he hadn’t a single care in the world, as though he was just choosing to ignore the fact that they’d never exchanged a single word since he was eighteen months old.

Lily shook away that feeling of wrongness, allowed herself a small smile, and followed on after him. If Harry was happy to put all that behind him, then he might be even more mature than John, and it would make ensuring that everything turned out all right in the end that much easier.

Back in the play room, unseen by the retreating noble muggleborn lady, three sets of eyes abandoned all pretext of restraint and glared at the closed door in undisguised loathing, watched by a fourth set of eyes that flittered between the first three in mild confusion. The fifth and last set idly watched the fourth before the body it was attached to smiled and took another spoonful of delicious mouth-watering pudding from the already half-empty communal bowl.

—End of Chapter Thirty-five—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: The setup is complete. The pieces are in place, whether visible or not. See you in July for the start of the game.

Sticky Note: I now have original fantasy fiction published. You can find it by following the bread crumb trail in my profile page. If you can’t wait for my next fanfic chapter release, you might like to check that out to tide you over.

Interlude — Daphne Goes Down to the Village

Chapter Notes

IMPORTANT AUTHOR NOTE:

This week’s chapter is NOT a continuation of the current season. It is instead a shortish, fluffy bonus chapter that was originally posted to the Gray Mailing List on June 25th, 2017. It takes place towards the end of the first summer, less than one month before current events, and features Daphne and Astoria Greengrass. I’ve posted a more detailed explanation of why we’re having a bonus chapter instead of a normal one this week on my website—[www * LeadVonE * com]

This chapter will stay as the most recent chapter for the next two weeks before being switched to where it belongs in the overall story chronology a few hours after the next chapter is posted.

My apologies for everyone who was desperately waiting for the continuation, but I hope this will be a satisfying alternative while I sort stuff out.

Enjoy!

See the end of the chapter for more notes

Daphne Greengrass stared at the parchment-work in front of her. Her bedroom desk groaned under it. Some of it was important. Some of it was useless, and quickly found its way into the bin beside her. But most of it occupied the frustrating space in-between—probably too important to throw away, but probably not important enough to read—and impossible to tell one way or the other without committing oneself and possibly getting it wrong.

Outside her open window, soft, fluffy clouds melted into blue summer sky. Birdsong gently tweeted away in nearby trees. A faint breeze ruffled the lush grasses, wafting up through the window and playing with a long strand of Daphne’s blonde hair, flicking it this way and that—a constant reminder that she was in here and not out there.

Daphne hooked the errant strand around her ear. “Milly!”

A small, female house elf popped into being beside her. She wore the Greengrass house elf uniform—a neatly pressed tea towel emblazoned with the Greengrass crest. “Yes, Mistress Daphy?”

“Has there been any word from Harry?”

“No, Mistress Daphy. There has been no more word from Lord Slytherin since last time you asked.”

Daphne sighed. “Thank you, Milly.”

Milly nodded and popped away.

Daphne stared, once again, at the piles of parchment in front of her.

Urgh.

She glanced at the perfect weather outside and then back at the pile of parchment again, then back to the open window.

It called to her. The outside—it called to her in a voice she knew well—the call to adventure—to explore. She’d had just about as much of the parchment-work as she could take.

Daphne turned and her gaze fell on the fluffy snake Harry had given her during the winter festival, still coiled around her bedpost. The toy snake met her gaze and tilted its head as though in question.

But Harry wasn’t here right now. He was off—somewhere—doing Lord Slytherin stuff—and without him she was stuck inside, bound to the familiar—to those places she already knew well—the manor, Diagon Alley, her friend’s houses, those places with a friendly floo connection—those places to which the only journey was a boring ten to fifteen minute whirring about inside a bland grey pipe.

Daphne returned to the parchment and was halfway through reading the latest update on the mandrake supply crisis when she snapped, threw the parchment down, pushed her chair back, and stomped over to the window.

Why!?

Daphne stared out over the forest that protected Greengrass Manor.

Why? She’d done so much in her first year at Hogwarts—had battled a troll and tangled with the dark lord. She and Hermione had helped Harry break past the best defences Albus Dumbledore and Nicholas Flamel could devise, and would have succeeded in claiming the philosopher’s stone, if Flamel hadn’t used a fake. Why then, was she sitting here like a delicate flower, waiting for an escort from her future husband? Was she so weak that she couldn’t even conceive of doing something as simple as … as even stepping outside the manor’s front gate?

The thought stilled her. Harry had taken her to the moors of Dartmoor and the forests of Brazil. She’d flown across Scotland and travelled under the North-Sea in a muggle-built magical submarine. But just beyond that front gate was almost unknown territory—unknown territory, which she at least knew contained a muggle-cum-magic village that she couldn’t ever remember visiting.

Daphne nodded to herself. That’s what she was going to do. She was going to go down to explore the village—to find out what was there for herself. She was old enough. She had wandless magic. She could protect herself. There had to be loads of other wizarding children her age that did it all the time. There was absolutely no reason why she couldn’t.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Lord Jacob Greengrass sat in his sitting room, reading the Daily Prophet as was his habit on a lazy Sunday afternoon. Thanks in no small part to his future son-in-law, it had been quite a while since he’d had a Sunday as lazy as this one.

The door to the sitting room creaked open and his oldest daughter poked her head through.

“Daphne?”

“Father.” She entered the room and presented herself before him in a manner that screamed, ‘I’m being super official here. I dare you to make fun of me.’

Jacob held back a grin.

“I wish to inform you,” she started, “that I plan to travel down to the village this afternoon.”

Jacob blinked. “The village?”

“Yes, I think it’s about time I saw it.”

Jacob put down his paper. “Okay, we can do that. Rodger did say—”

“—No!” Daphne suddenly looked flustered. “I mean, I want to go by myself.”

“Why?”

Daphne’s cheeks reddened. “Because I just do.”

Jacob studied his eldest intently. She stared back at him, more defiance in her eyes than he’d ever seen before. Eventually he nodded and picked up his paper again. “Okay. But I want you back here before sundown, understand?”

“I understand, Father.” She then turned around, beaming widely, and left.

Jacob waited for a few moments until the sound of retreating footsteps had fully faded away. “Milly!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne stood in front of her bedroom mirror, holding clothes up to her body and frowning. In one hand she held a pretty summer dress. In the other she held a pair of hiking trousers. It was a toss up between dressing like a muggle teenage girl or dressing like a muggle teenage girl who expected close encounters of the cow and mud variety.

“Daappphhhh.”

Oh, Merlin. Daphne turned. “Yes, Tory?”

Astoria Greengrass hung off the bedroom door, face a picture of innocence. “What are you doing?”

“I’m getting ready to go out.”

“You’re going down to the village.” Astoria announced this as though she’d just won something.

“How do you know that?”

“Asked great-great-great-grandfather.”

Daphne turned back and closed her eyes. That damn painting. “I’ll be back by sundown. I’m sure you’ll find something to—”

“—I’m going with you!”

“What?!” Daphne spun back around. “No, you’re not!”

“I am!”

“There’ll be muggles there! You don’t have the clothes.”

“You and Harry started going out around muggles years ago. I can just use some of your old clothes, can’t I?”

“I …” Daphne hesitated. “I’m still not sure it’s a good idea. You might get lost.”

“I won’t get lost!” Astoria pouted. “You just think I’ll slow you down, don’t you?”

“No!”

“I bet you’re secretly sneaking out to see Harry, aren’t you?”

“Why would I need to do that? He comes here!”

Astoria grinned. “I bet it’s because you two are secretly kissy kissy—”

“We are not!”

“—and that’s why you don’t want me along.”

Daphne’s face was now flushed red. “We haven’t done anything like that yet.” She didn’t count that one time they kissed in an empty classroom to trap Dumbledore. “And you’re not coming with me.”

“Maybe I should talk to Harry next time he comes over? I’m sure he’d say it was okay.”

“Harry’s not here.”

Astoria’s grin morphed into a deceptive smile so innocent and convincing as to make politicians cry tears of envy. “Maybe I should tell Harry what a certain someone keeps under their pillow at night.”

Daphne froze.

The two girls eyes flickered back and forth between each other and said pillow. Time slowed down. Then Daphne lunged, but with two items of clothing still in hand wasn’t able to reach her target before Astoria dived in front of her, landing on the bed, stomach first, and snatched out the item from under the pillow.

“Got it!”

“You—!”

Astoria rolled off the bed and held the framed magical photo up, triumphant. Said magical photo featured Harry’s amused, smiling face, although at the moment it was rolling its eyes at Astoria’s antics.

Daphne flung out her hand and wandlessly summoned the framed photo right back to her, her face now tomato red, but that didn’t stop Astoria from giggling up a storm.

“Don’t.” Daphne searched for words. “Don’t ever tell Harry about this.”

“But it’s so cute, Daphne.”

“And you shouldn’t be poking around my room either!”

Astoria made a kissy face at her.

Daphne huffed. “Okay, fine, I’ll take you with me, but not one word to Harry, okay?”

Astoria smiled. “Greengrass family secret!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Greengrass Manor backed out onto a muggle road that led into the depths of the Cumbrian wilderness. The Manor itself was hidden from muggle eyes—both by the hedge surrounding it, and by enchantments. Any muggle with the strength of will to overcome the muggle-repelling wards—who managed to poke their head over the top of the hedge—would see only an empty field with an abandoned shed in the middle.

And now, from out of the totally empty field, walked two girls, appearing from nothing through the front gate as though conjured from thin air. The girls now wore almost identical summer dresses in floral print—the result of a spirited negotiation that lasted almost twenty minutes.

Daphne closed the front gate behind her and wrapped her purse around her wrist, fully ready to start exploring without her usual escort. She looked up and down the road. Both directions looked identical. Ummm.

“Which way is it, Daphne?” Astoria asked.

Daphne cursed in her head. “Well, it has to be one of them,” she said, as though that was in anyway a helpful observation.

“Do your mirror trick!”

“I don’t have a mirror with me. But …” She looked up and down the road again. There hadn’t been a muggle car since they’d opened the gate. “Watch out for me okay? I’m going to use the eyeball.”

“Kay.”

Daphne sat down on the grass at the side of the road, doing her best not to get her dress dirty, and summoned her invisible magic seeing eyeball. Her world shifted and soon she was looking down on it from high up in the air. She looked around.

“Well?” Astoria asked, “Can you see it?”

“No, but there is a house not far up the road. Maybe we can ask whoever lives there which way it is.”

“We can ask the muggles!”

Daphne opened her own eyes again to see Astoria jumping up and down in obvious excitement. “Tory!” she snapped.

Astoria stopped jumping.

“Remember your studies. No using those kinds of words out in the open.”

Astoria looked down, suddenly all meek. “Sorry, Daphne.”

Daphne softened. “How would you like to do the asking?”

Astoria looked back up again, all smiles once again.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Mrs. Rollandson had nothing against hikers. They were usually polite and wanted little more than directions or the occasional glass of water, which she was happy to provide. But that didn’t mean they always chose the best moments to drop by. She’d just gotten her iron heated up and ready to attack her husband’s massive pile of wrinkled clothes, when the doorbell rang. Mrs. Rollandson sighed and put the iron down.

She walked across the living room and opened the front door. What greeted her was not what she’d expected. Two young girls—sisters by the looks of it—dressed more for a tea party than for hiking. “Can I help you?”

The younger girl stepped forward, pushed slightly by her big sister. She curtsied nervously. “Excuse us for bothering you, but perhaps you could tell us the direction to the village?”

Mrs. Rollandson couldn’t help but smile. “You mean Applybe-in-Westmoreland?”

The girls nodded.

“It’s just up that way.” She pointed up the road.

The younger girl cheered, all formality forgotten.

“But where did you two come from to not know that? There’s nothing up the other way for miles.”

The older girl put her hands on the younger girl’s shoulders. “Our parents just wanted to make sure. They’re waiting with the car not far away.”

“Oh.” That made sense, if a little irresponsible of them. “Well, I’m glad I could help.”

“Thank you, as well!” The little girl waved as her sister led her up the garden path back to the road.

Mrs. Rollandson smiled, turned, and closed the door behind her. Her gaze fell over her ironing and her eyes widened. She scuttled over to the pile of clothes and her jaw dropped. Every single item of clothing had been ironed, pressed, and folded with geometrical precision—even the damn socks! After an hour of fretting, she eventually decided she must have brownies living in the garden, and proceeded to leave out a bowl of milk for them, every morning, for the next thirty years.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Daph, do you think it’s much further?”

“We haven’t been walking that long, but as it happens, no, I don’t believe it’s too far away.”

“Why do you think that?”

Daphne pointed to a brown sign at the side of the road.

‘Welcome to Applybe-in-Westmoreland. Please drive carefully through our village.’

“Oh,” said Astoria, rather sheepishly.

They continued to walk down the road until the hedgerow to their right turned into rough grey masonry. They turned the next corner and stopped. Beautiful cottages with front gardens in full bloom stretched out down the road. They stood aside to let a muggle car pass. There didn’t seem to be a hint of magic anywhere.

Astoria leaned into her and whispered, “How do we know who’s one of us and who isn’t?”

Daphne glanced up the row of houses. A middle aged woman in a pointy hat waved cheerfully at them from behind a curtain in one of the cottage’s upper rooms before drawing the curtain shut. “I don’t think it’ll actually be all that hard.”

The two girls strolled further up the road until they turned another corner and reached the village centre. A massive oak tree stood on an island in the middle of the street, forcing the few muggles driving cars to circle around it. Muggle shops lined the street on both sides, displaying all sorts of things in their windows—some familiar, others not.

“Oh, oh, oh!” Astoria grabbed Daphne’s hand and pointed. “Look, Daph! Ice cream! Different from ours!”

Daphne looked at the pastel coloured shop window with uncertain eyes. “Umm …” She snapped open her purse even though she knew it was useless.

“Please, Daph!”

Daphne gazed down at the half dozen solid gold coins held within. “I don’t actually have any pounds on me.”

“Awwww!”

“But … maybe. …” She looked over at Astoria. “Are you sure you want this kind of ice-cream?”

“Yes!”

“It might not be as good as our kind.”

“Don’t care.”

“Okay, then.”

They continued to walk up the street. Daphne wasn’t quite sure what she was looking for, but she was sure she’d know it when she spotted it. And, indeed, in a shop window a dozen shops away from the ice cream parlour, someone had proudly displayed a small poster of a long, light blue triangle, containing a downward pointing, half invisible arrow. Daphne smiled and nudged Astoria. “See anything you recognise?”

Astoria looked around in puzzlement for a moment before her eyes fell on the poster. She gasped. “The Appleby Arrows,” she whispered.

Daphne smirked, put her hand on the door handle to the shop, and entered to the sound of a small tinkling bell.

The inside of the shop contained a little bit of everything. As with the shop windows up the street, some things Daphne recognised and some things she didn’t, but nothing screamed ‘magic.’ Behind the counter, an elderly gentleman looked momentary surprised before he schooled his features, gave them both a respectful nod, and returned to whatever business had been occupying him.

“Hey, Daph, what’s this?” Astoria picked up a thing made of red rubber with a wood handle.

Daphne cautiously took the device. “Let’s see.” She saw that the rubber bent quite easily. She pushed it against a wall and let go. The thing stayed stuck to the wall. “There, you go. It’s for hanging things on.”

“Oh.”

A hesitant cough interrupted them from the counter. “Miss Heiress?”

Daphne turned.

“That’s a plunger, Miss Heiress. Muggles use them to unblock toilets.”

“I see. Do you have any magical goods to sell?”

The shop keeper reached down and fumbled for something under the counter. There was a loud whoosh noise, and many of the shelves around the counter flipped over, faded away, or in the case of one shelf by a wall, actually picked itself up on little legs and scuttled off to one side, revealing a small hidden room beyond.

“Wow!” Astoria jumped up and ran to look over the newly exposed shelves. “Look, Daph, they have Top Broom!”

“Astoria,” Daphne said in a warning tone of voice, “you know Father doesn’t want you reading that until you’re of Hogwarts age.”

Astoria pouted.

The man behind the counter gave Daphne an apologetic look. “Sorry about that.”

“Please don’t let it worry you.” She looked towards the open door. “Won’t muggles see this stuff?”

“Oh, they can’t. There’s a muggle-repelling ward linked to the shelves when they turn. Had to get permission from the ministry and everything. Took three inspections to get it right.”

Daphne nodded. It made sense. Appleby was a mixed village—one of only fourteen in the whole country. It wasn’t pure, like Hogsmeade, or an enclave, like Holyhead. It was only natural that regulations here would be a lot tighter than elsewhere.

Astoria was by now ogling the many magical sweets behind the glass display next to the counter. There was plenty of choice, but not nearly as large as one might find in, say, London.

“So,” Daphne started, “what interesting things does the ministry let us do here? This is the first time my sister and I have visited.”

The man indicated a height somewhere about his shins. “Since you were yay high, yeah.”

Daphne smiled.

The man rubbed his chin. “Interesting things, huh? The quidditch field’s across the main road, hidden by the v-shaped maple tree. The children and younger lads spend most of their time there of a summer’s day—more than quidditch too—snap, quodpot, duelling as well—though I guess that wouldn’t be your thing.”

Daphne’s eyes flashed at ‘duelling,’ but said nothing.

“There’s one of the local pubs—The Winged Horse—occasionally seen your father there of an evening having a pint or a bite to eat.”

Daphne raised an eyebrow.

“Pretty sure he’s friends with old Rodger who owns it.”

Old Rodger … why did that name ring a bell?

“There’s also the local ministry office if you find yourself in need of a boner.”

The rubber plunger, still stuck to the wall, choose that exact moment to drop off and land on the floor.

“… Boner?” Daphne felt the heat rise in her cheeks.

“I mean the DMLE, sorry, Miss Heiress. That’s what we call the security wizards.”

Astoria was watching her with a puzzled expression.

Daphne decided to take control of this conversation before her sister made this way more awkward. “So, can you give change in muggle money for wizarding money?”

The man nodded, “I can do that.”

“Excellent. Then I’ll have a small nogtail pasty.” She fished in her purse for a one galleon coin.

The man stared at the solid gold coin with incredulity before carefully counting out £49.65, totally failing to hide his pained expression.

When they stepped outside, Astoria turned to her. “Daph, what’s wrong with something being called a bon—”

“—Tory. Do you want an ice cream?” Daphne asked in a warning tone of voice.

“Yes.”

“Then you’ll not ask that question until you’re a teenager.”

“You’re not a teenager either.”

“I will be in a few months—and I also read a lot more than you do too.”

Astoria pouted, but only until they arrived back at the muggle ice cream parlour. “I’ll have strawberry, and chocolate, and mint, and fudge, and coconut, and lemon—oh, and also rhubarb.” Astoria beamed at the woman behind the counter.

“Oh, you will, will you?” The muggle woman smiled and looked towards Daphne, who nodded.

“She will.”

Soon, the two witches were once again walking up the street, this time toward and over the River Eden, where the wizard from the shop said the quidditch grounds lay. Daphne nibbled on her pasty while Astoria enthusiastically licked her six story ice cream held together with wooden sticks—an endeavour that, without cooling magic to combat the summer heat, soon turned into a big, sticky race against time.

They could hear the rumble as they stepped off the bridge—a low thrum, getting louder, punctuated by a regular ‘Vrooom’ sound.

They turned another corner.

*Lick* “That’s a lot of cars.” *Lick*

A wall of noisy, fast moving muggle vehicles blocked their progress. It was, indeed, a lot of cars. “This must be a ‘main road’.”

*Lick* *Lick* *Lick*

Daphne looked up and down, searching for a way over—a bridge maybe? Or a tunnel? She couldn’t see anything.

*Lick* “Maybe someone will stop for us.” *Lick* Astoria’s ice cream was now melting down her hands faster than she could keep it in shape.

Daphne frowned. There didn’t seem to be anyone who might stop for them. Most of the muggle car riders didn’t even seem to see them before they passed. “I think we’ll just have to wait until there aren’t any coming.”

*Lick* *Lick* *Lick* *Lick* *Lick*

Astoria’s ice cream started forming a small puddle on the ground.

Daphne was getting annoyed. Car after car passed in front of them in a never ending stream. There had been times when she thought they might be able to get across, but she wasn’t quite sure. Daphne’s instincts screamed at her that running in front of several tonnes of speeding metal when you weren’t sure was a bad idea. But there just seemed no end of them. Surely there had to be some time when there weren’t any.

*Lick* *Lick* *Lick* *Lick* *Lick*

Daphne sighed. “Maybe we should just head back.”

Astoria made a small whining noise in between frantic licks.

“We can do some research on how to cross these things and try again another time. I’m sure there must be a book in Flourish and Blotts that will—” But Daphne didn’t get to finish her sentence because at that moment Astoria jabbed her finger up the road while squealing as loud as she could, her mouth jammed into the second-to-last, half-melted ball of dribbly stickiness.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Gunter Heartwood wasn’t an overly superstitious man—there wasn’t much call for that sort of thing on his overly long route between Calais and Edinburgh—but he’d still be happy to concede that, “Oh, yeah, of cause there’s weird stuff what goes on.” He’d be especially happy to concede this after several pints at journey’s end. Having said that, he’d never personally encountered anything that made him go, “Now that’s some weird shit, right there.”

So when his lorry’s power just suddenly cut out while half way down the A66, Gunter’s first instinct was to curse and try and get his machine back in gear. Needless to say, this didn’t work. Instead, his lorry came to a slow, controlled stop, all by itself, right in the middle of Appleby-in-Westmoreland.

This would have been weird enough, had it not been for that the fact that on the other side of the road, another man in a lorry just like his had also inexplicably stopped, and two girls in summer dresses started walking across the road as though his lorry had decided to obey some invisible zebra crossing.

While he desperately worked his key and pedals in an apparently futile attempt to re-start his engine, the elder girl stopped in front of his lorry and bobbed a curtsey.

Gunter stared as the older girl repeated the curtsey for the other lorry driver. Nonplussed, he watched the two girls reach the pavement on other side of the road, and then, with no input from him, his lorry rumbled back into life.

Gunter tried not to think too hard about it as he pulled away, totally ignoring the loud car horns blaring impatiently behind him, but one thing he did conclude was that that, right there, had been some seriously weird shit.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

“Daph! Daph! Here it is!” Astoria had finished her ice cream by now, or at least, what she’d been able to finish before the forces of entropy had their wicked, messy, way. She now pointed towards a v-shaped maple tree with a massive grin plastered on her surprisingly clean face—surprising, that is, to anyone who had seen it only a few minutes earlier.

Thankful that a couple of the muggle drivers had finally been polite enough to stop for them, Daphne carefully folded up her self-cleaning handkerchief and put it back in her purse. “Wait, Tory.” She wandered over to where Astoria had already put a foot through the magic gateway to the Appleby Quidditch Field. “What is it important that we remember?”

“Occlumency, manners, and custom.”

“Exactly. We are the daughters of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Greengrass. We have to act like it.”

Astoria nodded.

Daphne took her little sister’s hand and together they stepped through the v-shaped maple tree, through a wibbly wobbly portal thing, and right out into an open field bustling with activity.

“Wow,” Astoria whispered.

Close to three dozen wizards and witches zipped about above them on broomsticks—some of them looked younger than they were. On the field in front of them, several groups of children and teenagers, and even adults, were engaged in all manner of magical activity. The wizard from the shop hadn’t been joking—quodpot and snap, yes, but also wizard chess, bowls, and even what looked like competitive transfiguration. A pair of abraxan horses were tied up off to the side, grazing on the lush grass, and resting under a tree.

Daphne had to agree that it was impressive. If only because they’d actually walked here from the manor. They hadn’t used the floo or been apparated—they’d walked. A flash of red on the far side of the field caught her attention. A stunner. Several young men danced around each other throwing spells as fast as they could. Duelling.

“Daph!” Astoria whispered, pointing to the sky and clearly trying to stay as composed as she could while also obviously close to hyperventilation. “It’s the Appleby Arrows!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Appleby-in-Westmoreland had thirty-five magical children of Hogwarts age. Of those thirty-five, only six actually went to Hogwarts—the others went to one of the other three schools down south.

Robert Longsdale was one of the six, about to start his fourth year in Ravenclaw house. He sat with his small group of friends, busy on summer homework, occasionally aided by Jack, his older brother, and Adelaide, Jack’s muggle girlfriend, who knew nothing of magical theory, but did know plenty about spelling, grammar, and essay writing in general.

Robert was facing the village and was, therefore, the first to spot the new arrivals. He leaned in closer to the circle. “Okay, don’t look, but Daphne Greengrass just crossed the maple tree.”

“Is that her little sister?”

“Don’t look, idiot.”

“Who’s Daphne Greengrass?” Adelaide asked.

Robert’s friends hastened to explain.

“She’s like the closest thing Magical Britain has to an actual princess.”

“She lives in the manor just up the road, but we’ve never seen her before.”

“She’s going to be Lady Slytherin when she’s older.”

“What’s she doing here?”

“We don’t want to get into trouble for ignoring her.”

“Maybe one of the others will go talk to her.”

Robert looked around. No one else seemed to have noticed the two girls yet.

“Maybe you should go talk to her, Jack,” Adelaide said, slipping an arm into his older brother’s.

Jack looked torn. “I’m, ummm, not really comfortable with nobles. I didn’t go to Hogwarts, did I?”

There was a pause.

Robert realised with dawning horror that everyone, even Adelaide, was looking expectantly at him.

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne watched the young men duelling on the other side of the field with judging eyes. The spells being thrown about were basic and their casting speed wasn’t anything to write home about. She’d honestly expected more considering they were clearly of age.

“Daph, do you think I could fly too?” Astoria asked, pointing up to the many quidditch players still zipping around in the sky above them.

“I don’t think that would be a good idea—not unless one of the Arrows offers.”

“Aw.”

Off to the side, one of the boys from a random group sitting in the shade of a nearby tree had broken off from his friends and was making his way towards them.

“Maybe we could talk to Father about getting you some lessons back home.”

Astoria grinned.

Daphne turned to face the approaching boy.

“Heiress Greengrass?” The somewhat familiar boy hid his nervousness well, but not well enough. “I didn’t expect to see you here.”

“We’re just out for an afternoon stroll …” Daphne rifled through her memories. She had seen him before, she was certain. “… Longsdale, right? Robert Longsdale—Ravenclaw house.”

Longsdale’s shoulders noticeably relaxed. “You remember me.”

“You thanked me for saving Sophie from the troll.”

“Yes.”

“Mmm, I don’t recall your family having a political affiliation.”

Longsdale shifted nervously. “I’m the first in my family to go to Hogwarts. But I’d say we’re Gray-ish. We are an Appleby family after-all.”

Daphne smiled. “Lived here all your lives?”

“For five generations.”

Longsdale’s friends were all watching from the shade of a nearby tree with unashamed interest. One of the Appleby Arrows chose that moment to land next to them and, after introductions and several minutes of pleasantries, an ecstatic Astoria was flown up into the air, riding side-saddle on the back of the cheerful team captain’s broom, squealing and shouting as the captain gently lapped the field while throwing in the occasional dip and turn.

“Perhaps you could introduce me to the duellers?” Daphne suggested to Longsdale.

The duellers, it turned out, were two young men training to be security wizards for the DMLE. They’d gone to The Box together in London, which explained their rather basic offensive spell repertoire.

“Care for a friendly match?” Daphne asked. “One-on-one—best of three?”

The two young men gave each other sceptical looks. “No disrespect, Miss Heiress, but you’re not exactly allowed to use your wand during summer holidays.”

“Who said I needed a wand? Oh, hello, who’s this?”

The rest of Longsdale’s group had wandered over. Another quick round of introductions followed, finishing with a fascinated muggle girl who’d only recently been introduced to the magical world after her boyfriend had finally gotten his guide license.

“I thought you needed a wand to do magic?” Adelaide asked, apparently not noticing the looks of raw awe that Daphne’s faintly glowing finger-tips were receiving.

“Most people do,” her boyfriend half-whispered. “Only the most powerful wizards in history have been able to do wandless magic.”

Daphne smiled, but said nothing.

The two DMLE hopefuls were now looking at Daphne with rather more respect than before.

Daphne handed her purse to Robert before turning to them. “Shall we?”

What followed were six duels with astonishingly even match-ups, considering she was facing fully grown wizards wielding wands. They used stunners, body-binds, ropes, and shields. Daphne used stunners, stingers, shields, finite incantatem, banishers, and summoning. They focused on the attack, using their larger magical reserves to wear her down. Daphne focused on keeping her distance, only closing the gap when she was ready, then unloading with a practised speed far faster than the young men had yet mastered.

They took plenty of time between matches to rest and recover and by the end of it all they’d attracted quite the little crowd. Even some of the broomstick riders paused in their games to watch while floating overhead. The sun was far lower in the sky now. The final score came out at 2–1, 2–1, both in Daphne’s favour. She rested with her hands on her knees, breath fast and shallow, while the small crowd clapped.

“That was awesome, Daphne!”

Daphne looked up.

Astoria beamed down at her from where she sat on the broomstick behind the Arrows captain, who gave Daphne a big cheesy thumbs up and brought his broomstick down low to the ground next to her. Astoria hopped off and brushed down her skirts. “I’m hungry!”

—DP & SW: TFoP—

Daphne had to admit that getting back across the main road was a lot easier second time around. Robert Longsdale was a lot better than her at judging when it was okay to quick march across. The older boy then guided their group, which included his brother, Jack; Adelaide; and the rest of their friends, up the main street until they reached a pub, which the muggles around them—excepting Adelaide—didn’t even seem to notice.

“The Winged Horse,” Jack declared, holding the door open for her. The inside reminded Daphne strongly of a better kept Leaky Cauldron. Several faded posters on a wall advertised trivia night, snitch shooting, and witches night. They quickly found a table large enough for all of them.

Astoria copied Daphne’s elegant way of sitting down, although the effect was somewhat ruined by her grabbing and inspecting the novelty salt shaker with wide-eyed fascination.

“So … Miss Heiress?—is that right?” Adelaide addressed Daphne before looked around uncertainly. Everyone else was happily chatting among themselves.

“We’re about to eat together. Call me Daphne.”

The old barkeeper handed around a set of menus and gave Daphne a conspiratorial wink.

“Right—Daphne—so, what exactly is Lord Slytherin like?”

All conversation died.

“I mean, I’ve read about him—Jack gets me Witch Weekly—and everyone seems to think he’s some kind of cross between the Mask of Zorro and Lord Byron, but no one seems to actually know anything about him.”

“Lord Slytherin is …”

“I’ll have scampi and chips!” Astoria declared.

“… wonderfully complicated.”

They all proceeded to order food while Daphne told them what she could about Lord Slytherin. The group vacuumed up every little titbit, taking particular delight in her recounting of how Slytherin had saved her and Hermione in the Slytherin common room at the start of last term.

A commotion from the kitchen drew Daphne’s attention. A man wearing an apron appeared from a door at the back, threw a white, floppy hat onto the counter, and stomped off.

The barkeeper roared with laughter.

Daphne shrugged, turned back, and the group continued to chat until the food was brought out. Most, including Daphne, had chosen the daily special—Shepherd’s pie with butter beer.

Astoria glared at her fish and chips as it was placed in front of her.

Daphne had to agree that her sister’s serving did seem much smaller than everyone else’s. She turned back to her current favourite conversation partner. “So, Adelaide, what’s it like to join the magical world?”

“Incredible. Appleby isn’t a big place. I grew up knowing most everyone here. To find out that almost a third of them belonged to this secret magical society … well … it was like having the blinkers taken off. So many things suddenly made much more sense.”

Jack grinned and put an arm around Adelaide’s waist.

The conversation flowed freely from then on, much like the butter beer from the large tankard in the middle of the table.

Daphne was just polishing off her own serving of Shepherd’s pie, when the barkeeper started moving tables around. “Snitch shooting starting in five!” he shouted. The room was quickly filling up with older wizards and witches. “What about you, girl?” he said to Daphne. “I hear you’re a dab hand at wandless stingers.”

Daphne frowned. “I’m sorry, I fear you have me at a disadvantage.”

The old barkeeper tapped his forelock. “Rodger North, at your service, my lady.”

Daphne’s eyes widened. “Rodger North? As in Old Rodger? As in Lord Rodger North?”

“That’s me.”

Daphne quickly schooled her features.

Rodger roared with laughter again. “Don’t you start going all pureblood formal on me, girl. I won’t have it from your dad, and I won’t have it from you.”

“I’m sorry, I wasn’t expecting …”

“Weren’t expecting a lord of the Gray faction to be working a bar counter? We don’t all live in manors, you know.”

“I know, I know, it was just a bit of a shock.”

“So, how about it?” He pointed at the box of snitches. “Think you can manage a few?”

“Go on, Daph!”

Daphne glared at Astoria, but did rise from the table, pride easily overcoming embarrassment as those sitting around her cheered and clapped.

When her own round rolled around, she didn’t perform too horribly—some of the younger adults were clearly worse than her—but she was nowhere near as good as the older crowd who competed regularly. Snitch shooting wasn’t anything like duelling, and unless you’d reached Harry’s ability to sense magic, very difficult. She idly wondered whether Ginny, Luna, or even Alexandra would be able to do better, before gracefully sitting back down to numerous verbal pats on the back.

“You did better than some of the grown-ups.”

“Well done.”

“You’re still awesome, Daph!”

The snitch shooting continued and her dinner slowly settled into her stomach just as tiredness slowly settled over her like a warm, comfortable blanket. The group happily cheered the last contender who managed to pluck six snitches out of ten clean from the air.

A wizard and witch started playing the flute and lute a few tables over. The soft music filled the room, giving the many conversations a pleasant backdrop.

Daphne couldn’t help relaxing into it all. She’d set out earlier to explore the village without Harry’s or Father’s help, and she’d succeeded. The village was nice. So were the people. She could imagine herself coming down here more often in the future. Maybe she could even show Harry around if he hadn’t already been here.

“Daphne!”

Daphne looked up to see Astoria frantically pointing towards the window, which displayed a distinct lack of sunlight. Her heart leapt into her throat. The words of her father came back to her—‘Be back by sundown.’ Bugger.

“What do we do, Daph?”

Daphne quickly went through the possibilities in her mind and latched onto the easiest and most obvious solution. She’d really wanted to walk back home—to complete her exploration on her own—but that wasn’t an option anymore. “Milly!”

The female house elf popped in front of them a few seconds later. She was wearing a floppy white hat and an over-large apron with a picture of a winged horse adorning the front. The rest of their companions watched with interest, especially Adelaide, whose eyes had gone almost as wide as Milly’s.

“Milly, can you—wait, have you been cooking?”

Milly nodded. “Yes, Young Mistress Daphne.”

“Cooking for us?”

“Yes, Young Mistress Daphne.”

Astoria gasped. “You gave me a smaller portion!”

Milly frowned. “Young Mistress Astoria is not to be having a large dinner when she is eating so much ice-cream for lunch.”

Astoria made a small whining noise.

Daphne blinked. “You’ve been following us.”

“It is being Lord Greengrass’s orders, Young Mistress. Lord Greengrass and Lord Slytherin would be being most upset if anything bad were to be happening to you and Young Mistress Astoria.”

Adelaide gave Daphne a poorly concealed, amused look.

Daphne sighed. “Can you take us back to Greengrass Manor, Milly?”

Milly nodded. “Milly can be doing that.”

Daphne stood, picked up her purse, and made her way to the bar-counter to settle the tab with her father’s friend. She supposed she should have expected something like this. Oh, well. As far as she was concerned, she’d explored on her own. It was the intention that mattered, and she’d be sure to get Harry to take her somewhere truly amazing as soon as she could. She walked back over to the table to extract Astoria. The Greengrass sisters then said goodbye to their new friends, took hold of Milly’s long spindly arms, and felt the world squeeze around them.

—End of Chapter Thirty-Six—

Chapter End Notes

A/N: Normal posting schedule remains otherwise unchanged.

A/N: Conversion rate is:

1 Galleon to 50 British Pounds

1 Sickle to 3 British Pounds (roughly)

1 Knut to 10p (roughly)

All prices are normalised to 1991 values—about half of 2017’s value.

Sticky Note: As always, if you want to stay up to date on schedule changes and other bonuses before anyone else, you can get them on my mailing list, which you can find by following the breadcrumb trail through my profile page.